<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Guilty or not Guilty?</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/guilty-or-not-guilty/539354</link>
    <description>In 2010, the last year we put christmas lights up. This is the story of what i recall about the event. I only included for sure details unless otherwise stated. (None of the quotes are direct, just idea&#39;s behind them)

We have security cameras and game cameras installed along our driveway(Was only game cameras at this time). We also have two guard dogs now, at the time we had one. Our dog was barking at something that night, and i was still up on my computer. I walked out the driveway and sure enough, I saw the candle pieces scattered through out the yard, and my heart sank. I ran back to the house and got my dad. The first thing he did was call the sheriff, get dressed and come out with me. We took the cards from the game cameras and i took them inside to look at the pictures, trying to determine the exact time it happened. One of the cameras caught a dark colored car with long taillights leaving our driveway. I thought it was odd considering the lamps at the end of the road  were off in the picture. I thought we had turned the lights off already, but what actually happened was they had run them over right about when dad was turning them off. When they ran the row of candles over, it disconnected some of the extension cords, and ripped others. What they didn&#39;t know was my dad had used T-posts to put the candles in the ground because of what happened the last time, that is the reason we have the cameras now too. The front right tire of the vehicle that ran down our lights, ran directly over a metal spike that was part of one of the Snapped T-posts. Due to the cold temps they just snapped off. We found one of the T-posts pieces, out of its candle - farther up the driveway. (Also helping us figure out which direction they were headed) They were scrapes in the ground as if this T-post was drug along, from its end. (Relevance in future). While standing out talking to the sheriff, Either my brother or mother received a text message from his Ex, saying &quot;Why the cops at your house?&quot;. Considering she lives in town, far from us, and happened to be driving by, they found it suspicious. Then which ever received it replied, &quot;Someone ran down our lights&quot; or something to that effect. To which she replied something along the lines of &quot;oh, that sucks&quot;.  The fact that that hadn&#39;t talked in months, and this spur of the moment message, made us all a little suspicious. Then they asked her &quot;Why were you out by our house?&quot;
 apparently she happened to be cruising the back roads getting high. Hymm.
	The next morning we walked down to our neighbors house, who also have security cameras, to see what, if anything their cameras saw, and which way the person had come from. Right after the time stamp on our camera, There was a dark colored car with long taillights going up the road at a high rate of speed(in winter, around 10-11pm, i forgot which). The tracks in the yard verified that this was potentially the car that ran down our lights, considering it belonged to none of us. Due to his ex texting us at that time, we decided to drive around town to see if there was any bumper damage to her car. (Yes she drives a dark colored car with long tail lights(coincidence, according to police)). 
We went by what he believed to be her house, and could not find her car anywhere. So after a while we gave up, and decided to take the back roads home. On the way past the park, which is connected to our back-roads, and about a 9 minute drive from our house, he noticed her car parked in the outside lot, right against the road. We turned around and went to look now.
	There was some white paint scrapes on her  bumper, and the candles are made with white plastic, but red paint(and white rings), her car is a dark maroon color. The first thing we noticed was the flat front right tire. (coincidence) I then crawled under the rear of the car, because i was the only one of us two that would fit, and looked for any scrape marks, we hoped the t-post would of left. Right down her gas tank, there is a 3 grooved kind of gouge, that matches the shape of a T-post.(coincidence) and that fact that it(her car) was so close to our house, that she drove by, texted us, all coincidences. Thank you police force! What we should of done is check the tire for a puncture mark, but figured we had seen enough.(and got good pictures,timestamped!) 

You tell me guys, think it was her? I would also like to hear your reasoning behind your thoughts.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 29 Jan 2014 08:54:21 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>General Discussion</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/guilty-or-not-guilty/539354.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Guilty or not Guilty?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@matzie matzie]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/matzie">@matzie</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote" data-post="5" data-topic="539354">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 AtomicInt_:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Okay, why do you have lights that people can run down</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>It is christmas lights, and they were candles that lined our driveway.</p>
<p>Pic of our house when its up…<br>
<img src="http://media.younewstv.com/images/f31e04e3c3fc709ed56e9c7851688fe93481548c.jpg" alt width="" height=""><br>
Bottom right shows one of the types of candles that was hit.<br>
The picture was taken from the driveway.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/guilty-or-not-guilty/539354/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/guilty-or-not-guilty/539354/6</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 29 Jan 2014 08:54:21 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-539354-6</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/guilty-or-not-guilty/539354.rss">Guilty or not Guilty?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Guilty or not Guilty?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@ExtremeX-Scape Ryley]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/extremex-scape">@ExtremeX-Scape</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Okay, why do you have lights that people can run down</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/guilty-or-not-guilty/539354/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/guilty-or-not-guilty/539354/5</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 29 Jan 2014 08:49:55 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-539354-5</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/guilty-or-not-guilty/539354.rss">Guilty or not Guilty?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Guilty or not Guilty?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@matzie matzie]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/matzie">@matzie</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“AtomicInt_, post:2, topic:539354”]do we care</p>
<p>[size=2pt]ot: given what you provided, yes I think it was her.[/size]</p>
<p>why the fudge do you guys have cameras at your homes?[/quote]<br>
Because its not the first time this happened.</p>
<p>[quote=“Uncalled, post:3, topic:539354”][quote author=AtomicInt_ link=topic=658187.msg4402531#msg4402531 date=1390984396]<br>
do we care<br>
[/quote]No.</p>
<p>Who has a sheriff?</p>
<p><span class="mention">@OP</span>: Anyways, yes I think it was her.[/quote]<br>
The county does, and its a Sheriff’s department.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/guilty-or-not-guilty/539354/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/guilty-or-not-guilty/539354/4</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 29 Jan 2014 08:48:16 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-539354-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/guilty-or-not-guilty/539354.rss">Guilty or not Guilty?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Guilty or not Guilty?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Uncalled Uncalled]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/uncalled">@Uncalled</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“AtomicInt_, post:2, topic:539354”]do we care[/quote]No.</p>
<p>Who has a sheriff?</p>
<p><span class="mention">@OP</span>: Anyways, yes I think it was her.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/guilty-or-not-guilty/539354/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/guilty-or-not-guilty/539354/3</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 29 Jan 2014 08:45:44 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-539354-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/guilty-or-not-guilty/539354.rss">Guilty or not Guilty?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Guilty or not Guilty?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@ExtremeX-Scape Ryley]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/extremex-scape">@ExtremeX-Scape</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>do we care</p>
<p>[size=2pt]ot: given what you provided, yes I think it was her.[/size]</p>
<p>why the fuck do you guys have cameras at your homes?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/guilty-or-not-guilty/539354/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/guilty-or-not-guilty/539354/2</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 29 Jan 2014 08:33:16 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-539354-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/guilty-or-not-guilty/539354.rss">Guilty or not Guilty?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Guilty or not Guilty?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@matzie matzie]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/matzie">@matzie</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>In 2010, the last year we put christmas lights up. This is the story of what i recall about the event. I only included for sure details unless otherwise stated. (None of the quotes are direct, just idea’s behind them)</p>
<p>We have security cameras and game cameras installed along our driveway(Was only game cameras at this time). We also have two guard dogs now, at the time we had one. Our dog was barking at something that night, and i was still up on my computer. I walked out the driveway and sure enough, I saw the candle pieces scattered through out the yard, and my heart sank. I ran back to the house and got my dad. The first thing he did was call the sheriff, get dressed and come out with me. We took the cards from the game cameras and i took them inside to look at the pictures, trying to determine the exact time it happened. One of the cameras caught a dark colored car with long taillights leaving our driveway. I thought it was odd considering the lamps at the end of the road  were off in the picture. I thought we had turned the lights off already, but what actually happened was they had run them over right about when dad was turning them off. When they ran the row of candles over, it disconnected some of the extension cords, and ripped others. What they didn’t know was my dad had used T-posts to put the candles in the ground because of what happened the last time, that is the reason we have the cameras now too. The front right tire of the vehicle that ran down our lights, ran directly over a metal spike that was part of one of the Snapped T-posts. Due to the cold temps they just snapped off. We found one of the T-posts pieces, out of its candle - farther up the driveway. (Also helping us figure out which direction they were headed) They were scrapes in the ground as if this T-post was drug along, from its end. (Relevance in future). While standing out talking to the sheriff, Either my brother or mother received a text message from his Ex, saying “Why the cops at your house?”. Considering she lives in town, far from us, and happened to be driving by, they found it suspicious. Then which ever received it replied, “Someone ran down our lights” or something to that effect. To which she replied something along the lines of “oh, that sucks”.  The fact that that hadn’t talked in months, and this spur of the moment message, made us all a little suspicious. Then they asked her "Why were you out by our house?"<br>
apparently she happened to be cruising the back roads getting high. Hymm.<br>
The next morning we walked down to our neighbors house, who also have security cameras, to see what, if anything their cameras saw, and which way the person had come from. Right after the time stamp on our camera, There was a dark colored car with long taillights going up the road at a high rate of speed(in winter, around 10-11pm, i forgot which). The tracks in the yard verified that this was potentially the car that ran down our lights, considering it belonged to none of us. Due to his ex texting us at that time, we decided to drive around town to see if there was any bumper damage to her car. (Yes she drives a dark colored car with long tail lights(coincidence, according to police)).<br>
We went by what he believed to be her house, and could not find her car anywhere. So after a while we gave up, and decided to take the back roads home. On the way past the park, which is connected to our back-roads, and about a 9 minute drive from our house, he noticed her car parked in the outside lot, right against the road. We turned around and went to look now.<br>
There was some white paint scrapes on her  bumper, and the candles are made with white plastic, but red paint(and white rings), her car is a dark maroon color. The first thing we noticed was the flat front right tire. (coincidence) I then crawled under the rear of the car, because i was the only one of us two that would fit, and looked for any scrape marks, we hoped the t-post would of left. Right down her gas tank, there is a 3 grooved kind of gouge, that matches the shape of a T-post.(coincidence) and that fact that it(her car) was so close to our house, that she drove by, texted us, all coincidences. Thank you police force! What we should of done is check the tire for a puncture mark, but figured we had seen enough.(and got good pictures,timestamped!)</p>
<p>You tell me guys, think it was her? I would also like to hear your reasoning behind your thoughts.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/guilty-or-not-guilty/539354/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/guilty-or-not-guilty/539354/1</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 29 Jan 2014 06:44:10 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-539354-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/guilty-or-not-guilty/539354.rss">Guilty or not Guilty?</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
