<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Amulius 317 Ironman | Unique features | Stable Economy and much more! ★</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/amulius-317-ironman-unique-features-stable-economy-and-much-more/555210</link>
    <description>[center][img]http://i61.tinypic.com/2zscmsk.png[/img][/center]
[center][url=https://www.moparisthebest.com/forum]http://amuliusrsps.com/forum[/url]
[url=https://www.moparisthebest.com/forum/index.php?/topic/28-fixing-client-problems/]http://amuliusrsps.com/forum/index.php?/topic/28-fixing-client-problems/[/url][/center]
[center]
[youtube]https://youtu.be/FV8zjjAEg0c[/youtube]
Why AmuliusRSPS?

Welcome to Amulius. This is an absolutely great achievement for the server &amp; staff who have incredible experience in RSPS.

By now you are probably thinking why you should play on this server. Well, Amulius will offer you some quality gaming experience! We have many creative activities in the server &amp; our developers are awesome and will absolutely deliver awesome updates and joy to the players.


I would first like to thank from the bottom of my hearts to all the people supporting this server! which are the players themselves and the amazing people who are able to donate and keep the server alive and running! We appreciate them very much, we wouldn&#39;t be here without them, so I would like to thank them very much, from me and the high staff team!

We also have our own community forums which you can check out here: amuliusrsps.com/forum

This forum helps us to improve the server alot due to the fact that the players themselves get to give suggestions &amp; feedback.

[img]http://www.rune-server.org/static/toplist/300481.gif?1[/img]

Server Features

- Real RS Grand Exchange
- Loyalty Points
- Fully working Bank Tabs!
- Bounty Hunter
- Ironman Mode
- Ultimate Ironman Mode
- Well of Goodwill
- Automatic Voting + Highscores
- Automatic Donations
- Fully working Clan Chat!
- Full Gambling 
- Full working Trivia system with points!
- Working Dungeons
- Runespan



Bosses:
- God Wars Dungeon
- Nex
- Corporeal Beast
- Tormented Demons
- Dagannoth Kings
- Slash Bash
- Nomad
- Pheonix
- Bandos Avatar
- Kalphite Queen
- King Black Dragon
- Chaos Elemental
- Frost Dragons
- Glacors

Minigames:
- Warriors Guild
- Pest Control
- Duel Arena
- Barrows
- Fight Cave
- Fight Pits
- Soul Wars[/center]

[b][u]Updatelog[/u][/b]

&lt;blockquote&gt;[size=8pt]Fire making (Ring of Fire &amp; Flame Gloves) 
 Players have a 3% chance while firemaking to obtain any of the 2 pieces. Players can collect multiple pieces and/or sets. 
 Effect: Players have a 10% chance to put up to 3 logs into a bonfire in a single action, if both items are worn. If possible, the player can right-click the logs and automatically light it  (Without a tinderbox), if the player is wearing the Flame Gloves.Finally, the player earns additional experience if both items are worn. 
 
Herblore &amp; Hunter (Witchdoctor Clothing) -
 Players have a 3% chance while making potions or Hunting (Red Chinchompa, Ninja, Dragon &amp; Kingly) to obtain any of the 3 pieces Players can collect multiple pieces and/or sets. 
 Effect (Herblore) - Players have a 10% chance to create 4-dose potions instead of 3-dose. Players also have a 10% chance to create multiple potions in a single action, up to 4, if the f ull set is worn. Finally, the player has a slight increase in experience, if the full set is worn. 
 Effect (Hunter) - Players have a +10% increased chance at capturing Hunting NPC&#39;s, as well as a 10% chance to capture multiple in a single action, up to 4, if the full set is worn.  Finally, the player has a slight increase in experience, if the full set is worn. 
 
Mining (Golden Mining Suit &amp; Inferno Adze) 
 Players have a 3% chance while mining (1% for mining the Crashed Star) to obtain any of the 5 pieces of Golden Mining Suit or the Inferno Adze. Players can collect multiple pieces  and/or sets. 
 Effect (Golden Mining Suit): Players have a 10% chance to mine multiple ores in a single action, up to 4, if the full set is worn. Also, the player earns additional experience, if the full  set is worn. 
 Effect (Inferno Adze) - Players have a 10% chance to automatically smelt the ore (Excluding Coal), receiving smithing experience. This ability can be toggled off or no by operating the  item.
 
 
Woodcutting (Lumberjack Outfit &amp; Inferno Adze) 
 Players have a 3% chance while woodcutting to obtain any of the 4 pieces of Lumberjack Outfit or the Inferno Adze. Players can collect multiple pieces and/or sets. 
 Effect (Lumberjack outfit): Players have a 10% chance to cut multiple logs in a single action, up to 4, if the full set is worn. Players also have a +3% increase to obtain Bird&#39;s Nest with  eggs in them. Also, the player earns additional experience, if the full set is worn. 
 Effect (Inferno Adze) - Players have a 10% chance to automatically light the log, earning Firemaking experience. This can be toggled off or no by operating the item.
 
 
 
fixed the runecrafter robe
fixed the golden mining outfit
 Players have a 3% chance while Runecrafting to obtain any of the 3 pieces of Master Runecrafting outfit. Players can collect multiple pieces and/or sets. 
 Effect (Master Runecrafting Outfit): Players have a 7% chance to create double or triple the amount of runes that the player would normally make. Also, the player earns additional  experience, if the full set is worn.

Dragonkin lamps added in the dung shop
Dragon med helm needs now 60 defence to equip.
Slayer helm, full slayer helm, stat bonuses are fixed
Wizard boots - fixed the correct stat bonuses
vengeance will needs to reset when entering dung
ragefire,steadfast, glaivens are now tradeable
PC points needs to be reduced to 10
The money you start with in dung is now doubled.
You will recieve 5 extra loyalty points everytime you gain a level, and 2,500 loyalty points when you recieve 99 level.
A permanent fire added to the donator zone for a constant cooking/bonfire
Fletching animation needs is now looped until logs used
Whips price adjusted from 500k to 5mill
Reduce runite ore from 196k to 80k
Nerfed drop rates
Fixed CPU usage issue
Fixed highscore for the website and vote fully works.
Zammy pathfinding issue (The boss doesn&#39;t attack back, it just stands there)
Nerfed caskets
Trivia - so, from now on 3 players can win, and not just 1.
Heblore EXP fixed
Smithing EXP buffed
Max cash tickets: http://i.imgur.com/zvKDi4F.png
Ironman drop rate has been abit raised.
Fishing Reworked
Fishing guild.
Switched out npc fishing spots with objects. (Click Radius and Fish spot size solution.)
Added Sea Turtle and Manta proper cook levels and fish levels.
You no longer can fish Rocktail with worms, it is now proper living minerals.
Improved combat system
Interface when attacking NPC
Item definitions error occurred by character encodingi
Staking - full inventory bug fixed
Fixed gembags
Fishing - made it so fishing spots disappear and re-appear
Mining - made a ore re-spawn timer
erblore - when using herbs on a vial of water, made a menu pop up with &quot;make 1, 5, 10, X&quot; , same for 
when using a secondary on a potion (unf
Christmas scythe 
You can now use Iron arrows with shortbow / Longbow. 
Divine will no longer drain prayer for gold members 
Increase the rare drop table drop rate on Ring of Wealth 
Fixed playercount issue
Snow added, and snowflakes
fixed the trivia shop options
fixed zuriel’s hood
fixed skeleton helm
fixed the smithing furnace
Made the Starter tutorial much better, and understandable.
fixed the glitched npc @ home
fixed the flaming gloves
 fixed that ring of fire
fixed the star dust shop
added city teleports in the teleports tab
added the experience bonus for the golden mining suit
made the text of the achievement tab smaller but still need to think of something significant to make it unique

Ice Strykewyrms are stronger
You can no longer rest while walking
Players will now drop their items upon death in GWD boss rooms
added slayer requirement to dark beasts
Hexcres &amp; Focus sight will now go to your helmet slot and not weapon.
took away rocktails, sharks, ect. all the high level fish and make them fishable only
You can now make super restores.
More banking place
New rank system
Farming for plat + normal players broken
Fixed blurite ore at glacors (now mineable)
Animal bow - added range interface with correct female model
Double exp
Spirit shields wont drain for platinum and gold members
Added HP above heads (need to update client for that)
Clan chat error fixed
Interface bug fixed
Fixed herbs
Fixed nex map
Rings (i) are kept on death
Corrupt dragon spear needs to be fixed (Dropped by chaos elemental) once you have speced a player it has to freeze them for 12 seconds, reg spear does 6
Toggle music loading client
Removing snow and christmas shit
We&#39;ve also added a update server. That means the cache size have been reduced from 170 MB to 11 MB.
Auto donator fixed
Top donator on the homepage
Livechat on the homepage has been fixed
New donator page
Fletching animation will now loop until logs used.
The money which you start with in dungeoneering has been doubled. The food in dungeoneering now heals a lot more than before.
warriors guild, you shouldn&#39;t get dragon defender instantly now (The dragon defender can be obtained first but if you get unlucky and don&#39;t get it as your first defender you&#39;ll have to work your way up)
Dropping a lazy cat as actual pet
Fixed yell (just for you wise :*)
Fixed anvil at smithing arena
Clipping system re-worked meaning warrior guild bug is fixed.
You can now sell noted items to the thieving shop for the same value.
Staffchat - new features
Dicebag just like RS
Max cape - making it so u need 99 cons wearing it.
Construction - sawmill to make planks
The message saying Double XP is active is consistently on. The message is now replaced with double loot and it will only show on the weekends.
Portal at wild agility course removed
New TRIVIA questions.
New players now need 10 minutes in game time &amp; 150 total level to be able to talk in the clan chat (Stops spam advertisements)
Eating timers reduced by 0.2 seconds (200 ms)
Friends login &amp; logout display fixed
Enchant bolts added
Add anti bot for thieving
Text encoding/decoding issues
Toggle music loading client
Staffchat system
Double weekend loot system
Zatye bow added
525 maps with server sided pathfinding
We&#39;ve also added a update server. That means the cache size have been reduced from 170 MB to 11 MB.
Force movement player rendering and adjusted flag order
Rank system
Dicing like RuneScape
construction
Fixed blackscreen
Player Rights has been completely re-written. (DonatorRights &amp; PlayerRights are now separate | Staff no longer receive donator benefits, if they have not donated | The amount of donation ranks has been reduced to four instead of five | Priority system written, so that if your account has a higher player right than PLAYER; your DonatorRights will be secondary to the PlayerRights you have &amp; vise-versa. If you are just a player, then the server will prioritize your DonatorRights.)
Yell has been updated with Ranks/Colors/Etc... dependent on your Rights priority.
Donators can make their own titles by doing ::titles
Construction houses now save.
200m capes added
Fixed the nex items
Added pvp armour degrading
Added in the giant pouch for runecrafting
Any piece provides a direct teleport to the ZMI Runecrafting Altar
Effect (Gloves of Silence) - Players have a chance to steal multiple times in a single action, up to 4.
Snowball added
New players now need 10 minutes in game time &amp; 150 total level to be able to talk in the clan chat (Stops spam advertisements)
New players now need 30 minutes game time played &amp; 150 total level to be able to trade other players.
World message when someone buys max cape
More banking place
New rank system
Farming for plat + normal players broken
Fixed blurite ore at glacors (now mineable)
Animal bow - added range interface with correct female model
Double exp
Spirit shields wont drain for platinum and gold members
Added HP above heads (need to update client for that)
Clan chat error fixed
Interface bug fixed
Fixed herbs
Fixed nex map
525 maps with server sided pathfinding
Fog color changes
Improvements of bank dialouge
Loading and downloading improvement (Much faster)
Wilderness ditch (Working with the 525 map)
Fixed divine shield draining for plat members and diamond
 Farming patch growth error
Chaos elemental health nerfed
Friends login &amp; logout display fixed

and much more![/size]&lt;/blockquote&gt;</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 17 Apr 2016 08:09:32 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/amulius-317-ironman-unique-features-stable-economy-and-much-more/555210.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Amulius 317 Ironman | Unique features | Stable Economy and much more! ★</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@rslover32 rslover32]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/rslover32">@rslover32</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“briney21, post:2, topic:555210”]nothing works cant sign up to forums which is a awful idea tbh cant download a client. so yea dunno how you are ment to get players[/quote]<a href="http://amuliusrsps.com/forum/index.php?/topic/28-fixing-client-problems/" rel="nofollow noopener">http://amuliusrsps.com/forum/index.php?/topic/28-fixing-client-problems/</a></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/amulius-317-ironman-unique-features-stable-economy-and-much-more/555210/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/amulius-317-ironman-unique-features-stable-economy-and-much-more/555210/3</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 17 Apr 2016 08:09:32 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-555210-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/amulius-317-ironman-unique-features-stable-economy-and-much-more/555210.rss">Amulius 317 Ironman | Unique features | Stable Economy and much more! ★</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Amulius 317 Ironman | Unique features | Stable Economy and much more! ★</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@briney21 briney21]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/briney21">@briney21</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>nothing works cant sign up to forums which is a awful idea tbh cant download a client. so yea dunno how you are ment to get players</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/amulius-317-ironman-unique-features-stable-economy-and-much-more/555210/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/amulius-317-ironman-unique-features-stable-economy-and-much-more/555210/2</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 17 Apr 2016 01:48:23 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-555210-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/amulius-317-ironman-unique-features-stable-economy-and-much-more/555210.rss">Amulius 317 Ironman | Unique features | Stable Economy and much more! ★</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Amulius 317 Ironman | Unique features | Stable Economy and much more! ★</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@rslover32 rslover32]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/rslover32">@rslover32</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[center]<div class="lightbox-wrapper"><a class="lightbox" href="http://i61.tinypic.com/2zscmsk.png" title="2zscmsk.png" rel="nofollow noopener"><img src="http://i61.tinypic.com/2zscmsk.png" alt width="690" height="211"><div class="meta">
<svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-far-image svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#far-image"></use></svg><span class="filename">2zscmsk.png</span><span class="informations">955×293</span><svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-discourse-expand svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#discourse-expand"></use></svg>
</div></a></div>[/center]<br>
[center]<a href="https://www.moparisthebest.com/forum" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">http://amuliusrsps.com/forum</a><br>
<a href="https://www.moparisthebest.com/forum/index.php?/topic/28-fixing-client-problems/" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">http://amuliusrsps.com/forum/index.php?/topic/28-fixing-client-problems/</a>[/center]<br>
[center]<br>
[youtube]<a href="https://youtu.be/FV8zjjAEg0c%5B/youtube%5D" rel="nofollow noopener">https://youtu.be/FV8zjjAEg0c[/youtube]</a><br>
Why AmuliusRSPS?</p>
<p>Welcome to Amulius. This is an absolutely great achievement for the server &amp; staff who have incredible experience in RSPS.</p>
<p>By now you are probably thinking why you should play on this server. Well, Amulius will offer you some quality gaming experience! We have many creative activities in the server &amp; our developers are awesome and will absolutely deliver awesome updates and joy to the players.</p>
<p>I would first like to thank from the bottom of my hearts to all the people supporting this server! which are the players themselves and the amazing people who are able to donate and keep the server alive and running! We appreciate them very much, we wouldn’t be here without them, so I would like to thank them very much, from me and the high staff team!</p>
<p>We also have our own community forums which you can check out here: <a href="http://amuliusrsps.com/forum" rel="nofollow noopener">amuliusrsps.com/forum</a></p>
<p>This forum helps us to improve the server alot due to the fact that the players themselves get to give suggestions &amp; feedback.</p>
<p><img src="http://www.rune-server.org/static/toplist/300481.gif?1" alt width="500" height="70"></p>
<p>Server Features</p>
<ul>
<li>Real RS Grand Exchange</li>
<li>Loyalty Points</li>
<li>Fully working Bank Tabs!</li>
<li>Bounty Hunter</li>
<li>Ironman Mode</li>
<li>Ultimate Ironman Mode</li>
<li>Well of Goodwill</li>
<li>Automatic Voting + Highscores</li>
<li>Automatic Donations</li>
<li>Fully working Clan Chat!</li>
<li>Full Gambling</li>
<li>Full working Trivia system with points!</li>
<li>Working Dungeons</li>
<li>Runespan</li>
</ul>
<p>Bosses:</p>
<ul>
<li>God Wars Dungeon</li>
<li>Nex</li>
<li>Corporeal Beast</li>
<li>Tormented Demons</li>
<li>Dagannoth Kings</li>
<li>Slash Bash</li>
<li>Nomad</li>
<li>Pheonix</li>
<li>Bandos Avatar</li>
<li>Kalphite Queen</li>
<li>King Black Dragon</li>
<li>Chaos Elemental</li>
<li>Frost Dragons</li>
<li>Glacors</li>
</ul>
<p>Minigames:</p>
<ul>
<li>Warriors Guild</li>
<li>Pest Control</li>
<li>Duel Arena</li>
<li>Barrows</li>
<li>Fight Cave</li>
<li>Fight Pits</li>
<li>Soul Wars[/center]</li>
</ul>
<p><span class="bbcode-b"><span class="bbcode-u">Updatelog</span></span></p>
<blockquote>[size=8pt]Fire making (Ring of Fire &amp; Flame Gloves) 
 Players have a 3% chance while firemaking to obtain any of the 2 pieces. Players can collect multiple pieces and/or sets. 
 Effect: Players have a 10% chance to put up to 3 logs into a bonfire in a single action, if both items are worn. If possible, the player can right-click the logs and automatically light it  (Without a tinderbox), if the player is wearing the Flame Gloves.Finally, the player earns additional experience if both items are worn. 
<p>Herblore &amp; Hunter (Witchdoctor Clothing) -<br>
Players have a 3% chance while making potions or Hunting (Red Chinchompa, Ninja, Dragon &amp; Kingly) to obtain any of the 3 pieces Players can collect multiple pieces and/or sets.<br>
Effect (Herblore) - Players have a 10% chance to create 4-dose potions instead of 3-dose. Players also have a 10% chance to create multiple potions in a single action, up to 4, if the f ull set is worn. Finally, the player has a slight increase in experience, if the full set is worn.<br>
Effect (Hunter) - Players have a +10% increased chance at capturing Hunting NPC’s, as well as a 10% chance to capture multiple in a single action, up to 4, if the full set is worn.  Finally, the player has a slight increase in experience, if the full set is worn.</p>
<p>Mining (Golden Mining Suit &amp; Inferno Adze)<br>
Players have a 3% chance while mining (1% for mining the Crashed Star) to obtain any of the 5 pieces of Golden Mining Suit or the Inferno Adze. Players can collect multiple pieces  and/or sets.<br>
Effect (Golden Mining Suit): Players have a 10% chance to mine multiple ores in a single action, up to 4, if the full set is worn. Also, the player earns additional experience, if the full  set is worn.<br>
Effect (Inferno Adze) - Players have a 10% chance to automatically smelt the ore (Excluding Coal), receiving smithing experience. This ability can be toggled off or no by operating the  item.</p>
<p>Woodcutting (Lumberjack Outfit &amp; Inferno Adze)<br>
Players have a 3% chance while woodcutting to obtain any of the 4 pieces of Lumberjack Outfit or the Inferno Adze. Players can collect multiple pieces and/or sets.<br>
Effect (Lumberjack outfit): Players have a 10% chance to cut multiple logs in a single action, up to 4, if the full set is worn. Players also have a +3% increase to obtain Bird’s Nest with  eggs in them. Also, the player earns additional experience, if the full set is worn.<br>
Effect (Inferno Adze) - Players have a 10% chance to automatically light the log, earning Firemaking experience. This can be toggled off or no by operating the item.</p>
<p>fixed the runecrafter robe<br>
fixed the golden mining outfit<br>
Players have a 3% chance while Runecrafting to obtain any of the 3 pieces of Master Runecrafting outfit. Players can collect multiple pieces and/or sets.<br>
Effect (Master Runecrafting Outfit): Players have a 7% chance to create double or triple the amount of runes that the player would normally make. Also, the player earns additional  experience, if the full set is worn.</p>
<p>Dragonkin lamps added in the dung shop<br>
Dragon med helm needs now 60 defence to equip.<br>
Slayer helm, full slayer helm, stat bonuses are fixed<br>
Wizard boots - fixed the correct stat bonuses<br>
vengeance will needs to reset when entering dung<br>
ragefire,steadfast, glaivens are now tradeable<br>
PC points needs to be reduced to 10<br>
The money you start with in dung is now doubled.<br>
You will recieve 5 extra loyalty points everytime you gain a level, and 2,500 loyalty points when you recieve 99 level.<br>
A permanent fire added to the donator zone for a constant cooking/bonfire<br>
Fletching animation needs is now looped until logs used<br>
Whips price adjusted from 500k to 5mill<br>
Reduce runite ore from 196k to 80k<br>
Nerfed drop rates<br>
Fixed CPU usage issue<br>
Fixed highscore for the website and vote fully works.<br>
Zammy pathfinding issue (The boss doesn’t attack back, it just stands there)<br>
Nerfed caskets<br>
Trivia - so, from now on 3 players can win, and not just 1.<br>
Heblore EXP fixed<br>
Smithing EXP buffed<br>
Max cash tickets: <a href="http://i.imgur.com/zvKDi4F.png" rel="nofollow noopener">http://i.imgur.com/zvKDi4F.png</a><br>
Ironman drop rate has been abit raised.<br>
Fishing Reworked<br>
Fishing guild.<br>
Switched out npc fishing spots with objects. (Click Radius and Fish spot size solution.)<br>
Added Sea Turtle and Manta proper cook levels and fish levels.<br>
You no longer can fish Rocktail with worms, it is now proper living minerals.<br>
Improved combat system<br>
Interface when attacking NPC<br>
Item definitions error occurred by character encodingi<br>
Staking - full inventory bug fixed<br>
Fixed gembags<br>
Fishing - made it so fishing spots disappear and re-appear<br>
Mining - made a ore re-spawn timer<br>
erblore - when using herbs on a vial of water, made a menu pop up with “make 1, 5, 10, X” , same for<br>
when using a secondary on a potion (unf<br>
Christmas scythe<br>
You can now use Iron arrows with shortbow / Longbow.<br>
Divine will no longer drain prayer for gold members<br>
Increase the rare drop table drop rate on Ring of Wealth<br>
Fixed playercount issue<br>
Snow added, and snowflakes<br>
fixed the trivia shop options<br>
fixed zuriel’s hood<br>
fixed skeleton helm<br>
fixed the smithing furnace<br>
Made the Starter tutorial much better, and understandable.<br>
fixed the glitched npc @ home<br>
fixed the flaming gloves<br>
fixed that ring of fire<br>
fixed the star dust shop<br>
added city teleports in the teleports tab<br>
added the experience bonus for the golden mining suit<br>
made the text of the achievement tab smaller but still need to think of something significant to make it unique</p>
<p>Ice Strykewyrms are stronger<br>
You can no longer rest while walking<br>
Players will now drop their items upon death in GWD boss rooms<br>
added slayer requirement to dark beasts<br>
Hexcres &amp; Focus sight will now go to your helmet slot and not weapon.<br>
took away rocktails, sharks, ect. all the high level fish and make them fishable only<br>
You can now make super restores.<br>
More banking place<br>
New rank system<br>
Farming for plat + normal players broken<br>
Fixed blurite ore at glacors (now mineable)<br>
Animal bow - added range interface with correct female model<br>
Double exp<br>
Spirit shields wont drain for platinum and gold members<br>
Added HP above heads (need to update client for that)<br>
Clan chat error fixed<br>
Interface bug fixed<br>
Fixed herbs<br>
Fixed nex map<br>
Rings (i) are kept on death<br>
Corrupt dragon spear needs to be fixed (Dropped by chaos elemental) once you have speced a player it has to freeze them for 12 seconds, reg spear does 6<br>
Toggle music loading client<br>
Removing snow and christmas shit<br>
We’ve also added a update server. That means the cache size have been reduced from 170 MB to 11 MB.<br>
Auto donator fixed<br>
Top donator on the homepage<br>
Livechat on the homepage has been fixed<br>
New donator page<br>
Fletching animation will now loop until logs used.<br>
The money which you start with in dungeoneering has been doubled. The food in dungeoneering now heals a lot more than before.<br>
warriors guild, you shouldn’t get dragon defender instantly now (The dragon defender can be obtained first but if you get unlucky and don’t get it as your first defender you’ll have to work your way up)<br>
Dropping a lazy cat as actual pet<br>
Fixed yell (just for you wise :*)<br>
Fixed anvil at smithing arena<br>
Clipping system re-worked meaning warrior guild bug is fixed.<br>
You can now sell noted items to the thieving shop for the same value.<br>
Staffchat - new features<br>
Dicebag just like RS<br>
Max cape - making it so u need 99 cons wearing it.<br>
Construction - sawmill to make planks<br>
The message saying Double XP is active is consistently on. The message is now replaced with double loot and it will only show on the weekends.<br>
Portal at wild agility course removed<br>
New TRIVIA questions.<br>
New players now need 10 minutes in game time &amp; 150 total level to be able to talk in the clan chat (Stops spam advertisements)<br>
Eating timers reduced by 0.2 seconds (200 ms)<br>
Friends login &amp; logout display fixed<br>
Enchant bolts added<br>
Add anti bot for thieving<br>
Text encoding/decoding issues<br>
Toggle music loading client<br>
Staffchat system<br>
Double weekend loot system<br>
Zatye bow added<br>
525 maps with server sided pathfinding<br>
We’ve also added a update server. That means the cache size have been reduced from 170 MB to 11 MB.<br>
Force movement player rendering and adjusted flag order<br>
Rank system<br>
Dicing like RuneScape<br>
construction<br>
Fixed blackscreen<br>
Player Rights has been completely re-written. (DonatorRights &amp; PlayerRights are now separate | Staff no longer receive donator benefits, if they have not donated | The amount of donation ranks has been reduced to four instead of five | Priority system written, so that if your account has a higher player right than PLAYER; your DonatorRights will be secondary to the PlayerRights you have &amp; vise-versa. If you are just a player, then the server will prioritize your DonatorRights.)<br>
Yell has been updated with Ranks/Colors/Etc… dependent on your Rights priority.<br>
Donators can make their own titles by doing ::titles<br>
Construction houses now save.<br>
200m capes added<br>
Fixed the nex items<br>
Added pvp armour degrading<br>
Added in the giant pouch for runecrafting<br>
Any piece provides a direct teleport to the ZMI Runecrafting Altar<br>
Effect (Gloves of Silence) - Players have a chance to steal multiple times in a single action, up to 4.<br>
Snowball added<br>
New players now need 10 minutes in game time &amp; 150 total level to be able to talk in the clan chat (Stops spam advertisements)<br>
New players now need 30 minutes game time played &amp; 150 total level to be able to trade other players.<br>
World message when someone buys max cape<br>
More banking place<br>
New rank system<br>
Farming for plat + normal players broken<br>
Fixed blurite ore at glacors (now mineable)<br>
Animal bow - added range interface with correct female model<br>
Double exp<br>
Spirit shields wont drain for platinum and gold members<br>
Added HP above heads (need to update client for that)<br>
Clan chat error fixed<br>
Interface bug fixed<br>
Fixed herbs<br>
Fixed nex map<br>
525 maps with server sided pathfinding<br>
Fog color changes<br>
Improvements of bank dialouge<br>
Loading and downloading improvement (Much faster)<br>
Wilderness ditch (Working with the 525 map)<br>
Fixed divine shield draining for plat members and diamond<br>
Farming patch growth error<br>
Chaos elemental health nerfed<br>
Friends login &amp; logout display fixed</p>
<p>and much more![/size]</p>
</blockquote>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/amulius-317-ironman-unique-features-stable-economy-and-much-more/555210/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/amulius-317-ironman-unique-features-stable-economy-and-much-more/555210/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 16 Apr 2016 18:37:35 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-555210-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/amulius-317-ironman-unique-features-stable-economy-and-much-more/555210.rss">Amulius 317 Ironman | Unique features | Stable Economy and much more! ★</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
