<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Impulse [637/639]</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/impulse-637-639/535184</link>
    <description>[center]
[FONT=Tahoma][SIZE=4][B]Impulse[/B][/SIZE][/FONT] is Dementhium 637 loading 639 based server developed and improved upon by Myself and some people who have helped me along the way. I give big thanks and credits to the Dementhium team (Especially &#39;Mystic Flow), Sixpack, WildSkiller, AeroPK and Orel.

Impulse will be based around RuneScape in 2011 Bounty hunter / City PvP mode. This is a continue on from my previous project however I will be improving upon it.

[B][U]Core Lead Developer[/U][/B]

[ul][li][IMG]http://i.imgur.com/iWzjBqN.png[/img]Magnito[/li][/ul]


[i][u][b]Previous updates[/b][/u][/i]
- Diagonal combat corrected
- Flawless Bounty Hunter system / Target assigning added
- Functional Earned potential system with artifact drops
- Summoning supports wolpertinger, bull ant, pack yack, bunyip, wartortoise and a bunch of other familiars now
- Pirate huts have been added with lock picking
- Axe huts and mage arena and small bats area have been added with NPC definitions
- 100% Farming skill has been added ( Eco-based content really )
- Bugs / dupes corrected ( Can&#39;t remember what they were specifically )
- Equipping items while in view equipment stats is now functional
- Punishment &amp; Clan chats saving has been re-written 
- General server things have been done - Instead of it saying Friends List - RuneScape, it will now say the server name ( Same on logging out button )
- General donator requirements, yells, commands have all been added
- Nearly every bank in the world is now a safezone rather than a dangerous area
- Revenant caves + some more map data has been added. Revenants is now a multi-zone area.
- If a familiar stands over a player, the player is shown not the familiar - People like this feature due to hybridding

[u][i][b]Latest updates[/b][/i][/u]
[] - Made it so when city pvp ( world pvp ) is toggled, the pvp strings change according to how it was in runescape 2011. If you are level 138, it will show 108 - 138 and you can attack anyone in that range and this also updates according to wilderness level
[] - Fixed a autocasting issue where if you are autocasting and you switch weapon, the weapons selected attack style would be the last one you chose and be auto-matically selected. Fixed it, now when you switch weapons while autocasting, you have to select the attack style yourself and autocast will be disabled
[] - Added some item definitions ( bonuses ) to certain items that were missing
[] - Corrected the ep colour for when your ep is zero
------------------------------------------------------------------
[] - Fixed the praying issue for when you are using quickprayers and your prayer points run out, your headicon would still be there
[] - Fixed the issue of your special amount showing up as 0% even though its 100%, this will never be an issue again
[] - Added ring of vigour
[] - Decrease a delay in combat, if you was to eat, it would set a delay for how long you wait to hit back, this was way too high so its been reduced and its perfect
[] - Damage poisoning has been tweaked, it now grabs the amount to poison from the cache from what weapon you are wielding and is correct
[] - Added more ranging bolt specials
[] - Corrected so many attack / defence animations, re-wrote some of the ways animations were handled ( a bunch of cases for itemids could be handled with one if statement )
[] - Added a 5 minute afk timer, after your timer is out, your player will just do an animation which will show your player sitting down on a chair. ( I prefer this than logging out tbh :P )
[] - Corrected the combat magic following, once you are autocasting and the player starts to run, you will now chase him and mage at the same time. Credits to Mylyn.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
[] - Created a class known as &#39;PlayerLogic.java&#39;. This handles the setters and getters for the player. This is done as : player.getPlayerLogic() ... Its alot more efficient than packing it all into player.java itself and having it crammed up.
[] - Implemented the AStarPathFinder class. ( A* search algorithm ), &#39;Mystic Flow once stated that some lagg issues were to do with bad pathfinding. This has been fixed and is no longer an issue and stability is become alot stronger for the core of the source. Stability has &#39;fixed&#39; in a way and source runs alot smoother.
[] - Corrected the issue for when you switch items, the spell you selected doesn&#39;t clear
[] - Fixed the combat delays ( Been trying to do this since I started with dementhium ). Combat is alot smoother, players don&#39;t have to wait to get hit twice before attacking back after switching ( One of the best updates )
[] - Restoration of special attack has been tweaked, it was a little too high
-------------------------------------------------------------------------
[] - Fixed the bug where your icon ( config ) showing if you are in wildy or not in wildy kept flashing. It has stopped flashing
[] - The PvP Level strings are now in functionality, you can attack people according to the range of combat levels shown above your ep percentage
[] - Bounty hunter skulling system done depending on your wealth. These skulls only appear once you are in the bounty hunter crators
------------------------------------------------------------------------
[] - Fixed the &#39;moonwalking&#39; issue. When a player hit another player/npc with magic, and ran away, they would run backwards and face the opponent, this is now fixed. They will turn around and continue running straight like it should be
[] - Added 100% Bounty hunter crators. Everywhere before you go in the crators is safe and the stairs is too. Once you enter, your bounty hunter skull will be assigned according to wealth
[] - On logout, if you had a bounty hunter skull, next time you login your skull will stay the same. Once you fight someone in bounty hunter crator, your skull won&#39;t go and the normal one will not appear. You keep your skull.
[] - Perfected the PvP SafeZoneTimer. My final updated needed to perfect it was : if you attack someone ( and not get attacked back ) and you run straight out, it trigger for you and count down. If you attack someone then don&#39;t leave wilderness for some time ( and not get attacked back ), you won&#39;t trigger it
-------------------------------------------------------------------------
[] - Fixed the bug where players used to get stuck after trading/fighting. Normally, they would keep facing to wherever the other person goes to even if you are not interacting with them. This no longer happens
-------------------------------------------------------------------------
[] - Re-corrected my fix for the arrow on the minimap, if you have a gravestone and a target, both of them will now show up like in rs
[] - Added spirit kyatt familiar
[] - If a players wealth changed while in bounty hunter, their bounty hunter skull will update to what its supposed to be
-------------------------------------------------------------------------
[] - Added the spell book order saving, it will now save to how you last arranged your spells in your spell book
[] - Made it so if players die with barrows items, the broken version of it will now drop to the killer
[u][i][b]Media[/b][/i][/u]

[IMG]http://puu.sh/56fQO.jpg[/img]
[IMG]http://puu.sh/5733t.jpg[/img]
[IMG]http://puu.sh/59ysD.jpg[/img]
[IMG]http://puu.sh/5aJho.jpg[/img]

My 10 second PvP SafeZone Timer

http://youtu.be/tzDEmC0k-lI
[/center]</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 05 Nov 2013 16:15:14 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/impulse-637-639/535184.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Impulse [637/639]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Magnitoo Magnitoo]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/magnitoo">@Magnitoo</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Thanks to everyone supporting me, This is a continue on from my old project so i still have all my other features.<br>
Just a quick list of the things i can think of :</p>
<pre><code class="lang-auto">- 100% Farming, trees, herbs, flowers, allotments ( Done properly like RuneScape )
- All dupes fixed ( Bugs - as far as i know they're all fixed )
- Ability to toggle on PvP world ( Once toggled on, all cities will be pvp except from banks and the pvp strings etc will toggle on immediately ). When toggled off, all cities will be a safe zone, all strings will go and will look normal again
- 10 Second PvP SafeZone Timer ( Have 1 little issue with it which will be fixed real soon )
- Custom teleport system, an interface used with more than 3 pages but same interface.
- Ability to change your displayname but still login with your username. Displaynames save on logout and in
- Ability to disable a certain persons yell / and re-enable

I have lots more features but I just can't think of them. </code></pre>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/impulse-637-639/535184/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/impulse-637-639/535184/6</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 05 Nov 2013 16:15:14 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-535184-6</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/impulse-637-639/535184.rss">Impulse [637/639]</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Impulse [637/639]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Ix_Soulcist_xI Soulcist]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/ix_soulcist_xi">@Ix_Soulcist_xI</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Lookin’ nice so far mate, keep it up.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/impulse-637-639/535184/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/impulse-637-639/535184/5</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2013 19:05:18 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-535184-5</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/impulse-637-639/535184.rss">Impulse [637/639]</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Impulse [637/639]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@arham_4 arham 4]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/arham_4">@arham_4</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Looks good</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/impulse-637-639/535184/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/impulse-637-639/535184/4</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2013 17:37:53 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-535184-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/impulse-637-639/535184.rss">Impulse [637/639]</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Impulse [637/639]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Magnitoo Magnitoo]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/magnitoo">@Magnitoo</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[center]<br>
[B][U][FONT=Arial Black]Client Sided Work[/FONT][/U][/B]</p>
<p>[B][I]Titles :[/I][/B]</p>
<p><img src="http://puu.sh/55UHv.jpg" alt width="" height=""></p>
<p>[B][I]Crowns :[/I][/B]</p>
<p><img src="http://puu.sh/55UWQ.jpg" alt width="" height=""></p>
<p>[B][I]Snow Client Toggling On/Off :[/I][/B]</p>
<p><img src="http://puu.sh/55V7i.jpg" alt width="" height=""></p>
<p>[B][I]Some more features[/I][/B]</p>
<ul>
<li>If a player toggled the snow client and re-logged, their client will still be toggled on the snow client</li>
<li>Players can open the developer console and type the word ‘vote’ and this will browse the voting site for them</li>
<li>Players no longer have to right click then click attack to attack npcs, they can now just left click them. Thanks to [user]bando[/user] for this.</li>
<li>The clients ip/name can be changed simply by editing a static string. These are called where they are needed</li>
<li>The invisibility glitch has been fixed client sided. The equipids will be downloaded onto the user’s computer and read from there causing no invisibility while on the webclient</li>
<li>If a player has rights above 2 ( donators ), they can still use ‘::’ to do commands</li>
<li>Made it so the client sends the browse packet when it reads a certain string from the command packet. This meant that I added ::vote server sided and players can do it to browse vote page<br>
[/center]</li>
</ul>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/impulse-637-639/535184/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/impulse-637-639/535184/3</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2013 17:07:02 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-535184-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/impulse-637-639/535184.rss">Impulse [637/639]</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Impulse [637/639]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Docent Limits]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/docent">@Docent</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Good luck, looks very nice. Would you mind showing how you did PvP drops and I sorta need the Statuette Id’s. I’ve been trying to recreate PvP worlds for a while now and have been failing miserably.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/impulse-637-639/535184/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/impulse-637-639/535184/2</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 03 Nov 2013 23:03:28 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-535184-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/impulse-637-639/535184.rss">Impulse [637/639]</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Impulse [637/639]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Magnitoo Magnitoo]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/magnitoo">@Magnitoo</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[center]<br>
[FONT=Tahoma][SIZE=4][B]Impulse[/B][/SIZE][/FONT] is Dementhium 637 loading 639 based server developed and improved upon by Myself and some people who have helped me along the way. I give big thanks and credits to the Dementhium team (Especially 'Mystic Flow), Sixpack, WildSkiller, AeroPK and Orel.</p>
<p>Impulse will be based around RuneScape in 2011 Bounty hunter / City PvP mode. This is a continue on from my previous project however I will be improving upon it.</p>
<p>[B][U]Core Lead Developer[/U][/B]</p>
<p>[ul][li]<img src="http://i.imgur.com/iWzjBqN.png" alt width="" height="">Magnito[/li][/ul]</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-i"><span class="bbcode-u"><span class="bbcode-b">Previous updates</span></span></span></p>
<ul>
<li>Diagonal combat corrected</li>
<li>Flawless Bounty Hunter system / Target assigning added</li>
<li>Functional Earned potential system with artifact drops</li>
<li>Summoning supports wolpertinger, bull ant, pack yack, bunyip, wartortoise and a bunch of other familiars now</li>
<li>Pirate huts have been added with lock picking</li>
<li>Axe huts and mage arena and small bats area have been added with NPC definitions</li>
<li>100% Farming skill has been added ( Eco-based content really )</li>
<li>Bugs / dupes corrected ( Can’t remember what they were specifically )</li>
<li>Equipping items while in view equipment stats is now functional</li>
<li>Punishment &amp; Clan chats saving has been re-written</li>
<li>General server things have been done - Instead of it saying Friends List - RuneScape, it will now say the server name ( Same on logging out button )</li>
<li>General donator requirements, yells, commands have all been added</li>
<li>Nearly every bank in the world is now a safezone rather than a dangerous area</li>
<li>Revenant caves + some more map data has been added. Revenants is now a multi-zone area.</li>
<li>If a familiar stands over a player, the player is shown not the familiar - People like this feature due to hybridding</li>
</ul>
<h2>
<span class="bbcode-u"><span class="bbcode-i"><span class="bbcode-b">Latest updates</span></span></span><br>
[] - Made it so when city pvp ( world pvp ) is toggled, the pvp strings change according to how it was in runescape 2011. If you are level 138, it will show 108 - 138 and you can attack anyone in that range and this also updates according to wilderness level<br>
[] - Fixed a autocasting issue where if you are autocasting and you switch weapon, the weapons selected attack style would be the last one you chose and be auto-matically selected. Fixed it, now when you switch weapons while autocasting, you have to select the attack style yourself and autocast will be disabled<br>
[] - Added some item definitions ( bonuses ) to certain items that were missing<br>
[] - Corrected the ep colour for when your ep is zero</h2>
<h2>[] - Fixed the praying issue for when you are using quickprayers and your prayer points run out, your headicon would still be there<br>
[] - Fixed the issue of your special amount showing up as 0% even though its 100%, this will never be an issue again<br>
[] - Added ring of vigour<br>
[] - Decrease a delay in combat, if you was to eat, it would set a delay for how long you wait to hit back, this was way too high so its been reduced and its perfect<br>
[] - Damage poisoning has been tweaked, it now grabs the amount to poison from the cache from what weapon you are wielding and is correct<br>
[] - Added more ranging bolt specials<br>
[] - Corrected so many attack / defence animations, re-wrote some of the ways animations were handled ( a bunch of cases for itemids could be handled with one if statement )<br>
[] - Added a 5 minute afk timer, after your timer is out, your player will just do an animation which will show your player sitting down on a chair. ( I prefer this than logging out tbh <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=5" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"> )<br>
[] - Corrected the combat magic following, once you are autocasting and the player starts to run, you will now chase him and mage at the same time. Credits to Mylyn.</h2>
<h2>[] - Created a class known as ‘PlayerLogic.java’. This handles the setters and getters for the player. This is done as : player.getPlayerLogic() … Its alot more efficient than packing it all into player.java itself and having it crammed up.<br>
[] - Implemented the AStarPathFinder class. ( A* search algorithm ), 'Mystic Flow once stated that some lagg issues were to do with bad pathfinding. This has been fixed and is no longer an issue and stability is become alot stronger for the core of the source. Stability has ‘fixed’ in a way and source runs alot smoother.<br>
[] - Corrected the issue for when you switch items, the spell you selected doesn’t clear<br>
[] - Fixed the combat delays ( Been trying to do this since I started with dementhium ). Combat is alot smoother, players don’t have to wait to get hit twice before attacking back after switching ( One of the best updates )<br>
[] - Restoration of special attack has been tweaked, it was a little too high</h2>
<h2>[] - Fixed the bug where your icon ( config ) showing if you are in wildy or not in wildy kept flashing. It has stopped flashing<br>
[] - The PvP Level strings are now in functionality, you can attack people according to the range of combat levels shown above your ep percentage<br>
[] - Bounty hunter skulling system done depending on your wealth. These skulls only appear once you are in the bounty hunter crators</h2>
<h2>[] - Fixed the ‘moonwalking’ issue. When a player hit another player/npc with magic, and ran away, they would run backwards and face the opponent, this is now fixed. They will turn around and continue running straight like it should be<br>
[] - Added 100% Bounty hunter crators. Everywhere before you go in the crators is safe and the stairs is too. Once you enter, your bounty hunter skull will be assigned according to wealth<br>
[] - On logout, if you had a bounty hunter skull, next time you login your skull will stay the same. Once you fight someone in bounty hunter crator, your skull won’t go and the normal one will not appear. You keep your skull.<br>
[] - Perfected the PvP SafeZoneTimer. My final updated needed to perfect it was : if you attack someone ( and not get attacked back ) and you run straight out, it trigger for you and count down. If you attack someone then don’t leave wilderness for some time ( and not get attacked back ), you won’t trigger it</h2>
<h2>[] - Fixed the bug where players used to get stuck after trading/fighting. Normally, they would keep facing to wherever the other person goes to even if you are not interacting with them. This no longer happens</h2>
<h2>[] - Re-corrected my fix for the arrow on the minimap, if you have a gravestone and a target, both of them will now show up like in rs<br>
[] - Added spirit kyatt familiar<br>
[] - If a players wealth changed while in bounty hunter, their bounty hunter skull will update to what its supposed to be</h2>
<p>[] - Added the spell book order saving, it will now save to how you last arranged your spells in your spell book<br>
[] - Made it so if players die with barrows items, the broken version of it will now drop to the killer<br>
<span class="bbcode-u"><span class="bbcode-i"><span class="bbcode-b">Media</span></span></span></p>
<p><img src="http://puu.sh/56fQO.jpg" alt width="" height=""><br>
<img src="http://puu.sh/5733t.jpg" alt width="" height=""><br>
<img src="http://puu.sh/59ysD.jpg" alt width="" height=""><br>
<img src="http://puu.sh/5aJho.jpg" alt width="" height=""></p>
<p>My 10 second PvP SafeZone Timer</p>
<p><a href="http://youtu.be/tzDEmC0k-lI" class="onebox" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">http://youtu.be/tzDEmC0k-lI</a><br>
[/center]</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/impulse-637-639/535184/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/impulse-637-639/535184/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 03 Nov 2013 22:01:44 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-535184-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/impulse-637-639/535184.rss">Impulse [637/639]</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
