<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Fail education; rant</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/fail-education-rant/423829</link>
    <description>So i have been attending this college for 16 months excluding the 2 weeks I still have left. My question is should a teacher be able to make an assignment that has nothing to do with your current class worth enough to decide if you graduate or not?

I have attended this college every single day, not missing a single day; I have missed 3 classes, 2 from not being aware of the time and 1 from falling off the road when we had a bad snow day(I got pulled back on the road and made it to my last class but missed the class I was driving to). I have a been tardy a few time but not enough to harshly effect my grades. I currently have a 3.98/4.0 cumulative gpa and a 93+ is an A, 85-92 B, -7 C, etc a 70% is a F.

The current class is project management, the assignment is contacting 10 businesses every week that have possible positions for entry-level programming jobs that don&#39;t require a bachelors degree, or any work experience. Project management he told us we have to use microsoft project 2010 told us about like 3 things about the program and has told us nothing about project management and expects us to know what we are doing.

My problem with the assignment: there is no reason why it should ever determine whether you graduate or not, He has taught me nothing in the 16 months here so therefore i am inadequate compared to other programmers that may also apply or even to the minimum requirements, I would be wasting the companies&#39; time by calling b/c im not interested in their company nor do I want to work in a computer job right out of college when I have never had a normal job, the assignment is also a waste of my time.

He handed out a syllabus for each class which most of the time he never mentioned half the stuff he said we are suppose to cover. His teaching is ok so today this is what you guys are going to do, have any questions you know where ill be *walks out of classroom*, you ask him for help he may know how to help otherwise he tells you to just google the problem.

I came to this school b/c it was small and supposed to be good, I wanted to be help learn programming concepts and stuff that I couldnt grasp on my own, in the first couple weeks that was how it was, but after your trial period ended, so did everything good(by then I couldn&#39;t drop out and receive a full refund); not to use google all day and be held up in a college ran like a high school with a theme that you are in a work place. if I wanted to teach myself and use google all day every day I would have stayed home and saved myself from going $29,000(really only $12,000 for the loans grants and stuff paid the rest but that still doesnt account for living expenses: $500+/month in rent, $200+/month for food, and $100+/month in gas) in debt b/c i had to take out loans.

At this point I really don&#39;t care if I get my degree or not b/c to me it proves nothing but that I wasted about 1.3 years of my life on nothing. what I do care about is not paying for my loans but making the ones responsible for them pay them. If I don&#39;t graduate, mark my word, my college or teacher will be paying for them out of their own money.

so feel free to comment on my rant. I would like to know your opinions on the assignment, and if anyone knows if you can sue a college to not upholding their end of the contract(I signed up for an education in computer programming one I didn&#39;t get, I held up my end and was an excellent student always ready to learn but never was presented with any material to), or a teacher for malpractice(you can sue doctors and other professionals why wouldn&#39;t you be able to sue teachers over it, they shouldn&#39;t be exempt), or for emotional distress(the amount of stress he has caused me is beyond any amount of stress I&#39;ve ever had)?

p.s. I understand why he would like us to do the assignment, but I don&#39;t feel he has the right to make it so important. Also in a few hours we are going on a field trip which he made mandatory and worth 10% of out grade, which is bs b/c of the distance, and what the field trip is about.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 02 Dec 2011 20:02:58 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>General Discussion</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/fail-education-rant/423829.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Fail education; rant</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Loveandpower Loveandpower]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/loveandpower">@Loveandpower</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>You won’t get anywhere legal wise I can go ahead and tell you that now lol…</p>
<p>I understand that your frustrated that you have this class, you didn’t really get much instruction about what to do and wasn’t really taught anything ( been there before <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=5" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"> ) but in reality you join a school/college your pretty much saying you agree to the teachers schedule through and through. I have had rows before with academic deans over the absence of my professors but they just said nothing could be done and that as a student we are supposed to try to learn what we can on and off campus anyway.</p>
<p>Good luck either way though. There are several good online companies that are looking for entry level programmers though in America. So do some googling on IT job seeking companies.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/fail-education-rant/423829/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/fail-education-rant/423829/4</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 02 Dec 2011 20:02:58 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-423829-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/fail-education-rant/423829.rss">Fail education; rant</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Fail education; rant</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@The_Outsider The Outsider]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/the_outsider">@The_Outsider</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I’ll tell you one thing mate, you can write for England (or America) ;).</p>
<p>I am currently over a month behind my Programming course due to the funding not being processed until the day of my start date… they said it’s because they need to check if I’m actually on the course, but why couldn’t they check my registration?</p>
<p>Then my equipment took another week after the 4 weeks I waited for the funding to come through, so I feel like I’ve be left at a disadvantage. I’m now being hounded to complete the first 4 weeks of the course in a week (not happening), otherwise I risk being taken off of the course.</p>
<p>Hardly fair at all. Sounds to me as both our story’s lack the communication needed on their side.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/fail-education-rant/423829/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/fail-education-rant/423829/3</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 02 Dec 2011 15:13:22 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-423829-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/fail-education-rant/423829.rss">Fail education; rant</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Fail education; rant</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Andrew_Ferguson The317Guy]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/andrew_ferguson">@Andrew_Ferguson</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>They can but most don’t. Most that do, do it to see if you are ready for the random tasks that life will through at you.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/fail-education-rant/423829/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/fail-education-rant/423829/2</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 02 Dec 2011 15:00:36 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-423829-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/fail-education-rant/423829.rss">Fail education; rant</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Fail education; rant</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@xryz xryz]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/xryz">@xryz</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>So i have been attending this college for 16 months excluding the 2 weeks I still have left. My question is should a teacher be able to make an assignment that has nothing to do with your current class worth enough to decide if you graduate or not?</p>
<p>I have attended this college every single day, not missing a single day; I have missed 3 classes, 2 from not being aware of the time and 1 from falling off the road when we had a bad snow day(I got pulled back on the road and made it to my last class but missed the class I was driving to). I have a been tardy a few time but not enough to harshly effect my grades. I currently have a 3.98/4.0 cumulative gpa and a 93+ is an A, 85-92 B, -7 C, etc a 70% is a F.</p>
<p>The current class is project management, the assignment is contacting 10 businesses every week that have possible positions for entry-level programming jobs that don’t require a bachelors degree, or any work experience. Project management he told us we have to use microsoft project 2010 told us about like 3 things about the program and has told us nothing about project management and expects us to know what we are doing.</p>
<p>My problem with the assignment: there is no reason why it should ever determine whether you graduate or not, He has taught me nothing in the 16 months here so therefore i am inadequate compared to other programmers that may also apply or even to the minimum requirements, I would be wasting the companies’ time by calling b/c im not interested in their company nor do I want to work in a computer job right out of college when I have never had a normal job, the assignment is also a waste of my time.</p>
<p>He handed out a syllabus for each class which most of the time he never mentioned half the stuff he said we are suppose to cover. His teaching is ok so today this is what you guys are going to do, have any questions you know where ill be <em>walks out of classroom</em>, you ask him for help he may know how to help otherwise he tells you to just google the problem.</p>
<p>I came to this school b/c it was small and supposed to be good, I wanted to be help learn programming concepts and stuff that I couldnt grasp on my own, in the first couple weeks that was how it was, but after your trial period ended, so did everything good(by then I couldn’t drop out and receive a full refund); not to use google all day and be held up in a college ran like a high school with a theme that you are in a work place. if I wanted to teach myself and use google all day every day I would have stayed home and saved myself from going $29,000(really only $12,000 for the loans grants and stuff paid the rest but that still doesnt account for living expenses: $500+/month in rent, $200+/month for food, and $100+/month in gas) in debt b/c i had to take out loans.</p>
<p>At this point I really don’t care if I get my degree or not b/c to me it proves nothing but that I wasted about 1.3 years of my life on nothing. what I do care about is not paying for my loans but making the ones responsible for them pay them. If I don’t graduate, mark my word, my college or teacher will be paying for them out of their own money.</p>
<p>so feel free to comment on my rant. I would like to know your opinions on the assignment, and if anyone knows if you can sue a college to not upholding their end of the contract(I signed up for an education in computer programming one I didn’t get, I held up my end and was an excellent student always ready to learn but never was presented with any material to), or a teacher for malpractice(you can sue doctors and other professionals why wouldn’t you be able to sue teachers over it, they shouldn’t be exempt), or for emotional distress(the amount of stress he has caused me is beyond any amount of stress I’ve ever had)?</p>
<p>p.s. I understand why he would like us to do the assignment, but I don’t feel he has the right to make it so important. Also in a few hours we are going on a field trip which he made mandatory and worth 10% of out grade, which is bs b/c of the distance, and what the field trip is about.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/fail-education-rant/423829/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/fail-education-rant/423829/1</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 02 Dec 2011 14:55:45 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-423829-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/fail-education-rant/423829.rss">Fail education; rant</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
