<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Is raising minimum wage actually effective?</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/is-raising-minimum-wage-actually-effective/552801</link>
    <description>Hey everybody so I am from the U.S, and on the news it is always showing how this or that state increased their minimum wage significantly! Is it that simple? Will that fix our economy?? Here is my problem/case about this.

We will use [b]gas[/b] as an example.

Lets say Gas is 2.00$ a gallon. 

Now businesses have to watch and record how much gas is being bought by each customer. If gas prices are to [b]high[/b] then that would make it so less people bought gas because who wants to buy over-priced gas? Which would make the industries have to much product because no one is buying their gas.

And if gas prices are [b]super cheap [/b]then everybody would buy large quantities of gas which would make companies supply of gas go down! Because everyone is buying/taking their gas.


[b]Now lets say gas had to stay permanently at 2.00$ and the price can never rise or fall for this example.[/b]

Now lets say all of the states raised their minimum wage to 15$! WOOHOO MORE MONEY FOR US! 

How will that effect the gas companies? If everyone has way more money? well then 2.00$ a gallon for gas is super easy to buy because we have more money so people can buy more and more and more gas! Well then the companies would eventually run out of gas because people can take so much of it constantly because gas is super cheap to us because we all got raises.

So now that we know if prices stayed low and we got higher wages then companies would run out of product. So companies are always forced to raise or lower their prices of gas to match how much we get paid. So if all states really do become 15$ an hour then companies have to match that and raise their prices for their product. and would Make gas like 7.00$ a gallon. But the problem with that is you are still getting the same amount of gas for your buck.

So how is it that any different having a 15$ minimum wage if companies have to raise their prices along with you. It will still counter balance like how it did before you got a higher minimum wage right?


Lets say everyone in the world lost all of their money and had to start from scratch. But companies kept their prices the same. So gas is still 4.00$ a gallon. What will happen to the price for gas? It will drop significantly because no one has money to buy their gas.

My point is it does not matter if we all get paid more or less right? It really is mostly on the companies side and their prices. Not how much we get paid. I feel like increasing minimum wage is pointless. Prices will just go up as well so we are still getting the same amount for our buck as we did for when we made 7.50$ an hour. 

And that is what the goal is right? We want more stuff for our buck. That&#39;s why people like all you can eat restaurants. You get more food for your dollar rather then going to a high priced place and get little-to-no food.

So how do people get more stuff for their buck? would all companies just have to hold hands together and keep their costs for their product always super low?

I would love to hear what you guys think. Economy just makes me go cross-eyed but that is how I see it all. What do you guys think? If any part was confusing let me know and I will try to clear it up. Economics can be pretty confusing so I will do the best I can to answer any questions.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 06 Aug 2015 19:11:09 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>General Discussion</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/is-raising-minimum-wage-actually-effective/552801.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Is raising minimum wage actually effective?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Rodgerwilco Rodgerwilco]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/rodgerwilco">@Rodgerwilco</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>One of my grandparents use to sit there and when something happened with the stock market, or markets in general she would say “I told you so” The family joke was always, “well grandma, why didn’t you put any money into it”. Which goes back to my initial statement, not investing and talking about it and investing and talking about it are completely different. I swear, it takes an emotional toll on your body, I probably have been close to a heart attack on both my gains and losses. It also leads people to killing their SO/Family. It’s crazy how money can do that to people.</p>
<p>Don’t risk what you’re not willing to lose. If you’re in debt, pay that off first then take some risk.s</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/is-raising-minimum-wage-actually-effective/552801/34">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/is-raising-minimum-wage-actually-effective/552801/34</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 06 Aug 2015 19:11:09 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-552801-34</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/is-raising-minimum-wage-actually-effective/552801.rss">Is raising minimum wage actually effective?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Is raising minimum wage actually effective?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@xx_matty_xx Justin Bieber]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/xx_matty_xx">@xx_matty_xx</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“Rodgerwilco, post:32, topic:552801”][quote author=Justin Bieber link=topic=671715.msg4492245#msg4492245 date=1438882542]<br>
trying to make some shrapnel myself… can u recommend any good books on trading?<br>
[/quote]</p>
<p>Jim Cramer has some great insight, he use to trade 20 hours a day and owned a hedge fund. He covers a few of the “golden rules” in a few of his books. <a href="https://www.google.com/?gws_rd=ssl#q=jim+cramer+books" rel="nofollow noopener">https://www.google.com/?gws_rd=ssl#q=jim+cramer+books</a> In his book “Stay mad for life” he listed 10 stocks that would make you rich, all 10 of those stocks today prove his point.</p>
<p>Warren Buffet hustled and dimed as a kid selling soda, he will go on for days about coke products. <a href="https://www.google.com/?gws_rd=ssl#q=warren+buffett+books" rel="nofollow noopener">https://www.google.com/?gws_rd=ssl#q=warren+buffett+books</a></p>
<p>Pick up a few good reads on Goldman Sachs <a href="https://www.google.com/?gws_rd=ssl#q=goldman+sachs+books" rel="nofollow noopener">https://www.google.com/?gws_rd=ssl#q=goldman+sachs+books</a><br>
They keep the money flowing and pretty much own the market. Forget that, they own the market rofl.</p>
<p>Good to Great by Jim Collins is a great read that just gives an insight into the top 500 companies and why they are in the position they are in.</p>
<p>If you’re looking into the stock market and don’t know two cents about it, youtube and the internet will help. All the knowledge is publicly available.[/quote]o cool thanks - will definitely take a look at some of those. I know a bit but I’m starting to feel like a lot of people on the internet are full of shit, and I’ve picked up so many legit published books that just outright deny there’s money to be made trading stocks/fx.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/is-raising-minimum-wage-actually-effective/552801/33">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/is-raising-minimum-wage-actually-effective/552801/33</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 06 Aug 2015 18:55:24 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-552801-33</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/is-raising-minimum-wage-actually-effective/552801.rss">Is raising minimum wage actually effective?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Is raising minimum wage actually effective?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Rodgerwilco Rodgerwilco]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/rodgerwilco">@Rodgerwilco</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote" data-post="30" data-topic="552801">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 Justin Bieber:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>trying to make some shrapnel myself… can u recommend any good books on trading?</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Jim Cramer has some great insight, he use to trade 20 hours a day and owned a hedge fund. He covers a few of the “golden rules” in a few of his books. <a href="https://www.google.com/?gws_rd=ssl#q=jim+cramer+books" rel="nofollow noopener">https://www.google.com/?gws_rd=ssl#q=jim+cramer+books</a> In his book “Stay mad for life” he listed 10 stocks that would make you rich, all 10 of those stocks today prove his point.</p>
<p>Warren Buffet hustled and dimed as a kid selling soda, he will go on for days about coke products. <a href="https://www.google.com/?gws_rd=ssl#q=warren+buffett+books" rel="nofollow noopener">https://www.google.com/?gws_rd=ssl#q=warren+buffett+books</a></p>
<p>Pick up a few good reads on Goldman Sachs <a href="https://www.google.com/?gws_rd=ssl#q=goldman+sachs+books" rel="nofollow noopener">https://www.google.com/?gws_rd=ssl#q=goldman+sachs+books</a><br>
They keep the money flowing and pretty much own the market. Forget that, they own the market rofl.</p>
<p>Good to Great by Jim Collins is a great read that just gives an insight into the top 500 companies and why they are in the position they are in.</p>
<p>If you’re looking into the stock market and don’t know two cents about it, youtube and the internet will help. All the knowledge is publicly available.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/is-raising-minimum-wage-actually-effective/552801/32">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/is-raising-minimum-wage-actually-effective/552801/32</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 06 Aug 2015 18:16:48 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-552801-32</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/is-raising-minimum-wage-actually-effective/552801.rss">Is raising minimum wage actually effective?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Is raising minimum wage actually effective?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@bowserjr2 Bowser jr]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/bowserjr2">@bowserjr2</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“tyb97, post:25, topic:552801”][quote author=my-swagger link=topic=671715.msg4492146#msg4492146 date=1438798919]<br>
Study Economics if you’re that interested.<br>
[/quote]<br>
Sad part is you don’t even have to study economics to see the flaws in endlessly raising minimum wage.[/quote]<br>
We do it and it is not causing any problem. Sure we have some of the highest prices in the world, but with some protectionism it isn’t too much of a problem.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/is-raising-minimum-wage-actually-effective/552801/31">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/is-raising-minimum-wage-actually-effective/552801/31</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 06 Aug 2015 17:56:49 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-552801-31</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/is-raising-minimum-wage-actually-effective/552801.rss">Is raising minimum wage actually effective?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Is raising minimum wage actually effective?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@xx_matty_xx Justin Bieber]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/xx_matty_xx">@xx_matty_xx</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote" data-post="27" data-topic="552801">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/rodgerwilco/40/5_e05bb34c421432ee4d40de30c10af3e5.png" class="avatar"> Rodgerwilco:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Crazy financial person here, pretty much have read every book by the top dogs who run todays market. When I was 20, I dumped $32,000 into the stock market and lost about $1200 within the first 4 hours. Since then (23 now) I have made quite a few bucks. No I am not rich, but honestly I am enjoying my position. Looking to pay off my 3rd house in 2 years. This is just a glimpse of my experience with money, there is a difference between someone who has no money and talks about it compared to people who have lived it.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>trying to make some shrapnel myself… can u recommend any good books on trading?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/is-raising-minimum-wage-actually-effective/552801/30">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/is-raising-minimum-wage-actually-effective/552801/30</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 06 Aug 2015 17:35:42 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-552801-30</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/is-raising-minimum-wage-actually-effective/552801.rss">Is raising minimum wage actually effective?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Is raising minimum wage actually effective?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Rodgerwilco Rodgerwilco]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/rodgerwilco">@Rodgerwilco</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Fk, accidentally hit back and lost the post. Since retyping, ill keep it shorter.</p>
<p>GOOG is a public company with a 442.31B Market Cap (at the current moment) There last 5 quarterly dividends are around $5 per share after dilution. So for $67,329 you can make $500 every quarter, what a great dividend yield. This is where it gets tricky. Financial institutes have their hands all over the stock market, commodities, everything because its one of those golden rules. Don’t put all your eggs in one basket. If one sector fails, you can still make it up by gains in other sectors.</p>
<p>As of 2014, the amount of adults in America is : 245,273,438 / your $1 trillion in physical currency is $4,077 per person. GOOG can’t take out a billion because it has to be constantly circulated or as they call it “in the banks”. Even with the average idiot kids taking student loans for college, its just constant projection for the future. Lock them into the system baby.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/is-raising-minimum-wage-actually-effective/552801/29">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/is-raising-minimum-wage-actually-effective/552801/29</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 06 Aug 2015 06:50:39 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-552801-29</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/is-raising-minimum-wage-actually-effective/552801.rss">Is raising minimum wage actually effective?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Is raising minimum wage actually effective?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@davidi2 Davidi2]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/davidi2">@davidi2</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I doubt google couldn’t come up with a billion in cash. Current US M1 values are at around 3 trillion, and physical currency is at about 1 trillion. They’d probably have to buy it from foreign governments to be fair though.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/is-raising-minimum-wage-actually-effective/552801/28">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/is-raising-minimum-wage-actually-effective/552801/28</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 06 Aug 2015 05:47:15 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-552801-28</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/is-raising-minimum-wage-actually-effective/552801.rss">Is raising minimum wage actually effective?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Is raising minimum wage actually effective?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Rodgerwilco Rodgerwilco]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/rodgerwilco">@Rodgerwilco</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Crazy financial person here, pretty much have read every book by the top dogs who run todays market. When I was 20, I dumped $32,000 into the stock market and lost about $1200 within the first 4 hours. Since then (23 now) I have made quite a few bucks. No I am not rich, but honestly I am enjoying my position. Looking to pay off my 3rd house in 2 years. This is just a glimpse of my experience with money, there is a difference between someone who has no money and talks about it compared to people who have lived it.</p>
<p>Firstly, minimum wage is a great concept. It allows for an equal minimum playing field for people who seek a job. My personal belief is that everyone should be supported by the government for the basic necessities. EX: Housing, Food, extremely basic Health Care. There needs to be some form of system that allows for everyone to live on the basics with the ability to make aggressive moves to get “ahead”.</p>
<p>Credit allows for just that, you’re able to take a loan and buy shit you could never afford at your current state and you make a financial commitment (over time) to pay it off with an interest rate. Credit is how the game is played. The cash always needs to be flowing, if it stops you have 2008 or the great depression.</p>
<p>You can’t walk into google (which is about to hit half a trillion dollars) and ask them to show you all that money or even 100 billion in cash. Ask them to show you a billion dollars in cash and they still wont be able to. The number that’s floating around in the global economy cannot be matched because physical currency doesn’t even come close to it. This is where inflation comes into play. Of course there are always a way to reduce the credit number (wars, assassinations, bankrupting companies) but it’s too high.</p>
<p>People freak out about that number being so high that they “think” the fix is to give more money to the workers to keep the money circulating. Just because the number has “doubled” since Obama has been in office doesn’t mean that minimum wage needs to double. I’m sure you have heard it, go ahead google it “Obama doubled american debt” I am sure its there.</p>
<p>I’ll bring up my initial paragraph about the books I have read and there is a golden rule to all of this, small percentage of inflation over time is ideal. It allows for people who fail to make moves with their finances to get “ruled out” by time. (1,000 dollars in 1900 is 1,000 dollars today, not much now!) and it forces people to use the credit and follow the system. This is why they tell you to buy high dividend stocks that are making money which will give you that percentage over time. If you’re in the game, following the “golden rules”, understand and agree with the system, you’re safe compared to people who are not playing at all.</p>
<p>Also unless you don’t know what you’re doing. Stay away from Bonds, they don’t beat interest rates and are simply a parking place for your money. Ask Buffet.</p>
<p>TLDR : Minimum wage activists think they deserve more because the debt limit has doubled.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/is-raising-minimum-wage-actually-effective/552801/27">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/is-raising-minimum-wage-actually-effective/552801/27</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 06 Aug 2015 05:12:09 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-552801-27</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/is-raising-minimum-wage-actually-effective/552801.rss">Is raising minimum wage actually effective?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Is raising minimum wage actually effective?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@davidi2 Davidi2]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/davidi2">@davidi2</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“tyb97, post:25, topic:552801”][quote author=my-swagger link=topic=671715.msg4492146#msg4492146 date=1438798919]<br>
Study Economics if you’re that interested.<br>
[/quote]<br>
Sad part is you don’t even have to study economics to see the flaws in endlessly raising minimum wage.[/quote]and then you realize the minimum wage has been endlessly raising anyway because of inflation. and you can’t “stop” doing that.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/is-raising-minimum-wage-actually-effective/552801/26">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/is-raising-minimum-wage-actually-effective/552801/26</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 06 Aug 2015 03:33:53 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-552801-26</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/is-raising-minimum-wage-actually-effective/552801.rss">Is raising minimum wage actually effective?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Is raising minimum wage actually effective?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@tyb97 tyb97]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/tyb97">@tyb97</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote" data-post="23" data-topic="552801">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/my-swagger/40/5_e05bb34c421432ee4d40de30c10af3e5.png" class="avatar"> my-swagger:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Study Economics if you’re that interested.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Sad part is you don’t even have to study economics to see the flaws in endlessly raising minimum wage.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/is-raising-minimum-wage-actually-effective/552801/25">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/is-raising-minimum-wage-actually-effective/552801/25</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 06 Aug 2015 02:15:44 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-552801-25</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/is-raising-minimum-wage-actually-effective/552801.rss">Is raising minimum wage actually effective?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Is raising minimum wage actually effective?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@EcoPS_GM EcoPS GM]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/ecops_gm">@EcoPS_GM</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>As virtually stated by others; it would cause influxation.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/is-raising-minimum-wage-actually-effective/552801/24">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/is-raising-minimum-wage-actually-effective/552801/24</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 05 Aug 2015 19:01:27 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-552801-24</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/is-raising-minimum-wage-actually-effective/552801.rss">Is raising minimum wage actually effective?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Is raising minimum wage actually effective?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@my-swagger my-swagger]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/my-swagger">@my-swagger</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Study Economics if you’re that interested.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/is-raising-minimum-wage-actually-effective/552801/23">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/is-raising-minimum-wage-actually-effective/552801/23</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 05 Aug 2015 18:21:59 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-552801-23</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/is-raising-minimum-wage-actually-effective/552801.rss">Is raising minimum wage actually effective?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Is raising minimum wage actually effective?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@PaulT PaulT]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/pault">@PaulT</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>The argument is usually “The minimum wage workers will go spend the money right away and put it back into the economy, so the business won’t have to fire people or raise prices”. Yet this is not the case. Most people below the poverty line in the US actually don’t work, because government benefits are more substantial relative to the effort required. A majority of minimum wage jobs are in food service jobs. Raising the minimum wage is just going to mean you get served by a robot at McDonalds, and food is more expensive at nice restaurants. Also, many restaurants pay workers under the table, and many employees send their earnings back to their homecountries, so there’s no reason to believe a minimum wage will be effective at increasing available capital in the marketplace.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/is-raising-minimum-wage-actually-effective/552801/22">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/is-raising-minimum-wage-actually-effective/552801/22</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 05 Aug 2015 18:12:47 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-552801-22</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/is-raising-minimum-wage-actually-effective/552801.rss">Is raising minimum wage actually effective?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Is raising minimum wage actually effective?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Frell Frell]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/frell">@Frell</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Pretty sure one of two things happen:</p>
<p>The company fires workers</p>
<p>The company increases the price of their product, so a nationwide minimum wage increase would cause everything to be proportionally as expensive. Probably why it appears to work in isolated states, the profit streams from everywhere else help them take the hit.</p>
<p>It never achieves the goal of CEO’s cutting their salaries to save jobs unless it’s a small business that knows their employees on a personal level.</p>
<aside class="quote" data-post="1" data-topic="552801">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/retaliate/40/5_e05bb34c421432ee4d40de30c10af3e5.png" class="avatar"> Retaliate:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>How will that effect the gas companies? If everyone has way more money?</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>They’re also dishing out more money to their hundreds of thousands store clerks, though.</p>
<p>I do remember reading stuff saying it would work for x and y reason, but I can’t remember them</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/is-raising-minimum-wage-actually-effective/552801/21">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/is-raising-minimum-wage-actually-effective/552801/21</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 05 Aug 2015 16:09:33 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-552801-21</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/is-raising-minimum-wage-actually-effective/552801.rss">Is raising minimum wage actually effective?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Is raising minimum wage actually effective?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@PaulT PaulT]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/pault">@PaulT</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>A big mac, fries, and a soda at McDonalds in Norway costs $23.</p>
<p>It costs me about $8, in the US.</p>
<p>Now the worker at that McDonald’s makes $23/hr in Norway, and $8/hr in the US. This is not so much hypothetical, but these figures are actually pretty accurate for most of the US and Norway. Now, let me ask you something, who has more <span class="bbcode-b">real purchasing power</span>, the McDonalds worker in the US or Norway? The US worker does. Now that doesn’t necessarily equate to quality of life. The Norwegian worker may have more vacation time, more benefits, and greater opportunities for education, due to the social programs that have been enacted in that country.</p>
<p>Now, we have the US minimum wage.</p>
<blockquote>While the federal minimum wage was only $3.35 per hour in 1981 and is currently $7.25 per hour in real dollars, when adjusted for inflation, the current federal minimum wage would need to be more than $8 per hour to equal its buying power of the early 1980s and more nearly $11 per hour to equal its buying power of the late 1960s.</blockquote>
<p>The minimum wage has actually been <span class="bbcode-b">decreasing</span>, in real dollars. Adjusted for inflation, the federal minimum wage peaked in 1968. Increasing the real minimum wage, or indeed, even allowing it to keep pace with inflation,  has the well documented effect of increasing the spending power of the consumers on the lowest end of the spectrum, and will cause an influx of cash into the economy. But the question is really whether government interventionism for the purpose of redistribution of wealth is necessary, helpful, or even possible. Demonstrably, it is not possible. The very nature of currency and value guarantees that to subvert the Voluntary arrangements of the free market, is to debase the currency and destabilize the market.</p>
<p>Freedom of enterprise, and having true property rights without being coerced by force to use that property to benefit another, is economic freedom. When you enforce a minimum wage, quite simply you take it away. I believe that this is wrong.</p>
<blockquote>If economic inequality is an ailment, punishing effort and success is no cure in any event. Coercive, envy-based measures that aim to redistribute wealth prompt the smart or politically well-connected “haves” to seek refuge in havens here or abroad, while the hapless “have-nots” bear the full brunt of economic decline. A more productive expenditure of time would be to work to erase the mass of intrusive government that ensures that the “have-nots” are also the “cannots.”</blockquote>
<blockquote>After having thus successively taken each member of the community in its powerful grasp and fashioned him at will, the government then extends its arm over the whole community. It covers the surface of society with a network of small, complicated rules, minute and uniform, through which the most original minds and the most energetic characters cannot penetrate to rise above the crowd. The will of man is not shattered, but softened, bent, and guided; men are seldom forced by it to act, but they are constantly restrained from acting. Such a power does not destroy, but it prevents existence: it does not tyrannize, but it compresses, enervates, extinguishes, and stupefies a people, till each nation is reduced to nothing better than a flock of timid and industrious animals, of which the government is the shepherd.</blockquote>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/is-raising-minimum-wage-actually-effective/552801/20">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/is-raising-minimum-wage-actually-effective/552801/20</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 05 Aug 2015 11:58:07 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-552801-20</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/is-raising-minimum-wage-actually-effective/552801.rss">Is raising minimum wage actually effective?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Is raising minimum wage actually effective?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@xx_matty_xx Justin Bieber]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/xx_matty_xx">@xx_matty_xx</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“Bowser jr, post:18, topic:552801”]And here is a overview of unemployment rate in Norway: <a href="http://en.tradingeconomics.com/norway/unemployment-rate" rel="nofollow noopener">http://en.tradingeconomics.com/norway/unemployment-rate</a><br>
The wages has been increased, but the unemployment rate is stable around 3.5%. Increasing the wages does not lead to increased unemployment.[/quote]<br>
and I could point you to stats in different countries that “prove” the opposite effect. correlation does not imply causation etc</p>
<aside class="quote" data-post="18" data-topic="552801">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 Bowser jr:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Your ideas fails since it doesn’t take into account that higher wages make people able to spend more on non-essential goods. Thus giving small businesses more customers. Unless the small business you’re talking about is only exporting goods to foreign country, they would benefit from an increased minimum wage as more people can buy those pizzas. And maybe those pizzas are too cheap, an increase in price would be lower than the increase in wages.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<aside class="quote" data-post="2" data-topic="552801">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 Bowser jr:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>…not everyone gets more money with an increase in minimum wage. Those with good wages would not get a wage increase…</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>you can’t have it both ways. either wages are increasing across the board and OPs theory is correct, or only a subset of employees get the rise. if the latter is true then minimum wage employees keep the same buying power for minimum wage products, keeping these companies in business - great. but everyone else is still on the same wage, so get a reduction in buying power. so your theory only really works if most of the employees in the economy are on minimum wage.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/is-raising-minimum-wage-actually-effective/552801/19">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/is-raising-minimum-wage-actually-effective/552801/19</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 05 Aug 2015 11:46:19 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-552801-19</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/is-raising-minimum-wage-actually-effective/552801.rss">Is raising minimum wage actually effective?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Is raising minimum wage actually effective?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@bowserjr2 Bowser jr]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/bowserjr2">@bowserjr2</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>And here is a overview of unemployment rate in Norway: <a href="http://en.tradingeconomics.com/norway/unemployment-rate" rel="nofollow noopener">http://en.tradingeconomics.com/norway/unemployment-rate</a><br>
The wages has been increased, but the unemployment rate is stable around 3.5%. Increasing the wages does not lead to increased unemployment.</p>
<p>Your ideas fails since it doesn’t take into account that higher wages make people able to spend more on non-essential goods. Thus giving small businesses more customers. Unless the small business you’re talking about is only exporting goods to foreign country, they would benefit from an increased minimum wage as more people can buy those pizzas. And maybe those pizzas are too cheap, an increase in price would be lower than the increase in wages.</p>
<p>The only issue with a minimum wage is that it is set by congress, which lead to the current situation where it hasn’t increased with inflation.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/is-raising-minimum-wage-actually-effective/552801/18">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/is-raising-minimum-wage-actually-effective/552801/18</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 05 Aug 2015 10:53:48 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-552801-18</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/is-raising-minimum-wage-actually-effective/552801.rss">Is raising minimum wage actually effective?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Is raising minimum wage actually effective?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@PaulT PaulT]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/pault">@PaulT</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I’m not sure raising the minimum wage necessarily increases the price of commodities, though we can discuss that issue as well. My thesis is simply that less people will be hired when the minimum wage is raised, since businesses cannot afford to hire people at a wage which they are not worth.</p>
<p>I did use google translate to check that article out, but I am still having trouble deciphering it. Let’s assume that your analysis is right, then, and the real wage is increasing along with the actual wage. This doesn’t disprove the thesis that  less people will be hired, since businesses cannot afford to hire people at a wage which they are not worth. Now, Norway has no minimum wage. They have tariffs, which defines workers rights and payment. They are negotiated every two years between unions and corporations.</p>
<p>Now here’s two very good arguments <span class="bbcode-b">for</span> the minimum wage (Source: <a href="http://squashed.tumblr.com/post/51658308085/labor-economics" rel="nofollow noopener">http://squashed.tumblr.com/post/51658308085/labor-economics</a> )</p>
<blockquote>The next oasis we reach has the opposite problem. Specifically, this oasis contains a number of olive growers. Due to the peculiar weather, there has been a bumper crop of olives. Olives are falling off the trees, rotting on the ground. Due to the extreme supply, there has been a race to the bottom on pricing. The market price for olives is now below the cost of production—at least for this year.
Olive trees require water and care—which means that the market price is about to result in a lot of dead olive trees. That’s not a problem this year—but it takes at least three years to get an olive tree producing. Absent some intervention, so this one year anomaly is going to screw up the market for the forseeable future. In certain situations where there is an extreme surplus, a market intervention is prudent to preserve capacity.</blockquote>
<blockquote>A business with a company car pays for car insurance, repairs, routine maintenance, and whatever other licensing or taxes that go into the cost of owning and operating a car. There may be ways to do this more efficiently or effectively, but at some point there is a minimum amount you need to pay to operate a business with a car.
Why should an employee be treated worse than the company car? Employees need to eat, be sheltered, have medical care, plan for retirement, and generally have lives. If you pay your employees less than some minimal cost of living, you’re asking somebody else to subsidize your business.7 That is not a free and fair market. That is business socializing costs for private profit.</blockquote>
<p>So we can see, in these examples, it seems like you need to have a minimum wage in order to avoid corporations taking advantage of the common man. It’s <span class="bbcode-b">far</span> better to have some wages than no wages, so at the very bottom of the spectrum, the employer has all the power. And this situation actually really happened in the United States, in the early 20th century. The “Robber Barons” and the owners of the new industrial mills and workshops built whole Company Towns for the employees, they fed them, sheltered them, gave them coca-cola and whiskey, and paid them jack shit. It was a terrible situation. However, and this is a big however, it was <span class="bbcode-b">government over-regulation</span> that led to that situation to begin with. The robber barons were not market opportunists, they were political opportunists. They were buying senators, because it was a better investment than buying land. The same thing is happening now <span class="bbcode-b">Comcast buys senators</span> because it’s <span class="bbcode-b">cheaper than laying fiber.</span> They literally make more profit by enforcing their monopoly through corrupt politicians than by improving their service. What an evil corporation, right? Well, if you look at the other side, they are only doing what’s profitable for their shareholders, or their investors, or themselves. If it was more economically viable to lay fiber, they would lay fiber, and you would have 1GB internet, but it’s not.</p>
<p>So the minimum wage may be necessary, but that doesn’t make it right.</p>
<blockquote>Consider a community based pizza parlor selling 100 pies a day for 360 days at $10 each.  Total revenue is $360,000.  It employs 10 minimum wage workers earning $7 per hour, working 2000 hours a year, making labor costs $140,000.  Assume rent, utilities, equipment, depreciation, insurance, supplies, licenses, and food costs come to $170,000 per year, leaving a profit of $50,000 for the owner and his/her family.  Raising the minimum wage $1 would raise labor costs by $20,000 (paying more for the same amount of labor) and reduce profit to $30,000.  The owner must either move into a smaller house or raise prices, which reduces the demand for pizza, resulting in the loss of a worker.  So, the full increase in the wage cost of an increase in the minimum wage comes out of the pockets of customers or the owner’s family, and the one person who loses a job.  There was no net gain in income to increase spending in the community served as every dollar the minimum wage workers received came out of someone else’s pocket in the community.</blockquote>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/is-raising-minimum-wage-actually-effective/552801/17">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/is-raising-minimum-wage-actually-effective/552801/17</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 05 Aug 2015 02:35:59 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-552801-17</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/is-raising-minimum-wage-actually-effective/552801.rss">Is raising minimum wage actually effective?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Is raising minimum wage actually effective?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@bowserjr2 Bowser jr]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/bowserjr2">@bowserjr2</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p><aside class="onebox pdf">
  <header class="source">
      <a href="https://www.ssb.no/a/publikasjoner/pdf/oa_201101/07lonn-pris.pdf" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">ssb.no</a>
  </header>
  <article class="onebox-body">
    <a href="https://www.ssb.no/a/publikasjoner/pdf/oa_201101/07lonn-pris.pdf" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener"><span class="pdf-onebox-logo"></span></a>
<h3><a href="https://www.ssb.no/a/publikasjoner/pdf/oa_201101/07lonn-pris.pdf" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">07lonn-pris.pdf</a></h3>

<p class="filesize">224.07 KB</p>

  </article>
  <div class="onebox-metadata">
    
    
  </div>
  <div style="clear: both"></div>
</aside>
<br>
It is in Norwegian, but look at figure 7.1 showing the yearly increase in real wage each year in Norway. If you’re right, there should no yearly increase in real wage as any rise should also increase the price of commodities.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/is-raising-minimum-wage-actually-effective/552801/16">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/is-raising-minimum-wage-actually-effective/552801/16</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 05 Aug 2015 01:28:40 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-552801-16</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/is-raising-minimum-wage-actually-effective/552801.rss">Is raising minimum wage actually effective?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Is raising minimum wage actually effective?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@PaulT PaulT]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/pault">@PaulT</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I don’t know about bait. I mean, I like Freidman but I haven’t really taken any real in-depth economics courses, so I’m not sure if he’s been discredited by the establishment or what-not. From what I’ve read, it seems pretty clear that government regulation has specific, documented effects on different industries and sectors. And, in this case, it’s a well researched and documented that increasing the minimum wage is going to cause the economy to shed jobs, and is going to cause general instability and loss of productivity.</p>
<blockquote>As a jobs program, raising the minimum wage is a real loser.  Congress raised the minimum wage 10.6% in July, 2009 (know of anyone else getting a raise then?).  In the ensuring 6 months, nearly 600,000 teen jobs disappeared, even with nearly 4% growth in the economy, this compared to a loss of 250,000 jobs in the first half of the year as GDP growth declined by 4%  Why?  When you raise the price of anything, people take less of it, including labor.  The unemployment rate for teens remains unacceptably high.   Workers of all ages that are relatively unskilled are adversely impacted by this policy.</blockquote>
<p>When you raise prices on a commodity (labor) then consumers (employers, in this case) have less purchasing power. I would challenge you to explain how this is not the case.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/is-raising-minimum-wage-actually-effective/552801/15">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/is-raising-minimum-wage-actually-effective/552801/15</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 05 Aug 2015 01:19:16 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-552801-15</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/is-raising-minimum-wage-actually-effective/552801.rss">Is raising minimum wage actually effective?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Is raising minimum wage actually effective?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@bowserjr2 Bowser jr]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/bowserjr2">@bowserjr2</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Friedman…, nice bait mate.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/is-raising-minimum-wage-actually-effective/552801/14">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/is-raising-minimum-wage-actually-effective/552801/14</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 05 Aug 2015 01:15:58 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-552801-14</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/is-raising-minimum-wage-actually-effective/552801.rss">Is raising minimum wage actually effective?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Is raising minimum wage actually effective?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@PaulT PaulT]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/pault">@PaulT</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>The effect of government wage controls, specifically on the minimum wage allowed, is actually basic economics. There isn’t a real question as far as I know. It’s been very well described by many economists, many times.</p>
<blockquote>The minimum wage law is most properly described as a law saying that employers must discriminate against people who have low skills. That’s what the law says. The law says that here’s a man who has a skill that would justify a wage of $5 or $6 per hour (adjusted for today), but you may not employ him, it’s illegal, because if you employ him you must pay him $9 per hour. So what’s the result?  To employ him at $9 per hour is to engage in charity. There’s nothing wrong with charity. But most employers are not in the position to engage in that kind of charity. Thus, the consequences of minimum wage laws have been almost wholly bad. We have increased unemployment and increased poverty.
<p>Moreover, the effects have been concentrated on the groups that the do-gooders would most like to help. The people who have been hurt most by the minimum wage laws are the blacks. I have often said that the most anti-black law on the books of this land is the minimum wage law.</p>
</blockquote>
<div class="lazyYT" data-youtube-id="ca8Z__o52sk" data-youtube-title="Milton Friedman on Minimum Wage" data-width="480" data-height="270" data-parameters="feature=oembed&amp;wmode=opaque"></div>
<div class="lazyYT" data-youtube-id="x-BGi4NIFww" data-youtube-title="Milton Friedman - A Conversation On Minimum Wage" data-width="480" data-height="270" data-parameters="feature=oembed&amp;wmode=opaque"></div>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/is-raising-minimum-wage-actually-effective/552801/13">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/is-raising-minimum-wage-actually-effective/552801/13</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 05 Aug 2015 01:14:40 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-552801-13</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/is-raising-minimum-wage-actually-effective/552801.rss">Is raising minimum wage actually effective?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Is raising minimum wage actually effective?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@bowserjr2 Bowser jr]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/bowserjr2">@bowserjr2</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>My reality is the reality. This isn’t some wishful thinking, it actually works. Everything you import is going to stay the same price, and you’re not increasing the total amount of dollars, just changing how it circulate.</p>
<p>The RS economy is not a viable comparison, as it has no monetary policies controlling the value of it’s gold, and it has no control over minting gold coins.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/is-raising-minimum-wage-actually-effective/552801/12">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/is-raising-minimum-wage-actually-effective/552801/12</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 05 Aug 2015 01:09:08 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-552801-12</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/is-raising-minimum-wage-actually-effective/552801.rss">Is raising minimum wage actually effective?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Is raising minimum wage actually effective?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Retaliate Retaliate]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/retaliate">@Retaliate</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“Bowser jr, post:10, topic:552801”][quote author=Retaliate link=topic=671715.msg4492089#msg4492089 date=1438730894]</p>
<aside class="quote">
<blockquote>
<p>Retaliate: More money in the economy will lead to more jobs. If you can’t pay your workers an increased minimum wage, it’s best that you run out of business.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Exactly and that is what will happen to new small businesses they will not be able to pay their workers an increased minimum wage and so they have to “Run out of business” which leaves them and their employees unemployed.<br>
[/quote]<br>
The overall increased wages would give people more money to spend and thus stimulate the economy creating new jobs. Your scenario is simple not the reality.[/quote]</p>
<p>That is when the second half of my post comes in. If we have all of this money then the cost/worth of the dollar actually goes down. It’s like Runescape if everyone has max amount of gold on their accounts. The price of gold actually goes down.  Rare items like ags’s and bgs’s or dragon claws are not going to stay at the price they are at right now. The costs of those items are going to skyrocket big time! Because that is how it works in economics.The More money people have the costs go up as well. Because if someone has max cash and you worked super hard for your ags are you still only going to sell it for like 100m? 100m is junk change because everyone has billions of gold now. You are going to want 800m for it. And that is the problem with Rsps’s even. People can make so much money really quick. Each time you thieve from a stall you get 100k gold. After an hour you have like 8 billion gold. Are dragon claws going to stay at 25m like they used to be? Heck no! Because they are rare and you can make 25m in a heart beat. The price for dragon claws are now 5.5b!</p>
<p>See how it works like that?</p>
<p>I wish your reality was true. Let us give everyone tons of money and the prices stay the same and everyone can have a job and woohoo! But it does not work like that. If it was that easy don’t you think gas or a gallon of milk or a home would be dirt cheap like how it was in the 1800’s? Why is it so different now? Because people have way more money now! Cant just give people tons of money and say have fun. If that was the case I could take 1000 dollars and get 100+ acres of land. But 1000 dollars can barely get you a car these days. Because money is not worth the same as it was before.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/is-raising-minimum-wage-actually-effective/552801/11">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/is-raising-minimum-wage-actually-effective/552801/11</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 05 Aug 2015 00:43:21 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-552801-11</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/is-raising-minimum-wage-actually-effective/552801.rss">Is raising minimum wage actually effective?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Is raising minimum wage actually effective?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@bowserjr2 Bowser jr]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/bowserjr2">@bowserjr2</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“Retaliate, post:9, topic:552801”][quote author=Bowser jr link=topic=671715.msg4492088#msg4492088 date=1438729814]<br>
Retaliate: More money in the economy will lead to more jobs. If you can’t pay your workers an increased minimum wage, it’s best that you run out of business.<br>
[/quote]</p>
<p>Exactly and that is what will happen to new small businesses they will not be able to pay their workers an increased minimum wage and so they have to “Run out of business” which leaves them and their employees unemployed.[/quote]<br>
The overall increased wages would give people more money to spend and thus stimulate the economy creating new jobs. Your scenario is simple not the reality.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/is-raising-minimum-wage-actually-effective/552801/10">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/is-raising-minimum-wage-actually-effective/552801/10</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 04 Aug 2015 23:41:26 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-552801-10</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/is-raising-minimum-wage-actually-effective/552801.rss">Is raising minimum wage actually effective?</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
