<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Forum Improvements</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/forum-improvements/43788</link>
    <description>I saw no good topic to post this in, so I made a new one. Please post any if you have as well.

1.) 
[b]Problem:[/b] I was reading through a forum and I noticed lots of locked spam or flame threads were littering the forum. This gives not only a negative &#39;feeling&#39; but makes it just that bit harder to find a good topic.
e.g. http://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php/board,22.0.html

[b]Solution:[/b] [i]Locked topics are moved to a bin forum after 1 or 2 days. I would happily code something up if this idea were to go ahead. Locked posts need to stay in the forum for 1 to 2 days after in case participants need to find out the reason for locking before forgetting about it etc.[/i]

2.)
[b]Problem:[/b] Reading through some topics I see replies that include inappropriate &#39;forum&#39; pictures, or nasty replies.
e.g. http://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php/topic,60474.msg730636.html#msg730636

[b]Solution:[/b] [i]I am not too sure about the report to moderator function on these forums but I know much more emphasis should be placed on the use of it, rather than replying back and feeding the fire. A &#39;watchlist&#39; should be shown on the front page of the forums for the moderators and admins of any &#39;reported&#39; topics or posts. This would allow them to easily and quickly fix, remove and punish. Once again, I would be happy coding/moding the report system.[/i]

3.)
[b]Problem:[/b] Reading through some topics I see replies that are off topic and are leading away from the topic at hand. (Much like Problem 2, and is another solution [Preferably both are to be implemented, not one or the other].)

[b]Solution:[/b] [i]Mods are able to check box select the offending posts and are able to move the posts into a topic in the Bin forum with the name as something like: &quot;Discarded posts from thread #{IDnum} (Rock and roll, who likes it?)&quot;. Perhaps an additional punish feature, so the posts are moved &amp; authors have their blacklist level increased. Again, I offer my services to code/mod this as well.[/i]


I hope these are usable ideas, and you will take serious consideration in these ideas, and any more posted by other members.

Also: Yes yes, I know I have offended too, but so has most, which is why we need to get the forums out of the dark ages. Mopar, if you need this or anything else coded don&#39;t hesitate to give us a PM on IRC, chances are I will have nothing else to do ;(.

This is also posted in the public section of the forum, just to see if non-community members have any nice ideas too. This can be seen [url=http://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php/topic,60847.0.html]http://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php/topic,60847.0.html[/url].</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 05 Jan 2007 03:30:55 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Community Inside Talk</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/forum-improvements/43788.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Forum Improvements</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@moparisthebest Moparisthebest]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/moparisthebest">@moparisthebest</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote no-group" data-post="1" data-topic="43814">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/tree/40/5_6259e4fa9dfe0dec282fb0955bb1974c.png" class="avatar"><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/43814/1">On another topic</a>
</div>
<blockquote>
<p>/signed.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>In case you didn’t know, posts like that are spam as well and need deleted, please don’t do that again.</p>
<p>As to the suggestions, I will respond in the public thread.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/forum-improvements/43788/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/forum-improvements/43788/2</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 05 Jan 2007 03:30:55 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-43788-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/forum-improvements/43788.rss">Forum Improvements</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Forum Improvements</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Kamu Kamu]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/kamu">@Kamu</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I saw no good topic to post this in, so I made a new one. Please post any if you have as well.</p>
<p>1.)<br>
<span class="bbcode-b">Problem:</span> I was reading through a forum and I noticed lots of locked spam or flame threads were littering the forum. This gives not only a negative ‘feeling’ but makes it just that bit harder to find a good topic.<br>
e.g. <a href="http://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php/board,22.0.html" rel="nofollow noopener">http://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php/board,22.0.html</a></p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Solution:</span> <span class="bbcode-i">Locked topics are moved to a bin forum after 1 or 2 days. I would happily code something up if this idea were to go ahead. Locked posts need to stay in the forum for 1 to 2 days after in case participants need to find out the reason for locking before forgetting about it etc.</span></p>
<p>2.)<br>
<span class="bbcode-b">Problem:</span> Reading through some topics I see replies that include inappropriate ‘forum’ pictures, or nasty replies.<br>
e.g. <a href="http://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php/topic,60474.msg730636.html#msg730636" rel="nofollow noopener">http://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php/topic,60474.msg730636.html#msg730636</a></p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Solution:</span> <span class="bbcode-i">I am not too sure about the report to moderator function on these forums but I know much more emphasis should be placed on the use of it, rather than replying back and feeding the fire. A ‘watchlist’ should be shown on the front page of the forums for the moderators and admins of any ‘reported’ topics or posts. This would allow them to easily and quickly fix, remove and punish. Once again, I would be happy coding/moding the report system.</span></p>
<p>3.)<br>
<span class="bbcode-b">Problem:</span> Reading through some topics I see replies that are off topic and are leading away from the topic at hand. (Much like Problem 2, and is another solution [Preferably both are to be implemented, not one or the other].)</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Solution:</span> <span class="bbcode-i">Mods are able to check box select the offending posts and are able to move the posts into a topic in the Bin forum with the name as something like: “Discarded posts from thread #{IDnum} (Rock and roll, who likes it?)”. Perhaps an additional punish feature, so the posts are moved &amp; authors have their blacklist level increased. Again, I offer my services to code/mod this as well.</span></p>
<p>I hope these are usable ideas, and you will take serious consideration in these ideas, and any more posted by other members.</p>
<p>Also: Yes yes, I know I have offended too, but so has most, which is why we need to get the forums out of the dark ages. Mopar, if you need this or anything else coded don’t hesitate to give us a PM on IRC, chances are I will have nothing else to do ;(.</p>
<p>This is also posted in the public section of the forum, just to see if non-community members have any nice ideas too. This can be seen <a href="http://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php/topic,60847.0.html" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">http://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php/topic,60847.0.html</a>.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/forum-improvements/43788/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/forum-improvements/43788/1</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 04 Jan 2007 15:45:38 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-43788-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/forum-improvements/43788.rss">Forum Improvements</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
