<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>[REQ] Signature [REQ]</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/req-signature-req/183442</link>
    <description>I would like to have a nice signature with a nice Pk-ing feel to it. Please make sure to read ALL of the Requirements before attemptnig to make the signature, Thanks for all your help!

[b][u]TEXT:[/u][/b] Project PK --  Something with a fancy written type feel, but i want it to be a bit thick (otherwise known as not thin), like kind of messy cursive, I dont know a font name, i want it to be pretty large, taking up a good bit of the signature (Please put the title in the top-left hand corner of the signature). The font size should be around 24 or so, pretty large text, and i want the color to be a Dark or Light Blue-ish color (wichever looks better), outlined in White-ish color, and Glossy. The Cursive should have an Italics look BTW.

[b][u]OTHER TEXT:[/u][/b] I want the server&#39;s IP on the Bottom-Right hand corner, i want it to be smaller text than the Server&#39;s Title, but the same fonts and everything, if the cursive isn&#39;t readable that small, then please change it to a readable font that look good. I do want it to stand out too, because that will draw attention to my server. The server&#39;s IP is project-pk.no-ip.org ***This server is not finished yet, so it will not be online for a good while***

[b][u]IMAGE:[/u][/b] I want there to be piles of money (Larger Piles) and maybe a Dragon Scimitar and a DDS (Dragon Dagger Super Poisened) in the middle. Make the Pictures a little smaller than normal because i dont want the picture too large (I&#39;d like for the money to be more of a normal size, and the wepons to be smaller if required (needed)). I want the images to be overlapped by all text. (I want the Image to try to Convey a Picture of PK-ing and Wealth). If you could Outline the images in some color to make them stand out well against the Background, but not too much to take attention away from the text.

[b][u]BACKGROUND:[/u][/b] I want the background to be a Dark Black Shade. I want it to look more smoky than plain black. I want it to make the Objects stand out (But not too much as to take attention away from the text)
                                      ***You can change the background to whatever looks better if you want, but i want it to be a darker shade***

[b][u]SIZE:[/u][/b] I don&#39;t know any exact sizes, but I want it to be longer than it is tall, and i dont want it to be very tall because that would take up too much space after my posts.

[b][u]OVERALL:[/u][/b] I want the Signature to have a very new and cutting-edge look to it. I want it to really stand out.


If you take your time to make this Signature for me, then i thank you for your time and help!</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 21 Feb 2008 07:23:32 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Graphics</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/req-signature-req/183442.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>[REQ] Signature [REQ]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Project_PK Project PK]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/project_pk">@Project_PK</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I would like to have a nice signature with a nice Pk-ing feel to it. Please make sure to read ALL of the Requirements before attemptnig to make the signature, Thanks for all your help!</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b"><span class="bbcode-u">TEXT:</span></span> Project PK –  Something with a fancy written type feel, but i want it to be a bit thick (otherwise known as not thin), like kind of messy cursive, I dont know a font name, i want it to be pretty large, taking up a good bit of the signature (Please put the title in the top-left hand corner of the signature). The font size should be around 24 or so, pretty large text, and i want the color to be a Dark or Light Blue-ish color (wichever looks better), outlined in White-ish color, and Glossy. The Cursive should have an Italics look BTW.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b"><span class="bbcode-u">OTHER TEXT:</span></span> I want the server’s IP on the Bottom-Right hand corner, i want it to be smaller text than the Server’s Title, but the same fonts and everything, if the cursive isn’t readable that small, then please change it to a readable font that look good. I do want it to stand out too, because that will draw attention to my server. The server’s IP is <a href="http://project-pk.no-ip.org" rel="nofollow noopener">project-pk.no-ip.org</a> <em><strong>This server is not finished yet, so it will not be online for a good while</strong></em></p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b"><span class="bbcode-u">IMAGE:</span></span> I want there to be piles of money (Larger Piles) and maybe a Dragon Scimitar and a DDS (Dragon Dagger Super Poisened) in the middle. Make the Pictures a little smaller than normal because i dont want the picture too large (I’d like for the money to be more of a normal size, and the wepons to be smaller if required (needed)). I want the images to be overlapped by all text. (I want the Image to try to Convey a Picture of PK-ing and Wealth). If you could Outline the images in some color to make them stand out well against the Background, but not too much to take attention away from the text.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b"><span class="bbcode-u">BACKGROUND:</span></span> I want the background to be a Dark Black Shade. I want it to look more smoky than plain black. I want it to make the Objects stand out (But not too much as to take attention away from the text)<br>
<em><strong>You can change the background to whatever looks better if you want, but i want it to be a darker shade</strong></em></p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b"><span class="bbcode-u">SIZE:</span></span> I don’t know any exact sizes, but I want it to be longer than it is tall, and i dont want it to be very tall because that would take up too much space after my posts.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b"><span class="bbcode-u">OVERALL:</span></span> I want the Signature to have a very new and cutting-edge look to it. I want it to really stand out.</p>
<p>If you take your time to make this Signature for me, then i thank you for your time and help!</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/req-signature-req/183442/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/req-signature-req/183442/1</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Feb 2008 07:23:32 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-183442-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/req-signature-req/183442.rss">[REQ] Signature [REQ]</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
