<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>YoungInferno317 - now online</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/younginferno317-now-online/483076</link>
    <description>Hey, i&#39;ve been a member for a while, though i&#39;ve never posted. I&#39;ve been reading and learning, and with the help of my friends mod cole, and yz young, we were able to get this server onto a vps. I doubt anyone cares, but i do, and i want to show im gunna put forward effort to anyone that joins. Starting tommorow, we will begin daily updates, wether they be big or small, to improve our server. Now, before you blast me for using an already made source, please note, im new at this, and want to try. We had added alot of contet before hand, but someone(no names)accidently messed up, so we had to restart with out orig used source. 

MEDIA- I quickly thew together a video of some of the features around the server. This is a PK-BASED server, but it has skilling so you can obtain the comp cape. Here is the video http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=isDUVe-lgZw&amp;feature=youtu.be 

Theres a promotion to any new players that join soon, and that will be the gift of 2 mystery boxes, which can hold almost any item in the game, but most are good. You may even pull a divine. See me(Inferno), Yz Young, or Mod Cole, to recieve your boxes. HERES THE DL LINK http://up.ht/Y54z7B . Have a nice day. thankyou</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 11 Feb 2013 19:57:32 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/younginferno317-now-online/483076.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>YoungInferno317 - now online</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@teh_ags_prod teh ags prod]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/teh_ags_prod">@teh_ags_prod</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Hey, i’ve been a member for a while, though i’ve never posted. I’ve been reading and learning, and with the help of my friends mod cole, and yz young, we were able to get this server onto a vps. I doubt anyone cares, but i do, and i want to show im gunna put forward effort to anyone that joins. Starting tommorow, we will begin daily updates, wether they be big or small, to improve our server. Now, before you blast me for using an already made source, please note, im new at this, and want to try. We had added alot of contet before hand, but someone(no names)accidently messed up, so we had to restart with out orig used source.</p>
<p>MEDIA- I quickly thew together a video of some of the features around the server. This is a PK-BASED server, but it has skilling so you can obtain the comp cape. Here is the video <a href="http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=isDUVe-lgZw&amp;feature=youtu.be" rel="nofollow noopener">http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=isDUVe-lgZw&amp;feature=youtu.be</a></p>
<p>Theres a promotion to any new players that join soon, and that will be the gift of 2 mystery boxes, which can hold almost any item in the game, but most are good. You may even pull a divine. See me(Inferno), Yz Young, or Mod Cole, to recieve your boxes. HERES THE DL LINK <a href="http://up.ht/Y54z7B" rel="nofollow noopener">http://up.ht/Y54z7B</a> . Have a nice day. thankyou</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/younginferno317-now-online/483076/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/younginferno317-now-online/483076/1</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 11 Feb 2013 19:57:32 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-483076-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/younginferno317-now-online/483076.rss">YoungInferno317 - now online</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
