<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Savage Raid | Factions | PvP | Custom Plugins | Custom PvP/PvE Classes</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/savage-raid-factions-pvp-custom-plugins-custom-pvp-pve-classes/543857</link>
    <description>[center][b][size=24pt]Savage Raid[/size][/b][/center]


[center]Website: [url=http://www.savageraid.org]Savage Raid Home[/url]
Voting: [url=http://www.vote4raid.com]Savage Raid Voting Site
[youtube]https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Dp8dPf3dqvc [/youtube][/center]

About: 

Tired of looking for PvP, not being able to raid bases, no TNT, unresponsive admins, laggy servers, lack of content, or just being bored?  Then Savage Raid is the server for you!  We are getting RAVE reviews from everyone....  Isn&#39;t it time you checked out what all the talk is about?!  The purpose of this server is for you to log in and be able to PvP, Raid bases, and take on the world with no boredom!  No lag and a professional staff ensure fun and fair PvP no matter if you want to PvP, Raid Bases, Do a Warzone, or Create the Strongest Faction.  There is truly something for every PvPer!  Just read what our members have to say(listed further down in the post.) 

Server Info: 

[u]FULL PVP[/u] - We hate wandering aimlessly for PvP, so our world is designed so everyone can find meaningful PvP quickly!  Our large population helps to ensure you have new and relevant battles frequently rather than killing the same guy without gear over and over. 

[u]BASE RAIDING[/u] - How fun is it to go loot a whole base dry?  Well, we have designed our system around Base Raiding and Faction Battles over their bases.  Nothing is funner than creating a TNT Cannon to destroy the walls of a base and looting them dry.  Rise to the top and smash your competition by taking all of their stuff! 

[u]FACTIONS[/u]- To ensure amazing group fights and battles over territory we have a Faction based system.  Join a Faction and help them in their ongoing wars or start your own and Conquer the World! 

[u]LAG FREE[/u]- The number one thing that ruins PvP is lag.  We HATE Lag.  So, with our staff&#39;s massive amount of experience we have designed a revolutionary server side system to ensure the best PvP experience possible in Minecraft for all of you! 

[u]WARZONES [/u]- Want to just log in and get some quick battles?  That is exactly why we created our Warzones.  Not only are they quick and fun, but they are also meaningful! 

[u]ANTI CHEAT[/u] - We have one of the best anti cheat systems in place. We have applied tricks to fight hackers on our server not seen elsewhere. Also, with our professional admins if anybody does manage to hack, they are quickly caught and banned. 

[u]CLASSES[/u] - To spice up PvP and make it a little more fun we have completely designed unique classes for you to play.  While they are fun and add some neat things to do we have worked very hard to ensure they don&#39;t take away from those of you who like Vanilla Minecraft PvP.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2014 06:07:51 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Minecraft</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/savage-raid-factions-pvp-custom-plugins-custom-pvp-pve-classes/543857.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Savage Raid | Factions | PvP | Custom Plugins | Custom PvP/PvE Classes</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Kozs Kozs]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/kozs">@Kozs</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[center]<span class="bbcode-b">[size=24pt]Savage Raid[/size]</span>[/center]</p>
<p>[center]Website: <a href="http://www.savageraid.org" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">Savage Raid Home</a><br>
Voting: [url=http://www.vote4raid.com]Savage Raid Voting Site<br>
[youtube]<a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Dp8dPf3dqvc" rel="nofollow noopener">https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Dp8dPf3dqvc</a> [/youtube][/center]</p>
<p>About:</p>
<p>Tired of looking for PvP, not being able to raid bases, no TNT, unresponsive admins, laggy servers, lack of content, or just being bored?  Then Savage Raid is the server for you!  We are getting RAVE reviews from everyone…  Isn’t it time you checked out what all the talk is about?!  The purpose of this server is for you to log in and be able to PvP, Raid bases, and take on the world with no boredom!  No lag and a professional staff ensure fun and fair PvP no matter if you want to PvP, Raid Bases, Do a Warzone, or Create the Strongest Faction.  There is truly something for every PvPer!  Just read what our members have to say(listed further down in the post.)</p>
<p>Server Info:</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-u">FULL PVP</span> - We hate wandering aimlessly for PvP, so our world is designed so everyone can find meaningful PvP quickly!  Our large population helps to ensure you have new and relevant battles frequently rather than killing the same guy without gear over and over.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-u">BASE RAIDING</span> - How fun is it to go loot a whole base dry?  Well, we have designed our system around Base Raiding and Faction Battles over their bases.  Nothing is funner than creating a TNT Cannon to destroy the walls of a base and looting them dry.  Rise to the top and smash your competition by taking all of their stuff!</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-u">FACTIONS</span>- To ensure amazing group fights and battles over territory we have a Faction based system.  Join a Faction and help them in their ongoing wars or start your own and Conquer the World!</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-u">LAG FREE</span>- The number one thing that ruins PvP is lag.  We HATE Lag.  So, with our staff’s massive amount of experience we have designed a revolutionary server side system to ensure the best PvP experience possible in Minecraft for all of you!</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-u">WARZONES </span>- Want to just log in and get some quick battles?  That is exactly why we created our Warzones.  Not only are they quick and fun, but they are also meaningful!</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-u">ANTI CHEAT</span> - We have one of the best anti cheat systems in place. We have applied tricks to fight hackers on our server not seen elsewhere. Also, with our professional admins if anybody does manage to hack, they are quickly caught and banned.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-u">CLASSES</span> - To spice up PvP and make it a little more fun we have completely designed unique classes for you to play.  While they are fun and add some neat things to do we have worked very hard to ensure they don’t take away from those of you who like Vanilla Minecraft PvP.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/savage-raid-factions-pvp-custom-plugins-custom-pvp-pve-classes/543857/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/savage-raid-factions-pvp-custom-plugins-custom-pvp-pve-classes/543857/1</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2014 06:07:51 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-543857-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/savage-raid-factions-pvp-custom-plugins-custom-pvp-pve-classes/543857.rss">Savage Raid | Factions | PvP | Custom Plugins | Custom PvP/PvE Classes</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
