<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Duping</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/duping/394156</link>
    <description>Hi i currently own a 30 player usual ran server, webclient and all, but i&#39;ve been having one problem. Duping. I know it&#39;s obviously in the trade codes and i was just wondering if someone could help me fix this. I am an experienced coder and i do know what im doing but i just can&#39;t seem to find a trading code that isn&#39;t a pi one, i don&#39;t have a clickingmost.java, but the codes in there are in my client.java, they do work still. The duping problem i believe is the classic trade and decline problem which im sure is pretty simple for you coders. You could send me how to do it with step by step, or just go on teamviewer and i can show you some of the files so you could work on it. If you need any codes you wish me to submit that go along with my trading, accepting, and declining process&#39;s then just ask and ill be happy to post in a comment. Thanks</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 07 May 2011 21:49:13 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/duping/394156.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Duping</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Meeper98 Meeper98]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/meeper98">@Meeper98</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Gotcha, but the problem isn’t when they dissconnect it’s when theyre just trading, for instance if someone trades something and at the 2nd trade screen they quickly accept decline while the other person has allready accepted it gives them both the item. It’s a simple dupe but it loses me a lot of mula $$$. I just need the trading codes so i can replace them with my own. <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=5" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"> thanks for the help</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/duping/394156/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/duping/394156/3</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 07 May 2011 21:49:13 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-394156-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/duping/394156.rss">Duping</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Duping</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@iz3_legend iz3 legend]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/iz3_legend">@iz3_legend</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>to my understanding on this dupe when you log out it keeps your trade screen open which allows duping, although i have never delt with this dupe try working on making the trade screen close when one person “loses connection” that way the trade screen wont be open when the other person tries to except. Im probably not the most reliable because this sounds like delta and im mostly pi nowadays.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/duping/394156/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/duping/394156/2</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 07 May 2011 21:43:35 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-394156-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/duping/394156.rss">Duping</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Duping</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Meeper98 Meeper98]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/meeper98">@Meeper98</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Hi i currently own a 30 player usual ran server, webclient and all, but i’ve been having one problem. Duping. I know it’s obviously in the trade codes and i was just wondering if someone could help me fix this. I am an experienced coder and i do know what im doing but i just can’t seem to find a trading code that isn’t a pi one, i don’t have a clickingmost.java, but the codes in there are in my client.java, they do work still. The duping problem i believe is the classic trade and decline problem which im sure is pretty simple for you coders. You could send me how to do it with step by step, or just go on teamviewer and i can show you some of the files so you could work on it. If you need any codes you wish me to submit that go along with my trading, accepting, and declining process’s then just ask and ill be happy to post in a comment. Thanks</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/duping/394156/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/duping/394156/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 07 May 2011 21:35:06 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-394156-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/duping/394156.rss">Duping</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
