<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>First2zero Darts Flash Game</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/first2zero-darts-flash-game/227798</link>
    <description>Well I recently got hooked on a little flash game called first2zero, it&#39;s a fun little competetive dart game in which you can play people around the world (and humiliate them with consecutive triple 20&#39;s). So I was thinking of a way i could guarantee the highest score possible each turn, thus increasing the amount of satisfaction I gain from crushing people under my index finger. Yes i like to feel like i&#39;m better then all of them, it&#39;s a flaw in my morals.

On to the point of this post! Way back when i remember using SCAR for runescape, though i&#39;ve moved on from runescape (as we all know it is a pro at distracting you from major projects and deadlines) i still have the gamer in me. I never attempted scripting in my runescape days but i think it&#39;s about time i learn SOME form of programming (other than html/asp). I&#39;ve been able to learn a bit from tutorials strewn about over the internet, but what i really need is someone to tell me exactly what i need to do, and how to do it. I&#39;ve been able to move the mouse to the first dart and pick it up, and thats about as far as i&#39;ve gotten. If anyone could coach me on this script (which i&#39;m sure isn&#39;t that complicated for someone who knows what they are doing) that would be greatly appreciated. I&#39;m not sure if i&#39;m allowed to post a link to the game (would it come under the no advertising rule?) but if you google it you should find it. Hopefully, someone out there will be kind enough to help me out. Thank you in advance.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 24 Aug 2008 21:16:56 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/first2zero-darts-flash-game/227798.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>First2zero Darts Flash Game</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@NikkiN NikkiN]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/nikkin">@NikkiN</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Well I recently got hooked on a little flash game called first2zero, it’s a fun little competetive dart game in which you can play people around the world (and humiliate them with consecutive triple 20’s). So I was thinking of a way i could guarantee the highest score possible each turn, thus increasing the amount of satisfaction I gain from crushing people under my index finger. Yes i like to feel like i’m better then all of them, it’s a flaw in my morals.</p>
<p>On to the point of this post! Way back when i remember using SCAR for runescape, though i’ve moved on from runescape (as we all know it is a pro at distracting you from major projects and deadlines) i still have the gamer in me. I never attempted scripting in my runescape days but i think it’s about time i learn SOME form of programming (other than html/asp). I’ve been able to learn a bit from tutorials strewn about over the internet, but what i really need is someone to tell me exactly what i need to do, and how to do it. I’ve been able to move the mouse to the first dart and pick it up, and thats about as far as i’ve gotten. If anyone could coach me on this script (which i’m sure isn’t that complicated for someone who knows what they are doing) that would be greatly appreciated. I’m not sure if i’m allowed to post a link to the game (would it come under the no advertising rule?) but if you google it you should find it. Hopefully, someone out there will be kind enough to help me out. Thank you in advance.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/first2zero-darts-flash-game/227798/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/first2zero-darts-flash-game/227798/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 24 Aug 2008 21:16:56 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-227798-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/first2zero-darts-flash-game/227798.rss">First2zero Darts Flash Game</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
