<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Training pures</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/training-pures/182764</link>
    <description>Yes pking is dead, pures are dead, you may ask what is the point of this? well I think about these things while doing nothing and like to share my ideas.

Training pures.
In this guide I will tell you how to create 3 different types of pures: strength pure, range pure and magic pure.
these skills revolve around the &#39;combat triangle&#39;, being pures they totaly fuck it up :)

[size=20pt][color=blue][b]Strength pures[/b][/color][/size]

To start with you will need to make a runescape account. Then download this:
http://www.staticimp.com/rulercorner/1800/nexus18lite.rar
Open it then get it through the tutorial island, then equip: bronze axe + wooden shield, choose the cow fighting script and let it rune till 40 strenght (or 50 if you don&#39;t want to train later...). When 40/50 strength do &#39;Vampire slayer&#39; quest this will get you to 20 attack, now set up the lumbridge cow fighter script and train till 40 attack, no more no less. If earlyer you autoed untill 40 strenght you will need to train it to 50 at the monks near Barbarian village. finished stats should be 40 attack and 50 strength, well done you have a strength pure, to finish him or her off you will need monks robes, lobsters, rune scimitars and rune 2h swords have fun with a dead pure :)

Stats:
Attack: 40
Strenght: 50
Defence: 1
Items:
30x Monks robe (Tops)
30x Monks robe (Bottoms)
30x Amulets of Strength
5x Rune Scimitars
5x Rune 2h swords
1000x Lobsters

Alternatively you could get 31 prayer for ultimate strength but that would raise your combat level.

[size=20pt][b]Range pure[/b][/size]

Attack goblins at Lumbridge with a bow and 300 bronze arrows, this will get you to level 10. Then Attack level 12 Minotaurs at Stronghold of Security with an Oak bow and 332 Iron arrows, this will get you to level 20. Kill the level 82 lesser demon In the wizards tower with A willow bow and 4095 Iron arrows (iron because you can&#39;t collect them). This will get you to level 40 range. To get to level 50 stay at the lesser demon and use another 5500 Iron arrows assuming you hit 3 every time, after you use up all of the arrows you will have 50 ranged.

To finish off you range pure you are gonna need:
1000x Bronze arrows
2000x Iron arrows
3000x Steel arrows
4000x Mithril arrows
4000x Adamant arrows
10x Maple bows
10x Monks robe (Top)
10x Green D&#39;hide chaps
10x Green D&#39;hide vambs
10x Amulet of Accuracys

Done one range pure, have fun with a dead one.



[size=20pt][b]Magic pure[/b][/size]

Do the quest &#39;Witches potion&#39; then &#39;Imp catcher&#39; This will get you to 10 magic.


Will do rest in the morning. Night all!</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 19 Feb 2008 03:04:28 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/training-pures/182764.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Training pures</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@bootnecklad bootnecklad]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/bootnecklad">@bootnecklad</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Yes pking is dead, pures are dead, you may ask what is the point of this? well I think about these things while doing nothing and like to share my ideas.</p>
<p>Training pures.<br>
In this guide I will tell you how to create 3 different types of pures: strength pure, range pure and magic pure.<br>
these skills revolve around the ‘combat triangle’, being pures they totaly fuck it up <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=6" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
<p>[size=20pt][color=blue]<span class="bbcode-b">Strength pures</span>[/color][/size]</p>
<p>To start with you will need to make a runescape account. Then download this:<br>
<a href="http://www.staticimp.com/rulercorner/1800/nexus18lite.rar" class="onebox" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">http://www.staticimp.com/rulercorner/1800/nexus18lite.rar</a><br>
Open it then get it through the tutorial island, then equip: bronze axe + wooden shield, choose the cow fighting script and let it rune till 40 strenght (or 50 if you don’t want to train later…). When 40/50 strength do ‘Vampire slayer’ quest this will get you to 20 attack, now set up the lumbridge cow fighter script and train till 40 attack, no more no less. If earlyer you autoed untill 40 strenght you will need to train it to 50 at the monks near Barbarian village. finished stats should be 40 attack and 50 strength, well done you have a strength pure, to finish him or her off you will need monks robes, lobsters, rune scimitars and rune 2h swords have fun with a dead pure <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=6" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
<p>Stats:<br>
Attack: 40<br>
Strenght: 50<br>
Defence: 1<br>
Items:<br>
30x Monks robe (Tops)<br>
30x Monks robe (Bottoms)<br>
30x Amulets of Strength<br>
5x Rune Scimitars<br>
5x Rune 2h swords<br>
1000x Lobsters</p>
<p>Alternatively you could get 31 prayer for ultimate strength but that would raise your combat level.</p>
<p>[size=20pt]<span class="bbcode-b">Range pure</span>[/size]</p>
<p>Attack goblins at Lumbridge with a bow and 300 bronze arrows, this will get you to level 10. Then Attack level 12 Minotaurs at Stronghold of Security with an Oak bow and 332 Iron arrows, this will get you to level 20. Kill the level 82 lesser demon In the wizards tower with A willow bow and 4095 Iron arrows (iron because you can’t collect them). This will get you to level 40 range. To get to level 50 stay at the lesser demon and use another 5500 Iron arrows assuming you hit 3 every time, after you use up all of the arrows you will have 50 ranged.</p>
<p>To finish off you range pure you are gonna need:<br>
1000x Bronze arrows<br>
2000x Iron arrows<br>
3000x Steel arrows<br>
4000x Mithril arrows<br>
4000x Adamant arrows<br>
10x Maple bows<br>
10x Monks robe (Top)<br>
10x Green D’hide chaps<br>
10x Green D’hide vambs<br>
10x Amulet of Accuracys</p>
<p>Done one range pure, have fun with a dead one.</p>
<p>[size=20pt]<span class="bbcode-b">Magic pure</span>[/size]</p>
<p>Do the quest ‘Witches potion’ then ‘Imp catcher’ This will get you to 10 magic.</p>
<p>Will do rest in the morning. Night all!</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/training-pures/182764/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/training-pures/182764/1</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 19 Feb 2008 03:04:28 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-182764-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/training-pures/182764.rss">Training pures</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
