<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>InsidiaX Client Cache packing</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/insidiax-client-cache-packing/450223</link>
    <description>[color=black][b]Okay, well I&#39;m somewhat new to Java programming. Not entirely though. I have been trying to create new methods to make it so the Titlebox and the titlebutton on my client (I&#39;m using InsidiaX) Project Insanity, 317 loading a 634 cache. I can use Tom&#39;s Cache Editor, I can see the titlebox and titlebutton in there. I exported them to my desktop, edited them. I kept them the same size and everything just changed the color. Regardless, I imported them both into the cache editor and as I did that I hit save archive, and then I get a message saying that the cache has been repacked successfully. I reload the client, and nothing has changed. Also, I have looked for the sprites in the sprites folder of my cache, and neither of the .png&#39;s are in there. Can someone maybe catch what I&#39;m doing wrong here? Also, just an off topic question, is there even a way to make clients fullscreen? I can&#39;t find anything on a search, all i need is a simple answer yes or no so i can continue my search or not. Thanks in advance! Best of luck in helping me out! I ALSO JUST REALISED THIS IS THE WRONG FRICKEN BOARD TO PUT THIS ON!! CAN SOMEONE MOVE THIS! DAMNIT lmfao</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 20 Jul 2012 20:41:54 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/insidiax-client-cache-packing/450223.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>InsidiaX Client Cache packing</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@FantasyXCoder FantasyXCoder]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/fantasyxcoder">@FantasyXCoder</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Yea, after everytime i replace a file.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/insidiax-client-cache-packing/450223/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/insidiax-client-cache-packing/450223/3</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jul 2012 20:41:54 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-450223-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/insidiax-client-cache-packing/450223.rss">InsidiaX Client Cache packing</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>InsidiaX Client Cache packing</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Ambition_Rsps Ambition Rsps]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/ambition_rsps">@Ambition_Rsps</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>did you click “rebuild cache” on the toms cache editor?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/insidiax-client-cache-packing/450223/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/insidiax-client-cache-packing/450223/2</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jul 2012 07:45:01 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-450223-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/insidiax-client-cache-packing/450223.rss">InsidiaX Client Cache packing</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>InsidiaX Client Cache packing</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@FantasyXCoder FantasyXCoder]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/fantasyxcoder">@FantasyXCoder</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[color=black][b]Okay, well I’m somewhat new to Java programming. Not entirely though. I have been trying to create new methods to make it so the Titlebox and the titlebutton on my client (I’m using InsidiaX) Project Insanity, 317 loading a 634 cache. I can use Tom’s Cache Editor, I can see the titlebox and titlebutton in there. I exported them to my desktop, edited them. I kept them the same size and everything just changed the color. Regardless, I imported them both into the cache editor and as I did that I hit save archive, and then I get a message saying that the cache has been repacked successfully. I reload the client, and nothing has changed. Also, I have looked for the sprites in the sprites folder of my cache, and neither of the .png’s are in there. Can someone maybe catch what I’m doing wrong here? Also, just an off topic question, is there even a way to make clients fullscreen? I can’t find anything on a search, all i need is a simple answer yes or no so i can continue my search or not. Thanks in advance! Best of luck in helping me out! I ALSO JUST REALISED THIS IS THE WRONG FRICKEN BOARD TO PUT THIS ON!! CAN SOMEONE MOVE THIS! DAMNIT lmfao</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/insidiax-client-cache-packing/450223/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/insidiax-client-cache-packing/450223/1</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jul 2012 04:27:41 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-450223-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/insidiax-client-cache-packing/450223.rss">InsidiaX Client Cache packing</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
