<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Adding New Index to File Server</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/adding-new-index-to-file-server/536875</link>
    <description>Ok, so I&#39;ve added a new index to my cache to load all textures for my client and i have it loading fine client sided. Its also being loaded in the file server too. The problem is when I delete my cache and go to download a fresh one, it downloads and loads fine up to the login screen. When you hit login its stuck at &quot;Please allow a few moments for the region to download.&quot; I can&#39;t figure out why this is happening. I&#39;ve packed the crc and versionlist for the index in versionlist.dat and i&#39;ve found that Texture.java is communicating with it through ondemand found here: [code=java]updateManager.method558(4, id);[/code] which requests files as 4 is the newest data block. If anyone could help me figure this out, i&#39;d forever be in your favor. :D</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2013 19:48:33 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Game Development</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/adding-new-index-to-file-server/536875.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Adding New Index to File Server</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@RiiPiiNFtW RiiPiiNFtW]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/riipiinftw">@RiiPiiNFtW</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Ok, so I’ve added a new index to my cache to load all textures for my client and i have it loading fine client sided. Its also being loaded in the file server too. The problem is when I delete my cache and go to download a fresh one, it downloads and loads fine up to the login screen. When you hit login its stuck at “Please allow a few moments for the region to download.” I can’t figure out why this is happening. I’ve packed the crc and versionlist for the index in versionlist.dat and i’ve found that Texture.java is communicating with it through ondemand found here: <code>updateManager.method558(4, id);</code> which requests files as 4 is the newest data block. If anyone could help me figure this out, i’d forever be in your favor. <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/smiley.png?v=5" title=":smiley:" class="emoji" alt=":smiley:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/adding-new-index-to-file-server/536875/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/adding-new-index-to-file-server/536875/1</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2013 19:48:33 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-536875-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/adding-new-index-to-file-server/536875.rss">Adding New Index to File Server</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
