<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Writing a bot: a tutorial of sorts</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/writing-a-bot-a-tutorial-of-sorts/168330</link>
    <description>Here I intend to teach the anatomy of a Runescape bot and various methods employed to &#39;auto&#39; on Runescape. I don&#39;t mean to spoon-feed the reader how to write a bot and you shouldn&#39;t expect to come into this knowing nothing about Java and come out with a functional bot written. That would teach you nothing, and education is really all that Runescape client fuckery is good for nowadays. By necessity, I&#39;ll digress from the main point very often because I&#39;ll be branching out over a wide variety of topics. Also, I&#39;m only going to talk about bytecode injection bots. I don&#39;t consider color seeking bots below me, but I really can&#39;t be bothered learning about them or writing one. So... here we go.

Bytecode injection bots
These are the more common breed of modern Runescape bots for a variety of reasons: simplicity, speed, and so on. Once, clients were decompiled, modified, and recompiled to form a bot. Jagex eventually ended this for the fool by adding a basic reflection system. This is easy to get around, but bytecode injection is easier anyway. Bytecode injection is the modification of existing class files to add methods, modify methods, etc. All bots that I have seen complicate the process of loading their modified classes. The simplest way is to pack the bot with the Runescape client and replace the original packed client in the cache with the pretty little modified client. Doing so removes the necessity for glorified class loaders. However, I&#39;ll write on their purpose too, for the sake of completion.

    Subtopic 2A) Bytecode: Bytecode, for the purposes here, is what composes a class file. If you don&#39;t already have an intimate knowledge of bytecode and intend to write a bytecode injection bot, read the Java class specification and both memorize and cherish every detail. I won&#39;t provide a link; Google is more than willing to find it for you. Alternatively, you can read the various tutorials in the Java programming section on bytecode and BCEL. Do not continue reading until you are proficient enough in bytecode to translate raw Java code into bytecode and vice versa.
     Subtopic 2B) Updaters: Those who write bots for Runescape probably are without social lives and only want an updater so they can pretend they have better things to do. I&#39;ve been guilty of this on many occasions. Updaters are, in my opinion, unnecessary yet very convenient. Don&#39;t want to spend a few hours every week updating your bot for the new Runescape build? Updaters are the way to go. First off, don&#39;t care about time. It is the greatest fault of all accuracy to value speed. It doesn&#39;t matter whether your updating takes a tenth of a second or ten minutes as long as it is accurate. Worrying about speed is another thing I am guilty of, and my creations were exponentially better when I cast off the idea that my accuracy should be sacrificed for e-penis size. Anyhow, updater theory is to find patterns in builds and identify fields based on those patterns. These patterns should not repeat themselves. &quot;ALOAD GETFIELD&quot; is not a good pattern because it&#39;s too simple and repeating. On the other hand, &quot;ALOAD GETFIELD PUTFIELD ALOAD GETFIELD LDC (unique number) IADD&quot; is a very good pattern. Use BCEL&#39;s InstructionFinder or a similar item to find your patterns. 
[center][b]Continued when I stop shaking. For the record, triple-brewed coffee is a bad idea.[/b][/center]</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 02 Jan 2008 15:38:06 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/writing-a-bot-a-tutorial-of-sorts/168330.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Writing a bot: a tutorial of sorts</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@unlimitedorb unlimitedorb]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/unlimitedorb">@unlimitedorb</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“Silver Lining, post:6, topic:168330”]My RS client experience = cock + barrel - 17. Yeah, it’s that high.[/quote] (…or programming)</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/writing-a-bot-a-tutorial-of-sorts/168330/7">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/writing-a-bot-a-tutorial-of-sorts/168330/7</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 02 Jan 2008 15:38:06 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-168330-7</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/writing-a-bot-a-tutorial-of-sorts/168330.rss">Writing a bot: a tutorial of sorts</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Writing a bot: a tutorial of sorts</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Silver_Lining Silver Lining]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/silver_lining">@Silver_Lining</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>My RS client experience = cock + barrel - 17. Yeah, it’s that high.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/writing-a-bot-a-tutorial-of-sorts/168330/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/writing-a-bot-a-tutorial-of-sorts/168330/6</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 02 Jan 2008 15:36:31 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-168330-6</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/writing-a-bot-a-tutorial-of-sorts/168330.rss">Writing a bot: a tutorial of sorts</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Writing a bot: a tutorial of sorts</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@unlimitedorb unlimitedorb]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/unlimitedorb">@unlimitedorb</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Very good pattern finding theory Krichevskoy.</p>
<p>Keep it up Silver Lining, I know that you find the client a waste of your time nowadays, but it’s extremely helpful to have the knowledgeable support of people that have a solid amount of experience with the client.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/writing-a-bot-a-tutorial-of-sorts/168330/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/writing-a-bot-a-tutorial-of-sorts/168330/5</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 02 Jan 2008 15:00:32 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-168330-5</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/writing-a-bot-a-tutorial-of-sorts/168330.rss">Writing a bot: a tutorial of sorts</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Writing a bot: a tutorial of sorts</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Krichevskoy Krichevskoy]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/krichevskoy">@Krichevskoy</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote no-group quote-modified" data-post="1" data-topic="168330">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 Silver Lining:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>On the other hand, “ALOAD GETFIELD PUTFIELD ALOAD GETFIELD LDC (unique number) IADD” is a very good pattern.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Just some additional commentary.</p>
<p>While a unique pattern can be great, it also gives you a single point of failure. Usually, with a unique pattern, it’s a good idea to have more than one place in the code (and thus more than one pattern) for finding that method/field/whatever. That way, if they change something, you just get an error saying one of your patterns is broken rather than no result at all or, worse, a wrong one. The longer the pattern, the more fragile it is - but it’s a tradeoff between false positives and robustness. In some cases, a series of short patterns that form a pattern themselves is better than one big unique pattern. What if that “ALOAD GETFIELD” is always after a “SIPUSH INVOKESTATIC” and before a “IFNE ISTORE”, no matter what else changes, but in one revision that second GETFIELD becomes a GETSTATIC instead?</p>
<p>And if you’re using BCEL’s InstructionFinder, you have the luxury of supertypes like “PushInstruction” and such that encompass several different opcodes (in the failure example above, “FieldInstruction” would have found both GETFIELD and GETSTATIC).</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/writing-a-bot-a-tutorial-of-sorts/168330/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/writing-a-bot-a-tutorial-of-sorts/168330/4</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 02 Jan 2008 09:20:14 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-168330-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/writing-a-bot-a-tutorial-of-sorts/168330.rss">Writing a bot: a tutorial of sorts</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Writing a bot: a tutorial of sorts</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@ripzone Triton]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/ripzone">@ripzone</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Really nice job, hope you continue it.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/writing-a-bot-a-tutorial-of-sorts/168330/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/writing-a-bot-a-tutorial-of-sorts/168330/3</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jan 2008 10:43:36 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-168330-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/writing-a-bot-a-tutorial-of-sorts/168330.rss">Writing a bot: a tutorial of sorts</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Writing a bot: a tutorial of sorts</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@darkblitz darkblitz]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/darkblitz">@darkblitz</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Good tut <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=6" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"> hehe . However, i second that </p><blockquote>First off, don’t care about time. It is the greatest fault of all accuracy to value speed.</blockquote>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/writing-a-bot-a-tutorial-of-sorts/168330/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/writing-a-bot-a-tutorial-of-sorts/168330/2</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Dec 2007 05:40:08 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-168330-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/writing-a-bot-a-tutorial-of-sorts/168330.rss">Writing a bot: a tutorial of sorts</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Writing a bot: a tutorial of sorts</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Silver_Lining Silver Lining]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/silver_lining">@Silver_Lining</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Here I intend to teach the anatomy of a Runescape bot and various methods employed to ‘auto’ on Runescape. I don’t mean to spoon-feed the reader how to write a bot and you shouldn’t expect to come into this knowing nothing about Java and come out with a functional bot written. That would teach you nothing, and education is really all that Runescape client fuckery is good for nowadays. By necessity, I’ll digress from the main point very often because I’ll be branching out over a wide variety of topics. Also, I’m only going to talk about bytecode injection bots. I don’t consider color seeking bots below me, but I really can’t be bothered learning about them or writing one. So… here we go.</p>
<p>Bytecode injection bots<br>
These are the more common breed of modern Runescape bots for a variety of reasons: simplicity, speed, and so on. Once, clients were decompiled, modified, and recompiled to form a bot. Jagex eventually ended this for the fool by adding a basic reflection system. This is easy to get around, but bytecode injection is easier anyway. Bytecode injection is the modification of existing class files to add methods, modify methods, etc. All bots that I have seen complicate the process of loading their modified classes. The simplest way is to pack the bot with the Runescape client and replace the original packed client in the cache with the pretty little modified client. Doing so removes the necessity for glorified class loaders. However, I’ll write on their purpose too, for the sake of completion.</p>
<pre><code>Subtopic 2A) Bytecode: Bytecode, for the purposes here, is what composes a class file. If you don't already have an intimate knowledge of bytecode and intend to write a bytecode injection bot, read the Java class specification and both memorize and cherish every detail. I won't provide a link; Google is more than willing to find it for you. Alternatively, you can read the various tutorials in the Java programming section on bytecode and BCEL. Do not continue reading until you are proficient enough in bytecode to translate raw Java code into bytecode and vice versa.
 Subtopic 2B) Updaters: Those who write bots for Runescape probably are without social lives and only want an updater so they can pretend they have better things to do. I've been guilty of this on many occasions. Updaters are, in my opinion, unnecessary yet very convenient. Don't want to spend a few hours every week updating your bot for the new Runescape build? Updaters are the way to go. First off, don't care about time. It is the greatest fault of all accuracy to value speed. It doesn't matter whether your updating takes a tenth of a second or ten minutes as long as it is accurate. Worrying about speed is another thing I am guilty of, and my creations were exponentially better when I cast off the idea that my accuracy should be sacrificed for e-penis size. Anyhow, updater theory is to find patterns in builds and identify fields based on those patterns. These patterns should not repeat themselves. "ALOAD GETFIELD" is not a good pattern because it's too simple and repeating. On the other hand, "ALOAD GETFIELD PUTFIELD ALOAD GETFIELD LDC (unique number) IADD" is a very good pattern. Use BCEL's InstructionFinder or a similar item to find your patterns. 
</code></pre>
<p>[center]<span class="bbcode-b">Continued when I stop shaking. For the record, triple-brewed coffee is a bad idea.</span>[/center]</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/writing-a-bot-a-tutorial-of-sorts/168330/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/writing-a-bot-a-tutorial-of-sorts/168330/1</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Dec 2007 04:34:39 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-168330-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/writing-a-bot-a-tutorial-of-sorts/168330.rss">Writing a bot: a tutorial of sorts</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
