<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>508/525 Questions</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/508-525-questions/362771</link>
    <description>Hey can you guys help me i&#39;m fairly new and would love to learn some new coding stuff but i&#39;ve searched everywhere and can&#39;t seem to find information on how to do it. Anyways.. The Client and the Source i&#39;m using is a D&#39;bow base and im having trouble with the following.. One is i cannot figure out how to make it so the KBD doesn&#39;t hit through my DFS. Two how do i add portals and other teleportation things like in the magic book or whatever. Three how the heck do i add shops i mean this is the third time i&#39;ve asked this one question and nobody will help me. Fourth how do i edit the specials for weapons. Fifth how would i add more items like weapons, armor, commands, and maybe even customs. Lastly when all is said and done how would i make it so my IP works with the server i&#39;ve post fowarded and change it in no-ip but it always says error when i put in my Ip.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 26 Oct 2010 14:16:04 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Game Development</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/508-525-questions/362771.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>508/525 Questions</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@TempahScape TempahScape]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/tempahscape">@TempahScape</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Well I know how to change the teleports but I dunno how to do the portals as im tryin to find that out myself. Anyway, to do the teleports go to bulby/player and open up magic.java, if your on a palidino76 server like i am then go to src/palidino76/rs2/player and open up magic.java. now when you’ve opened it up do ctrl + F and search varrock, if that doesnt work then try falador or lumbridge etc. then when you’ve got there change the “TeleTo(p, coordx,coordy);” to your coords. to find coords you must be admin/owner of your server and type in ::mypos or ::coords to find them out.</p>
<p>Hope this helped and Good Luck making your 508</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/508-525-questions/362771/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/508-525-questions/362771/2</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 26 Oct 2010 14:16:04 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-362771-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/508-525-questions/362771.rss">508/525 Questions</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>508/525 Questions</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@XxicemanxX XxicemanxX]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/xxicemanxx">@XxicemanxX</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Hey can you guys help me i’m fairly new and would love to learn some new coding stuff but i’ve searched everywhere and can’t seem to find information on how to do it. Anyways… The Client and the Source i’m using is a D’bow base and im having trouble with the following… One is i cannot figure out how to make it so the KBD doesn’t hit through my DFS. Two how do i add portals and other teleportation things like in the magic book or whatever. Three how the heck do i add shops i mean this is the third time i’ve asked this one question and nobody will help me. Fourth how do i edit the specials for weapons. Fifth how would i add more items like weapons, armor, commands, and maybe even customs. Lastly when all is said and done how would i make it so my IP works with the server i’ve post fowarded and change it in no-ip but it always says error when i put in my Ip.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/508-525-questions/362771/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/508-525-questions/362771/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 03 Oct 2010 20:49:32 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-362771-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/508-525-questions/362771.rss">508/525 Questions</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
