<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Runescript</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/runescript/544211</link>
    <description>With the recent release of Old Runescape the developers have been posting a ton of photos of their work. I stumbled across the thread by Leanbow and also the archive of Andrew Gowers notes from 2001. In his notes he outlines a very primitive scripting system which wouldn&#39;t be very hard to implement to be honest.

Notes:
One server cycle is 0.6 seconds, so 100 cycles = 1 minute
Probabilities range from 0=impossible to 256=certain
[hr]
[b]Misc commands[/b]
[table]
    [tr]
        [td]thinkbubble();[/td]
        [td]Should only be called if the player has just triggered a &#39;use&#39; script. Displays a thinkbubble above the players head which contains the object they are currently using. For instance this is used to display the axe above your head when you chop a tree down.[/td]
    [/tr]
    [tr]
        [td]ifmale();[/td]
        [td]Test the player&#39;s gender, useful for getting gender specific language correct in the scripts.[/td]
    [/tr]
    [tr]
        [td]nodefault();[/td]
        [td]Stops the game executing the default action when this script is complete. For example can be used to stop an object from being taken, or a spell being cast.[/td]
    [/tr]
    [tr]
        [td]openshop(shop);[/td]
        [td]Displays the specified shop dialog, and allows the player to buy and sell items. Doing so frees the npc, so no npc specific commands can be used after this point.[/td]
    [/tr]
    [tr]
        [td]displaybalance();[/td]
        [td]Displays the players current bank balance[/td]
    [/tr]
[/table]
[hr]
[b]Control flow based[/b]
[table]
    [tr]
        [td]Delay(delay);[/td]
        [td]Delays both the script and the player for the specified number ofserver cycles[/td]
    [/tr]
    [tr]
        [td]Pause(mindelay, maxdelay);[/td]
        [td]Pauses the script for a random amount of time inbetween the specifiedminimum and maximum. The player is free to do other stuff meanwhile, useful for making trees regrow etc.. Be very careful when using delay orpause, as the player may have logged out meanwhile. Normally this doesn&#39;t matter, but don&#39;t rely on things after it to do anything permament whichaffects the player (such as setting a player variable) as it may be lost.[/td]
    [/tr]
    [tr]
        [td]modpause(mindelay, maxdelay);[/td]
        [td]Similar to the pause command, except the total delay is modified bythe number of players in the game. If more than 60 people are playing, the delay is calculated as: delay=(delay*60)/player-count;[/td]
    [/tr]
    [tr]
        [td]ifrandom(probability);[/td]
        [td]Randomly sets the condition flag to true or false. A probability of0=impossible, and 256=certain[/td]
    [/tr]
    [tr]
        [td]jump(labelname);[/td]
        [td]Jumps to the script block with the trigger &#39;Label,labelname&#39; The otherscript will not return to this one[/td]
    [/tr]
    [tr]
        [td]fork(labelname);[/td]
        [td]Starts the script block with trigger &#39;Label,labelname&#39; running at thesame time as this one! Be careful with this command :-) If the target block has no pause, wait, say, or npcsay commands then will behave like agosub command. (due to non-preemptive multitasking)[/td]
    [/tr]
    [tr]
        [td]end();[/td]
        [td]Terminates processing of the current script block[/td]
    [/tr]
[/table]
[hr]
[b]Chat based[/b]
[table]
    [tr]
        [td]mes(string);[/td]
        [td]Displays the specified message at the bottom of the playerscreen[/td]
    [/tr]
    [tr]
        [td]say(string);[/td]
        [td]Makes the players character say the specified string, all nearbypeople will also see this. The command will then automatically delay the script depending on the length of the string.[/td]
    [/tr]
    [tr]
        [td]multi2(string, label, string, label);[/td]
        [td]Displays a multiple choice menu with 2 items, depending which theplayers chooses the relevant block of script will be called. Note: The player may decide not to choose either item in which case the scriptterminates[/td]
    [/tr]
    [tr]
        [td]multi3(string, label, string, label, string, label);[/td]
        [td]Displays a multiple choice menu with 3 items[/td]
    [/tr]
    [tr]
        [td]multi4(string, label, string, label, string, label, string, label);[/td]
        [td]Displays a multiple choice menu with 4 items[/td]
    [/tr]
[/table]
[hr]
[b]Movement based[/b]
[table]
    [tr]
        [td]changelevel(int level);[/td]
        [td]Moves the player to the specified level, without changing the x and yposition. Level-codes: 0=ground floor, 1=1st floor, 2=2nd floor, 3=basement[/td]
    [/tr]
    [tr]
        [td]changelevelup();[/td]
        [td]Moves the player up one level if possible.[/td]
    [/tr]
    [tr]
        [td]changeleveldown();[/td]
        [td]Moves the player down one level if possible.[/td]
    [/tr]
[/table]
[hr]
[b]Stat based[/b]
[table]
    [tr]
        [td]ifstatrandom(stat, base-probability, top-probability);[/td]
        [td]Like the random command but stat modified, if the stat is 0 thebase-probability is used, if the stat is 100 the top-probability is used. If the stat is inbetween then the 2 values are interpolated.[/td]
    [/tr]
    [tr]
        [td]advancestat(stat, base, exp);[/td]
        [td]Permanently increases the specified stat, and sets the new levels asthe current normal. The equation used is: stat+=base+exp*stat;[/td]
    [/tr]
    [tr]
        [td]addstat(stat, constant, percent);[/td]
        [td]Temporarily adds constant+(current*percent)/100 to the 2nd playersspecified stat. Where current is the current level of the stat[/td]
    [/tr]
    [tr]
        [td]substat(stat, constant, percent);[/td]
        [td]Like addstat, except it subtracts.[/td]
    [/tr]
    [tr]
        [td]healstat(stat, constant, percent);[/td]
        [td]Like addstat, but won&#39;t take the players stat above the normallevel[/td]
    [/tr]
    [tr]
        [td]ifstatup(stat);[/td]
        [td]Sets the condition to true if the players stat is currently above thenormal level, false otherwise[/td]
    [/tr]
    [tr]
        [td]ifstatdown(stat);[/td]
        [td]Sets the condition to true if the players stat is currently below thenormal level, false otherwise[/td]
    [/tr]
    [tr]
        [td]ifstatabove(stat,value);[/td]
        [td]Sets the condition to true if the players stat is above (but not equalto) the specified value, false otherwise[/td]
    [/tr]
    [tr]
        [td]ifstatatleast(stat, variable, value);[/td]
        [td]Sets the condition to true if the players stat is more than or equalto getvar(variable)+value, false otherwise[/td]
    [/tr]
    [tr]
        [td]giveqp(value);[/td]
        [td]Gives the player the specified number of quest points[/td]
    [/tr]
    [tr]
        [td]ifqp(value);[/td]
        [td]Sets the condition to true if the players quest points are more thanor equal to the specified value, false otherwise[/td]
    [/tr]
[/table]
[hr]
[b]Variable based[/b]
[table]
    [tr]
        [td]ifvar(variable, value);[/td]
        [td]Sets the condition flag to true if the variable is equal to thespecified value. Sets false otherwise[/td]
    [/tr]
    [tr]
        [td]ifvarmore(variable, value);[/td]
        [td]Sets the condition flag to true if the variable is greater than (butnot equal to) the specifed value. Sets false otherwise[/td]
    [/tr]
    [tr][td][/td][/tr]
    [tr]
        [td]ifvarless(variable, value);[/td]
        [td]Sets the condition flag to true if the variable is less than (but notequal to) the specifed value. Sets false otherwise[/td]
    [/tr]
    [tr][td][/td][/tr]
    [tr]
        [td]setvar(variable, value);[/td]
        [td]Sets the variable to the specified value. A variable can only hold thevalue 0-127. Always try to zero variables when they are no longer needed to save memory.[/td]
    [/tr]
    [tr]
        [td]addvar(variable, value);[/td]
        [td]Adds the specified amount to the variables value. A variable can onlyhold the value 0-127. [/td]
    [/tr]
    [tr]
        [td]subvar(variable, value);[/td]
        [td]Subtracts the specified amount to the variables value. A variable canonly hold the value 0-127. [/td]
    [/tr]
    [tr]
        [td]randomvar(value);[/td]
        [td]Sets the variable &#39;random&#39; to a random integer between 0 andvalue-1[/td]
    [/tr]
    [tr]
        [td]addbigvar(variable, value);[/td]
        [td]Add the specified value to the variable. A big-variable can holdvalues between 0-268435455[/td]
    [/tr]
    [tr]
        [td]subbigvar(variable, value);[/td]
        [td]Subtracts the specified value from the variable. A big-variable canhold values between 0-268435455[/td]
    [/tr]
    [tr]
        [td]ifbigvarmore(variable, value);[/td]
        [td]Same as ifvarmore except for big-variables[/td]
    [/tr]
[/table]
[hr]
[b]Coordinate based[/b]
These commands all require a map coordinate to operate. The coordinate used can be set using the setcoord command below. If the setcoord command is not used the system will attempt to use the coordinate of the item the player is currently interacting with.
[table]
    [tr]
        [td]setcoord(coordinate);[/td]
        [td]Sets the active coordinate to the specified absolute position. Thecoordinate can only be worked out with the aid of the runescape map editor.[/td]
    [/tr]
    [tr]
        [td]playercoord();[/td]
        [td]Sets the active coordinate to the players current position.[/td]
    [/tr]
    [tr]
        [td]addobject(object, count, time);[/td]
        [td]Adds the specified object at the active coordinate. If the object isstackable - count indicates how many to place in the stack. Time indicates how long in server cycles before the object despawns.[/td]
    [/tr]
    [tr]
        [td]addnpc(npc);[/td]
        [td]Spawns the specified npc at the active coordinate.[/td]
    [/tr]
    [tr]
        [td]addloc(location);[/td]
        [td]Adds the specified location at the active coordinate.[/td]
    [/tr]
    [tr]
        [td]ifblocked();[/td]
        [td]Sets the condition flag to true if the square indicated by theactivate coordinate is currently blocked, sets false otherwise[/td]
    [/tr]
    [tr]
        [td]teleport();[/td]
        [td]Teleports the player to the active coordinate.[/td]
    [/tr]
    [tr][td][/td][/tr]
    [tr]
        [td]showeffect(type);[/td]
        [td]Displays a special effect animation of the specified type at theactive coordinate.[/td]
    [/tr]
[/table]
[hr]
[b]Inventory based[/b]
[table]
    [tr]
        [td]give(object, count);[/td]
        [td]Gives the specified number of the specified object to playersinventory[/td]
    [/tr]
    [tr]
        [td]remove(object, count);[/td]
        [td]Removes the specified number of the specified object from playersinventory (or as many as possible)[/td]
    [/tr]
    [tr]
        [td]ifworn(object);[/td]
        [td]Sets condition flag to true if player is wearing specifiedobject[/td]
    [/tr]
    [tr]
        [td]ifheld(object, count);[/td]
        [td]Sets condition flag to true if player is holding specifiedobject[/td]
    [/tr]
[/table]
[b]The commands below may only be used when player isinteracting with an object in their inventory[/b]
[table]
    [tr]
        [td]sellinv(percentage);[/td]
        [td]Removes the active inventory object from the players inventory, andreplaces it with the specified percentage of it&#39;s value in gold coins[/td]
    [/tr]
    [tr]
        [td]delinv();[/td]
        [td]Deletes the active inventory object from the playersinventory[/td]
    [/tr]
[/table]
[hr]
[b]Object based[/b]
[b]These commands may only be used when a player isinteracting with an object on the ground[/b]
[table]
    [tr]
        [td]ifobjectvisible();[/td]
        [td]Sets the condition code to true if a line of sight can be tracedbetween the player and the object, false otherwise[/td]
    [/tr]
    [tr]
        [td]takeobject();[/td]
        [td]Removes the object from the ground and places it in the playersinventory[/td]
    [/tr]
    [tr]
        [td]delobject();[/td]
        [td]Removes the object from the world[/td]
    [/tr]
[/table]
[hr]
[b]Location based[/b]
[b]These commands may only be used when a player isinteracting with a location[/b]
[table]
    [tr]
        [td]changeloc(location);[/td]
        [td]Changes the location to the new specified location type[/td]
    [/tr]
    [tr]
        [td]upstairs();[/td]
        [td]Moves the player up a level, and adjusts their position horizontallyto account for the stairs[/td]
    [/tr]
    [tr][td][/td][/tr]
    [tr]
        [td]downstairs();[/td]
        [td]Moves the player down a level, and adjusts their position horizontallyto account for the statis[/td]
    [/tr]
    [tr][td][/td][/tr]
    [tr]
        [td]delloc();[/td]
        [td]Removes the location from the world[/td]
    [/tr]
[/table]
[hr]
[b]Boundary based[/b]
[b]These commands may only be used when a player isinteracting with a boundary[/b]
[table]
    [tr]
        [td]changebound(boundary);[/td]
        [td]Changes the boundary to the new specified boundary type[/td]
    [/tr]
    [tr]
        [td]boundaryteleport();[/td]
        [td]Walks the player through the boundary to the opposite side. Useful forlocked doors, and secret pasages.[/td]
    [/tr]
    [tr][td][/td][/tr]
[/table]
[hr]
[b]Npc based[/b]
[table]
    [tr]
        [td]ifnearnpc(npc);[/td]
        [td]Attempt to find a nearby npc of the type specified. Sets the conditionflag to true if sucessful. If succesful the player is marked as interacting with the npc so the other npc commands can also be used.[/td]
    [/tr]
    [tr]
        [td]ifnearvisnpc(npc);[/td]
        [td]Simliar to ifnearnpc, except the npc must be within 8 squares, andthere must be a line of sight between the player and npc for the command to succeed.[/td]
    [/tr]
[/table]
[b]The commands below may only be used when player isinteracting with an npc[/b]
[table]
    [tr]
        [td]npcsay(string);[/td]
        [td]Makes the npc say the specified string, all nearby people will alsosee this. The command will then automatically delay the script depending on the length of the string.[/td]
    [/tr]
    [tr]
        [td]npcbusy();[/td]
        [td]Sets the npc to busy, and stops it walking around. Not normallynecessary as the system attempts to trigger this automatically.[/td]
    [/tr]
    [tr]
        [td]npcunbusy();[/td]
        [td]Sets the npc to unbusy, and allows it to walk around again. Notnormally necessary as the system attempt to trigger this automatically.[/td]
    [/tr]
    [tr][td][/td][/tr]
    [tr]
        [td]shootnpc(projectile);[/td]
        [td]Fires a projectile at the npc[/td]
    [/tr]
    [tr][td][/td][/tr]
    [tr]
        [td]npcattack();[/td]
        [td]Causes the npcs to pursue and attack the player[/td]
    [/tr]
    [tr]
        [td]ifnpcvisible();[/td]
        [td]Sets the condition code to true if a line of sight can be tracedbetween the player and npc[/td]
    [/tr]
    [tr][td][/td][/tr]
    [tr]
        [td]addnpcstat(stat,constant,percent);[/td]
        [td]Temporarily adds constant+(current*percent)/100 to the npcs specifiedstat[/td]
    [/tr]
    [tr][td][/td][/tr]
    [tr]
        [td]subnpcstat(stat,constant,percent);[/td]
        [td]Like addnpc stat, except it subtracts[/td]
    [/tr]
    [tr][td][/td][/tr]
    [tr]
        [td]healnpcstat(stat,constant,percent);[/td]
        [td]Like addnpc stat, but won&#39;t take npcs stat above the normal level[/td]
    [/tr]
    [tr][td][/td][/tr]
    [tr]
        [td]ifnpcstatup(stat);[/td]
        [td]Sets the condition to true if the npcs specified stat is currentlyabove the normal level, false otherwise[/td]
    [/tr]
    [tr]
        [td]ifnpcstatdown(stat);[/td]
        [td]Sets the condition to true if the npcs specified stat is currentlybelow the normal level, false otherwise[/td]
    [/tr]
    [tr]
        [td]delnpc();[/td]
        [td]Removes the npc from the world[/td]
    [/tr]
    [tr]
        [td]changenpc(npc);[/td]
        [td]Changes the npc into a the new npc type specified![/td]
    [/tr]
    [tr]
        [td]npcretreat(time);[/td]
        [td]Causes the npc to run away from the player for the specified number ofserver cycles[/td]
    [/tr]
[/table]
[hr]
[b]Other player based[/b]
[b]These commands may only be used when a player isinteracting with another player.[/b]
[table]
    [tr]
        [td]addplaystat(stat, constant, percent);[/td]
        [td]Temporarily adds constant+(current*percent)/100 to the 2nd playersspecified stat. Where current is the current level of the stat[/td]
    [/tr]
    [tr]
        [td]subplaystat(stat, constant, percent);[/td]
        [td]Like addplaystat, except it subtracts.[/td]
    [/tr]
    [tr]
        [td]healplaystat(stat, constant, percent);[/td]
        [td]Like addplaystat, but won&#39;t take the players stat above the normallevel[/td]
    [/tr]
    [tr]
        [td]ifplaystatup(stat);[/td]
        [td]Sets the condition to true if the 2nd players stat is currently abovethe normal level, false otherwise[/td]
    [/tr]
    [tr]
        [td]ifplaystatdown(stat)[/td]
        [td]Sets the condition to true if the 2nd players stat is currently belowthe normal level, false otherwise[/td]
    [/tr]
    [tr]
        [td]omes(string);[/td]
        [td]Displays a message on the 2nd players screen[/td]
    [/tr]
    [tr]
        [td]ifplayervisible();[/td]
        [td]Sets the condition code to true if a line of sight can be tracedbetween the 2 players, false otherwise[/td]
    [/tr]
    [tr]
        [td]shootplayer(projectile);[/td]
        [td]Fires a projectile at the 2nd player[/td]
    [/tr]
[/table]

Modern Runescript:

[img]https://pbs.twimg.com/media/BpN1MapCYAA-Rvv.png:large[/img]
[img]https://pbs.twimg.com/media/BpdZ9mWIYAAYoLj.png:large[/img]
[img]https://pbs.twimg.com/media/BpIV0yIIUAAsVmu.png:large[/img]
[img]http://i.imgur.com/DRJBAXC.png[/img]
[img]http://i.imgur.com/heXbHMP.png[/img]

A lot different :P, not entirely sure how enumerations are handled. The enum command seems to have two type declarations then two parameters.

% - variable
$ - script variable
~ - gosub
@ - jump
&lt;&gt; - evaluate

The enumerations probably have something to do with how the scripts in the client captured variables (could return string/integer).</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 15 Jul 2014 21:11:17 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/runescript/544211.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Runescript</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@artem543 artem543]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/artem543">@artem543</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Is it released or not?  <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/expressionless.png?v=5" title=":expressionless:" class="emoji" alt=":expressionless:"> I guess no lol.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/runescript/544211/23">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/runescript/544211/23</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 15 Jul 2014 21:11:17 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-544211-23</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/runescript/544211.rss">Runescript</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Runescript</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Ambokile Ambokile]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/ambokile">@Ambokile</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“AtomicInt_, post:21, topic:544211”][quote author=Ambokile link=topic=663093.msg4431764#msg4431764 date=1403553907]<br>
When did they release “Old Runescape”? Anyone got a link?<br>
[/quote]</p>
<p><a href="http://oldschool.runescape.com/" class="onebox" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">http://oldschool.runescape.com/</a></p>
<p>Been out for over a year…[/quote]</p>
<p>I thought he meant that they’d released the source code.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/runescript/544211/22">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/runescript/544211/22</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 14 Jul 2014 20:02:20 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-544211-22</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/runescript/544211.rss">Runescript</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Runescript</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@ExtremeX-Scape Ryley]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/extremex-scape">@ExtremeX-Scape</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote" data-post="7" data-topic="544211">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/sinisoul/40/5_e05bb34c421432ee4d40de30c10af3e5.png" class="avatar"> sinisoul:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>locale? location?</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Gower stated what we call ‘objects’ are locations.</p>
<aside class="quote" data-post="14" data-topic="544211">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/ambokile/40/5_e05bb34c421432ee4d40de30c10af3e5.png" class="avatar"> Ambokile:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>When did they release “Old Runescape”? Anyone got a link?</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p><a href="http://oldschool.runescape.com/" class="onebox" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">http://oldschool.runescape.com/</a></p>
<p>Been out for over a year…</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/runescript/544211/21">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/runescript/544211/21</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 03 Jul 2014 02:54:23 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-544211-21</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/runescript/544211.rss">Runescript</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Runescript</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@sorecheeny sorecheeny]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/sorecheeny">@sorecheeny</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>This is so cool.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/runescript/544211/20">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/runescript/544211/20</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 03 Jul 2014 02:49:31 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-544211-20</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/runescript/544211.rss">Runescript</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Runescript</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Clawz_fury lare69]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/clawz_fury">@Clawz_fury</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>looks ugly as hell</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/runescript/544211/19">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/runescript/544211/19</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 30 Jun 2014 13:38:34 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-544211-19</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/runescript/544211.rss">Runescript</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Runescript</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@sinisoul sini]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/sinisoul">@sinisoul</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“Pure_, post:17, topic:544211”][quote author=arham 4 link=topic=663093.msg4431770#msg4431770 date=1403555444]<br>
Lel, jagex using ints as booleans.</p>
<p><img src="http://i.imgur.com/heXbHMP.png" alt width="" height=""></p>
<p>teh first line.<br>
[/quote]Protip: a boolean is basically an integer (wrapped in a specialized class, ie Boolean)… Bits 1/0 true/false.</p>
<p>tldr ur retarded af[/quote]</p>
<p>Fixed.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/runescript/544211/18">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/runescript/544211/18</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 24 Jun 2014 02:37:32 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-544211-18</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/runescript/544211.rss">Runescript</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Runescript</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@pure2ownage Pure_]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/pure2ownage">@pure2ownage</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“arham 4, post:15, topic:544211”]Lel, jagex using ints as booleans.</p>
<p><img src="http://i.imgur.com/heXbHMP.png" alt width="" height=""></p>
<p>teh first line.[/quote]Protip: a boolean is basically an integer (wrapped in a specialized class, ie Boolean)… Bits 1/0 true/false.</p>
<p>tldr ur retarded</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/runescript/544211/17">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/runescript/544211/17</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 23 Jun 2014 21:00:35 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-544211-17</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/runescript/544211.rss">Runescript</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Runescript</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Ambokile Ambokile]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/ambokile">@Ambokile</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“arham 4, post:15, topic:544211”]Lel, jagex using ints as booleans.</p>
<p><img src="http://i.imgur.com/heXbHMP.png" alt width="" height=""></p>
<p>teh first line.[/quote]</p>
<p>Or map_members is an integer that stores the amount of members, and they’re checking if it is equal to 0 <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/wink.png?v=5" title=":wink:" class="emoji" alt=":wink:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/runescript/544211/16">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/runescript/544211/16</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 23 Jun 2014 20:33:01 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-544211-16</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/runescript/544211.rss">Runescript</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Runescript</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@arham_4 arham 4]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/arham_4">@arham_4</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Lel, jagex using ints as booleans.</p>
<p><img src="http://i.imgur.com/heXbHMP.png" alt width="" height=""></p>
<p>teh first line.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/runescript/544211/15">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/runescript/544211/15</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 23 Jun 2014 20:30:44 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-544211-15</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/runescript/544211.rss">Runescript</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Runescript</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Ambokile Ambokile]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/ambokile">@Ambokile</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>When did they release “Old Runescape”? Anyone got a link?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/runescript/544211/14">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/runescript/544211/14</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 23 Jun 2014 20:05:07 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-544211-14</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/runescript/544211.rss">Runescript</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Runescript</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@vortex vortex]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/vortex">@vortex</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>whens interpreter</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/runescript/544211/13">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/runescript/544211/13</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 23 Jun 2014 19:50:41 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-544211-13</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/runescript/544211.rss">Runescript</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Runescript</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@sppt sppt]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/sppt">@sppt</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>For some reason all those commands remind me heavily of scripting in the early days with bots like AR and Slave ^</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/runescript/544211/12">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/runescript/544211/12</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 23 Jun 2014 12:48:20 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-544211-12</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/runescript/544211.rss">Runescript</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Runescript</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@vortex vortex]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/vortex">@vortex</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Notes:<br>
One server cycle is 0.6 seconds, so 100 cycles = 1 minute<br>
Probabilities range from 0=impossible to 256=certain<br>
[hr]<br>
<span class="bbcode-b">Misc commands</span><br>
[table]<br>
[tr]<br>
[td]thinkbubble();[/td]<br>
[td]Should only be called if the player has just triggered a ‘use’ script. Displays a thinkbubble above the players head which contains the object they are currently using. For instance this is used to display the axe above your head when you chop a tree down.[/td]<br>
[/tr]<br>
[tr]<br>
[td]ifmale();[/td]<br>
[td]Test the player’s gender, useful for getting gender specific language correct in the scripts.[/td]<br>
[/tr]<br>
[tr]<br>
[td]nodefault();[/td]<br>
[td]Stops the game executing the default action when this script is complete. For example can be used to stop an object from being taken, or a spell being cast.[/td]<br>
[/tr]<br>
[tr]<br>
[td]openshop(shop);[/td]<br>
[td]Displays the specified shop dialog, and allows the player to buy and sell items. Doing so frees the npc, so no npc specific commands can be used after this point.[/td]<br>
[/tr]<br>
[tr]<br>
[td]displaybalance();[/td]<br>
[td]Displays the players current bank balance[/td]<br>
[/tr]<br>
[/table]<br>
[hr]<br>
<span class="bbcode-b">Control flow based</span><br>
[table]<br>
[tr]<br>
[td]Delay(delay);[/td]<br>
[td]Delays both the script and the player for the specified number ofserver cycles[/td]<br>
[/tr]<br>
[tr]<br>
[td]Pause(mindelay, maxdelay);[/td]<br>
[td]Pauses the script for a random amount of time inbetween the specifiedminimum and maximum. The player is free to do other stuff meanwhile, useful for making trees regrow etc… Be very careful when using delay orpause, as the player may have logged out meanwhile. Normally this doesn’t matter, but don’t rely on things after it to do anything permament whichaffects the player (such as setting a player variable) as it may be lost.[/td]<br>
[/tr]<br>
[tr]<br>
[td]modpause(mindelay, maxdelay);[/td]<br>
[td]Similar to the pause command, except the total delay is modified bythe number of players in the game. If more than 60 people are playing, the delay is calculated as: delay=(delay<em>60)/player-count;[/td]<br>
[/tr]<br>
[tr]<br>
[td]ifrandom(probability);[/td]<br>
[td]Randomly sets the condition flag to true or false. A probability of0=impossible, and 256=certain[/td]<br>
[/tr]<br>
[tr]<br>
[td]jump(labelname);[/td]<br>
[td]Jumps to the script block with the trigger ‘Label,labelname’ The otherscript will not return to this one[/td]<br>
[/tr]<br>
[tr]<br>
[td]fork(labelname);[/td]<br>
[td]Starts the script block with trigger ‘Label,labelname’ running at thesame time as this one! Be careful with this command <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=5" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"> If the target block has no pause, wait, say, or npcsay commands then will behave like agosub command. (due to non-preemptive multitasking)[/td]<br>
[/tr]<br>
[tr]<br>
[td]end();[/td]<br>
[td]Terminates processing of the current script block[/td]<br>
[/tr]<br>
[/table]<br>
[hr]<br>
<span class="bbcode-b">Chat based</span><br>
[table]<br>
[tr]<br>
[td]mes(string);[/td]<br>
[td]Displays the specified message at the bottom of the playerscreen[/td]<br>
[/tr]<br>
[tr]<br>
[td]say(string);[/td]<br>
[td]Makes the players character say the specified string, all nearbypeople will also see this. The command will then automatically delay the script depending on the length of the string.[/td]<br>
[/tr]<br>
[tr]<br>
[td]multi2(string, label, string, label);[/td]<br>
[td]Displays a multiple choice menu with 2 items, depending which theplayers chooses the relevant block of script will be called. Note: The player may decide not to choose either item in which case the scriptterminates[/td]<br>
[/tr]<br>
[tr]<br>
[td]multi3(string, label, string, label, string, label);[/td]<br>
[td]Displays a multiple choice menu with 3 items[/td]<br>
[/tr]<br>
[tr]<br>
[td]multi4(string, label, string, label, string, label, string, label);[/td]<br>
[td]Displays a multiple choice menu with 4 items[/td]<br>
[/tr]<br>
[/table]<br>
[hr]<br>
<span class="bbcode-b">Movement based</span><br>
[table]<br>
[tr]<br>
[td]changelevel(int level);[/td]<br>
[td]Moves the player to the specified level, without changing the x and yposition. Level-codes: 0=ground floor, 1=1st floor, 2=2nd floor, 3=basement[/td]<br>
[/tr]<br>
[tr]<br>
[td]changelevelup();[/td]<br>
[td]Moves the player up one level if possible.[/td]<br>
[/tr]<br>
[tr]<br>
[td]changeleveldown();[/td]<br>
[td]Moves the player down one level if possible.[/td]<br>
[/tr]<br>
[/table]<br>
[hr]<br>
<span class="bbcode-b">Stat based</span><br>
[table]<br>
[tr]<br>
[td]ifstatrandom(stat, base-probability, top-probability);[/td]<br>
[td]Like the random command but stat modified, if the stat is 0 thebase-probability is used, if the stat is 100 the top-probability is used. If the stat is inbetween then the 2 values are interpolated.[/td]<br>
[/tr]<br>
[tr]<br>
[td]advancestat(stat, base, exp);[/td]<br>
[td]Permanently increases the specified stat, and sets the new levels asthe current normal. The equation used is: stat+=base+exp</em>stat;[/td]<br>
[/tr]<br>
[tr]<br>
[td]addstat(stat, constant, percent);[/td]<br>
[td]Temporarily adds constant+(current<em>percent)/100 to the 2nd playersspecified stat. Where current is the current level of the stat[/td]<br>
[/tr]<br>
[tr]<br>
[td]substat(stat, constant, percent);[/td]<br>
[td]Like addstat, except it subtracts.[/td]<br>
[/tr]<br>
[tr]<br>
[td]healstat(stat, constant, percent);[/td]<br>
[td]Like addstat, but won’t take the players stat above the normallevel[/td]<br>
[/tr]<br>
[tr]<br>
[td]ifstatup(stat);[/td]<br>
[td]Sets the condition to true if the players stat is currently above thenormal level, false otherwise[/td]<br>
[/tr]<br>
[tr]<br>
[td]ifstatdown(stat);[/td]<br>
[td]Sets the condition to true if the players stat is currently below thenormal level, false otherwise[/td]<br>
[/tr]<br>
[tr]<br>
[td]ifstatabove(stat,value);[/td]<br>
[td]Sets the condition to true if the players stat is above (but not equalto) the specified value, false otherwise[/td]<br>
[/tr]<br>
[tr]<br>
[td]ifstatatleast(stat, variable, value);[/td]<br>
[td]Sets the condition to true if the players stat is more than or equalto getvar(variable)+value, false otherwise[/td]<br>
[/tr]<br>
[tr]<br>
[td]giveqp(value);[/td]<br>
[td]Gives the player the specified number of quest points[/td]<br>
[/tr]<br>
[tr]<br>
[td]ifqp(value);[/td]<br>
[td]Sets the condition to true if the players quest points are more thanor equal to the specified value, false otherwise[/td]<br>
[/tr]<br>
[/table]<br>
[hr]<br>
<span class="bbcode-b">Variable based</span><br>
[table]<br>
[tr]<br>
[td]ifvar(variable, value);[/td]<br>
[td]Sets the condition flag to true if the variable is equal to thespecified value. Sets false otherwise[/td]<br>
[/tr]<br>
[tr]<br>
[td]ifvarmore(variable, value);[/td]<br>
[td]Sets the condition flag to true if the variable is greater than (butnot equal to) the specifed value. Sets false otherwise[/td]<br>
[/tr]<br>
[tr][td][/td][/tr]<br>
[tr]<br>
[td]ifvarless(variable, value);[/td]<br>
[td]Sets the condition flag to true if the variable is less than (but notequal to) the specifed value. Sets false otherwise[/td]<br>
[/tr]<br>
[tr][td][/td][/tr]<br>
[tr]<br>
[td]setvar(variable, value);[/td]<br>
[td]Sets the variable to the specified value. A variable can only hold thevalue 0-127. Always try to zero variables when they are no longer needed to save memory.[/td]<br>
[/tr]<br>
[tr]<br>
[td]addvar(variable, value);[/td]<br>
[td]Adds the specified amount to the variables value. A variable can onlyhold the value 0-127. [/td]<br>
[/tr]<br>
[tr]<br>
[td]subvar(variable, value);[/td]<br>
[td]Subtracts the specified amount to the variables value. A variable canonly hold the value 0-127. [/td]<br>
[/tr]<br>
[tr]<br>
[td]randomvar(value);[/td]<br>
[td]Sets the variable ‘random’ to a random integer between 0 andvalue-1[/td]<br>
[/tr]<br>
[tr]<br>
[td]addbigvar(variable, value);[/td]<br>
[td]Add the specified value to the variable. A big-variable can holdvalues between 0-268435455[/td]<br>
[/tr]<br>
[tr]<br>
[td]subbigvar(variable, value);[/td]<br>
[td]Subtracts the specified value from the variable. A big-variable canhold values between 0-268435455[/td]<br>
[/tr]<br>
[tr]<br>
[td]ifbigvarmore(variable, value);[/td]<br>
[td]Same as ifvarmore except for big-variables[/td]<br>
[/tr]<br>
[/table]<br>
[hr]<br>
<span class="bbcode-b">Coordinate based</span><br>
These commands all require a map coordinate to operate. The coordinate used can be set using the setcoord command below. If the setcoord command is not used the system will attempt to use the coordinate of the item the player is currently interacting with.<br>
[table]<br>
[tr]<br>
[td]setcoord(coordinate);[/td]<br>
[td]Sets the active coordinate to the specified absolute position. Thecoordinate can only be worked out with the aid of the runescape map editor.[/td]<br>
[/tr]<br>
[tr]<br>
[td]playercoord();[/td]<br>
[td]Sets the active coordinate to the players current position.[/td]<br>
[/tr]<br>
[tr]<br>
[td]addobject(object, count, time);[/td]<br>
[td]Adds the specified object at the active coordinate. If the object isstackable - count indicates how many to place in the stack. Time indicates how long in server cycles before the object despawns.[/td]<br>
[/tr]<br>
[tr]<br>
[td]addnpc(npc);[/td]<br>
[td]Spawns the specified npc at the active coordinate.[/td]<br>
[/tr]<br>
[tr]<br>
[td]addloc(location);[/td]<br>
[td]Adds the specified location at the active coordinate.[/td]<br>
[/tr]<br>
[tr]<br>
[td]ifblocked();[/td]<br>
[td]Sets the condition flag to true if the square indicated by theactivate coordinate is currently blocked, sets false otherwise[/td]<br>
[/tr]<br>
[tr]<br>
[td]teleport();[/td]<br>
[td]Teleports the player to the active coordinate.[/td]<br>
[/tr]<br>
[tr][td][/td][/tr]<br>
[tr]<br>
[td]showeffect(type);[/td]<br>
[td]Displays a special effect animation of the specified type at theactive coordinate.[/td]<br>
[/tr]<br>
[/table]<br>
[hr]<br>
<span class="bbcode-b">Inventory based</span><br>
[table]<br>
[tr]<br>
[td]give(object, count);[/td]<br>
[td]Gives the specified number of the specified object to playersinventory[/td]<br>
[/tr]<br>
[tr]<br>
[td]remove(object, count);[/td]<br>
[td]Removes the specified number of the specified object from playersinventory (or as many as possible)[/td]<br>
[/tr]<br>
[tr]<br>
[td]ifworn(object);[/td]<br>
[td]Sets condition flag to true if player is wearing specifiedobject[/td]<br>
[/tr]<br>
[tr]<br>
[td]ifheld(object, count);[/td]<br>
[td]Sets condition flag to true if player is holding specifiedobject[/td]<br>
[/tr]<br>
[/table]<br>
<span class="bbcode-b">The commands below may only be used when player isinteracting with an object in their inventory</span><br>
[table]<br>
[tr]<br>
[td]sellinv(percentage);[/td]<br>
[td]Removes the active inventory object from the players inventory, andreplaces it with the specified percentage of it’s value in gold coins[/td]<br>
[/tr]<br>
[tr]<br>
[td]delinv();[/td]<br>
[td]Deletes the active inventory object from the playersinventory[/td]<br>
[/tr]<br>
[/table]<br>
[hr]<br>
<span class="bbcode-b">Object based</span><br>
<span class="bbcode-b">These commands may only be used when a player isinteracting with an object on the ground</span><br>
[table]<br>
[tr]<br>
[td]ifobjectvisible();[/td]<br>
[td]Sets the condition code to true if a line of sight can be tracedbetween the player and the object, false otherwise[/td]<br>
[/tr]<br>
[tr]<br>
[td]takeobject();[/td]<br>
[td]Removes the object from the ground and places it in the playersinventory[/td]<br>
[/tr]<br>
[tr]<br>
[td]delobject();[/td]<br>
[td]Removes the object from the world[/td]<br>
[/tr]<br>
[/table]<br>
[hr]<br>
<span class="bbcode-b">Location based</span><br>
<span class="bbcode-b">These commands may only be used when a player isinteracting with a location</span><br>
[table]<br>
[tr]<br>
[td]changeloc(location);[/td]<br>
[td]Changes the location to the new specified location type[/td]<br>
[/tr]<br>
[tr]<br>
[td]upstairs();[/td]<br>
[td]Moves the player up a level, and adjusts their position horizontallyto account for the stairs[/td]<br>
[/tr]<br>
[tr][td][/td][/tr]<br>
[tr]<br>
[td]downstairs();[/td]<br>
[td]Moves the player down a level, and adjusts their position horizontallyto account for the statis[/td]<br>
[/tr]<br>
[tr][td][/td][/tr]<br>
[tr]<br>
[td]delloc();[/td]<br>
[td]Removes the location from the world[/td]<br>
[/tr]<br>
[/table]<br>
[hr]<br>
<span class="bbcode-b">Boundary based</span><br>
<span class="bbcode-b">These commands may only be used when a player isinteracting with a boundary</span><br>
[table]<br>
[tr]<br>
[td]changebound(boundary);[/td]<br>
[td]Changes the boundary to the new specified boundary type[/td]<br>
[/tr]<br>
[tr]<br>
[td]boundaryteleport();[/td]<br>
[td]Walks the player through the boundary to the opposite side. Useful forlocked doors, and secret pasages.[/td]<br>
[/tr]<br>
[tr][td][/td][/tr]<br>
[/table]<br>
[hr]<br>
<span class="bbcode-b">Npc based</span><br>
[table]<br>
[tr]<br>
[td]ifnearnpc(npc);[/td]<br>
[td]Attempt to find a nearby npc of the type specified. Sets the conditionflag to true if sucessful. If succesful the player is marked as interacting with the npc so the other npc commands can also be used.[/td]<br>
[/tr]<br>
[tr]<br>
[td]ifnearvisnpc(npc);[/td]<br>
[td]Simliar to ifnearnpc, except the npc must be within 8 squares, andthere must be a line of sight between the player and npc for the command to succeed.[/td]<br>
[/tr]<br>
[/table]<br>
<span class="bbcode-b">The commands below may only be used when player isinteracting with an npc</span><br>
[table]<br>
[tr]<br>
[td]npcsay(string);[/td]<br>
[td]Makes the npc say the specified string, all nearby people will alsosee this. The command will then automatically delay the script depending on the length of the string.[/td]<br>
[/tr]<br>
[tr]<br>
[td]npcbusy();[/td]<br>
[td]Sets the npc to busy, and stops it walking around. Not normallynecessary as the system attempts to trigger this automatically.[/td]<br>
[/tr]<br>
[tr]<br>
[td]npcunbusy();[/td]<br>
[td]Sets the npc to unbusy, and allows it to walk around again. Notnormally necessary as the system attempt to trigger this automatically.[/td]<br>
[/tr]<br>
[tr][td][/td][/tr]<br>
[tr]<br>
[td]shootnpc(projectile);[/td]<br>
[td]Fires a projectile at the npc[/td]<br>
[/tr]<br>
[tr][td][/td][/tr]<br>
[tr]<br>
[td]npcattack();[/td]<br>
[td]Causes the npcs to pursue and attack the player[/td]<br>
[/tr]<br>
[tr]<br>
[td]ifnpcvisible();[/td]<br>
[td]Sets the condition code to true if a line of sight can be tracedbetween the player and npc[/td]<br>
[/tr]<br>
[tr][td][/td][/tr]<br>
[tr]<br>
[td]addnpcstat(stat,constant,percent);[/td]<br>
[td]Temporarily adds constant+(current</em>percent)/100 to the npcs specifiedstat[/td]<br>
[/tr]<br>
[tr][td][/td][/tr]<br>
[tr]<br>
[td]subnpcstat(stat,constant,percent);[/td]<br>
[td]Like addnpc stat, except it subtracts[/td]<br>
[/tr]<br>
[tr][td][/td][/tr]<br>
[tr]<br>
[td]healnpcstat(stat,constant,percent);[/td]<br>
[td]Like addnpc stat, but won’t take npcs stat above the normal level[/td]<br>
[/tr]<br>
[tr][td][/td][/tr]<br>
[tr]<br>
[td]ifnpcstatup(stat);[/td]<br>
[td]Sets the condition to true if the npcs specified stat is currentlyabove the normal level, false otherwise[/td]<br>
[/tr]<br>
[tr]<br>
[td]ifnpcstatdown(stat);[/td]<br>
[td]Sets the condition to true if the npcs specified stat is currentlybelow the normal level, false otherwise[/td]<br>
[/tr]<br>
[tr]<br>
[td]delnpc();[/td]<br>
[td]Removes the npc from the world[/td]<br>
[/tr]<br>
[tr]<br>
[td]changenpc(npc);[/td]<br>
[td]Changes the npc into a the new npc type specified![/td]<br>
[/tr]<br>
[tr]<br>
[td]npcretreat(time);[/td]<br>
[td]Causes the npc to run away from the player for the specified number ofserver cycles[/td]<br>
[/tr]<br>
[/table]<br>
[hr]<br>
<span class="bbcode-b">Other player based</span><br>
<span class="bbcode-b">These commands may only be used when a player isinteracting with another player.</span><br>
[table]<br>
[tr]<br>
[td]addplaystat(stat, constant, percent);[/td]<br>
[td]Temporarily adds constant+(current*percent)/100 to the 2nd playersspecified stat. Where current is the current level of the stat[/td]<br>
[/tr]<br>
[tr]<br>
[td]subplaystat(stat, constant, percent);[/td]<br>
[td]Like addplaystat, except it subtracts.[/td]<br>
[/tr]<br>
[tr]<br>
[td]healplaystat(stat, constant, percent);[/td]<br>
[td]Like addplaystat, but won’t take the players stat above the normallevel[/td]<br>
[/tr]<br>
[tr]<br>
[td]ifplaystatup(stat);[/td]<br>
[td]Sets the condition to true if the 2nd players stat is currently abovethe normal level, false otherwise[/td]<br>
[/tr]<br>
[tr]<br>
[td]ifplaystatdown(stat)[/td]<br>
[td]Sets the condition to true if the 2nd players stat is currently belowthe normal level, false otherwise[/td]<br>
[/tr]<br>
[tr]<br>
[td]omes(string);[/td]<br>
[td]Displays a message on the 2nd players screen[/td]<br>
[/tr]<br>
[tr]<br>
[td]ifplayervisible();[/td]<br>
[td]Sets the condition code to true if a line of sight can be tracedbetween the 2 players, false otherwise[/td]<br>
[/tr]<br>
[tr]<br>
[td]shootplayer(projectile);[/td]<br>
[td]Fires a projectile at the 2nd player[/td]<br>
[/tr]<br>
[/table]</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/runescript/544211/11">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/runescript/544211/11</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 23 Jun 2014 11:55:05 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-544211-11</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/runescript/544211.rss">Runescript</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Runescript</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Lin Lin]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/lin">@Lin</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“asshole_rule, post:5, topic:544211”]ugh looks so messy and gross to look at</p>
<p>what does loc actually stand for anyway?[/quote]Local object I believe.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/runescript/544211/10">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/runescript/544211/10</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 23 Jun 2014 01:26:32 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-544211-10</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/runescript/544211.rss">Runescript</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Runescript</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Death_Style Death Style]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/death_style">@Death_Style</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Well this is disappointing.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/runescript/544211/9">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/runescript/544211/9</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 22 Jun 2014 22:40:07 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-544211-9</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/runescript/544211.rss">Runescript</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Runescript</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@imthenull imthenull]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/imthenull">@imthenull</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I have been interested in RuneScript for quite a while, mainly just wanting to know what it looks like. It’s really quite ugly, but still a pretty cool concept… It would be pretty cool if jagex released a version of it for the public to play with.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/runescript/544211/8">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/runescript/544211/8</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 22 Jun 2014 22:19:34 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-544211-8</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/runescript/544211.rss">Runescript</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Runescript</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@sinisoul sini]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/sinisoul">@sinisoul</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>locale? location?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/runescript/544211/7">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/runescript/544211/7</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 22 Jun 2014 21:41:58 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-544211-7</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/runescript/544211.rss">Runescript</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Runescript</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Ashi Ashi]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/ashi">@Ashi</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote" data-post="3" data-topic="544211">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/sinisoul/40/5_e05bb34c421432ee4d40de30c10af3e5.png" class="avatar"> sinisoul:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Its based off a legacy system. Btw ‘loc’ is object, ‘obj’ is item.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>That naming is so misleading omg!</p>
<p>I really doubt that they have anything good right now anyway.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/runescript/544211/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/runescript/544211/6</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 22 Jun 2014 21:28:37 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-544211-6</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/runescript/544211.rss">Runescript</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Runescript</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@asshole_rule asshole_rule]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/asshole_rule">@asshole_rule</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>ugh looks so messy and gross to look at</p>
<p>what does loc actually stand for anyway?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/runescript/544211/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/runescript/544211/5</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 22 Jun 2014 21:19:07 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-544211-5</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/runescript/544211.rss">Runescript</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Runescript</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@pure2ownage Pure_]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/pure2ownage">@pure2ownage</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Yeah the legacy aspect definitely shows off, I think it’s lacking in some features (perhaps a good alternative to mass if-else would be nice). Some of the syntax is meh too.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/runescript/544211/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/runescript/544211/4</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 22 Jun 2014 21:01:39 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-544211-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/runescript/544211.rss">Runescript</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Runescript</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@sinisoul sini]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/sinisoul">@sinisoul</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Its based off a legacy system. Btw ‘loc’ is object, ‘obj’ is item.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/runescript/544211/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/runescript/544211/3</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 22 Jun 2014 20:42:40 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-544211-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/runescript/544211.rss">Runescript</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Runescript</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Ashi Ashi]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/ashi">@Ashi</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>And this was meant so Jagex could easily add content? It looks ugly.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/runescript/544211/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/runescript/544211/2</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 22 Jun 2014 20:15:11 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-544211-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/runescript/544211.rss">Runescript</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Runescript</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@sinisoul sini]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/sinisoul">@sinisoul</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>With the recent release of Old Runescape the developers have been posting a ton of photos of their work. I stumbled across the thread by Leanbow and also the archive of Andrew Gowers notes from 2001. In his notes he outlines a very primitive scripting system which wouldn’t be very hard to implement to be honest.</p>
<p>Notes:<br>
One server cycle is 0.6 seconds, so 100 cycles = 1 minute<br>
Probabilities range from 0=impossible to 256=certain<br>
[hr]<br>
<span class="bbcode-b">Misc commands</span><br>
[table]<br>
[tr]<br>
[td]thinkbubble();[/td]<br>
[td]Should only be called if the player has just triggered a ‘use’ script. Displays a thinkbubble above the players head which contains the object they are currently using. For instance this is used to display the axe above your head when you chop a tree down.[/td]<br>
[/tr]<br>
[tr]<br>
[td]ifmale();[/td]<br>
[td]Test the player’s gender, useful for getting gender specific language correct in the scripts.[/td]<br>
[/tr]<br>
[tr]<br>
[td]nodefault();[/td]<br>
[td]Stops the game executing the default action when this script is complete. For example can be used to stop an object from being taken, or a spell being cast.[/td]<br>
[/tr]<br>
[tr]<br>
[td]openshop(shop);[/td]<br>
[td]Displays the specified shop dialog, and allows the player to buy and sell items. Doing so frees the npc, so no npc specific commands can be used after this point.[/td]<br>
[/tr]<br>
[tr]<br>
[td]displaybalance();[/td]<br>
[td]Displays the players current bank balance[/td]<br>
[/tr]<br>
[/table]<br>
[hr]<br>
<span class="bbcode-b">Control flow based</span><br>
[table]<br>
[tr]<br>
[td]Delay(delay);[/td]<br>
[td]Delays both the script and the player for the specified number ofserver cycles[/td]<br>
[/tr]<br>
[tr]<br>
[td]Pause(mindelay, maxdelay);[/td]<br>
[td]Pauses the script for a random amount of time inbetween the specifiedminimum and maximum. The player is free to do other stuff meanwhile, useful for making trees regrow etc… Be very careful when using delay orpause, as the player may have logged out meanwhile. Normally this doesn’t matter, but don’t rely on things after it to do anything permament whichaffects the player (such as setting a player variable) as it may be lost.[/td]<br>
[/tr]<br>
[tr]<br>
[td]modpause(mindelay, maxdelay);[/td]<br>
[td]Similar to the pause command, except the total delay is modified bythe number of players in the game. If more than 60 people are playing, the delay is calculated as: delay=(delay<em>60)/player-count;[/td]<br>
[/tr]<br>
[tr]<br>
[td]ifrandom(probability);[/td]<br>
[td]Randomly sets the condition flag to true or false. A probability of0=impossible, and 256=certain[/td]<br>
[/tr]<br>
[tr]<br>
[td]jump(labelname);[/td]<br>
[td]Jumps to the script block with the trigger ‘Label,labelname’ The otherscript will not return to this one[/td]<br>
[/tr]<br>
[tr]<br>
[td]fork(labelname);[/td]<br>
[td]Starts the script block with trigger ‘Label,labelname’ running at thesame time as this one! Be careful with this command <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=5" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"> If the target block has no pause, wait, say, or npcsay commands then will behave like agosub command. (due to non-preemptive multitasking)[/td]<br>
[/tr]<br>
[tr]<br>
[td]end();[/td]<br>
[td]Terminates processing of the current script block[/td]<br>
[/tr]<br>
[/table]<br>
[hr]<br>
<span class="bbcode-b">Chat based</span><br>
[table]<br>
[tr]<br>
[td]mes(string);[/td]<br>
[td]Displays the specified message at the bottom of the playerscreen[/td]<br>
[/tr]<br>
[tr]<br>
[td]say(string);[/td]<br>
[td]Makes the players character say the specified string, all nearbypeople will also see this. The command will then automatically delay the script depending on the length of the string.[/td]<br>
[/tr]<br>
[tr]<br>
[td]multi2(string, label, string, label);[/td]<br>
[td]Displays a multiple choice menu with 2 items, depending which theplayers chooses the relevant block of script will be called. Note: The player may decide not to choose either item in which case the scriptterminates[/td]<br>
[/tr]<br>
[tr]<br>
[td]multi3(string, label, string, label, string, label);[/td]<br>
[td]Displays a multiple choice menu with 3 items[/td]<br>
[/tr]<br>
[tr]<br>
[td]multi4(string, label, string, label, string, label, string, label);[/td]<br>
[td]Displays a multiple choice menu with 4 items[/td]<br>
[/tr]<br>
[/table]<br>
[hr]<br>
<span class="bbcode-b">Movement based</span><br>
[table]<br>
[tr]<br>
[td]changelevel(int level);[/td]<br>
[td]Moves the player to the specified level, without changing the x and yposition. Level-codes: 0=ground floor, 1=1st floor, 2=2nd floor, 3=basement[/td]<br>
[/tr]<br>
[tr]<br>
[td]changelevelup();[/td]<br>
[td]Moves the player up one level if possible.[/td]<br>
[/tr]<br>
[tr]<br>
[td]changeleveldown();[/td]<br>
[td]Moves the player down one level if possible.[/td]<br>
[/tr]<br>
[/table]<br>
[hr]<br>
<span class="bbcode-b">Stat based</span><br>
[table]<br>
[tr]<br>
[td]ifstatrandom(stat, base-probability, top-probability);[/td]<br>
[td]Like the random command but stat modified, if the stat is 0 thebase-probability is used, if the stat is 100 the top-probability is used. If the stat is inbetween then the 2 values are interpolated.[/td]<br>
[/tr]<br>
[tr]<br>
[td]advancestat(stat, base, exp);[/td]<br>
[td]Permanently increases the specified stat, and sets the new levels asthe current normal. The equation used is: stat+=base+exp</em>stat;[/td]<br>
[/tr]<br>
[tr]<br>
[td]addstat(stat, constant, percent);[/td]<br>
[td]Temporarily adds constant+(current<em>percent)/100 to the 2nd playersspecified stat. Where current is the current level of the stat[/td]<br>
[/tr]<br>
[tr]<br>
[td]substat(stat, constant, percent);[/td]<br>
[td]Like addstat, except it subtracts.[/td]<br>
[/tr]<br>
[tr]<br>
[td]healstat(stat, constant, percent);[/td]<br>
[td]Like addstat, but won’t take the players stat above the normallevel[/td]<br>
[/tr]<br>
[tr]<br>
[td]ifstatup(stat);[/td]<br>
[td]Sets the condition to true if the players stat is currently above thenormal level, false otherwise[/td]<br>
[/tr]<br>
[tr]<br>
[td]ifstatdown(stat);[/td]<br>
[td]Sets the condition to true if the players stat is currently below thenormal level, false otherwise[/td]<br>
[/tr]<br>
[tr]<br>
[td]ifstatabove(stat,value);[/td]<br>
[td]Sets the condition to true if the players stat is above (but not equalto) the specified value, false otherwise[/td]<br>
[/tr]<br>
[tr]<br>
[td]ifstatatleast(stat, variable, value);[/td]<br>
[td]Sets the condition to true if the players stat is more than or equalto getvar(variable)+value, false otherwise[/td]<br>
[/tr]<br>
[tr]<br>
[td]giveqp(value);[/td]<br>
[td]Gives the player the specified number of quest points[/td]<br>
[/tr]<br>
[tr]<br>
[td]ifqp(value);[/td]<br>
[td]Sets the condition to true if the players quest points are more thanor equal to the specified value, false otherwise[/td]<br>
[/tr]<br>
[/table]<br>
[hr]<br>
<span class="bbcode-b">Variable based</span><br>
[table]<br>
[tr]<br>
[td]ifvar(variable, value);[/td]<br>
[td]Sets the condition flag to true if the variable is equal to thespecified value. Sets false otherwise[/td]<br>
[/tr]<br>
[tr]<br>
[td]ifvarmore(variable, value);[/td]<br>
[td]Sets the condition flag to true if the variable is greater than (butnot equal to) the specifed value. Sets false otherwise[/td]<br>
[/tr]<br>
[tr][td][/td][/tr]<br>
[tr]<br>
[td]ifvarless(variable, value);[/td]<br>
[td]Sets the condition flag to true if the variable is less than (but notequal to) the specifed value. Sets false otherwise[/td]<br>
[/tr]<br>
[tr][td][/td][/tr]<br>
[tr]<br>
[td]setvar(variable, value);[/td]<br>
[td]Sets the variable to the specified value. A variable can only hold thevalue 0-127. Always try to zero variables when they are no longer needed to save memory.[/td]<br>
[/tr]<br>
[tr]<br>
[td]addvar(variable, value);[/td]<br>
[td]Adds the specified amount to the variables value. A variable can onlyhold the value 0-127. [/td]<br>
[/tr]<br>
[tr]<br>
[td]subvar(variable, value);[/td]<br>
[td]Subtracts the specified amount to the variables value. A variable canonly hold the value 0-127. [/td]<br>
[/tr]<br>
[tr]<br>
[td]randomvar(value);[/td]<br>
[td]Sets the variable ‘random’ to a random integer between 0 andvalue-1[/td]<br>
[/tr]<br>
[tr]<br>
[td]addbigvar(variable, value);[/td]<br>
[td]Add the specified value to the variable. A big-variable can holdvalues between 0-268435455[/td]<br>
[/tr]<br>
[tr]<br>
[td]subbigvar(variable, value);[/td]<br>
[td]Subtracts the specified value from the variable. A big-variable canhold values between 0-268435455[/td]<br>
[/tr]<br>
[tr]<br>
[td]ifbigvarmore(variable, value);[/td]<br>
[td]Same as ifvarmore except for big-variables[/td]<br>
[/tr]<br>
[/table]<br>
[hr]<br>
<span class="bbcode-b">Coordinate based</span><br>
These commands all require a map coordinate to operate. The coordinate used can be set using the setcoord command below. If the setcoord command is not used the system will attempt to use the coordinate of the item the player is currently interacting with.<br>
[table]<br>
[tr]<br>
[td]setcoord(coordinate);[/td]<br>
[td]Sets the active coordinate to the specified absolute position. Thecoordinate can only be worked out with the aid of the runescape map editor.[/td]<br>
[/tr]<br>
[tr]<br>
[td]playercoord();[/td]<br>
[td]Sets the active coordinate to the players current position.[/td]<br>
[/tr]<br>
[tr]<br>
[td]addobject(object, count, time);[/td]<br>
[td]Adds the specified object at the active coordinate. If the object isstackable - count indicates how many to place in the stack. Time indicates how long in server cycles before the object despawns.[/td]<br>
[/tr]<br>
[tr]<br>
[td]addnpc(npc);[/td]<br>
[td]Spawns the specified npc at the active coordinate.[/td]<br>
[/tr]<br>
[tr]<br>
[td]addloc(location);[/td]<br>
[td]Adds the specified location at the active coordinate.[/td]<br>
[/tr]<br>
[tr]<br>
[td]ifblocked();[/td]<br>
[td]Sets the condition flag to true if the square indicated by theactivate coordinate is currently blocked, sets false otherwise[/td]<br>
[/tr]<br>
[tr]<br>
[td]teleport();[/td]<br>
[td]Teleports the player to the active coordinate.[/td]<br>
[/tr]<br>
[tr][td][/td][/tr]<br>
[tr]<br>
[td]showeffect(type);[/td]<br>
[td]Displays a special effect animation of the specified type at theactive coordinate.[/td]<br>
[/tr]<br>
[/table]<br>
[hr]<br>
<span class="bbcode-b">Inventory based</span><br>
[table]<br>
[tr]<br>
[td]give(object, count);[/td]<br>
[td]Gives the specified number of the specified object to playersinventory[/td]<br>
[/tr]<br>
[tr]<br>
[td]remove(object, count);[/td]<br>
[td]Removes the specified number of the specified object from playersinventory (or as many as possible)[/td]<br>
[/tr]<br>
[tr]<br>
[td]ifworn(object);[/td]<br>
[td]Sets condition flag to true if player is wearing specifiedobject[/td]<br>
[/tr]<br>
[tr]<br>
[td]ifheld(object, count);[/td]<br>
[td]Sets condition flag to true if player is holding specifiedobject[/td]<br>
[/tr]<br>
[/table]<br>
<span class="bbcode-b">The commands below may only be used when player isinteracting with an object in their inventory</span><br>
[table]<br>
[tr]<br>
[td]sellinv(percentage);[/td]<br>
[td]Removes the active inventory object from the players inventory, andreplaces it with the specified percentage of it’s value in gold coins[/td]<br>
[/tr]<br>
[tr]<br>
[td]delinv();[/td]<br>
[td]Deletes the active inventory object from the playersinventory[/td]<br>
[/tr]<br>
[/table]<br>
[hr]<br>
<span class="bbcode-b">Object based</span><br>
<span class="bbcode-b">These commands may only be used when a player isinteracting with an object on the ground</span><br>
[table]<br>
[tr]<br>
[td]ifobjectvisible();[/td]<br>
[td]Sets the condition code to true if a line of sight can be tracedbetween the player and the object, false otherwise[/td]<br>
[/tr]<br>
[tr]<br>
[td]takeobject();[/td]<br>
[td]Removes the object from the ground and places it in the playersinventory[/td]<br>
[/tr]<br>
[tr]<br>
[td]delobject();[/td]<br>
[td]Removes the object from the world[/td]<br>
[/tr]<br>
[/table]<br>
[hr]<br>
<span class="bbcode-b">Location based</span><br>
<span class="bbcode-b">These commands may only be used when a player isinteracting with a location</span><br>
[table]<br>
[tr]<br>
[td]changeloc(location);[/td]<br>
[td]Changes the location to the new specified location type[/td]<br>
[/tr]<br>
[tr]<br>
[td]upstairs();[/td]<br>
[td]Moves the player up a level, and adjusts their position horizontallyto account for the stairs[/td]<br>
[/tr]<br>
[tr][td][/td][/tr]<br>
[tr]<br>
[td]downstairs();[/td]<br>
[td]Moves the player down a level, and adjusts their position horizontallyto account for the statis[/td]<br>
[/tr]<br>
[tr][td][/td][/tr]<br>
[tr]<br>
[td]delloc();[/td]<br>
[td]Removes the location from the world[/td]<br>
[/tr]<br>
[/table]<br>
[hr]<br>
<span class="bbcode-b">Boundary based</span><br>
<span class="bbcode-b">These commands may only be used when a player isinteracting with a boundary</span><br>
[table]<br>
[tr]<br>
[td]changebound(boundary);[/td]<br>
[td]Changes the boundary to the new specified boundary type[/td]<br>
[/tr]<br>
[tr]<br>
[td]boundaryteleport();[/td]<br>
[td]Walks the player through the boundary to the opposite side. Useful forlocked doors, and secret pasages.[/td]<br>
[/tr]<br>
[tr][td][/td][/tr]<br>
[/table]<br>
[hr]<br>
<span class="bbcode-b">Npc based</span><br>
[table]<br>
[tr]<br>
[td]ifnearnpc(npc);[/td]<br>
[td]Attempt to find a nearby npc of the type specified. Sets the conditionflag to true if sucessful. If succesful the player is marked as interacting with the npc so the other npc commands can also be used.[/td]<br>
[/tr]<br>
[tr]<br>
[td]ifnearvisnpc(npc);[/td]<br>
[td]Simliar to ifnearnpc, except the npc must be within 8 squares, andthere must be a line of sight between the player and npc for the command to succeed.[/td]<br>
[/tr]<br>
[/table]<br>
<span class="bbcode-b">The commands below may only be used when player isinteracting with an npc</span><br>
[table]<br>
[tr]<br>
[td]npcsay(string);[/td]<br>
[td]Makes the npc say the specified string, all nearby people will alsosee this. The command will then automatically delay the script depending on the length of the string.[/td]<br>
[/tr]<br>
[tr]<br>
[td]npcbusy();[/td]<br>
[td]Sets the npc to busy, and stops it walking around. Not normallynecessary as the system attempts to trigger this automatically.[/td]<br>
[/tr]<br>
[tr]<br>
[td]npcunbusy();[/td]<br>
[td]Sets the npc to unbusy, and allows it to walk around again. Notnormally necessary as the system attempt to trigger this automatically.[/td]<br>
[/tr]<br>
[tr][td][/td][/tr]<br>
[tr]<br>
[td]shootnpc(projectile);[/td]<br>
[td]Fires a projectile at the npc[/td]<br>
[/tr]<br>
[tr][td][/td][/tr]<br>
[tr]<br>
[td]npcattack();[/td]<br>
[td]Causes the npcs to pursue and attack the player[/td]<br>
[/tr]<br>
[tr]<br>
[td]ifnpcvisible();[/td]<br>
[td]Sets the condition code to true if a line of sight can be tracedbetween the player and npc[/td]<br>
[/tr]<br>
[tr][td][/td][/tr]<br>
[tr]<br>
[td]addnpcstat(stat,constant,percent);[/td]<br>
[td]Temporarily adds constant+(current</em>percent)/100 to the npcs specifiedstat[/td]<br>
[/tr]<br>
[tr][td][/td][/tr]<br>
[tr]<br>
[td]subnpcstat(stat,constant,percent);[/td]<br>
[td]Like addnpc stat, except it subtracts[/td]<br>
[/tr]<br>
[tr][td][/td][/tr]<br>
[tr]<br>
[td]healnpcstat(stat,constant,percent);[/td]<br>
[td]Like addnpc stat, but won’t take npcs stat above the normal level[/td]<br>
[/tr]<br>
[tr][td][/td][/tr]<br>
[tr]<br>
[td]ifnpcstatup(stat);[/td]<br>
[td]Sets the condition to true if the npcs specified stat is currentlyabove the normal level, false otherwise[/td]<br>
[/tr]<br>
[tr]<br>
[td]ifnpcstatdown(stat);[/td]<br>
[td]Sets the condition to true if the npcs specified stat is currentlybelow the normal level, false otherwise[/td]<br>
[/tr]<br>
[tr]<br>
[td]delnpc();[/td]<br>
[td]Removes the npc from the world[/td]<br>
[/tr]<br>
[tr]<br>
[td]changenpc(npc);[/td]<br>
[td]Changes the npc into a the new npc type specified![/td]<br>
[/tr]<br>
[tr]<br>
[td]npcretreat(time);[/td]<br>
[td]Causes the npc to run away from the player for the specified number ofserver cycles[/td]<br>
[/tr]<br>
[/table]<br>
[hr]<br>
<span class="bbcode-b">Other player based</span><br>
<span class="bbcode-b">These commands may only be used when a player isinteracting with another player.</span><br>
[table]<br>
[tr]<br>
[td]addplaystat(stat, constant, percent);[/td]<br>
[td]Temporarily adds constant+(current*percent)/100 to the 2nd playersspecified stat. Where current is the current level of the stat[/td]<br>
[/tr]<br>
[tr]<br>
[td]subplaystat(stat, constant, percent);[/td]<br>
[td]Like addplaystat, except it subtracts.[/td]<br>
[/tr]<br>
[tr]<br>
[td]healplaystat(stat, constant, percent);[/td]<br>
[td]Like addplaystat, but won’t take the players stat above the normallevel[/td]<br>
[/tr]<br>
[tr]<br>
[td]ifplaystatup(stat);[/td]<br>
[td]Sets the condition to true if the 2nd players stat is currently abovethe normal level, false otherwise[/td]<br>
[/tr]<br>
[tr]<br>
[td]ifplaystatdown(stat)[/td]<br>
[td]Sets the condition to true if the 2nd players stat is currently belowthe normal level, false otherwise[/td]<br>
[/tr]<br>
[tr]<br>
[td]omes(string);[/td]<br>
[td]Displays a message on the 2nd players screen[/td]<br>
[/tr]<br>
[tr]<br>
[td]ifplayervisible();[/td]<br>
[td]Sets the condition code to true if a line of sight can be tracedbetween the 2 players, false otherwise[/td]<br>
[/tr]<br>
[tr]<br>
[td]shootplayer(projectile);[/td]<br>
[td]Fires a projectile at the 2nd player[/td]<br>
[/tr]<br>
[/table]</p>
<p>Modern Runescript:</p>
<p><img src="https://pbs.twimg.com/media/BpN1MapCYAA-Rvv.png:large" alt width="" height=""><br>
<img src="https://pbs.twimg.com/media/BpdZ9mWIYAAYoLj.png:large" alt width="" height=""><br>
<img src="https://pbs.twimg.com/media/BpIV0yIIUAAsVmu.png:large" alt width="" height=""><br>
<img src="http://i.imgur.com/DRJBAXC.png" alt width="" height=""><br>
<img src="http://i.imgur.com/heXbHMP.png" alt width="" height=""></p>
<p>A lot different :P, not entirely sure how enumerations are handled. The enum command seems to have two type declarations then two parameters.</p>
<p>% - variable<br>
$ - script variable<br>
~ - gosub<br>
@ - jump<br>
&lt;&gt; - evaluate</p>
<p>The enumerations probably have something to do with how the scripts in the client captured variables (could return string/integer).</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/runescript/544211/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/runescript/544211/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 22 Jun 2014 20:13:10 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-544211-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/runescript/544211.rss">Runescript</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
