<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Device Problem</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/device-problem/396945</link>
    <description>I&#39;m having a little problem with opening my device on my computer, it seems when I plug the wire into the computer, and connecting the wire to my music device and attempting to make it open on the computer (all the media files), it doesn&#39;t even bother to show up on the &#39;My Computer&#39; bin.

I&#39;ve attempted to even have it formatted by plugging it into my Xbox and making it 360 compatiable and then redoing it all over again, but not even that worked! And then I tried plugging it into another computer, and of course not even that worked.

So I was wondering, does anyone have any suggestions on this?</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 29 May 2011 17:14:59 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>General Discussion</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/device-problem/396945.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Device Problem</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Ix_Soulcist_xI Soulcist]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/ix_soulcist_xi">@Ix_Soulcist_xI</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I’m having a little problem with opening my device on my computer, it seems when I plug the wire into the computer, and connecting the wire to my music device and attempting to make it open on the computer (all the media files), it doesn’t even bother to show up on the ‘My Computer’ bin.</p>
<p>I’ve attempted to even have it formatted by plugging it into my Xbox and making it 360 compatiable and then redoing it all over again, but not even that worked! And then I tried plugging it into another computer, and of course not even that worked.</p>
<p>So I was wondering, does anyone have any suggestions on this?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/device-problem/396945/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/device-problem/396945/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 29 May 2011 17:14:59 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-396945-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/device-problem/396945.rss">Device Problem</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
