<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Starting server on website?</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/starting-server-on-website/199500</link>
    <description>Hello everyone,

A friend and I would like to start a server on a website. I currently own a website (and no, this isn&#39;t some cheap Freewebs one) and he owns a MoparScape server. I was wondering if it was possible to run the Java program (and of course, all of the other files needed) on my website so it would be up 100% of the time, without him having to turn on his computer and run the server.

Is this possible? I know the batch file starts the server; would a job scheduler for UNIX be the same if I entered a UNIX command to be performed every time to run the server? Also, does MySQL have anything to do with it? I know a user asked this earlier, but he just got a response saying &quot;MySQL,&quot; which doesn&#39;t tell me much.

Thanks.[br][br][size=1]Posted on: April 13, 2008, 03:28:02 PM[/size][hr]Anybody? I really think this would be an interesting project to do. Do I just upload all of the files to my website, edit a few contents in the .java files (and compile them), and then create a job scheduler to run the server?

I am sure I&#39;m capable of doing it, I just don&#39;t know where to get started.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 13 Apr 2008 22:02:38 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/starting-server-on-website/199500.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Starting server on website?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@JohnInteractive JohnInteractive]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/johninteractive">@JohnInteractive</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Hello everyone,</p>
<p>A friend and I would like to start a server on a website. I currently own a website (and no, this isn’t some cheap Freewebs one) and he owns a MoparScape server. I was wondering if it was possible to run the Java program (and of course, all of the other files needed) on my website so it would be up 100% of the time, without him having to turn on his computer and run the server.</p>
<p>Is this possible? I know the batch file starts the server; would a job scheduler for UNIX be the same if I entered a UNIX command to be performed every time to run the server? Also, does MySQL have anything to do with it? I know a user asked this earlier, but he just got a response saying “MySQL,” which doesn’t tell me much.</p>
<p>Thanks.[br][br][size=1]Posted on: April 13, 2008, 03:28:02 PM[/size][hr]Anybody? I really think this would be an interesting project to do. Do I just upload all of the files to my website, edit a few contents in the .java files (and compile them), and then create a job scheduler to run the server?</p>
<p>I am sure I’m capable of doing it, I just don’t know where to get started.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/starting-server-on-website/199500/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/starting-server-on-website/199500/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 13 Apr 2008 22:02:38 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-199500-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/starting-server-on-website/199500.rss">Starting server on website?</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
