<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Couple Things</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/couple-things/445135</link>
    <description>Just a couple things to address:

[center][b]Nominations[/b][/center]

Nominations for staff positions and awards are something incredibly new. It also presents an issue of judgement of receiving awards and positions. 

Something that might become an issue is for the awards is the knowledge of the nominators. There is a certain caliber of programming expertise to receive an award (like any award). This previously was not an issue when awards were not nominated, since all of the people awarding awards have a large amount of programming experience. However, the average knowledge of people over at MSCP is significantly less than that of most of the people over at MITB and the staff members. 

Some of the awards may be better for members to nominate and are fine for this (e.g. Tutorial Author), but most of the others are questionable. 

The same issue can arise from the staff standpoint; some of the people that might be better for moderating and stuff from a the point of view of the moderators and administrators, and some might be better from the viewpoint of the members. 

On related note, which awards can people be nominated for? Is it just the Moparscape awards, or all of the awards on MITB + Moparscape? 

[center][b]Lots of Change[/b][/center]

There has been a load of change lately: three promotions in a week, the addition of two new boards, a bunch of people receiving awards, etc. Why?

Before, things happened gradually, with a board or promotion happening every once and a while; now, changes are happening at light speed, and there has been more change occuring in the past couple weeks than the past couple months. Why have there been so many changes all of a sudden. 

It is fine to change things up every once and a while, and some of the changes that have been implemented over the past couple weeks are fantastic. It&#39;s just that the amount of change that has happened recently and the frequency of change has been increased dramatically. It&#39;s a good idea to draw change out over a little bit more time and slow down a bit; that way, there is a little bit more time to think things out and the specifics of the changes, and all the changes are not burned out over a short period of time. 

Also, it seems like the changes are being a little bit rushed and the logistics are being figured out after the fact, when previously everything was hammered out and then the change was made. 

In short:


[ul][li]Why all of the change lately?[/li]
[li]Why has change become much more widespread and frequent?[/li][/ul]


PS:[b]Please do not make this public[/b]</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 01 Jul 2012 14:46:38 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Community Suggestions</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/couple-things/445135.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Couple Things</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@mod_taharok Taharok]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/mod_taharok">@mod_taharok</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Alright. Thanks for bringing this to our attention. Given this topic is now half a month old, it may no longer be valid or is simply not being discussed. If you feel this is still an issue, feel free to post another topic regarding it. For now, though, I’m marking it as resolved.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/couple-things/445135/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/couple-things/445135/4</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 01 Jul 2012 14:46:38 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-445135-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/couple-things/445135.rss">Couple Things</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Couple Things</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@mod_taharok Taharok]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/mod_taharok">@mod_taharok</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Well regarding nominations, I’m not sure you understand how they work. Nominations never guarantee a promotion or award. The point of a nomination is to bring to the staff’s attention someone we may have overlooked in regards to a position or an award. If we agree with the nominator’s argument, we will then go through our normal process for deciding whether they deserve it. Given that nominations lead to many validity errors, we go through extra effort to ensure the person in question is worth for the nominated award or position.</p>
<p>As far as the changes go, they have been in discussion for days and weeks before actually going into effect. Some holes do exist because we are moving a bit faster than normal, but in reality, this isn’t a lot faster than we normally run. The only reason this wasn’t noticeable earlier was because there was no time for any administrators to implement the features. That has slightly changed now.</p>
<p>Beyond that, my goal is very simple: increase the activity of this website. Nearly every change and feature I am endorsing and/or implementing is with that idea in mind. I want this site to become more successful in activity and popularity, and each thing happening now has a certain role it’s serving in its own way.</p>
<p>Hope this helps.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/couple-things/445135/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/couple-things/445135/3</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Jun 2012 23:41:59 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-445135-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/couple-things/445135.rss">Couple Things</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Couple Things</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Frell Frell]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/frell">@Frell</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>This is how it should be. If people cant see why there were 3 promotions then they probably aren’t paying attention <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/wink.png?v=5" title=":wink:" class="emoji" alt=":wink:"></p>
<p>More boards = more mods.</p>
<p>Nothing is being rushed, I can assure you.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/couple-things/445135/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/couple-things/445135/2</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 14 Jun 2012 23:28:54 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-445135-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/couple-things/445135.rss">Couple Things</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Couple Things</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Syfal Syfal]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/syfal">@Syfal</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Just a couple things to address:</p>
<p>[center]<span class="bbcode-b">Nominations</span>[/center]</p>
<p>Nominations for staff positions and awards are something incredibly new. It also presents an issue of judgement of receiving awards and positions.</p>
<p>Something that might become an issue is for the awards is the knowledge of the nominators. There is a certain caliber of programming expertise to receive an award (like any award). This previously was not an issue when awards were not nominated, since all of the people awarding awards have a large amount of programming experience. However, the average knowledge of people over at MSCP is significantly less than that of most of the people over at MITB and the staff members.</p>
<p>Some of the awards may be better for members to nominate and are fine for this (e.g. Tutorial Author), but most of the others are questionable.</p>
<p>The same issue can arise from the staff standpoint; some of the people that might be better for moderating and stuff from a the point of view of the moderators and administrators, and some might be better from the viewpoint of the members.</p>
<p>On related note, which awards can people be nominated for? Is it just the Moparscape awards, or all of the awards on MITB + Moparscape?</p>
<p>[center]<span class="bbcode-b">Lots of Change</span>[/center]</p>
<p>There has been a load of change lately: three promotions in a week, the addition of two new boards, a bunch of people receiving awards, etc. Why?</p>
<p>Before, things happened gradually, with a board or promotion happening every once and a while; now, changes are happening at light speed, and there has been more change occuring in the past couple weeks than the past couple months. Why have there been so many changes all of a sudden.</p>
<p>It is fine to change things up every once and a while, and some of the changes that have been implemented over the past couple weeks are fantastic. It’s just that the amount of change that has happened recently and the frequency of change has been increased dramatically. It’s a good idea to draw change out over a little bit more time and slow down a bit; that way, there is a little bit more time to think things out and the specifics of the changes, and all the changes are not burned out over a short period of time.</p>
<p>Also, it seems like the changes are being a little bit rushed and the logistics are being figured out after the fact, when previously everything was hammered out and then the change was made.</p>
<p>In short:</p>
<p>[ul][li]Why all of the change lately?[/li]<br>
[li]Why has change become much more widespread and frequent?[/li][/ul]</p>
<p>PS:<span class="bbcode-b">Please do not make this public</span></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/couple-things/445135/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/couple-things/445135/1</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 14 Jun 2012 20:37:50 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-445135-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/couple-things/445135.rss">Couple Things</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
