<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Re: Karamja RSC : Online</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/re-karamja-rsc-online/541837</link>
    <description>I love this server, no downtime, DDOs hasn&#39;t effected us. This is a unique RSC server, brilliantly made and constantly updated. Completely unique server being updated every day personally by Rodgerwilco.. Give it a try if you like RSC and don&#39;t mind changing it up a little.

Features:
-----------------
[IMG]http://i.imgur.com/ZWETo2J.png[/img]

K, this is how it goes on Karamja.net

Yes the entire world is on Karamja. There are 3 factions/guilds/teams, whatever you want to kill them. Guthix, Saradomin and Zamorack. The servers updated every day almost by Wilcoskill (admin, add him...)

The whole maps 10 wilderness. You fight NPC&#39;s to gain points for your team. With your points you can collaborate to buy shops for your teams. At the start, no one has any shops. 


[b]You can find each factions points here:[/b] http://classic.karamja.net/
Top of the page you&#39;ll see team points.



[b]Here is a list of where you&#39;ll find what you can buy with your team points by contacting an admin.[/b]
Right here: http://karamja.net/index.php?topic=28.0

[b]Here is where you post on the forums to register your accounts for a certain faction to see the factions private message boards.[/b]
Here: http://karamja.net/index.php?topic=118.0


By killing NPC&#39;s you gain points for your team. Find out who your other team mates are via in game or by registering the forums and talking to them on your board.

You&#39;re free to do any skill but heres a few tips:

1. Play 2 accounts, either have both AFKing to get your team points or one doing a skill.
2. Always afk train to boost your team, even if ur busy logout time is 10m, u can get a lot done.
3. Have fun dont take it serious.

Also, by finding out whos on your team if you have a good smith, fisher, crafter they may be willing to help you out because you&#39;re helping them by leveling up, pking or doing whatever.

[b]----------------------------------------------------------[/b]
[b]CLASS SYSTEM[/b]

1. [b]Warrior:[/b] Warriors get 2x combat experience, 1/2 range of rangers and cannot use Magic. These are the first type of character you want to make so you can AFK earn your team points and level up.

2. [b]Ranger:[/b] Rangers get 1/2 combat experience, 2x range exp and cannot use magic. Rangers can shoot 12 squares and fire 40% faster then normal.

3. [b]Mages:[/b] Mages gain 1/2 combat exp and 1/2 range exp. They get 2x magic exp, but currently have no special spells until the new spellbook is released, expected sometime in April. Best use for a mage now would be for a support character, used for stuff like Enchanting amulets.

[b]----------------------------------------------------------[/b]
[b]Faction Territory[/b]
1. [b]Guthix[/b] Guthix Territory lies in brimhaven. 
2. [b]Zammy[/b] Zammy&#39;s Territory is Shilo Village.
3. [b]Saradomin[/b] Sara&#39;s territory is southern Karamja, near the docks that would lead to Port Sarim in RSC. Currently there base is still under construction and landscapes could be updated at any time.

At death everyone re spawns back in their territory.

Depending on the team you choose depends on what shops you could have. If your team doesn&#39;t have fishing store you&#39;re going to have a hard time fishing lobsters and swordfish without a harpoon. You need to discuss with your team mates what you have and what you would like to get and work together to reach your goals. 

By exploring you&#39;ll find monsters to train on randomly spread around the island. Do some exploring.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2014 03:10:11 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Uncategorized</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/re-karamja-rsc-online/541837.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Re: Karamja RSC : Online</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@xbumis49 xbumis49]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/xbumis49">@xbumis49</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I love this server, no downtime, DDOs hasn’t effected us. This is a unique RSC server, brilliantly made and constantly updated. Completely unique server being updated every day personally by Rodgerwilco… Give it a try if you like RSC and don’t mind changing it up a little.</p>
<h2>Features:</h2>
<p><img src="http://i.imgur.com/ZWETo2J.png" alt width="" height=""></p>
<p>K, this is how it goes on <a href="http://Karamja.net" rel="nofollow noopener">Karamja.net</a></p>
<p>Yes the entire world is on Karamja. There are 3 factions/guilds/teams, whatever you want to kill them. Guthix, Saradomin and Zamorack. The servers updated every day almost by Wilcoskill (admin, add him…)</p>
<p>The whole maps 10 wilderness. You fight NPC’s to gain points for your team. With your points you can collaborate to buy shops for your teams. At the start, no one has any shops.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">You can find each factions points here:</span> <a href="http://classic.karamja.net/" rel="nofollow noopener">http://classic.karamja.net/</a><br>
Top of the page you’ll see team points.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Here is a list of where you’ll find what you can buy with your team points by contacting an admin.</span><br>
Right here: <a href="http://karamja.net/index.php?topic=28.0" rel="nofollow noopener">http://karamja.net/index.php?topic=28.0</a></p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Here is where you post on the forums to register your accounts for a certain faction to see the factions private message boards.</span><br>
Here: <a href="http://karamja.net/index.php?topic=118.0" rel="nofollow noopener">http://karamja.net/index.php?topic=118.0</a></p>
<p>By killing NPC’s you gain points for your team. Find out who your other team mates are via in game or by registering the forums and talking to them on your board.</p>
<p>You’re free to do any skill but heres a few tips:</p>
<ol>
<li>Play 2 accounts, either have both AFKing to get your team points or one doing a skill.</li>
<li>Always afk train to boost your team, even if ur busy logout time is 10m, u can get a lot done.</li>
<li>Have fun dont take it serious.</li>
</ol>
<p>Also, by finding out whos on your team if you have a good smith, fisher, crafter they may be willing to help you out because you’re helping them by leveling up, pking or doing whatever.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">----------------------------------------------------------</span><br>
<span class="bbcode-b">CLASS SYSTEM</span></p>
<ol>
<li>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Warrior:</span> Warriors get 2x combat experience, 1/2 range of rangers and cannot use Magic. These are the first type of character you want to make so you can AFK earn your team points and level up.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Ranger:</span> Rangers get 1/2 combat experience, 2x range exp and cannot use magic. Rangers can shoot 12 squares and fire 40% faster then normal.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Mages:</span> Mages gain 1/2 combat exp and 1/2 range exp. They get 2x magic exp, but currently have no special spells until the new spellbook is released, expected sometime in April. Best use for a mage now would be for a support character, used for stuff like Enchanting amulets.</p>
</li>
</ol>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">----------------------------------------------------------</span><br>
<span class="bbcode-b">Faction Territory</span></p>
<ol>
<li>
<span class="bbcode-b">Guthix</span> Guthix Territory lies in brimhaven.</li>
<li>
<span class="bbcode-b">Zammy</span> Zammy’s Territory is Shilo Village.</li>
<li>
<span class="bbcode-b">Saradomin</span> Sara’s territory is southern Karamja, near the docks that would lead to Port Sarim in RSC. Currently there base is still under construction and landscapes could be updated at any time.</li>
</ol>
<p>At death everyone re spawns back in their territory.</p>
<p>Depending on the team you choose depends on what shops you could have. If your team doesn’t have fishing store you’re going to have a hard time fishing lobsters and swordfish without a harpoon. You need to discuss with your team mates what you have and what you would like to get and work together to reach your goals.</p>
<p>By exploring you’ll find monsters to train on randomly spread around the island. Do some exploring.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/re-karamja-rsc-online/541837/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/re-karamja-rsc-online/541837/1</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2014 03:10:11 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-541837-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/re-karamja-rsc-online/541837.rss">Re: Karamja RSC : Online</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
