<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Free stuff?!?!</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/free-stuff/2848</link>
    <description>Ok, well I&#39;m pretty sure these things are mostly legal. If not, just delete this. kthxbye.

[code]
1. Introduction
2. Payphones
2a. Free Calls
2b. Money
3. Postage
4. Food &amp; Drink
5. Vending Machines
6. Arcade Games
8. Conclusion

1. Introduction

allright, so i&#39;ve come to notice that i have gathered a large collection of
textfiles on how to rip off all sorts of machinery. So, i&#39;ve decided to compile
all of it together into this tutorial. I have personally tested each of these
methods and they do work. some tricks may require some social engineering experience.
so lets get started.

2. Payphones

lets face it, they&#39;re everywhere. and personally, i couldn&#39;t be happier about that
fact. if you know what you are doing, payphones can save you an ample sum of money.

2a. Free Calls

this is a fairly simple technique that works on some phones. somewhree on the
phone there should be a number listed as the &quot;repair and refund number&quot;. call
that number and tell them the phone dropped your call and didn&#39;t return any change.
they&#39;ll ask you for a name and address, feel free to bullshit that (you might not
want to though, we&#39;ll get to that in a second). when they ask what number you were
calling, give them the number you want to make a free call to. some companies will
put through a free 3 minute call, but often times these are monitored.

2b. Money

so lets say you called the &quot;repair and refund number&quot; from section 2a. and the
company doesn&#39;t offer the free call? well, the alternative is the phone company sends
a check for the amount of money you say you lost to the name and address you told them.
(most phone companies notice if you do this more than once on the same payphone in a day,
so don&#39;t be a retard)

don&#39;t feel like going through the trouble of cashing a $0.50 check? there are other ways
to get money from payphones. for example, try stuffing a large wad of toilet paper into
the coin return shute. (be sure not to block the door, as this will arouse suspicion.)
now, wait for about a day (or less, depending on how often the payphone is used) and
then go back to the payphone. reach into the shute and pull a bit of the toilet paper down.
while holding the door open about half way, light the toilet paper on fire. any change that
was returned should have stopped on top of the wad of toilet paper, and has now fallen down
to the coin return. however, you should be careful as some payphone manufacturers have
started putting a sharp point inside the coin return shutes to stick anyone who tries this.

the 100% guaranteed way to get change out of the payphone is to take the entire payphone to
your home and mess around until you get into it. the locks on payphones are usually on the
side or the top, while the lock in the front is to open the change box. pick the lock on
the side and then insert a t-shaped piece of metal into the front lock and turn. try not
to damage the phone itself so you can hook it up in your house (tutorial coming soon).

3. Postage

there comes a time in everyones life when they have to leave the luxuries of
electronic mail and send via the postal system. but postage is and expense
you don&#39;t really have to pay too much for.

mix 2 parts white school glue and one part water. fill out the envelope the
normal way and put a stamp on it. then brush a light coat of the glue/water
over the stamp. now send the letter. when the person recieves the letter, they
just have to run the stamp under some water for a few seconds and the postal
service mark will wash off. (this makes for free postage for THEM)

4. Food &amp; Drink

fast food restaurants. lets face it, we all eat at these shtiholes all the time. and little do
we know that we can make ourselves fat without paying a dime.

4a. Food

in order to get some free food at a fast food place, the first step is to find out when the shifts
change at that particular location. about an hour after the second shift starts, walk into the
restaurant and ask to speak to the manager. when the manager walks up give them something like &quot;hi, i&#39;m
Micheal Taurus. i believe you talked to my father earlier&quot; then tell them that your father had phoned
earlier because they had forgotten a sandwich in his order, and that you were here to pick up the sandwich.
they&#39;ll probably just give you the sandwich, and maybe something extra if you have a real good story.

4b. Drink

the first method is so simple i&#39;m ashamed not everyone does it. first you order an ice water
with your food. now, if this is the kind of restaurant where you pour your own soda, just
fill the cup up with soda instead of water (most fast food employees couldn&#39;t give two shits
about you stealing a soda). however, some places still have the soda fountains located behind
the counter. what can you do about that?

this trick is also very simple but you must use it either when there is more than one person
working the register, or when the restaurant is farily busy. take the ice water you ordered back
to your table and tear the bottom out of the cup. now go up with the empty cup and tell them that
the cup had a hole in it and ask them for another soda. they&#39;ll probably give it to you without a
second thought.

5. Vending Machines

a fairly simple method of getting money from vending machines is to use the stuffing method
we discussed with payphones. however, this time, instead of using toilet paper, we&#39;ll be using
a piece of cardboard. simply stuff the cardboard up into the chute for the coine return and come
back in a day or so and remove the cardboard. if successfull, you should have a fairly large
sum of money. note, if there is a door of any sort to the coin return, make sure you don&#39;t let it close
or all your change will be stuck there and just mock you like the idiot you are.

6. Arcade Games

i discovered this trick at my work while playing pinball. some older arcade games
(this one was made in 1997) have a flaw that allows you to get a small amount of
change out of them. first you need to locate the two buttons labeled &#39;push for coin return&#39;.
if you can&#39;t find those buttons, go kill yourself. now, push the button on the left in as
far as it will go. while holding in the first one, push the right button down as far as it
will go. if successfull, you should have about fifty cents. some machines will let you do
this at least a good 10 times.

8. Conclusion

so, there you have it. with some practice you should be able to pull these off without
drawing too much attention to yourself. good luck!
most of the info in this tutorial can be found in &#39;vending machines, payphones and bill changers&#39; at
http://www.textfiles.com/uploads/vendingm.txt , &#39;the anarchist cookbook, by jolly roger&#39; (available
all over the fucking internet)., or Phone Losers of America www.phonelosers.org. the rest is just things
i&#39;ve discovered on my own. [/code]

[url=http://www.fagex.net/fgx/viewtopic.php?t=17146]http://www.fagex.net/fgx/viewtopic.php?t=17146[/url]</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2006 18:52:42 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>General Discussion</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/free-stuff/2848.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Free stuff?!?!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@mobscene mobscene]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/mobscene">@mobscene</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>:|hehe ur great u made a few bucks,but im lovin the vendin machine ones hehe</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/free-stuff/2848/17">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/free-stuff/2848/17</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2006 18:52:42 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-2848-17</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/free-stuff/2848.rss">Free stuff?!?!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Free stuff?!?!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@R.I.P_RSC R.I.P RSC]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/r.i.p_rsc">@R.I.P_RSC</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>i cant try the phone boot ones cuz most use this pass thingys like a credit card so there is no coin stuff involved but i can try the vending machine at school =)</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/free-stuff/2848/16">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/free-stuff/2848/16</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2006 00:26:40 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-2848-16</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/free-stuff/2848.rss">Free stuff?!?!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Free stuff?!?!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Naota22 Naota22]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/naota22">@Naota22</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>doode i did the vendign machine and got atleast $2.68, its really nice tut ill have to try phone next</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/free-stuff/2848/15">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/free-stuff/2848/15</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2006 08:10:59 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-2848-15</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/free-stuff/2848.rss">Free stuff?!?!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Free stuff?!?!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@bumr055 bumr055]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/bumr055">@bumr055</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>nice tut! but the free food one probly wont work… at the big M you know what im talkin about lol they have a big book and they ask your name when you call in and i assume that hey do that at alot of “shitholes” lol</p>
<p>you own, nun the less!</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/free-stuff/2848/14">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/free-stuff/2848/14</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jul 2006 12:55:23 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-2848-14</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/free-stuff/2848.rss">Free stuff?!?!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Free stuff?!?!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@lmiles15 lmiles15]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/lmiles15">@lmiles15</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>oh ok i thought it was yours lol</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/free-stuff/2848/13">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/free-stuff/2848/13</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jun 2006 15:09:43 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-2848-13</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/free-stuff/2848.rss">Free stuff?!?!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Free stuff?!?!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@yna_ajhear5 yna_ajhear5]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/yna_ajhear5">@yna_ajhear5</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote no-group" data-post="11" data-topic="2848">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/lmiles15/40/5_8504b32b4165840149d2c3dd52eb0686.png" class="avatar"> lmiles15:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>lol this great, good job</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Good job? It’s not mine. I’m mearly posting it here for people not registered on Fagex(well now Talkgeek)</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/free-stuff/2848/12">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/free-stuff/2848/12</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jun 2006 19:36:10 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-2848-12</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/free-stuff/2848.rss">Free stuff?!?!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Free stuff?!?!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@lmiles15 lmiles15]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/lmiles15">@lmiles15</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>lol this great, good job</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/free-stuff/2848/11">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/free-stuff/2848/11</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jun 2006 14:38:34 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-2848-11</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/free-stuff/2848.rss">Free stuff?!?!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Free stuff?!?!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@nipplesandlicks nipplesandlicks]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/nipplesandlicks">@nipplesandlicks</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>HAHA nice I like it.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/free-stuff/2848/10">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/free-stuff/2848/10</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 28 May 2006 07:31:36 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-2848-10</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/free-stuff/2848.rss">Free stuff?!?!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Free stuff?!?!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@purepka purepka]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/purepka">@purepka</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>lol nice guide im going to try some of these…</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/free-stuff/2848/9">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/free-stuff/2848/9</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 28 May 2006 03:40:24 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-2848-9</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/free-stuff/2848.rss">Free stuff?!?!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Free stuff?!?!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Mr.Chris Mr.Chris]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/mr.chris">@Mr.Chris</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I done the phone booth one, to the one down my read in the middle of a busy town <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=9" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"> I made Â£5.45 <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/wink.png?v=9" title=":wink:" class="emoji" alt=":wink:"> <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/smiley.png?v=9" title=":smiley:" class="emoji" alt=":smiley:"> I’m gonna do it again today <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=9" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"> Although, some people asked me what I was doing shoving a lighter up the machine <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=9" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/free-stuff/2848/8">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/free-stuff/2848/8</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 21 May 2006 11:30:28 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-2848-8</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/free-stuff/2848.rss">Free stuff?!?!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Free stuff?!?!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@shadow shadow]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/shadow">@shadow</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Hey, i really like the arcade game thing im so going to do that. but anyways On some soda machines that are old and u feel as if u are really thirsty and no one is around do this.</p>
<p>Put in the amount of money needed now press the soda u want now this is where u make sure noone is around i found out that most old ones have the wires close to the button thing so right when u are pressing the botton hit the machine as hard as u can on the side thats right next to the botton (note: i have done this 10 tiumes 4 out of 10 times it has worked on the 4 times i kiked it really hard so  dont get mad if it doesnt work its acculay an old trick :P)</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/free-stuff/2848/7">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/free-stuff/2848/7</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 21 May 2006 02:52:18 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-2848-7</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/free-stuff/2848.rss">Free stuff?!?!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Free stuff?!?!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@jme jme]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/jme">@jme</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I did the vending machine one twice, but quite often they check them every night. Most machine vendors are aware of these scams.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/free-stuff/2848/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/free-stuff/2848/6</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 18 May 2006 03:19:23 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-2848-6</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/free-stuff/2848.rss">Free stuff?!?!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Free stuff?!?!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@White_Castle White Castle]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/white_castle">@White_Castle</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Damn. I’m trying the vending machine one at school tomarrow.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/free-stuff/2848/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/free-stuff/2848/5</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 18 May 2006 02:56:31 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-2848-5</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/free-stuff/2848.rss">Free stuff?!?!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Free stuff?!?!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@jme jme]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/jme">@jme</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Something else I heard to send free mail is:</p>
<p>Put the return address as the person you want to send the mail to. Dont use a stamp or anything at all, and the post office will return it to the “return address” because there is no stamp.</p>
<p>I also reccommend you go to <a href="http://rotteneggs.com" rel="nofollow noopener">rotteneggs.com</a>, however be aware the majority of them talk like hillbillies.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/free-stuff/2848/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/free-stuff/2848/4</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 17 May 2006 22:47:11 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-2848-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/free-stuff/2848.rss">Free stuff?!?!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Free stuff?!?!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@anarkial anarkial]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/anarkial">@anarkial</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I like the one where you take the phone home. Don’t you think that maybe it’ll be a bit too conspicious?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/free-stuff/2848/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/free-stuff/2848/3</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 16 May 2006 20:58:14 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-2848-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/free-stuff/2848.rss">Free stuff?!?!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Free stuff?!?!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@l3etal3lade l3etal3lade]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/l3etal3lade">@l3etal3lade</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Nice man if I don’t try some of these at least it gave me a laugh, I wonder why have I never thought of stuffing that stuff up chutes b4 either :s.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/free-stuff/2848/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/free-stuff/2848/2</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 15 May 2006 15:58:41 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-2848-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/free-stuff/2848.rss">Free stuff?!?!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Free stuff?!?!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@yna_ajhear5 yna_ajhear5]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/yna_ajhear5">@yna_ajhear5</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Ok, well I’m pretty sure these things are mostly legal. If not, just delete this. kthxbye.</p>
<p>[code]</p>
<ol>
<li>
<p>Introduction</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Payphones<br>
2a. Free Calls<br>
2b. Money</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Postage</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Food &amp; Drink</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Vending Machines</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Arcade Games</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Conclusion</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Introduction</p>
</li>
</ol>
<p>allright, so i’ve come to notice that i have gathered a large collection of<br>
textfiles on how to rip off all sorts of machinery. So, i’ve decided to compile<br>
all of it together into this tutorial. I have personally tested each of these<br>
methods and they do work. some tricks may require some social engineering experience.<br>
so lets get started.</p>
<ol start="2">
<li>Payphones</li>
</ol>
<p>lets face it, they’re everywhere. and personally, i couldn’t be happier about that<br>
fact. if you know what you are doing, payphones can save you an ample sum of money.</p>
<p>2a. Free Calls</p>
<p>this is a fairly simple technique that works on some phones. somewhree on the<br>
phone there should be a number listed as the “repair and refund number”. call<br>
that number and tell them the phone dropped your call and didn’t return any change.<br>
they’ll ask you for a name and address, feel free to bullshit that (you might not<br>
want to though, we’ll get to that in a second). when they ask what number you were<br>
calling, give them the number you want to make a free call to. some companies will<br>
put through a free 3 minute call, but often times these are monitored.</p>
<p>2b. Money</p>
<p>so lets say you called the “repair and refund number” from section 2a. and the<br>
company doesn’t offer the free call? well, the alternative is the phone company sends<br>
a check for the amount of money you say you lost to the name and address you told them.<br>
(most phone companies notice if you do this more than once on the same payphone in a day,<br>
so don’t be a retard)</p>
<p>don’t feel like going through the trouble of cashing a $0.50 check? there are other ways<br>
to get money from payphones. for example, try stuffing a large wad of toilet paper into<br>
the coin return shute. (be sure not to block the door, as this will arouse suspicion.)<br>
now, wait for about a day (or less, depending on how often the payphone is used) and<br>
then go back to the payphone. reach into the shute and pull a bit of the toilet paper down.<br>
while holding the door open about half way, light the toilet paper on fire. any change that<br>
was returned should have stopped on top of the wad of toilet paper, and has now fallen down<br>
to the coin return. however, you should be careful as some payphone manufacturers have<br>
started putting a sharp point inside the coin return shutes to stick anyone who tries this.</p>
<p>the 100% guaranteed way to get change out of the payphone is to take the entire payphone to<br>
your home and mess around until you get into it. the locks on payphones are usually on the<br>
side or the top, while the lock in the front is to open the change box. pick the lock on<br>
the side and then insert a t-shaped piece of metal into the front lock and turn. try not<br>
to damage the phone itself so you can hook it up in your house (tutorial coming soon).</p>
<ol start="3">
<li>Postage</li>
</ol>
<p>there comes a time in everyones life when they have to leave the luxuries of<br>
electronic mail and send via the postal system. but postage is and expense<br>
you don’t really have to pay too much for.</p>
<p>mix 2 parts white school glue and one part water. fill out the envelope the<br>
normal way and put a stamp on it. then brush a light coat of the glue/water<br>
over the stamp. now send the letter. when the person recieves the letter, they<br>
just have to run the stamp under some water for a few seconds and the postal<br>
service mark will wash off. (this makes for free postage for THEM)</p>
<ol start="4">
<li>Food &amp; Drink</li>
</ol>
<p>fast food restaurants. lets face it, we all eat at these shtiholes all the time. and little do<br>
we know that we can make ourselves fat without paying a dime.</p>
<p>4a. Food</p>
<p>in order to get some free food at a fast food place, the first step is to find out when the shifts<br>
change at that particular location. about an hour after the second shift starts, walk into the<br>
restaurant and ask to speak to the manager. when the manager walks up give them something like “hi, i’m<br>
Micheal Taurus. i believe you talked to my father earlier” then tell them that your father had phoned<br>
earlier because they had forgotten a sandwich in his order, and that you were here to pick up the sandwich.<br>
they’ll probably just give you the sandwich, and maybe something extra if you have a real good story.</p>
<p>4b. Drink</p>
<p>the first method is so simple i’m ashamed not everyone does it. first you order an ice water<br>
with your food. now, if this is the kind of restaurant where you pour your own soda, just<br>
fill the cup up with soda instead of water (most fast food employees couldn’t give two shits<br>
about you stealing a soda). however, some places still have the soda fountains located behind<br>
the counter. what can you do about that?</p>
<p>this trick is also very simple but you must use it either when there is more than one person<br>
working the register, or when the restaurant is farily busy. take the ice water you ordered back<br>
to your table and tear the bottom out of the cup. now go up with the empty cup and tell them that<br>
the cup had a hole in it and ask them for another soda. they’ll probably give it to you without a<br>
second thought.</p>
<ol start="5">
<li>Vending Machines</li>
</ol>
<p>a fairly simple method of getting money from vending machines is to use the stuffing method<br>
we discussed with payphones. however, this time, instead of using toilet paper, we’ll be using<br>
a piece of cardboard. simply stuff the cardboard up into the chute for the coine return and come<br>
back in a day or so and remove the cardboard. if successfull, you should have a fairly large<br>
sum of money. note, if there is a door of any sort to the coin return, make sure you don’t let it close<br>
or all your change will be stuck there and just mock you like the idiot you are.</p>
<ol start="6">
<li>Arcade Games</li>
</ol>
<p>i discovered this trick at my work while playing pinball. some older arcade games<br>
(this one was made in 1997) have a flaw that allows you to get a small amount of<br>
change out of them. first you need to locate the two buttons labeled ‘push for coin return’.<br>
if you can’t find those buttons, go kill yourself. now, push the button on the left in as<br>
far as it will go. while holding in the first one, push the right button down as far as it<br>
will go. if successfull, you should have about fifty cents. some machines will let you do<br>
this at least a good 10 times.</p>
<ol start="8">
<li>Conclusion</li>
</ol>
<p>so, there you have it. with some practice you should be able to pull these off without<br>
drawing too much attention to yourself. good luck!<br>
most of the info in this tutorial can be found in ‘vending machines, payphones and bill changers’ at<br>
<a href="http://www.textfiles.com/uploads/vendingm.txt" rel="nofollow noopener">http://www.textfiles.com/uploads/vendingm.txt</a> , ‘the anarchist cookbook, by jolly roger’ (available<br>
all over the fucking internet)., or Phone Losers of America <a href="http://www.phonelosers.org" rel="nofollow noopener">www.phonelosers.org</a>. the rest is just things<br>
i’ve discovered on my own. [/code]</p>
<p><a href="http://www.fagex.net/fgx/viewtopic.php?t=17146" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">http://www.fagex.net/fgx/viewtopic.php?t=17146</a></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/free-stuff/2848/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/free-stuff/2848/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 14 May 2006 21:05:09 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-2848-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/free-stuff/2848.rss">Free stuff?!?!</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
