<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Cwars ~317~</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/cwars-317/265046</link>
    <description>I&#39;ve been working on coding a 317 server lately, and im having issues adding the timer for cwars... I&#39;ve coded every object... I got the pwnscape source and it &quot;had cwars&quot; but no objects worked.... stairs didn&#39;t go up or down.. portals didn&#39;t teleport.. It was a freaking joke, but ive added pretty much added every aspect of cwars, the only thing i can&#39;t figure out is:

                       HOW DO YOU ADD A TIMER! 
                                          ~A timer for the waiting lobby;
                                          ~A timer for the actual game itself;
                                          ~An interface that displays remaining time.

Also, i plan to release the source when im done with it, (cwars is probably the smallest thing i&#39;ve done to the server).

So people be excited. The first 317 with working cwars(I THINK, IVE NEVER SEEN A 317 WITH WORKING CWARS!) and much more never before seen things</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2009 22:01:26 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/cwars-317/265046.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Cwars ~317~</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Infineon Infineon]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/infineon">@Infineon</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I’ve been working on coding a 317 server lately, and im having issues adding the timer for cwars… I’ve coded every object… I got the pwnscape source and it “had cwars” but no objects worked… stairs didn’t go up or down… portals didn’t teleport… It was a freaking joke, but ive added pretty much added every aspect of cwars, the only thing i can’t figure out is:</p>
<pre><code>                   HOW DO YOU ADD A TIMER! 
                                      ~A timer for the waiting lobby;
                                      ~A timer for the actual game itself;
                                      ~An interface that displays remaining time.
</code></pre>
<p>Also, i plan to release the source when im done with it, (cwars is probably the smallest thing i’ve done to the server).</p>
<p>So people be excited. The first 317 with working cwars(I THINK, IVE NEVER SEEN A 317 WITH WORKING CWARS!) and much more never before seen things</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/cwars-317/265046/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/cwars-317/265046/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2009 22:01:26 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-265046-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/cwars-317/265046.rss">Cwars ~317~</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
