<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>[659] Unorthodox Gaming - Dedi 24/7 - Most advanced 562+ today! x100 hits and mo</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/659-unorthodox-gaming-dedi-24-7-most-advanced-562-today-x100-hits-and-mo/539921</link>
    <description>[CENTER][IMG]http://img845.imageshack.us/img845/7776/1plm.png[/img]


[FONT=Arial Black][SIZE=4]Hate and trolls are not welcome in this thread[/SIZE], 
I will not reply to hate nor will i reply to trolls who seem to think there always right....[/FONT]

[SIZE=3]We have been developing this server for over 2 and a half years from an old very glitch base, After lots of hard effort and trail and error&#39;s we now have developed it into a very stable server with lots of custom features.
We have advertised it in the past under a different name. This time we are back! with a fresh appearance!![/SIZE]

[SIZE=5]Regular updates will be posted at our forums - [URL=http://www.unorthodoxgaming.co.uk/forums/]Click here[/URL][/SIZE]

[SIZE=6][COLOR=#CC0000]Custom - Unique - Amazing - Friendly Staff - DDoS Protected - Dedicated Servers[/COLOR][/SIZE]


[SIZE=5][COLOR=#CC0000]Join UnorthodoxGaming today! The community is waiting![/COLOR][/SIZE]


- Fully working x100 hits in both PVM/PVP

- Fully working Claw spec (Perfected)

- No known glitches with the new x100 system.

- Original content

- Wildywyrm combat system (never before seen)

- Perfected Combat system for all combat styles! Both in PVP and PVM.

- World Boss which spawns every hour and drops very rare loot. This also has a very hard and complex combat system, similar to Wildywyrm.

- Hard bosses, powerful multi-target moves, that will require a team of players to defeat.

- Nex - Corp - Normad - Wildywyrm - World Bosses - Countless number of bosses~

- All armor and items in 659 cache has been added with correct stats and gfx/Anim

- Decent drop rates

- Easy to make money

- Good Economy

- Great selection of items available in shops

- Lots of donator benefits from the pkshop/donatorshop

- Curses work in both pvp and pvm (Fully working) + Custom effects against bosses

- Lots of custom events and ways to receive items.

- Fully working makeover mage

- Custom Nex combat system

-1 Click combat (PVP/PVM)

-1 Click pickup

- Custom and extremely unique content.

-Weekly updates with developers that can basically achieve anything. Where time is available.

-Lots of more positive content....

(This is not a leech)



[IMG]http://img46.imageshack.us/img46/3757/zqq.png[/img]

[IMG]http://img28.imageshack.us/img28/5392/m5a.png[/img]

[IMG]http://imageshack.com/a/img855/6666/qnlu.png[/img]

[IMG]http://img825.imageshack.us/img825/6151/adver2.jpg[/img]

[IMG]http://img3.imageshack.us/img3/3287/pic6xy.png[/img]

[IMG]http://img3.imageshack.us/img3/8471/pic7h.png[/img]
 

[COLOR=#CC0000][SIZE=5]For webclient please visit [URL=http://unorthodoxgaming.co.uk/webclients/webclient659.php]Unorthodox 659[/URL]

For our JAR Client please visit [URL=http://unorthodoxgaming.co.uk/webclients/UG659.jar]Unorthodox 659 - JAR Client[/URL]

For our Client Package please visit [URL=http://unorthodoxgaming.co.uk/webclients/UG659Package.zip]Unorthodox 659 - Client Package[/URL]

Visit our Website - [URL=http://www.unorthodoxgaming.co.uk]Unorthodox Gaming[/URL][/SIZE][/COLOR]


[B][SIZE=6]Recent Updates
[/SIZE][/B]


[B]Slayer: [/B]

Slayer has been improved for the better, there is a 30% chance to get a boss task and now 70% chance for a normal task.

Boss tasks: you will be assigned to kill 1-31.
Normal tasks: you will be assigned to kill 1-71.

Each kill gives you 1 tokkul an a further 25 tokkul per task.


[B]Magic:[/B]

Magic has been greatly improved for fairness and features, Miasmic spells can now be autocasted on both monsters and players.

However damage has been decreased in PVP to stop overpowered Fcing.
On monsters the damage is still high!

Freezing in pvp is now less overpowered also, now when you freeze a player you will not be able to freeze them for a further 5 seconds to allow them to move if they do not want to be frozen.


[B]Range:[/B]

A few bows have been nurfed in pvp, however some bows still need to be nurfed, I have not forgotten!



[B]Divine and Ely:[/B]

These can work against all combat styles! and no longer stop rangers from attacking. 


[B]Shop: [/B]

All shops have been reworked with new items and a further 4 or 5 shops have been added new.
Also: notes have been added to the shops to allow it easier to buy items for skills.



[B]Prices: [/B]

All prices have been lowered of drops to help the ECO re-stabilize itself. 


[B]Drops:[/B]

All drop rates have been lowered, Some more then others.
Also crystal keys have been added to most high level monsters.


[B]Bugged NPCs:[/B]

Some npcs such as torms and elites have been known to glitch which causes them to keep killing themselves and drop items. These have been fixed! 


[B]Minigames:[/B]

Graft Central: Is a skilling mini-game still in beta, with only Wcing added, cutting trees in this mini-game will give you noted logs rather then un-noted, however these logs can be sold to the GE store for a high price which is a good money making method for you pures!

Also per note you will receive GraftCentral Points to spend on EXP, and also items in the near future.

SW: High prices rewards have been removed from the random item rewards to avoid easy profit.


[B]Trading:[/B]

The trading system has been perfected to stop players losing items if another player doesn&#39;t not have enough slots in his/her inventory, You will now not lose items because it will no longer let you trade if there&#39;s not enough space. 


[B]Banking:[/B]

A few bugs have been fixed concerning the Ancient coins system, they will not be converted unless you add coins to your bank and also there will be no chance to lose them, like in the past a bug would make them glitch and disappear if you didn&#39;t have enough space.


[B]New commands: [/B]

Most new commands will be added to ::commands
also a new command ::points will list all of your in game points that you currently hold.
also to claim your vote rewards do ::vote


[B]Automatic Vote System:[/B]

I spent over 12 hours creating the HTML, CSS and PHP scripts to allow users to vote on the website to claim in game rewards, the system is very stable and will not cause any bugs.

However at the moment because of the security I have added into the PHP scripts it will not let people vote while having port 80 open because it thinks they are using a proxy or VPN connection.

This will change in the near future to allow all players to vote even if they have port 80 open

Rewards can be claimed by typing ::vote in game.



[B]Vengeance: [/B]

I have greatly improved the vengeance system allowing any combat style and weapon to be venged if the other player has vengeance active.

In the further this effect will be added against NPCS.



[B]PVP: [/B]

Purple sweets are now not effective in PVP because they are too common and players abuse this feature.

Easter eggs now have the feature that purple sweets once had.

While in PVP combat players can no longer teleport or drop items, however to this update if a player is in LEVEL 20 or above wilderness, they can use a teletab crafted by RC to safely teleport back to a main town. However this will not work while in combat either.


[B][SIZE=3]Monsters New Update:[/SIZE][/B]

[B]Nomad:[/B]

Nomad has been added and is now the strongest boss InGame with good drops .
Protection which can be used against him is Mage Protection
his best drops can be Primal Weapons.
To go there you need to type ::nomad

[B]Ice Strykewyrm:[/B]

They have been added to drop Staff of lights, due to this update, staff of lights are no longer available in the shops.
You can use melee Protection against it to soak some damage.
To teleport there you have to type ::iceworms

[B]Frost Dragons:[/B]

They have been added to drop noted frost dragon bones with chances to drop other valuable items.
Protection used for Frost Dragons is Melee Protection.
You can get Frost Dragon Mask as a drop from Frost Dragons.
You can teleport there by typing ::frosts.



[B]Melee Vs Combat[/B]:

This has always been a problem until now, I managed to figure out the problem causing it and fix it in under 20 mins, which was quite a fast fix considering the mount of trouble it was causing in game. I can now say Melee feels a lot better.


[B]Auto Click Detector:[/B]

This has been added to thieving only because it is still in beta, as you may know it needs some improvements, however when finished this should stop those selfish Auto-Clickers permanently.


[B][SIZE=6]Older Updates loged[/SIZE][/B]


[B]06-24-2013, 02:40 PM[/B]

All teleports reworked to stop the bug abusers and glitches while using a ranged.
NOTE: anyone suspected of doing this previously will be punished if found out!! We do not tolerate BUG ABUSERS. Bugs should be reported not exploited!
If further bugs are still present then do the right thing and report them or suffer consequences!
Lots of other commands such as:
::commands
::monsters
::pricelist
::drops
::players
Have also be reworked for improvements.
Also a few locations have changed to fix other known glitches.


[B]06-25-2013, 01:27 AM[/B]

Updates implemented follow such as: (Small description)
Further areas which enabled players to glitch when ranging bosses.
Players should now not be able to attack each other when over the SafeZone borders.
Server-sided Player Logs improved making them easier to be searched etc...
Few other small bugs not worth mentioning...


[B]06-27-2013, 02:34 PM[/B]

Altered the curse prayers to make them more realistic due to the fact people have been complaining about turmoil not being powerful and common PVP glitches with Soul Split.
All these problems have been fixed.

The bug fix I did this week failed to stop bug abusers, but with help from players feedback I managed to create a solution to this matter.
The Bug regarding, being able to teleport and still attack monsters has now also been fixed.

Also with reports of being able to glitch the Dbow in both PVP and PVM, I had to changed a few range weapons in order to achieve the bug fix.
The Dark bow can now only be used with Dragon arrows.
The Zaryte Bow has been changed so that it no long can use normal arrows, it now required a new type of arrow called &#39;Sagittarian arrows (p++)&#39; which can be brought from the slayer shop for 100 tokkul.
The actual bow has lost its overpowered ranged strength, however with the &#39;Sagittarian arrows (p++)&#39; equipped the bow now actually has more ranged strength combined.
The Slayer Shop has also had some changes regarding item costs, I hope you are all pleased with the lowed prices of these items, The items are now between 50%-75% lower in price.
The following items now require a Defence level to wear:
All Nex items including Torva, Pernix, Virtus require 80 Defence.
The Zaryle Bow &amp; Sagittarian arrows (p++) require 90 Ranged.
Chaotic Rapier, Chaotic Maul, Chaotic Longsword and the Abyssal vine whip require 80 Attack &amp; Strength.
Chaotic C&#39;Bow requires 80 Attack &amp; Ranged.
Chaotic Staff requires 80 Attack &amp; Magic.


[B]07-03-2013, 09:42 PM[/B]


New Clanwars area &amp; purple portal for further updates( check it out by doing the normal ::clanwars command).
All Crossbows now require bolts to fire (previously could be fired with arrows too).
Both melee and Ranged Void have damage increases when wearing the full set (20%).
Dharoks now increases players strength when falling below 5000 health(40%).
A few weapons that did have attack anaimations have now been fixed(Such as Vesta&#39;s Spear &amp; Statius Warhammer).
Some PVP specials have been Nerfed due to being Overpowered and Unfair, although specials have not been altered when fighting NPC&#39;s(Weapons will be Nerfed again if seen too strong).
The Magic skill in PVP has been improved making it better to fight with and also requires no runes. including both 1 click &amp; Auto attack.
Some items have had their stats changed to avoid being to overpowered along with some prayer effects.
Both Divine and Ely Spirit Shields have been altered to absorb damage, and also allow ranged to hit(Previously glitched when getting hit by a ranger).
Some known items in stores has no stats, they have now been restored(Ranged gear).


[B]07-04-2013, 05:41 PM[/B]


Nex has had improvements making it more enjoyable, The health has been lowered from 300k to 250k, however the damage has been increased due to many players finding it easy. Also all the animations have changed to bring a better experience while fighting him.
Previously if a player was frozen him or her could still follow another player, this glitch caused hassle in many areas, but today I can report that it has been fixed and you can no longer follow if you are frozen.
The prayer alter at ::pray, now allows you to burn dragon bones and Ourg bones, however the prices have been increased in order to help players train prayer while also improving the ECO very slightly.
The slayer shop now buys back your previously brought or PKed items for 70% of the original buying price while also not allowing any other &#39;Non Tokkul&#39; items to be sold.


[B]07-08-2013, 04:13 PM[/B]


PVP:
The glitch where players teleport on dealth is now fixed.
Also the teleblock feature on the normal spellbook works again.
Players cannot teleport while in combat with another player through out the game
Teletabs can be used beyond level 20 wilderness as long as your not effected by teleblock nor in combat.
Jail:
Complete new jail with a flawless freezing and teleblock system. players are now permanently jailed until a member of staff releases them, unlike before when you could re-log.
Commands:
Moderators are now excluded from the 5 second command rule to ensure they can do there job correctly.

Skills:
Mining has been re-worked to stop any flaws it had and I can now safely say its allot more stable.
Due to the fix of mining, it would of been a lot slower to level so the exp rates have be greatly increased.

Bugs/Dupes:
Over 5 big glitches have been fixed, the majority of people didn&#39;t know about which is why I took immediate action in case of these glitches being detected. However details on these bugs will not be released for security reasons.
The biggest of all glitches was the one glitch that kept taking us offline last year due to exploiters but I can now safely say its been fixed.
Global Drops:
The Drops system has been re-worked to give the game a better sense of feel, while also letting other fellow players know your drops. These features display both Loot share and solo kill drops.
Chatbox:
A Chat box has been added to the forums for all users, to use this you will need to login.


[B]07-09-2013, 09:38 PM[/B]

All shops have bee reworked to make them more user friendly, While also adding a titles on all interfaces.
At least 5 new shops, and a lot of items have been added to the game via the shops.
Some prices have been increased. and all items have prices if they didn&#39;t before.
All items available in shops now work properly(Some items didn&#39;t have attack animations before hand).



[SIZE=3]Join now, We are growing fast!, We have industry standard qualifications in Networking and expert skills in Web development/Design, Java Programming.[/SIZE]



[SIZE=5]You will not regret it![/SIZE]

[/center]</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 05 Apr 2014 19:30:24 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/659-unorthodox-gaming-dedi-24-7-most-advanced-562-today-x100-hits-and-mo/539921.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>[659] Unorthodox Gaming - Dedi 24/7 - Most advanced 562+ today! x100 hits and mo</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@gregsterere gregsterere]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/gregsterere">@gregsterere</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Get online guys!</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/659-unorthodox-gaming-dedi-24-7-most-advanced-562-today-x100-hits-and-mo/539921/12">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/659-unorthodox-gaming-dedi-24-7-most-advanced-562-today-x100-hits-and-mo/539921/12</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 05 Apr 2014 19:30:24 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-539921-12</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/659-unorthodox-gaming-dedi-24-7-most-advanced-562-today-x100-hits-and-mo/539921.rss">[659] Unorthodox Gaming - Dedi 24/7 - Most advanced 562+ today! x100 hits and mo</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[659] Unorthodox Gaming - Dedi 24/7 - Most advanced 562+ today! x100 hits and mo</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@UGNetwork UGNetwork]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/ugnetwork">@UGNetwork</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Nice server, we need more players though!</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/659-unorthodox-gaming-dedi-24-7-most-advanced-562-today-x100-hits-and-mo/539921/11">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/659-unorthodox-gaming-dedi-24-7-most-advanced-562-today-x100-hits-and-mo/539921/11</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2014 04:22:51 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-539921-11</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/659-unorthodox-gaming-dedi-24-7-most-advanced-562-today-x100-hits-and-mo/539921.rss">[659] Unorthodox Gaming - Dedi 24/7 - Most advanced 562+ today! x100 hits and mo</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[659] Unorthodox Gaming - Dedi 24/7 - Most advanced 562+ today! x100 hits and mo</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@gregsterere gregsterere]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/gregsterere">@gregsterere</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Thanks for the support, i’ll look forward to seeing you in-game! <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/smiley.png?v=5" title=":smiley:" class="emoji" alt=":smiley:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/659-unorthodox-gaming-dedi-24-7-most-advanced-562-today-x100-hits-and-mo/539921/10">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/659-unorthodox-gaming-dedi-24-7-most-advanced-562-today-x100-hits-and-mo/539921/10</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 23 Feb 2014 14:29:30 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-539921-10</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/659-unorthodox-gaming-dedi-24-7-most-advanced-562-today-x100-hits-and-mo/539921.rss">[659] Unorthodox Gaming - Dedi 24/7 - Most advanced 562+ today! x100 hits and mo</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[659] Unorthodox Gaming - Dedi 24/7 - Most advanced 562+ today! x100 hits and mo</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Devastor Devastor]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/devastor">@Devastor</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Really a great RSPS.<br>
I am so happy I have found this server. The economy is really good, the bosses are not too easy, and the players are really friendly.<br>
I hope to see you guys ingame <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=5" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/659-unorthodox-gaming-dedi-24-7-most-advanced-562-today-x100-hits-and-mo/539921/9">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/659-unorthodox-gaming-dedi-24-7-most-advanced-562-today-x100-hits-and-mo/539921/9</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2014 22:16:53 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-539921-9</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/659-unorthodox-gaming-dedi-24-7-most-advanced-562-today-x100-hits-and-mo/539921.rss">[659] Unorthodox Gaming - Dedi 24/7 - Most advanced 562+ today! x100 hits and mo</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[659] Unorthodox Gaming - Dedi 24/7 - Most advanced 562+ today! x100 hits and mo</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@gregsterere gregsterere]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/gregsterere">@gregsterere</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Thanks man i must of made a mistake! Glad to see you all back <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=5" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/659-unorthodox-gaming-dedi-24-7-most-advanced-562-today-x100-hits-and-mo/539921/8">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/659-unorthodox-gaming-dedi-24-7-most-advanced-562-today-x100-hits-and-mo/539921/8</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 17 Feb 2014 14:15:23 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-539921-8</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/659-unorthodox-gaming-dedi-24-7-most-advanced-562-today-x100-hits-and-mo/539921.rss">[659] Unorthodox Gaming - Dedi 24/7 - Most advanced 562+ today! x100 hits and mo</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[659] Unorthodox Gaming - Dedi 24/7 - Most advanced 562+ today! x100 hits and mo</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@morterdestroyer morterdestroyer]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/morterdestroyer">@morterdestroyer</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I love 659’s, my name IG is “Synx” downloading cache right now, my links didn’t work but I found the adv on another forum so i posted below, i hope you don’t mind.</p>
<p>The links are bad. Here are the working ones.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Webclient </span><a href="http://unorthodoxgaming.co.uk/webclients/webclient659.php" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">http://unorthodoxgaming.co.uk/webclients/webclient659.php</a><br>
<span class="bbcode-b">JAR Download</span> <a href="http://unorthodoxgaming.co.uk/webclients/UG659.jar" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">http://unorthodoxgaming.co.uk/webclients/UG659.jar</a><br>
<span class="bbcode-b">Client Packages</span> <a href="http://unorthodoxgaming.co.uk/webclients/UG659Package.zip" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">http://unorthodoxgaming.co.uk/webclients/UG659Package.zip</a><br>
<span class="bbcode-b">Website</span> <a href="http://www.unorthodoxgaming.co.uk" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">http://www.unorthodoxgaming.co.uk</a></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/659-unorthodox-gaming-dedi-24-7-most-advanced-562-today-x100-hits-and-mo/539921/7">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/659-unorthodox-gaming-dedi-24-7-most-advanced-562-today-x100-hits-and-mo/539921/7</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 16 Feb 2014 04:47:29 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-539921-7</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/659-unorthodox-gaming-dedi-24-7-most-advanced-562-today-x100-hits-and-mo/539921.rss">[659] Unorthodox Gaming - Dedi 24/7 - Most advanced 562+ today! x100 hits and mo</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[659] Unorthodox Gaming - Dedi 24/7 - Most advanced 562+ today! x100 hits and mo</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@lord0ftacos lord0ftacos]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/lord0ftacos">@lord0ftacos</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Wow! Glad to see this back! I remember this <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/smiley.png?v=5" title=":smiley:" class="emoji" alt=":smiley:"> I was a donator and maxed <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/smiley.png?v=5" title=":smiley:" class="emoji" alt=":smiley:"></p>
<p>Can’t wait to come back guys!</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/659-unorthodox-gaming-dedi-24-7-most-advanced-562-today-x100-hits-and-mo/539921/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/659-unorthodox-gaming-dedi-24-7-most-advanced-562-today-x100-hits-and-mo/539921/6</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 16 Feb 2014 03:11:55 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-539921-6</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/659-unorthodox-gaming-dedi-24-7-most-advanced-562-today-x100-hits-and-mo/539921.rss">[659] Unorthodox Gaming - Dedi 24/7 - Most advanced 562+ today! x100 hits and mo</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[659] Unorthodox Gaming - Dedi 24/7 - Most advanced 562+ today! x100 hits and mo</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Devastor Devastor]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/devastor">@Devastor</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Amazing server!<br>
Really, so happy it’s back online <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=5" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/659-unorthodox-gaming-dedi-24-7-most-advanced-562-today-x100-hits-and-mo/539921/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/659-unorthodox-gaming-dedi-24-7-most-advanced-562-today-x100-hits-and-mo/539921/5</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 15 Feb 2014 19:17:35 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-539921-5</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/659-unorthodox-gaming-dedi-24-7-most-advanced-562-today-x100-hits-and-mo/539921.rss">[659] Unorthodox Gaming - Dedi 24/7 - Most advanced 562+ today! x100 hits and mo</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[659] Unorthodox Gaming - Dedi 24/7 - Most advanced 562+ today! x100 hits and mo</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@gregsterere gregsterere]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/gregsterere">@gregsterere</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Thanks! Hopefully see some new faces soon</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/659-unorthodox-gaming-dedi-24-7-most-advanced-562-today-x100-hits-and-mo/539921/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/659-unorthodox-gaming-dedi-24-7-most-advanced-562-today-x100-hits-and-mo/539921/4</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 15 Feb 2014 02:25:11 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-539921-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/659-unorthodox-gaming-dedi-24-7-most-advanced-562-today-x100-hits-and-mo/539921.rss">[659] Unorthodox Gaming - Dedi 24/7 - Most advanced 562+ today! x100 hits and mo</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[659] Unorthodox Gaming - Dedi 24/7 - Most advanced 562+ today! x100 hits and mo</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Ix_Soulcist_xI Soulcist]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/ix_soulcist_xi">@Ix_Soulcist_xI</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Looks interesting enough I’d say, good luck.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/659-unorthodox-gaming-dedi-24-7-most-advanced-562-today-x100-hits-and-mo/539921/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/659-unorthodox-gaming-dedi-24-7-most-advanced-562-today-x100-hits-and-mo/539921/3</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 11 Feb 2014 12:38:11 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-539921-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/659-unorthodox-gaming-dedi-24-7-most-advanced-562-today-x100-hits-and-mo/539921.rss">[659] Unorthodox Gaming - Dedi 24/7 - Most advanced 562+ today! x100 hits and mo</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[659] Unorthodox Gaming - Dedi 24/7 - Most advanced 562+ today! x100 hits and mo</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@UGNetwork UGNetwork]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/ugnetwork">@UGNetwork</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Nice, i see its back online! i loved this server</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/659-unorthodox-gaming-dedi-24-7-most-advanced-562-today-x100-hits-and-mo/539921/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/659-unorthodox-gaming-dedi-24-7-most-advanced-562-today-x100-hits-and-mo/539921/2</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 11 Feb 2014 12:32:44 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-539921-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/659-unorthodox-gaming-dedi-24-7-most-advanced-562-today-x100-hits-and-mo/539921.rss">[659] Unorthodox Gaming - Dedi 24/7 - Most advanced 562+ today! x100 hits and mo</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[659] Unorthodox Gaming - Dedi 24/7 - Most advanced 562+ today! x100 hits and mo</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@gregsterere gregsterere]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/gregsterere">@gregsterere</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[CENTER]<img src="http://img845.imageshack.us/img845/7776/1plm.png" alt width="" height=""></p>
<p>[FONT=Arial Black][SIZE=4]Hate and trolls are not welcome in this thread[/SIZE],<br>
I will not reply to hate nor will i reply to trolls who seem to think there always right…[/FONT]</p>
<p>[SIZE=3]We have been developing this server for over 2 and a half years from an old very glitch base, After lots of hard effort and trail and error’s we now have developed it into a very stable server with lots of custom features.<br>
We have advertised it in the past under a different name. This time we are back! with a fresh appearance!![/SIZE]</p>
<p>[SIZE=5]Regular updates will be posted at our forums - [URL=http://www.unorthodoxgaming.co.uk/forums/]Click here[/URL][/SIZE]</p>
<p>[SIZE=6][COLOR=#CC0000]Custom - Unique - Amazing - Friendly Staff - DDoS Protected - Dedicated Servers[/COLOR][/SIZE]</p>
<p>[SIZE=5][COLOR=#CC0000]Join UnorthodoxGaming today! The community is waiting![/COLOR][/SIZE]</p>
<ul>
<li>
<p>Fully working x100 hits in both PVM/PVP</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Fully working Claw spec (Perfected)</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>No known glitches with the new x100 system.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Original content</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Wildywyrm combat system (never before seen)</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Perfected Combat system for all combat styles! Both in PVP and PVM.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>World Boss which spawns every hour and drops very rare loot. This also has a very hard and complex combat system, similar to Wildywyrm.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Hard bosses, powerful multi-target moves, that will require a team of players to defeat.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Nex - Corp - Normad - Wildywyrm - World Bosses - Countless number of bosses~</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>All armor and items in 659 cache has been added with correct stats and gfx/Anim</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Decent drop rates</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Easy to make money</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Good Economy</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Great selection of items available in shops</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Lots of donator benefits from the pkshop/donatorshop</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Curses work in both pvp and pvm (Fully working) + Custom effects against bosses</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Lots of custom events and ways to receive items.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Fully working makeover mage</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Custom Nex combat system</p>
</li>
</ul>
<p>-1 Click combat (PVP/PVM)</p>
<p>-1 Click pickup</p>
<ul>
<li>Custom and extremely unique content.</li>
</ul>
<p>-Weekly updates with developers that can basically achieve anything. Where time is available.</p>
<p>-Lots of more positive content…</p>
<p>(This is not a leech)</p>
<p><img src="http://img46.imageshack.us/img46/3757/zqq.png" alt width="" height=""></p>
<p><img src="http://img28.imageshack.us/img28/5392/m5a.png" alt width="" height=""></p>
<p><img src="http://imageshack.com/a/img855/6666/qnlu.png" alt width="" height=""></p>
<p><img src="http://img825.imageshack.us/img825/6151/adver2.jpg" alt width="" height=""></p>
<p><img src="http://img3.imageshack.us/img3/3287/pic6xy.png" alt width="" height=""></p>
<p><img src="http://img3.imageshack.us/img3/8471/pic7h.png" alt width="" height=""></p>
<p>[COLOR=#CC0000][SIZE=5]For webclient please visit [URL=http://unorthodoxgaming.co.uk/webclients/webclient659.php]Unorthodox 659[/URL]</p>
<p>For our JAR Client please visit [URL=http://unorthodoxgaming.co.uk/webclients/UG659.jar]Unorthodox 659 - JAR Client[/URL]</p>
<p>For our Client Package please visit [URL=http://unorthodoxgaming.co.uk/webclients/UG659Package.zip]Unorthodox 659 - Client Package[/URL]</p>
<p>Visit our Website - [URL=http://www.unorthodoxgaming.co.uk]Unorthodox Gaming[/URL][/SIZE][/COLOR]</p>
<p>[B][SIZE=6]Recent Updates<br>
[/SIZE][/B]</p>
<p>[B]Slayer: [/B]</p>
<p>Slayer has been improved for the better, there is a 30% chance to get a boss task and now 70% chance for a normal task.</p>
<p>Boss tasks: you will be assigned to kill 1-31.<br>
Normal tasks: you will be assigned to kill 1-71.</p>
<p>Each kill gives you 1 tokkul an a further 25 tokkul per task.</p>
<p>[B]Magic:[/B]</p>
<p>Magic has been greatly improved for fairness and features, Miasmic spells can now be autocasted on both monsters and players.</p>
<p>However damage has been decreased in PVP to stop overpowered Fcing.<br>
On monsters the damage is still high!</p>
<p>Freezing in pvp is now less overpowered also, now when you freeze a player you will not be able to freeze them for a further 5 seconds to allow them to move if they do not want to be frozen.</p>
<p>[B]Range:[/B]</p>
<p>A few bows have been nurfed in pvp, however some bows still need to be nurfed, I have not forgotten!</p>
<p>[B]Divine and Ely:[/B]</p>
<p>These can work against all combat styles! and no longer stop rangers from attacking.</p>
<p>[B]Shop: [/B]</p>
<p>All shops have been reworked with new items and a further 4 or 5 shops have been added new.<br>
Also: notes have been added to the shops to allow it easier to buy items for skills.</p>
<p>[B]Prices: [/B]</p>
<p>All prices have been lowered of drops to help the ECO re-stabilize itself.</p>
<p>[B]Drops:[/B]</p>
<p>All drop rates have been lowered, Some more then others.<br>
Also crystal keys have been added to most high level monsters.</p>
<p>[B]Bugged NPCs:[/B]</p>
<p>Some npcs such as torms and elites have been known to glitch which causes them to keep killing themselves and drop items. These have been fixed!</p>
<p>[B]Minigames:[/B]</p>
<p>Graft Central: Is a skilling mini-game still in beta, with only Wcing added, cutting trees in this mini-game will give you noted logs rather then un-noted, however these logs can be sold to the GE store for a high price which is a good money making method for you pures!</p>
<p>Also per note you will receive GraftCentral Points to spend on EXP, and also items in the near future.</p>
<p>SW: High prices rewards have been removed from the random item rewards to avoid easy profit.</p>
<p>[B]Trading:[/B]</p>
<p>The trading system has been perfected to stop players losing items if another player doesn’t not have enough slots in his/her inventory, You will now not lose items because it will no longer let you trade if there’s not enough space.</p>
<p>[B]Banking:[/B]</p>
<p>A few bugs have been fixed concerning the Ancient coins system, they will not be converted unless you add coins to your bank and also there will be no chance to lose them, like in the past a bug would make them glitch and disappear if you didn’t have enough space.</p>
<p>[B]New commands: [/B]</p>
<p>Most new commands will be added to ::commands<br>
also a new command ::points will list all of your in game points that you currently hold.<br>
also to claim your vote rewards do ::vote</p>
<p>[B]Automatic Vote System:[/B]</p>
<p>I spent over 12 hours creating the HTML, CSS and PHP scripts to allow users to vote on the website to claim in game rewards, the system is very stable and will not cause any bugs.</p>
<p>However at the moment because of the security I have added into the PHP scripts it will not let people vote while having port 80 open because it thinks they are using a proxy or VPN connection.</p>
<p>This will change in the near future to allow all players to vote even if they have port 80 open</p>
<p>Rewards can be claimed by typing ::vote in game.</p>
<p>[B]Vengeance: [/B]</p>
<p>I have greatly improved the vengeance system allowing any combat style and weapon to be venged if the other player has vengeance active.</p>
<p>In the further this effect will be added against NPCS.</p>
<p>[B]PVP: [/B]</p>
<p>Purple sweets are now not effective in PVP because they are too common and players abuse this feature.</p>
<p>Easter eggs now have the feature that purple sweets once had.</p>
<p>While in PVP combat players can no longer teleport or drop items, however to this update if a player is in LEVEL 20 or above wilderness, they can use a teletab crafted by RC to safely teleport back to a main town. However this will not work while in combat either.</p>
<p>[B][SIZE=3]Monsters New Update:[/SIZE][/B]</p>
<p>[B]Nomad:[/B]</p>
<p>Nomad has been added and is now the strongest boss InGame with good drops .<br>
Protection which can be used against him is Mage Protection<br>
his best drops can be Primal Weapons.<br>
To go there you need to type ::nomad</p>
<p>[B]Ice Strykewyrm:[/B]</p>
<p>They have been added to drop Staff of lights, due to this update, staff of lights are no longer available in the shops.<br>
You can use melee Protection against it to soak some damage.<br>
To teleport there you have to type ::iceworms</p>
<p>[B]Frost Dragons:[/B]</p>
<p>They have been added to drop noted frost dragon bones with chances to drop other valuable items.<br>
Protection used for Frost Dragons is Melee Protection.<br>
You can get Frost Dragon Mask as a drop from Frost Dragons.<br>
You can teleport there by typing ::frosts.</p>
<p>[B]Melee Vs Combat[/B]:</p>
<p>This has always been a problem until now, I managed to figure out the problem causing it and fix it in under 20 mins, which was quite a fast fix considering the mount of trouble it was causing in game. I can now say Melee feels a lot better.</p>
<p>[B]Auto Click Detector:[/B]</p>
<p>This has been added to thieving only because it is still in beta, as you may know it needs some improvements, however when finished this should stop those selfish Auto-Clickers permanently.</p>
<p>[B][SIZE=6]Older Updates loged[/SIZE][/B]</p>
<p>[B]06-24-2013, 02:40 PM[/B]</p>
<p>All teleports reworked to stop the bug abusers and glitches while using a ranged.<br>
NOTE: anyone suspected of doing this previously will be punished if found out!! We do not tolerate BUG ABUSERS. Bugs should be reported not exploited!<br>
If further bugs are still present then do the right thing and report them or suffer consequences!<br>
Lots of other commands such as:<br>
::commands<br>
::monsters<br>
::pricelist<br>
::drops<br>
::players<br>
Have also be reworked for improvements.<br>
Also a few locations have changed to fix other known glitches.</p>
<p>[B]06-25-2013, 01:27 AM[/B]</p>
<p>Updates implemented follow such as: (Small description)<br>
Further areas which enabled players to glitch when ranging bosses.<br>
Players should now not be able to attack each other when over the SafeZone borders.<br>
Server-sided Player Logs improved making them easier to be searched etc…<br>
Few other small bugs not worth mentioning…</p>
<p>[B]06-27-2013, 02:34 PM[/B]</p>
<p>Altered the curse prayers to make them more realistic due to the fact people have been complaining about turmoil not being powerful and common PVP glitches with Soul Split.<br>
All these problems have been fixed.</p>
<p>The bug fix I did this week failed to stop bug abusers, but with help from players feedback I managed to create a solution to this matter.<br>
The Bug regarding, being able to teleport and still attack monsters has now also been fixed.</p>
<p>Also with reports of being able to glitch the Dbow in both PVP and PVM, I had to changed a few range weapons in order to achieve the bug fix.<br>
The Dark bow can now only be used with Dragon arrows.<br>
The Zaryte Bow has been changed so that it no long can use normal arrows, it now required a new type of arrow called ‘Sagittarian arrows (p++)’ which can be brought from the slayer shop for 100 tokkul.<br>
The actual bow has lost its overpowered ranged strength, however with the ‘Sagittarian arrows (p++)’ equipped the bow now actually has more ranged strength combined.<br>
The Slayer Shop has also had some changes regarding item costs, I hope you are all pleased with the lowed prices of these items, The items are now between 50%-75% lower in price.<br>
The following items now require a Defence level to wear:<br>
All Nex items including Torva, Pernix, Virtus require 80 Defence.<br>
The Zaryle Bow &amp; Sagittarian arrows (p++) require 90 Ranged.<br>
Chaotic Rapier, Chaotic Maul, Chaotic Longsword and the Abyssal vine whip require 80 Attack &amp; Strength.<br>
Chaotic C’Bow requires 80 Attack &amp; Ranged.<br>
Chaotic Staff requires 80 Attack &amp; Magic.</p>
<p>[B]07-03-2013, 09:42 PM[/B]</p>
<p>New Clanwars area &amp; purple portal for further updates( check it out by doing the normal ::clanwars command).<br>
All Crossbows now require bolts to fire (previously could be fired with arrows too).<br>
Both melee and Ranged Void have damage increases when wearing the full set (20%).<br>
Dharoks now increases players strength when falling below 5000 health(40%).<br>
A few weapons that did have attack anaimations have now been fixed(Such as Vesta’s Spear &amp; Statius Warhammer).<br>
Some PVP specials have been Nerfed due to being Overpowered and Unfair, although specials have not been altered when fighting NPC’s(Weapons will be Nerfed again if seen too strong).<br>
The Magic skill in PVP has been improved making it better to fight with and also requires no runes. including both 1 click &amp; Auto attack.<br>
Some items have had their stats changed to avoid being to overpowered along with some prayer effects.<br>
Both Divine and Ely Spirit Shields have been altered to absorb damage, and also allow ranged to hit(Previously glitched when getting hit by a ranger).<br>
Some known items in stores has no stats, they have now been restored(Ranged gear).</p>
<p>[B]07-04-2013, 05:41 PM[/B]</p>
<p>Nex has had improvements making it more enjoyable, The health has been lowered from 300k to 250k, however the damage has been increased due to many players finding it easy. Also all the animations have changed to bring a better experience while fighting him.<br>
Previously if a player was frozen him or her could still follow another player, this glitch caused hassle in many areas, but today I can report that it has been fixed and you can no longer follow if you are frozen.<br>
The prayer alter at ::pray, now allows you to burn dragon bones and Ourg bones, however the prices have been increased in order to help players train prayer while also improving the ECO very slightly.<br>
The slayer shop now buys back your previously brought or PKed items for 70% of the original buying price while also not allowing any other ‘Non Tokkul’ items to be sold.</p>
<p>[B]07-08-2013, 04:13 PM[/B]</p>
<p>PVP:<br>
The glitch where players teleport on dealth is now fixed.<br>
Also the teleblock feature on the normal spellbook works again.<br>
Players cannot teleport while in combat with another player through out the game<br>
Teletabs can be used beyond level 20 wilderness as long as your not effected by teleblock nor in combat.<br>
Jail:<br>
Complete new jail with a flawless freezing and teleblock system. players are now permanently jailed until a member of staff releases them, unlike before when you could re-log.<br>
Commands:<br>
Moderators are now excluded from the 5 second command rule to ensure they can do there job correctly.</p>
<p>Skills:<br>
Mining has been re-worked to stop any flaws it had and I can now safely say its allot more stable.<br>
Due to the fix of mining, it would of been a lot slower to level so the exp rates have be greatly increased.</p>
<p>Bugs/Dupes:<br>
Over 5 big glitches have been fixed, the majority of people didn’t know about which is why I took immediate action in case of these glitches being detected. However details on these bugs will not be released for security reasons.<br>
The biggest of all glitches was the one glitch that kept taking us offline last year due to exploiters but I can now safely say its been fixed.<br>
Global Drops:<br>
The Drops system has been re-worked to give the game a better sense of feel, while also letting other fellow players know your drops. These features display both Loot share and solo kill drops.<br>
Chatbox:<br>
A Chat box has been added to the forums for all users, to use this you will need to login.</p>
<p>[B]07-09-2013, 09:38 PM[/B]</p>
<p>All shops have bee reworked to make them more user friendly, While also adding a titles on all interfaces.<br>
At least 5 new shops, and a lot of items have been added to the game via the shops.<br>
Some prices have been increased. and all items have prices if they didn’t before.<br>
All items available in shops now work properly(Some items didn’t have attack animations before hand).</p>
<p>[SIZE=3]Join now, We are growing fast!, We have industry standard qualifications in Networking and expert skills in Web development/Design, Java Programming.[/SIZE]</p>
<p>[SIZE=5]You will not regret it![/SIZE]</p>
<p>[/center]</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/659-unorthodox-gaming-dedi-24-7-most-advanced-562-today-x100-hits-and-mo/539921/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/659-unorthodox-gaming-dedi-24-7-most-advanced-562-today-x100-hits-and-mo/539921/1</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 10 Feb 2014 15:25:54 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-539921-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/659-unorthodox-gaming-dedi-24-7-most-advanced-562-today-x100-hits-and-mo/539921.rss">[659] Unorthodox Gaming - Dedi 24/7 - Most advanced 562+ today! x100 hits and mo</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
