<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>My computer-breaking/fixing experience/tech tips</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-computer-breaking-fixing-experience-tech-tips/375626</link>
    <description>Random story / possibly useful technical tips ahead.

[b]Symptom: computer randomly and suddenly turns off [possibly also loud fan noises][/b]
I was at university and my desktop computer kept suddenly turning off while I was using it. I determined that it was probably a temperature issue, because if I started it up again immediately it would not work, but if I left it alone for a while it would.

I found this great (and free software): 
http://www.almico.com/speedfan.php

It shows the temperature measured by every temperature sensor in your computer - CPU, hard drive if your HD has one, etc. I found that my CPU was idling at around 80 degrees Celsius. I took apart the case, cleaned the dust out of the fan, and didn&#39;t put the cover back on, and it went right down to 40-50 and I&#39;ve had no stability issues since.

[b]Symptom: clicking on links from search engines leads you to an unexpected site with a download based on your search term[/b]
I was trying to download the xampp (http://www.apachefriends.org/en/xampp.html) for setting up a web server on my computer to practice web development on. (I do not recommend xampp for production sites, but it&#39;s great for getting a web server up quickly). I typed in &#39;xampp download&#39; into Google and was click-jacked (http://leofiles.com/ was one of the sites serving up this crap). I tried Spybot, Ad-aware, and a bunch of other programs to find the software, but with no luck. While doing some security updates I found Microsoft Security Essentials (http://www.microsoft.com/security_essentials/). Highly recommend, easily the best anti-malware programs I have ever used. It&#39;s bare-bones (as it must be for legal reasons) but very powerful.

MSE found this malware easily; it infected Chrome, Firefox, and Internet Explorer to occasionally serve up this download page on popular search engines (Google, Yahoo, etc). I just clicked &#39;remove&#39; and it was gone, no more problems.

[b]Problem: you nuked your operating system and can&#39;t access files or use your computer[/b]
I just came home from university for Christmas break, leaving my desktop behind. I brought along the laptop I had taken. Early in the semester, it had automatically restarted to install updates while I was using it, so I restarted it when it said not to. (Don&#39;t do this, if this happens to you just leave it be). When I got back in, networking and many other things were completely broken. So I just left that alone and started using my desktop.

As time to come home was coming, I realized I couldn&#39;t take my desktop back, so I worked on fixing my laptop. I decided a live Linux boot USB would be the best way (I dislike CD-shaped media). Most computers have the capability to boot from USB. Here is a complete instruction guide: http://www.ubuntu.com/desktop/get-ubuntu/download.

[b]Problem: you want to use your Windows computer remotely, with capabilities for both file access AND graphical control[/b]
Of course, I still wanted to use Windows, so I did some research. I found this absolutely great site: https://secure.logmein.com/. Just make an account, no payment necessary, and you can set up software on the computer you want to control remotely. (Make sure you turn off automatic updating, restarting, all that crap before going away).

The great part about this site: there is NO client software. I can use any browser to control my computer remotely. In Internet Explorer I get an ActiveX control, and all other browsers get a Java client. With this, I am able to use my computer at university for random things (mainly MATLAB and having a permanent connection to IRC when I want it).

The graphical part was awesome, it showed the screen, although just a warning: don&#39;t be surprised when the mouse cursor doesn&#39;t change when you&#39;d expect it to, just keep resizing your window or whatever. It doesn&#39;t show up on the client machine.

[b]Random note: a permanent connection to IRC [and a good IRC client for Ubuntu][/b]
Some IRC programs have the capability to have a persistent connection set up on a computer, and then you just connect to the computer whenever you want to. Smuxi for Ubuntu claims to have this capability, though I never used it like this. I just used this because Ubuntu&#39;s built-in chat program had absolutely terrible IRC support. Smuxi is great though.

[b]Symptom: your computer slows down suddenly, freezes, then makes a constant beeping noise[/b]
I came home with my laptop and wanted to use a Windows computer / tinker with old hardware, so I brought up a relic from 2005-ish that still had Adobe Reader 8 and Internet Explorer 6. It worked great, it was very responsive, except suddenly it would just freeze completely, and make a beeping nouse.

This is probably a poorly-coded MBR (Master Boot Record) rootkit. [If it weren&#39;t crap / incompatible it would just steal your info without affecting performance]. MSE did a good job with detection, though was unable to remove it. It just said Not Found when attempting removal.

So, I looked at the available programs for dealing with this stuff. Most were too complicated / unwieldy for such a task, but RootRepeal (http://sites.google.com/site/rootrepeal/) took care of it. To find a MBR rootkit, just go to the files tab and select the appropriate drive. After detection, you can stop search and right-click the rootkit entry and select Restore and Reboot Immediately (you can also just restore, but the software can just re-write itself if you don&#39;t reboot immediately after removal).

I also looked at http://www.gmer.net/ but it was poorly-documented and I didn&#39;t want to spend too much time learning it for this single purpose.

[b]Current status:[/b]

[ul][li]Working desktop at university[/li]
[li]Working laptop with Ubuntu, would like to fix Windows on it at some time[/li]
[li]Newly-fixed desktop at home[/li]
[li]Another broken desktop at home: this one just beeps constantly and immediately on start up, no output to monitor etc. I suspect a disconnected cable / damage as it stopped working after it was moved. Ideas?[/li]
[li]Laptop with broken screen. I think I have to log in to my account to use the function-F4 shortcut to direct output to a connected monitor, which is problematic as I cannot see anything. I would rather not have to take my computer apart to access the hard drive. Any suggestions? [/li]
[li]Various ancient computers I haven&#39;t bothered working with in a while (Windows 95, Windows ME/2000/NT or whatever it was) and will probably never look at again, except for the Win95.[/li][/ul]


Final note: I have Vista/XP/a bunch of other stuff from a MSDN subscription (that has now expired), so I can reinstall my operating systems if necessary. I think I also have some keys associated with them. More importantly, I have keys written on my computer boxes. If I reinstall the operating system, can I use the same key to activate?

P.S.: Random / obvious security tip: always keep your software / system up to date. Even if you only visit sites you trust, sites you trust can host malicious content through XSS attacks and dynamic advertisements (Java/Flash/etc) and other stuff. Even innocuous things like PDF reader can screw you over.

P.P.S.: If your computer crashes for apparently no reason and Windows offers to send an error report, it might be helpful to send it. I never bothered sending them due to not really caring but I found out that they can diagnose your problem if you send the report. e.g. I found out it was a graphics driver issue that was crashing the system when I tried to log into a particular character in a game, so I had a game master move the character out of the location and it worked fine.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 01 Jan 2011 10:56:24 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>General Discussion</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-computer-breaking-fixing-experience-tech-tips/375626.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>My computer-breaking/fixing experience/tech tips</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@lesterknome lesterknome]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/lesterknome">@lesterknome</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I would also add that Combofix should not be used unless told by an expert, and MBAM with a combination of Dr.webs cure it can fix and computer-infection related issue.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-computer-breaking-fixing-experience-tech-tips/375626/14">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-computer-breaking-fixing-experience-tech-tips/375626/14</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 01 Jan 2011 10:56:24 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-375626-14</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-computer-breaking-fixing-experience-tech-tips/375626.rss">My computer-breaking/fixing experience/tech tips</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>My computer-breaking/fixing experience/tech tips</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Aftermath_961 Aftermath]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/aftermath_961">@Aftermath_961</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Updated with another tip - apparently sending error reports can help you as well as others.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-computer-breaking-fixing-experience-tech-tips/375626/13">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-computer-breaking-fixing-experience-tech-tips/375626/13</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 31 Dec 2010 06:01:29 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-375626-13</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-computer-breaking-fixing-experience-tech-tips/375626.rss">My computer-breaking/fixing experience/tech tips</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>My computer-breaking/fixing experience/tech tips</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Greeny Greeny]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/greeny">@Greeny</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>If you’re on windows, CPU-Z is a great alternative to speedfan, plus they have a few other programs released that do some excellent diagnostics. (Like Everest, but free) [<a href="http://www.cpuid.com/softwares.html" rel="nofollow noopener">http://www.cpuid.com/softwares.html</a>].</p>
<p>Smuxi is OK if you find irssi too complicated or want a GUI, otherwise screen+irssi is just a clear winner for me.</p>
<p>Also be careful using XAMPP and other similar home-PC webservers, they’re mostly for testing and not very secure which is why you could be so vulnerable to malware and such.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-computer-breaking-fixing-experience-tech-tips/375626/12">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-computer-breaking-fixing-experience-tech-tips/375626/12</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 29 Dec 2010 16:20:09 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-375626-12</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-computer-breaking-fixing-experience-tech-tips/375626.rss">My computer-breaking/fixing experience/tech tips</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>My computer-breaking/fixing experience/tech tips</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@tL tL]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/tl">@tL</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote no-group" data-post="9" data-topic="375626">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/eczema3/40/5_1887921562df0dabfae55079ddabeb03.png" class="avatar"> eczema3:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>If you define an external DNS in your computers internet settings the local cache is ignored.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Even if that were true, the use of the local cache remains the same regardless of you using another DNS provider or not.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-computer-breaking-fixing-experience-tech-tips/375626/11">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-computer-breaking-fixing-experience-tech-tips/375626/11</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 29 Dec 2010 15:27:48 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-375626-11</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-computer-breaking-fixing-experience-tech-tips/375626.rss">My computer-breaking/fixing experience/tech tips</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>My computer-breaking/fixing experience/tech tips</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Mopman Mopman]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/mopman">@Mopman</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>no, no it isnt</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-computer-breaking-fixing-experience-tech-tips/375626/10">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-computer-breaking-fixing-experience-tech-tips/375626/10</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 29 Dec 2010 15:17:41 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-375626-10</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-computer-breaking-fixing-experience-tech-tips/375626.rss">My computer-breaking/fixing experience/tech tips</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>My computer-breaking/fixing experience/tech tips</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@eczema3 eczema3]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/eczema3">@eczema3</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>If you define an external DNS in your computers internet settings the local cache is ignored.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-computer-breaking-fixing-experience-tech-tips/375626/9">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-computer-breaking-fixing-experience-tech-tips/375626/9</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 29 Dec 2010 15:13:25 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-375626-9</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-computer-breaking-fixing-experience-tech-tips/375626.rss">My computer-breaking/fixing experience/tech tips</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>My computer-breaking/fixing experience/tech tips</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@tL tL]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/tl">@tL</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“eczema3, post:3, topic:375626”][quote author=abraham2119 link=topic=471560.msg3449175#msg3449175 date=1293621829]</p>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Symptom: clicking on links from search engines leads you to an unexpected site with a download based on your search term</span></p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>It’s usually not as easy as simply removing any malware the browser was infected with, as it was with my case. A few months ago, I was infected with really potent malware. After having ran Malwarebytes’ Ant-Malware and Avast, I thought it had been completely removed and no trace of it was left. However, when I performed random searches on Google, (I never use any other search engine, so I don’t know if it also occurred with others) it would redirect me to some random advertisement. After some research, it turned out my DNS cache was “poisoned” (<a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/DNS_cache_poisoning" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">as it’s termed</a>). All that’s needed to clear the cache is to run the following command:</p>
<pre><code class="lang-auto">ipconfig /flushdns</code></pre>
<p>[/quote]<br>
Or you could just use and external DNS like <a href="http://code.google.com/speed/public-dns/" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">google</a> or <a href="http://www.opendns.com/" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">OpenDNS</a>[/quote]</p>
<p>But it would have been any local DNS cache being kept on his computer that was infected, not the external one (Such as those provided by your ISP).</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-computer-breaking-fixing-experience-tech-tips/375626/8">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-computer-breaking-fixing-experience-tech-tips/375626/8</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 29 Dec 2010 14:37:13 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-375626-8</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-computer-breaking-fixing-experience-tech-tips/375626.rss">My computer-breaking/fixing experience/tech tips</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>My computer-breaking/fixing experience/tech tips</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@eczema3 eczema3]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/eczema3">@eczema3</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“R.I.P RSC, post:6, topic:375626”][quote author=eczema3 link=topic=471560.msg3449204#msg3449204 date=1293625585]</p>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p>Is it possible that Speedfan fucks up your fan? After installing Speedfan on my laptop, my fan is very loud and during booting it makes rattling noises that go away after a few minutes.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Sounds like the bearings are gone in your fan<br>
[/quote]</p>
<p>The noise only lasts for a few minutes, and then returns to normal.[/quote]<br>
My old fan used to do it, I just replaced it thats all.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-computer-breaking-fixing-experience-tech-tips/375626/7">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-computer-breaking-fixing-experience-tech-tips/375626/7</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 29 Dec 2010 13:10:37 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-375626-7</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-computer-breaking-fixing-experience-tech-tips/375626.rss">My computer-breaking/fixing experience/tech tips</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>My computer-breaking/fixing experience/tech tips</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@R.I.P_RSC R.I.P RSC]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/r.i.p_rsc">@R.I.P_RSC</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“eczema3, post:5, topic:375626”][quote author=R.I.P RSC link=topic=471560.msg3449202#msg3449202 date=1293625288]<br>
Is it possible that Speedfan fucks up your fan? After installing Speedfan on my laptop, my fan is very loud and during booting it makes rattling noises that go away after a few minutes.<br>
[/quote]<br>
Sounds like the bearings are gone in your fan[/quote]</p>
<p>The noise only lasts for a few minutes, and then returns to normal.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-computer-breaking-fixing-experience-tech-tips/375626/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-computer-breaking-fixing-experience-tech-tips/375626/6</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 29 Dec 2010 12:40:42 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-375626-6</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-computer-breaking-fixing-experience-tech-tips/375626.rss">My computer-breaking/fixing experience/tech tips</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>My computer-breaking/fixing experience/tech tips</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@eczema3 eczema3]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/eczema3">@eczema3</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote no-group" data-post="4" data-topic="375626">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 R.I.P RSC:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Is it possible that Speedfan fucks up your fan? After installing Speedfan on my laptop, my fan is very loud and during booting it makes rattling noises that go away after a few minutes.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Sounds like the bearings are gone in your fan</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-computer-breaking-fixing-experience-tech-tips/375626/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-computer-breaking-fixing-experience-tech-tips/375626/5</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 29 Dec 2010 12:26:25 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-375626-5</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-computer-breaking-fixing-experience-tech-tips/375626.rss">My computer-breaking/fixing experience/tech tips</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>My computer-breaking/fixing experience/tech tips</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@R.I.P_RSC R.I.P RSC]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/r.i.p_rsc">@R.I.P_RSC</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Is it possible that Speedfan fucks up your fan? After installing Speedfan on my laptop, my fan is very loud and during booting it makes rattling noises that go away after a few minutes.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-computer-breaking-fixing-experience-tech-tips/375626/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-computer-breaking-fixing-experience-tech-tips/375626/4</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 29 Dec 2010 12:21:28 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-375626-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-computer-breaking-fixing-experience-tech-tips/375626.rss">My computer-breaking/fixing experience/tech tips</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>My computer-breaking/fixing experience/tech tips</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@eczema3 eczema3]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/eczema3">@eczema3</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote no-group quote-modified" data-post="2" data-topic="375626">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/abraham2119/40/5_1887921562df0dabfae55079ddabeb03.png" class="avatar"> abraham2119:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>[quote]<span class="bbcode-b">Symptom: clicking on links from search engines leads you to an unexpected site with a download based on your search term</span></p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>It’s usually not as easy as simply removing any malware the browser was infected with, as it was with my case. A few months ago, I was infected with really potent malware. After having ran Malwarebytes’ Ant-Malware and Avast, I thought it had been completely removed and no trace of it was left. However, when I performed random searches on Google, (I never use any other search engine, so I don’t know if it also occurred with others) it would redirect me to some random advertisement. After some research, it turned out my DNS cache was “poisoned” (<a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/DNS_cache_poisoning" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">as it’s termed</a>). All that’s needed to clear the cache is to run the following command:</p>
<pre><code class="lang-auto">ipconfig /flushdns</code></pre>
<p>Or you could just use and external DNS like <a href="http://code.google.com/speed/public-dns/" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">google</a> or <a href="http://www.opendns.com/" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">OpenDNS</a></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-computer-breaking-fixing-experience-tech-tips/375626/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-computer-breaking-fixing-experience-tech-tips/375626/3</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 29 Dec 2010 12:11:32 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-375626-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-computer-breaking-fixing-experience-tech-tips/375626.rss">My computer-breaking/fixing experience/tech tips</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>My computer-breaking/fixing experience/tech tips</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@abraham2119 abraham2119]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/abraham2119">@abraham2119</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <blockquote>[b]Symptom: clicking on links from search engines leads you to an unexpected site with a download based on your search term[/b]</blockquote>
It's usually not as easy as simply removing any malware the browser was infected with, as it was with my case. A few months ago, I was infected with really potent malware. After having ran Malwarebytes' Ant-Malware and Avast, I thought it had been completely removed and no trace of it was left. However, when I performed random searches on Google, (I never use any other search engine, so I don't know if it also occurred with others) it would redirect me to some random advertisement. After some research, it turned out my DNS cache was "poisoned" ([url=http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/DNS_cache_poisoning]as it's termed[/url]). All that's needed to clear the cache is to run the following command:
[code=cmd]ipconfig /flushdns[/code]
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-computer-breaking-fixing-experience-tech-tips/375626/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-computer-breaking-fixing-experience-tech-tips/375626/2</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 29 Dec 2010 11:23:49 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-375626-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-computer-breaking-fixing-experience-tech-tips/375626.rss">My computer-breaking/fixing experience/tech tips</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>My computer-breaking/fixing experience/tech tips</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Aftermath_961 Aftermath]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/aftermath_961">@Aftermath_961</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Random story / possibly useful technical tips ahead.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Symptom: computer randomly and suddenly turns off [possibly also loud fan noises]</span><br>
I was at university and my desktop computer kept suddenly turning off while I was using it. I determined that it was probably a temperature issue, because if I started it up again immediately it would not work, but if I left it alone for a while it would.</p>
<p>I found this great (and free software):<br>
<a href="http://www.almico.com/speedfan.php" class="onebox" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">http://www.almico.com/speedfan.php</a></p>
<p>It shows the temperature measured by every temperature sensor in your computer - CPU, hard drive if your HD has one, etc. I found that my CPU was idling at around 80 degrees Celsius. I took apart the case, cleaned the dust out of the fan, and didn’t put the cover back on, and it went right down to 40-50 and I’ve had no stability issues since.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Symptom: clicking on links from search engines leads you to an unexpected site with a download based on your search term</span><br>
I was trying to download the xampp (<a href="http://www.apachefriends.org/en/xampp.html" rel="nofollow noopener">http://www.apachefriends.org/en/xampp.html</a>) for setting up a web server on my computer to practice web development on. (I do not recommend xampp for production sites, but it’s great for getting a web server up quickly). I typed in ‘xampp download’ into Google and was click-jacked (<a href="http://leofiles.com/" rel="nofollow noopener">http://leofiles.com/</a> was one of the sites serving up this crap). I tried Spybot, Ad-aware, and a bunch of other programs to find the software, but with no luck. While doing some security updates I found Microsoft Security Essentials (<a href="http://www.microsoft.com/security_essentials/" rel="nofollow noopener">http://www.microsoft.com/security_essentials/</a>). Highly recommend, easily the best anti-malware programs I have ever used. It’s bare-bones (as it must be for legal reasons) but very powerful.</p>
<p>MSE found this malware easily; it infected Chrome, Firefox, and Internet Explorer to occasionally serve up this download page on popular search engines (Google, Yahoo, etc). I just clicked ‘remove’ and it was gone, no more problems.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Problem: you nuked your operating system and can’t access files or use your computer</span><br>
I just came home from university for Christmas break, leaving my desktop behind. I brought along the laptop I had taken. Early in the semester, it had automatically restarted to install updates while I was using it, so I restarted it when it said not to. (Don’t do this, if this happens to you just leave it be). When I got back in, networking and many other things were completely broken. So I just left that alone and started using my desktop.</p>
<p>As time to come home was coming, I realized I couldn’t take my desktop back, so I worked on fixing my laptop. I decided a live Linux boot USB would be the best way (I dislike CD-shaped media). Most computers have the capability to boot from USB. Here is a complete instruction guide: <a href="http://www.ubuntu.com/desktop/get-ubuntu/download" rel="nofollow noopener">http://www.ubuntu.com/desktop/get-ubuntu/download</a>.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Problem: you want to use your Windows computer remotely, with capabilities for both file access AND graphical control</span><br>
Of course, I still wanted to use Windows, so I did some research. I found this absolutely great site: <a href="https://secure.logmein.com/" rel="nofollow noopener">https://secure.logmein.com/</a>. Just make an account, no payment necessary, and you can set up software on the computer you want to control remotely. (Make sure you turn off automatic updating, restarting, all that crap before going away).</p>
<p>The great part about this site: there is NO client software. I can use any browser to control my computer remotely. In Internet Explorer I get an ActiveX control, and all other browsers get a Java client. With this, I am able to use my computer at university for random things (mainly MATLAB and having a permanent connection to IRC when I want it).</p>
<p>The graphical part was awesome, it showed the screen, although just a warning: don’t be surprised when the mouse cursor doesn’t change when you’d expect it to, just keep resizing your window or whatever. It doesn’t show up on the client machine.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Random note: a permanent connection to IRC [and a good IRC client for Ubuntu]</span><br>
Some IRC programs have the capability to have a persistent connection set up on a computer, and then you just connect to the computer whenever you want to. Smuxi for Ubuntu claims to have this capability, though I never used it like this. I just used this because Ubuntu’s built-in chat program had absolutely terrible IRC support. Smuxi is great though.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Symptom: your computer slows down suddenly, freezes, then makes a constant beeping noise</span><br>
I came home with my laptop and wanted to use a Windows computer / tinker with old hardware, so I brought up a relic from 2005-ish that still had Adobe Reader 8 and Internet Explorer 6. It worked great, it was very responsive, except suddenly it would just freeze completely, and make a beeping nouse.</p>
<p>This is probably a poorly-coded MBR (Master Boot Record) rootkit. [If it weren’t crap / incompatible it would just steal your info without affecting performance]. MSE did a good job with detection, though was unable to remove it. It just said Not Found when attempting removal.</p>
<p>So, I looked at the available programs for dealing with this stuff. Most were too complicated / unwieldy for such a task, but RootRepeal (<a href="http://sites.google.com/site/rootrepeal/" rel="nofollow noopener">http://sites.google.com/site/rootrepeal/</a>) took care of it. To find a MBR rootkit, just go to the files tab and select the appropriate drive. After detection, you can stop search and right-click the rootkit entry and select Restore and Reboot Immediately (you can also just restore, but the software can just re-write itself if you don’t reboot immediately after removal).</p>
<p>I also looked at <a href="http://www.gmer.net/" rel="nofollow noopener">http://www.gmer.net/</a> but it was poorly-documented and I didn’t want to spend too much time learning it for this single purpose.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Current status:</span></p>
<p>[ul][li]Working desktop at university[/li]<br>
[li]Working laptop with Ubuntu, would like to fix Windows on it at some time[/li]<br>
[li]Newly-fixed desktop at home[/li]<br>
[li]Another broken desktop at home: this one just beeps constantly and immediately on start up, no output to monitor etc. I suspect a disconnected cable / damage as it stopped working after it was moved. Ideas?[/li]<br>
[li]Laptop with broken screen. I think I have to log in to my account to use the function-F4 shortcut to direct output to a connected monitor, which is problematic as I cannot see anything. I would rather not have to take my computer apart to access the hard drive. Any suggestions? [/li]<br>
[li]Various ancient computers I haven’t bothered working with in a while (Windows 95, Windows ME/2000/NT or whatever it was) and will probably never look at again, except for the Win95.[/li][/ul]</p>
<p>Final note: I have Vista/XP/a bunch of other stuff from a MSDN subscription (that has now expired), so I can reinstall my operating systems if necessary. I think I also have some keys associated with them. More importantly, I have keys written on my computer boxes. If I reinstall the operating system, can I use the same key to activate?</p>
<p>P.S.: Random / obvious security tip: always keep your software / system up to date. Even if you only visit sites you trust, sites you trust can host malicious content through XSS attacks and dynamic advertisements (Java/Flash/etc) and other stuff. Even innocuous things like PDF reader can screw you over.</p>
<p>P.P.S.: If your computer crashes for apparently no reason and Windows offers to send an error report, it might be helpful to send it. I never bothered sending them due to not really caring but I found out that they can diagnose your problem if you send the report. e.g. I found out it was a graphics driver issue that was crashing the system when I tried to log into a particular character in a game, so I had a game master move the character out of the location and it worked fine.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-computer-breaking-fixing-experience-tech-tips/375626/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-computer-breaking-fixing-experience-tech-tips/375626/1</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 29 Dec 2010 06:37:53 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-375626-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-computer-breaking-fixing-experience-tech-tips/375626.rss">My computer-breaking/fixing experience/tech tips</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
