<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Help With Running 503 Clients =)</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/help-with-running-503-clients/230822</link>
    <description>Ok I downloaded and saved Ploxagescape and some other clients and its now on my desktop. My problem is they won&#39;t open and I dont know how to get em started. I&#39;ve download Winrar and now they look like 3 colors of books I extracted it and now a new folder looking like the vanilla folderthingys come out saying Ploxagescape. I double click on it and its says ClientFiles then after that when i click on it says .jagex_catche_32 after that it says loginapplet or runescape or random or randomDeob503. After I click on all of em they lead me to a dead end and says computer cant open files or some crap and I need some help. Thanks alot and dang took me like 10 mins to figure out how to make a new post yeh im new to moparscape

Also or what do I do after I extract the files to a folder?</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2008 20:04:56 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/help-with-running-503-clients/230822.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Help With Running 503 Clients =)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Blazin_Fury Blazin Fury]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/blazin_fury">@Blazin_Fury</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Ok I downloaded and saved Ploxagescape and some other clients and its now on my desktop. My problem is they won’t open and I dont know how to get em started. I’ve download Winrar and now they look like 3 colors of books I extracted it and now a new folder looking like the vanilla folderthingys come out saying Ploxagescape. I double click on it and its says ClientFiles then after that when i click on it says .jagex_catche_32 after that it says loginapplet or runescape or random or randomDeob503. After I click on all of em they lead me to a dead end and says computer cant open files or some crap and I need some help. Thanks alot and dang took me like 10 mins to figure out how to make a new post yeh im new to moparscape</p>
<p>Also or what do I do after I extract the files to a folder?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/help-with-running-503-clients/230822/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/help-with-running-503-clients/230822/1</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2008 20:04:56 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-230822-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/help-with-running-503-clients/230822.rss">Help With Running 503 Clients =)</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
