<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Getting Free Stuff</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/getting-free-stuff/66161</link>
    <description>We&#39;ve all seen those flashing banners that say &quot;Click here for free PS3(or Xbox 360, or iMac, or iPod...)&quot; and hoped they could be true.  Well, after a little bit of hard work(really you just post your referral link anywhere you can) you&#39;ll score some free stuff.  Now, onto the steps!

1. Go to [url=http://forum.freeipodguide.com/]Free Ipod Guide&#39;s Forums[/url] and do some research.

2. Choose the site that fits your needs and that you can successfully complete the requirements for. Sign up for the site. ( I recommend trainn)

3. Complete an offer.  In my experience the &quot;Stamps.com&quot; offer has been the easiest and is completely free if you cancel before the 4 week trial is up. (You still need a credit card even though it is free!)

4. Reach your referral goal for the item you want.

5. Fill out a couple of missing credit and support tickets.

6. Confirm your item and shipping address. They ship it out. You get it quick like (mostly likely a week or two.)

And that, ladies and gentlemen, is all there is to getting free stuff.  If you took the time to check out the free ipod guide forum you&#39;ll see that prizes range from cash money, paypal money, and gift cards to Wii&#39;s, PS3&#39;s, and Xbox 360&#39;s.  If you don&#39;t have a credit card and the parents won&#39;t let you use theirs, find a friend with a visa giftcard or go buy one at Albertsons. And finally, if you can, use someone&#39;s referral link, you would hope they would do the same for you.

If you decide to use [url=http://www.3604free.com/index.php?ref=3776192]www.3604free.com [/url] (a subsidary of trainn) please use [url=http://www.3604free.com/index.php?ref=3776192]my referral link[/url]. I would greatly appreciate it.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 09 Apr 2007 20:13:30 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>General Discussion</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/getting-free-stuff/66161.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Getting Free Stuff</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@system system]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/system">@system</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Nah I Wouldnt Trust it…<br>
Still Needs Your Credit Card -.-</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/getting-free-stuff/66161/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/getting-free-stuff/66161/2</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 09 Apr 2007 20:13:30 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-66161-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/getting-free-stuff/66161.rss">Getting Free Stuff</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Getting Free Stuff</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Aukake Aukake]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/aukake">@Aukake</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>We’ve all seen those flashing banners that say “Click here for free PS3(or Xbox 360, or iMac, or iPod…)” and hoped they could be true.  Well, after a little bit of hard work(really you just post your referral link anywhere you can) you’ll score some free stuff.  Now, onto the steps!</p>
<ol>
<li>
<p>Go to <a href="http://forum.freeipodguide.com/" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">Free Ipod Guide’s Forums</a> and do some research.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Choose the site that fits your needs and that you can successfully complete the requirements for. Sign up for the site. ( I recommend trainn)</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Complete an offer.  In my experience the “<a href="http://Stamps.com" rel="nofollow noopener">Stamps.com</a>” offer has been the easiest and is completely free if you cancel before the 4 week trial is up. (You still need a credit card even though it is free!)</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Reach your referral goal for the item you want.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Fill out a couple of missing credit and support tickets.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Confirm your item and shipping address. They ship it out. You get it quick like (mostly likely a week or two.)</p>
</li>
</ol>
<p>And that, ladies and gentlemen, is all there is to getting free stuff.  If you took the time to check out the free ipod guide forum you’ll see that prizes range from cash money, paypal money, and gift cards to Wii’s, PS3’s, and Xbox 360’s.  If you don’t have a credit card and the parents won’t let you use theirs, find a friend with a visa giftcard or go buy one at Albertsons. And finally, if you can, use someone’s referral link, you would hope they would do the same for you.</p>
<p>If you decide to use <a href="http://www.3604free.com/index.php?ref=3776192" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">www.3604free.com </a> (a subsidary of trainn) please use <a href="http://www.3604free.com/index.php?ref=3776192" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">my referral link</a>. I would greatly appreciate it.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/getting-free-stuff/66161/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/getting-free-stuff/66161/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 10 Mar 2007 12:20:19 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-66161-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/getting-free-stuff/66161.rss">Getting Free Stuff</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
