<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Webclient Trouble</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/webclient-trouble/545854</link>
    <description>Okay, so i&#39;ve been faced with this problem for a couple days now and i need it fixed, i&#39;m 80% sure the problem is my java of some sort but i want to ask you guys what the problem is, i&#39;m happy to teamview, skype idc.

Okay so i&#39;ve successfully jarred and signed my client through jarr maker through jdk 8 and jdk 7 to see if theres any difference.
i test it out on my website http://www.cryptic317.com/webclient.html and get a loading error with says its missing a massifest attribute and i have no idea what that means,
[img]http://i.imgur.com/ZK3MdwW.png[/img]
[img]http://i.imgur.com/8dHuIFz.png[/img]

Now i&#39;m not sure what the problem is, ive compiled the client with both jdk7 and 8 and no difference at all, if anyone can help it would be great and i&#39;m sure we could sort something out on skype or teamviewer

-Jaximus</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2014 11:27:58 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Game Development</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/webclient-trouble/545854.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Webclient Trouble</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@jaximus jaximus]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/jaximus">@jaximus</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Okay, so i’ve been faced with this problem for a couple days now and i need it fixed, i’m 80% sure the problem is my java of some sort but i want to ask you guys what the problem is, i’m happy to teamview, skype idc.</p>
<p>Okay so i’ve successfully jarred and signed my client through jarr maker through jdk 8 and jdk 7 to see if theres any difference.<br>
i test it out on my website <a href="http://www.cryptic317.com/webclient.html" rel="nofollow noopener">http://www.cryptic317.com/webclient.html</a> and get a loading error with says its missing a massifest attribute and i have no idea what that means,<br>
<img src="http://i.imgur.com/ZK3MdwW.png" alt width="" height=""><br>
<img src="http://i.imgur.com/8dHuIFz.png" alt width="" height=""></p>
<p>Now i’m not sure what the problem is, ive compiled the client with both jdk7 and 8 and no difference at all, if anyone can help it would be great and i’m sure we could sort something out on skype or teamviewer</p>
<p>-Jaximus</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/webclient-trouble/545854/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/webclient-trouble/545854/1</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2014 11:27:58 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-545854-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/webclient-trouble/545854.rss">Webclient Trouble</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
