<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Can You Help Please</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/can-you-help-please/281291</link>
    <description>How do i make a pk zone i got the pk box but i aint got the pk zone i have looked in the tut section but that say how to make a funkpk i tryed it but it didn&#39;t work i only want to the pk box so u can kill anyone at any lvl for e.g lvl 3 vs lvl 126 and when you go out of wildy your 

 i also really want to know this there is a teleport called teleport to ape atoll how do i change the text and how do i make it teleport? because it isn&#39;t in the text handler.java when i serached in it and i cant telport and were when i click it.

And how do i add a command were when you type it in u join a clan and get the clan armour?

I poasted this before but on th eother thread i didn&#39;t get much help -.-</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 31 May 2009 08:54:08 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/can-you-help-please/281291.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Can You Help Please</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@freeky freeky]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/freeky">@freeky</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>How do i make a pk zone i got the pk box but i aint got the pk zone i have looked in the tut section but that say how to make a funkpk i tryed it but it didn’t work i only want to the pk box so u can kill anyone at any lvl for e.g lvl 3 vs lvl 126 and when you go out of wildy your</p>
<p>i also really want to know this there is a teleport called teleport to ape atoll how do i change the text and how do i make it teleport? because it isn’t in the text handler.java when i serached in it and i cant telport and were when i click it.</p>
<p>And how do i add a command were when you type it in u join a clan and get the clan armour?</p>
<p>I poasted this before but on th eother thread i didn’t get much help -.-</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/can-you-help-please/281291/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/can-you-help-please/281291/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 31 May 2009 08:54:08 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-281291-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/can-you-help-please/281291.rss">Can You Help Please</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
