<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Lack of good servers out. Why?</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/lack-of-good-servers-out-why/549611</link>
    <description>Only two servers out right now that aren&#39;t EasyRSC XML edits.

RSCE: No person with self-respect would play that corrupt piece of shit server.
RSCR: Ghost town infected with a disease called &quot;replica&quot;.

So what&#39;s the deal? No new servers in development? Anyone with at least a glimmer of hope for us RSC starved plebs?</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2015 18:27:50 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/lack-of-good-servers-out-why/549611.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Lack of good servers out. Why?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Rodgerwilco Rodgerwilco]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/rodgerwilco">@Rodgerwilco</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>The game is boring because we already know how to get what we want. I felt this same experience on old school runescape. I was one of the top players for a while after release cuz I spent a month with other players planning how we can effectively manage our resources and get the most out of our game play. The same thing happens with RSC.</p>
<p>We already know the map, know the npcs, know the quests, gear etcetc.</p>
<p>The map you can change but people who do it lack design. The RSC map was carefully planned, wooden fence was used to make the map seem larger than it actually was. Skilling locations were properly placed with a walking distance that fit how much a player is willing to go.</p>
<p>Npcs lack features and AFKing is the worse thing that could ever happen to this game. Players need to have a constant game play experience for a better exp rate. Most RSC servers 80%+ of people will afk train at any given time. It’s a great way to separate the community.</p>
<p>New Quests won’t do anything as peoples lack a story, I don’t expect these to go anywhere unless someone just dedicates all their time to creating a proper story.</p>
<p>The first thing I did on RSC was go to lumby castle, loot bronze daggers and sold them to the lumby store. Once you play the game, you know that would be stupid to do. When you first played, it was the best way to collect gold and train. Everyone knows the best way to make money which makes everything else in the world, sorta useless.</p>
<p>That is what the RSC game is, useless, especially as our average player age increases, why would we ever use a iron square shield?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/lack-of-good-servers-out-why/549611/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/lack-of-good-servers-out-why/549611/5</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2015 18:27:50 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-549611-5</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/lack-of-good-servers-out-why/549611.rss">Lack of good servers out. Why?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Lack of good servers out. Why?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@malikz malikz]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/malikz">@malikz</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>This community is self destructive. Blame most of the greedy, selfish admins who focused more on $$$, rather than trying to keep the community alive…now their easy money source is basically gone…this community looks like it’s been sucked dry and I think it’s basically finished.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/lack-of-good-servers-out-why/549611/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/lack-of-good-servers-out-why/549611/4</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2015 14:03:41 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-549611-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/lack-of-good-servers-out-why/549611.rss">Lack of good servers out. Why?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Lack of good servers out. Why?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Nothing1 -Nothing]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/nothing1">@Nothing1</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Shitty community which dont know what the hell they want. Nothing is ever good</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/lack-of-good-servers-out-why/549611/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/lack-of-good-servers-out-why/549611/3</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2015 10:45:33 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-549611-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/lack-of-good-servers-out-why/549611.rss">Lack of good servers out. Why?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Lack of good servers out. Why?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@gifix2 gifix2]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/gifix2">@gifix2</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>It’s a combination of things. The user base for the game is growing older and other priorities are taking over their lives. Not to mention most of the servers out right now are still trying to push low EXP rates means less and less people have time to actually play the game.</p>
<p>The few hours people do have to squeeze in for gaming, they’d rather play some dopamine releasing jump right into it game like Counter-Strike, League of legends, Smash, etc. As oppose to “AFK” training on an almost 15 year old game.</p>
<p>Not to mention the few servers left are only out to exploit the few remaining members for money. (Seriously try logging into RSCE, every-little-thing requires a subscription card. Soon you will need to buy a subscription just to walk in the damn game).</p>
<p>The lack of new content and innovation in the scene combined with the resistance of the player base any time a server tries to introduce a new concept into the game has stagnated the scene.</p>
<p>The few people that release servers every few months are the same toxic people that have screwed players over for years with their for-profit churn and burn bullshit, most people got sick of it and left the community.</p>
<p>Not to mention unless you got a considerable amount of start-up money for a Ddos protected dedicated server you will almost certainly be taken offline with attacks if your server shows any sign of momentum.</p>
<p>But I do have hope, there are still brilliant people in this community.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/lack-of-good-servers-out-why/549611/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/lack-of-good-servers-out-why/549611/2</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2015 10:42:01 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-549611-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/lack-of-good-servers-out-why/549611.rss">Lack of good servers out. Why?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Lack of good servers out. Why?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Jr_Mafio_865 Jr Mafio 865]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/jr_mafio_865">@Jr_Mafio_865</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Only two servers out right now that aren’t EasyRSC XML edits.</p>
<p>RSCE: No person with self-respect would play that corrupt piece of shit server.<br>
RSCR: Ghost town infected with a disease called “replica”.</p>
<p>So what’s the deal? No new servers in development? Anyone with at least a glimmer of hope for us RSC starved plebs?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/lack-of-good-servers-out-why/549611/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/lack-of-good-servers-out-why/549611/1</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2015 10:27:56 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-549611-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/lack-of-good-servers-out-why/549611.rss">Lack of good servers out. Why?</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
