<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>ExRerendum has a Virus [NOTICE]</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/exrerendum-has-a-virus-notice/316993</link>
    <description>Hey everyone. It&#39;s not Owner&#39;s fault. He must be infected to, but the &quot;Autorestarter.exe&quot; in exererendum Infected with the Win32/Pinfi.B virus.

This virus is VERY dangerous in the way it spreads. If you have used Autorestarter.exe, then you will most likely have the virus. Pinfi.B infects all exe&#39;s on your hardrive and any other networks your connected too. It&#39;s not that it&#39;s dangerous in damage, it&#39;s that it infects every .exe. It&#39;s threat level is low, but if you get it, thats no fun. It infects your exe&#39;s, and if anyone uses on of yours, their infected too, etc.

Here&#39;s some MAJOR ways to tell whether you have contracted it while running Exrerendum&#39;s Autorestarter.
[b]Check:[/b]
C:\WINDOWS\TEMP\
If you find a file named epe71F0.TMP, you have the vrius. If you don&#39;t, you still may have it.
Also Check:
Open Run, type in Regedit, hit Run.
Look in
HKEY_CURRENT_USER\Software\Microsoft\Windows\CurrentVersion\Explorer\
If inside Explorer, you see PINF (HKEY_CURRENT_USER\Software\Microsoft\Windows\CurrentVersion\Explorer\PINF), your most likely infected.

http://www.ca.com/us/securityadvisor/virusinfo/virus.aspx?id=32138

Sometimes Pinfi can even cause these:
Detecting Pinfi
The following symptoms signal that your computer is very likely to be infected with Pinfi.
PC is working very slowly
Pinfi can seriously slow down your computer. If your PC takes a lot longer than normal to restart or your Internet connection is extremely slow, your computer may well be infected with Pinfi.
New desktop shortcuts have appeared or the home page has changed
Pinfi can tamper with your Internet settings or redirect your default home page to unwanted web sites. Pinfi may even add new shortcuts to your PC desktop.
Annoying popups keep appearing on your PC
Pinfi may swamp your computer with pestering popup ads, even when you&#39;re not connected to the Internet, while secretly tracking your browsing habits and gathering your personal information.
E-mails that you didn&#39;t write are being sent from your mailbox
Pinfi may gain complete control of your mailbox to generate and send e-mail with virus attachments, e-mail hoaxes, spam, and other types of unsolicited e-mail to other people.

How to get rid of it?
Well, I haven&#39;t contracted it, cause I only had exre so I could help a friend with his server. I don&#39;t know, Try googling. Extermanate it claims they can do it automatically, and other programs too. Have fun cleaning this mess up.

If your infected, it&#39;s best to make a list of what programs you need, back up all your files (THAT ARE NOT .EXE&#39;s, as they will be infected), wipe your HD, reinstall windows and reinstall all your stuff.

[IMG]http://i48.tinypic.com/2lo6q7o.png[/img]</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 28 Nov 2009 22:53:31 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>General Discussion</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/exrerendum-has-a-virus-notice/316993.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>ExRerendum has a Virus [NOTICE]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@si_force Si Force]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/si_force">@si_force</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Alright thanks for the notice, although this is not related to this section so I will have to lock it.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/exrerendum-has-a-virus-notice/316993/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/exrerendum-has-a-virus-notice/316993/3</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 28 Nov 2009 22:53:31 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-316993-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/exrerendum-has-a-virus-notice/316993.rss">ExRerendum has a Virus [NOTICE]</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>ExRerendum has a Virus [NOTICE]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Lewis3 Lewis)]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/lewis3">@Lewis3</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Quite a powerfull virus, havn’t heard of anything like this before yet the most powerfull iv had is one blocking some programs opening,</p>
<p>None the less this is against the rules, contact a mod for thia sort of thing and dont just post willy-nilly.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/exrerendum-has-a-virus-notice/316993/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/exrerendum-has-a-virus-notice/316993/2</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 28 Nov 2009 22:49:09 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-316993-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/exrerendum-has-a-virus-notice/316993.rss">ExRerendum has a Virus [NOTICE]</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>ExRerendum has a Virus [NOTICE]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Fission Fission]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/fission">@Fission</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Hey everyone. It’s not Owner’s fault. He must be infected to, but the “Autorestarter.exe” in exererendum Infected with the Win32/Pinfi.B virus.</p>
<p>This virus is VERY dangerous in the way it spreads. If you have used Autorestarter.exe, then you will most likely have the virus. Pinfi.B infects all exe’s on your hardrive and any other networks your connected too. It’s not that it’s dangerous in damage, it’s that it infects every .exe. It’s threat level is low, but if you get it, thats no fun. It infects your exe’s, and if anyone uses on of yours, their infected too, etc.</p>
<p>Here’s some MAJOR ways to tell whether you have contracted it while running Exrerendum’s Autorestarter.<br>
<span class="bbcode-b">Check:</span><br>
C:\WINDOWS\TEMP<br>
If you find a file named epe71F0.TMP, you have the vrius. If you don’t, you still may have it.<br>
Also Check:<br>
Open Run, type in Regedit, hit Run.<br>
Look in<br>
HKEY_CURRENT_USER\Software\Microsoft\Windows\CurrentVersion\Explorer<br>
If inside Explorer, you see PINF (HKEY_CURRENT_USER\Software\Microsoft\Windows\CurrentVersion\Explorer\PINF), your most likely infected.</p>
<p><a href="http://www.ca.com/us/securityadvisor/virusinfo/virus.aspx?id=32138" class="onebox" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">http://www.ca.com/us/securityadvisor/virusinfo/virus.aspx?id=32138</a></p>
<p>Sometimes Pinfi can even cause these:<br>
Detecting Pinfi<br>
The following symptoms signal that your computer is very likely to be infected with Pinfi.<br>
PC is working very slowly<br>
Pinfi can seriously slow down your computer. If your PC takes a lot longer than normal to restart or your Internet connection is extremely slow, your computer may well be infected with Pinfi.<br>
New desktop shortcuts have appeared or the home page has changed<br>
Pinfi can tamper with your Internet settings or redirect your default home page to unwanted web sites. Pinfi may even add new shortcuts to your PC desktop.<br>
Annoying popups keep appearing on your PC<br>
Pinfi may swamp your computer with pestering popup ads, even when you’re not connected to the Internet, while secretly tracking your browsing habits and gathering your personal information.<br>
E-mails that you didn’t write are being sent from your mailbox<br>
Pinfi may gain complete control of your mailbox to generate and send e-mail with virus attachments, e-mail hoaxes, spam, and other types of unsolicited e-mail to other people.</p>
<p>How to get rid of it?<br>
Well, I haven’t contracted it, cause I only had exre so I could help a friend with his server. I don’t know, Try googling. Extermanate it claims they can do it automatically, and other programs too. Have fun cleaning this mess up.</p>
<p>If your infected, it’s best to make a list of what programs you need, back up all your files (THAT ARE NOT .EXE’s, as they will be infected), wipe your HD, reinstall windows and reinstall all your stuff.</p>
<p><img src="http://i48.tinypic.com/2lo6q7o.png" alt width="617" height="162"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/exrerendum-has-a-virus-notice/316993/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/exrerendum-has-a-virus-notice/316993/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 28 Nov 2009 22:20:59 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-316993-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/exrerendum-has-a-virus-notice/316993.rss">ExRerendum has a Virus [NOTICE]</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
