<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Help with a client</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/help-with-a-client/378792</link>
    <description>[s]Okay, i havnt been on moparscape, in well....a very long time. Basically, ive been &quot;trying&quot; to code servers on and off, starting from blanks. I always end up running into problems, so i got sick of it, And rather just be called a leecher. So now im just taking all stars source, and changing it up a BIT, not a whole lot. Just enough to feel i have a right to call it partially mine. 

ANYWAY, there lies a problem..... I need a client that runs with all star&#39;s source. Ive been spending the last past 2 days looking up and down the server downloads section, and making constant use of the search bar. All i require is a client that Runs with allstar, So with that said, Can someone give me some clues of where i could get one? Im not saying to post a link, im just saying if u know a source that had a client link, and u think it would work, to give me the name of it, and ill find it myself. 

(not sure if what i just put up is aginst the rules :O) Thanks for reading, wuvs ya all =][/s]



crap , posted in wrong section. SORRY! im fixing that right now!</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 17 Jan 2011 17:24:42 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/help-with-a-client/378792.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Help with a client</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Ahyo Ahyo]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/ahyo">@Ahyo</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[s]Okay, i havnt been on moparscape, in well…a very long time. Basically, ive been “trying” to code servers on and off, starting from blanks. I always end up running into problems, so i got sick of it, And rather just be called a leecher. So now im just taking all stars source, and changing it up a BIT, not a whole lot. Just enough to feel i have a right to call it partially mine.</p>
<p>ANYWAY, there lies a problem… I need a client that runs with all star’s source. Ive been spending the last past 2 days looking up and down the server downloads section, and making constant use of the search bar. All i require is a client that Runs with allstar, So with that said, Can someone give me some clues of where i could get one? Im not saying to post a link, im just saying if u know a source that had a client link, and u think it would work, to give me the name of it, and ill find it myself.</p>
<p>(not sure if what i just put up is aginst the rules :O) Thanks for reading, wuvs ya all =][/s]</p>
<p>crap , posted in wrong section. SORRY! im fixing that right now!</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/help-with-a-client/378792/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/help-with-a-client/378792/1</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 17 Jan 2011 17:24:42 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-378792-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/help-with-a-client/378792.rss">Help with a client</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
