<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Not even sure if anyone knows how</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/not-even-sure-if-anyone-knows-how/37048</link>
    <description>ok this one is with the bug that i know certain ppl know of, but not sure if anyone has figured it out.  So here i am asking anyways:

You know how you have to have shops and stuff near the top of the autospawn or they won&#39;t work?  well i figured out the reason for that is because if the npcslot is over a certain number it gives a wrong slot when clicking the npc, and causes a arrayoutofbounds.  so i tried by myself, and searched around, on a different way of getting npcslot when u click the npc.  and none of my tries worked.  

this is one of the codes i&#39;m talking about:  

[code]            case 17: //second Click npc
                NPCSlot = ((misc.HexToInt(inStream.buffer, 0, packetSize) / 1000) - 128);
                NPCID = server.npcHandler.npcs[NPCSlot].npcType;[/code]

if the real slot is higher than a certain number then it NPCSlot will be wrong, which will cause the next line to crash.
so what i&#39;m asking is, has anyone figured out the fix for this, other than just putting shops/etc in the top of the autospawn?  cuz i am working on pets, and when u spawn an npc, it is at the end, so causes crash..  hmm just thought to my self, u know how when u try to bank more than 255 u have to do something diff? wonder if it&#39;s like that...  doubt it but anyways, good luck figuring this out.  and if u have can u plz help?  [br][size=1]Posted at: November 15, 2006, 05:45:34 PM[/size][hr]Still not answered, and still looking around, haven&#39;t found any server sources, using anything different.  if you don&#39;t understand what i mean ask, and i&#39;ll try to explain better.  [br][size=1]Posted at: November 22, 2006, 09:27:19 AM[/size][hr]still can&#39;t figure this out, i&#39;ve tried a lot of diff things, like using different hex to int convert codes i found on net, and nothing works at all, just the one i got, and only for a certain set of numbers...  anyone??  no one has figured this out yet?  or is it that no one wants to share it?[br][size=1]Posted at: November 28, 2006, 04:07:29 PM[/size][hr]i still haven&#39;t found a source or tut or anything on fixing this common bug...why is everyone &quot;okay&quot; with this bug?  cuz they can&#39;t figure it out, or cuz they just put to top of list and &quot;oh well&quot;?  anyways, can someone help me work on this?</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 19 Dec 2006 12:54:42 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/not-even-sure-if-anyone-knows-how/37048.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Not even sure if anyone knows how</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@adam2348 adam2348]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/adam2348">@adam2348</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>ok this one is with the bug that i know certain ppl know of, but not sure if anyone has figured it out.  So here i am asking anyways:</p>
<p>You know how you have to have shops and stuff near the top of the autospawn or they won’t work?  well i figured out the reason for that is because if the npcslot is over a certain number it gives a wrong slot when clicking the npc, and causes a arrayoutofbounds.  so i tried by myself, and searched around, on a different way of getting npcslot when u click the npc.  and none of my tries worked.</p>
<p>this is one of the codes i’m talking about:</p>
<p><code>            case 17: //second Click npc
                NPCSlot = ((misc.HexToInt(inStream.buffer, 0, packetSize) / 1000) - 128);
                NPCID = server.npcHandler.npcs[NPCSlot].npcType;</code></p>
<p>if the real slot is higher than a certain number then it NPCSlot will be wrong, which will cause the next line to crash.<br>
so what i’m asking is, has anyone figured out the fix for this, other than just putting shops/etc in the top of the autospawn?  cuz i am working on pets, and when u spawn an npc, it is at the end, so causes crash…  hmm just thought to my self, u know how when u try to bank more than 255 u have to do something diff? wonder if it’s like that…  doubt it but anyways, good luck figuring this out.  and if u have can u plz help?  [br][size=1]Posted at: November 15, 2006, 05:45:34 PM[/size][hr]Still not answered, and still looking around, haven’t found any server sources, using anything different.  if you don’t understand what i mean ask, and i’ll try to explain better.  [br][size=1]Posted at: November 22, 2006, 09:27:19 AM[/size][hr]still can’t figure this out, i’ve tried a lot of diff things, like using different hex to int convert codes i found on net, and nothing works at all, just the one i got, and only for a certain set of numbers…  anyone??  no one has figured this out yet?  or is it that no one wants to share it?[br][size=1]Posted at: November 28, 2006, 04:07:29 PM[/size][hr]i still haven’t found a source or tut or anything on fixing this common bug…why is everyone “okay” with this bug?  cuz they can’t figure it out, or cuz they just put to top of list and “oh well”?  anyways, can someone help me work on this?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/not-even-sure-if-anyone-knows-how/37048/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/not-even-sure-if-anyone-knows-how/37048/1</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 19 Dec 2006 12:54:42 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-37048-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/not-even-sure-if-anyone-knows-how/37048.rss">Not even sure if anyone knows how</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
