<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Far Cry 3</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/far-cry-3/478264</link>
    <description>I wrote this drunk so maybe it isn&#39;t as entertaining as I would have liked, but let me know what you think.

&lt;blockquote&gt;Far Cry 3

Preface: I’m not sure if I would be considered a “gamer”. I have four or five games on steam and maybe a small handful of physical titles. I have however racked up an awful lot of time on various FPS games, and no-lifed HoN (Heroes Of Newerth - a MOBA type game. Think League of Legends but for grown ups) and Diablo 3, so I’m definitely no stranger to gaming. I purchased Far Cry 3 whilst quite inebriated on a whim, needing something to do to whittle away a boring evening, and without further ado, here are some words about the game.

I had high hopes for this game what with it being the #1 seller on Steam at the time (though now I realise it was only selling so well because it was on sale), and when the download was *finally* over and I started it up the it was impossible not to be frustrated by how god-damn awful the interface was. It’s reasonably pretty to look at but clearly designed for consoles and ported badly: a lot of jiggling of the mouse is involved in trying to actually get to where you want to be. Not a particularly good start.

First thing I notice on getting into the game: the game is really quite good looking. Now, I wasn’t running it on ULTRA SETTINGS because I’m not some sort of ultra nerd with a crazy overclocked rig, but it was still real nice to look at.

As for the story, the premise is fairly simple - a group of young, attractive, free-spirited american twenty-somethings are having the time of their lives on holiday on some remote island somewhere, but after a skydiving incident goes wrong they end up captured by a group of mean looking pirates. Fair enough, it could happen to anyone. The first ‘level’ is a sort of tutorial type thing, where you and your bad-ass ex-army-or-whatever brother try to escape the camp full of bad guys. This features the usual ‘use the mouse to look around’, and ‘press C to crouch’ tips, as well as a little stealthy stuff - teaching you that if you crouch and hide in some foliage (I think they were marijuana plants - any chance I could pocket a few?) bad guys can’t see you.

More escaping ensues, and eventually you find some friendly islanders willing to help you out on your quest. They introduce you to the skilling system - a fairly limited tree of abilities you can unlock by doing the usual stuff - killing bad guys and some side quests. None of these abilities struck me as especially exciting and most of them seem to be locked until the later stages of the game anyway, and if I’m honest they felt a little tacked on, more like an afterthought than anything particularly integral or worth pursuing. At no point did I find myself getting excited when ‘leveling up’: “Sweet, now I can breathe 50% longer while underwater!”. Whoopee.

The game essentially boils down to a big open-world first person shooter. The main quest being to jump through a bunch of seemingly inconsequential hoops to try and eventually save your buddies, but there’s also a bunch of side quests that seem to mostly involve killing small groups of bad guys (like you’ve never done that before) and hunting various animals (I’ll get to that in a minute). There’s also outposts to re-capture from the bad guys, which admittedly was rather fun: You have the option of going all rambo style on them or opting for a more stealthy avenue, but there’s only about twenty or so to take which proved a nice respite from seemingly aimlessly wandering around a giant tropical island.

But, inevitably, all this fun must come to an end and the crafting system rears its ugly head. To acquire weapons, ammunition, and supplies in this game you need cash, and while there are a couple of different ways to get cash, there’s only one place to store it: your wallet. When starting out, your wallet can only hold $1,000 which in game terms is a pretty paltry amount. That said, you can upgrade your wallet - and this is where the crafting system comes in. In order to do this, you need to hunt down some animal (I think it’s a pig or something but I forget), kill it, and harvest its skin, and then turn it into a wallet. When your wallet is full, you can’t pick up any more money or sell any items, so if your inventory gets full as well you’ll have to start throwing stuff away. Frankly I found this not only immensely frustrating to have to stop killing whatever bad guys you were killing to go wander round the jungle looking for a pig just so you can craft a bigger wallet. I didn’t find it fun at all, and it kinda tarnished the rest of the game for me.

Speaking of crafting, the game also featured ‘syringes’ that seem to be used primarily for restoring health quickly, but can also be used for other things. I never figured out what these other things were because my syringe pack was always full (and I’d have to go hunt &amp; slaughter some other poor animal to make a bigger one), they didn’t sound very interesting, and I couldn’t for the life of me figure out how to use them because the built-for-consoles-first UI was built for, well, consoles.

I couldn’t possibly write this review without a mention of the most terrifying video game character I’ve yet to meet: the terrifying and vaguely homosexual Buck (“he likes to fuck”). About half way through the game you discover this monstrosity is holding one of your friends captive, and he sets you off on a wild goose chase to find some antique to get your friend back. Interspersing these quests are a series of threatening and euphemistic cutscenes that made me as a player a little uncomfortable. The frank brutality of it in comparison to the rest of the games trivialities (killing defenceless animals to craft gear, harvesting plants) made the whole game feel sort of surreal and a bit silly.

Later on, you ‘unlock’ a new island, where the bad guys are a little tougher the game gets a little bit more interesting from a FPS perspective. Capturing outposts gets more challenging and there’s a lot more planning involved in mob fights. Unfortunately, this is where the story ends. Just as things were starting to warm up I ran out of things to do, having cleared out all the outposts on the island and finished the main story.

So, that’s that. Just as it’s starting to get interesting, it’s all over. That pretty much sums up Far Cry 3 for me. A lot of build up and then just nothing - it keeps getting better (by that I mean it gets less frustrating once you’ve crafted the things you need) but by the time it is actually enjoyable as an FPS there’s nothing left to do. Truthfully, I had no idea what to expect when I impulse-purchased this game, and really I should have read more into it before I bought it, because this whole half-arsed open-world format really didn’t do anything for me. I expect my fps games to be full of action, but in Far Cry 3 there’s more running around the map than anything else. But with that said, if running around a well-rendered jungle half-heartedly trying to rescue  is your thing, maybe this might be the game for you.&lt;/blockquote&gt;</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 18 Feb 2013 06:44:11 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>General Discussion</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/far-cry-3/478264.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Far Cry 3</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Yz85Racer Yz85Racer]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/yz85racer">@Yz85Racer</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I actually loved Far Cry 3, but I’m a bit of a fanboy of the series :S</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/far-cry-3/478264/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/far-cry-3/478264/4</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 18 Feb 2013 06:44:11 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-478264-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/far-cry-3/478264.rss">Far Cry 3</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Far Cry 3</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@MujaheD Radeon]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/mujahed">@MujaheD</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>tl;dr but I finished the game yesterday and it was incredible</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/far-cry-3/478264/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/far-cry-3/478264/3</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 11 Feb 2013 22:59:40 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-478264-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/far-cry-3/478264.rss">Far Cry 3</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Far Cry 3</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@latifundio latifundio]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/latifundio">@latifundio</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Thanks for the info, i just hope to never play this game.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/far-cry-3/478264/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/far-cry-3/478264/2</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 10 Feb 2013 04:30:22 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-478264-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/far-cry-3/478264.rss">Far Cry 3</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Far Cry 3</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Stork Stork]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/stork">@Stork</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I wrote this drunk so maybe it isn’t as entertaining as I would have liked, but let me know what you think.</p>
<blockquote>Far Cry 3
<p>Preface: I’m not sure if I would be considered a “gamer”. I have four or five games on steam and maybe a small handful of physical titles. I have however racked up an awful lot of time on various FPS games, and no-lifed HoN (Heroes Of Newerth - a MOBA type game. Think League of Legends but for grown ups) and Diablo 3, so I’m definitely no stranger to gaming. I purchased Far Cry 3 whilst quite inebriated on a whim, needing something to do to whittle away a boring evening, and without further ado, here are some words about the game.</p>
<p>I had high hopes for this game what with it being the <span class="hashtag">#1</span> seller on Steam at the time (though now I realise it was only selling so well because it was on sale), and when the download was <em>finally</em> over and I started it up the it was impossible not to be frustrated by how god-damn awful the interface was. It’s reasonably pretty to look at but clearly designed for consoles and ported badly: a lot of jiggling of the mouse is involved in trying to actually get to where you want to be. Not a particularly good start.</p>
<p>First thing I notice on getting into the game: the game is really quite good looking. Now, I wasn’t running it on ULTRA SETTINGS because I’m not some sort of ultra nerd with a crazy overclocked rig, but it was still real nice to look at.</p>
<p>As for the story, the premise is fairly simple - a group of young, attractive, free-spirited american twenty-somethings are having the time of their lives on holiday on some remote island somewhere, but after a skydiving incident goes wrong they end up captured by a group of mean looking pirates. Fair enough, it could happen to anyone. The first ‘level’ is a sort of tutorial type thing, where you and your bad-ass ex-army-or-whatever brother try to escape the camp full of bad guys. This features the usual ‘use the mouse to look around’, and ‘press C to crouch’ tips, as well as a little stealthy stuff - teaching you that if you crouch and hide in some foliage (I think they were marijuana plants - any chance I could pocket a few?) bad guys can’t see you.</p>
<p>More escaping ensues, and eventually you find some friendly islanders willing to help you out on your quest. They introduce you to the skilling system - a fairly limited tree of abilities you can unlock by doing the usual stuff - killing bad guys and some side quests. None of these abilities struck me as especially exciting and most of them seem to be locked until the later stages of the game anyway, and if I’m honest they felt a little tacked on, more like an afterthought than anything particularly integral or worth pursuing. At no point did I find myself getting excited when ‘leveling up’: “Sweet, now I can breathe 50% longer while underwater!”. Whoopee.</p>
<p>The game essentially boils down to a big open-world first person shooter. The main quest being to jump through a bunch of seemingly inconsequential hoops to try and eventually save your buddies, but there’s also a bunch of side quests that seem to mostly involve killing small groups of bad guys (like you’ve never done that before) and hunting various animals (I’ll get to that in a minute). There’s also outposts to re-capture from the bad guys, which admittedly was rather fun: You have the option of going all rambo style on them or opting for a more stealthy avenue, but there’s only about twenty or so to take which proved a nice respite from seemingly aimlessly wandering around a giant tropical island.</p>
<p>But, inevitably, all this fun must come to an end and the crafting system rears its ugly head. To acquire weapons, ammunition, and supplies in this game you need cash, and while there are a couple of different ways to get cash, there’s only one place to store it: your wallet. When starting out, your wallet can only hold $1,000 which in game terms is a pretty paltry amount. That said, you can upgrade your wallet - and this is where the crafting system comes in. In order to do this, you need to hunt down some animal (I think it’s a pig or something but I forget), kill it, and harvest its skin, and then turn it into a wallet. When your wallet is full, you can’t pick up any more money or sell any items, so if your inventory gets full as well you’ll have to start throwing stuff away. Frankly I found this not only immensely frustrating to have to stop killing whatever bad guys you were killing to go wander round the jungle looking for a pig just so you can craft a bigger wallet. I didn’t find it fun at all, and it kinda tarnished the rest of the game for me.</p>
<p>Speaking of crafting, the game also featured ‘syringes’ that seem to be used primarily for restoring health quickly, but can also be used for other things. I never figured out what these other things were because my syringe pack was always full (and I’d have to go hunt &amp; slaughter some other poor animal to make a bigger one), they didn’t sound very interesting, and I couldn’t for the life of me figure out how to use them because the built-for-consoles-first UI was built for, well, consoles.</p>
<p>I couldn’t possibly write this review without a mention of the most terrifying video game character I’ve yet to meet: the terrifying and vaguely homosexual Buck (“he likes to fuck”). About half way through the game you discover this monstrosity is holding one of your friends captive, and he sets you off on a wild goose chase to find some antique to get your friend back. Interspersing these quests are a series of threatening and euphemistic cutscenes that made me as a player a little uncomfortable. The frank brutality of it in comparison to the rest of the games trivialities (killing defenceless animals to craft gear, harvesting plants) made the whole game feel sort of surreal and a bit silly.</p>
<p>Later on, you ‘unlock’ a new island, where the bad guys are a little tougher the game gets a little bit more interesting from a FPS perspective. Capturing outposts gets more challenging and there’s a lot more planning involved in mob fights. Unfortunately, this is where the story ends. Just as things were starting to warm up I ran out of things to do, having cleared out all the outposts on the island and finished the main story.</p>
<p>So, that’s that. Just as it’s starting to get interesting, it’s all over. That pretty much sums up Far Cry 3 for me. A lot of build up and then just nothing - it keeps getting better (by that I mean it gets less frustrating once you’ve crafted the things you need) but by the time it is actually enjoyable as an FPS there’s nothing left to do. Truthfully, I had no idea what to expect when I impulse-purchased this game, and really I should have read more into it before I bought it, because this whole half-arsed open-world format really didn’t do anything for me. I expect my fps games to be full of action, but in Far Cry 3 there’s more running around the map than anything else. But with that said, if running around a well-rendered jungle half-heartedly trying to rescue  is your thing, maybe this might be the game for you.</p>
</blockquote>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/far-cry-3/478264/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/far-cry-3/478264/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 12 Jan 2013 19:28:11 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-478264-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/far-cry-3/478264.rss">Far Cry 3</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
