<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Ya I need a bit of help with private servers</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/ya-i-need-a-bit-of-help-with-private-servers/22687</link>
    <description>If you flame me you will not get a reply. People who flame newbs for being NEW at something are just noobs themselves. Now I&#39;m not incompentant, I&#39;ve been searching for 2 straight days all over this site and others trying to figure out what the hell I&#39;m supposed to do and am still stuck. So here&#39;s my problem...

I have no-ip, and hamachi, I have testscape, I&#39;m willing to download w/e, delete w/e, but everytime I try to log onto the private server, it logs me onto someone elses :/

(BTW These errors have occered on both my hamachi and no-ip.)

So heres the thing, I&#39;ve read tons of those tut&#39;s on how to make a private server, and I&#39;ve got testscape up and running, got the 0.0.0.0.43594 up and running. So I try to log on with that up and running and it&#39;ll say &quot;Error: unable to starup listener on 43594 - port already in use?&quot; That&#39;s what it says on running bot. So here I am, just really really confused, as for the administration stuff, try to help me out on that or w/e but I&#39;ve searched all over test scape and hybridscape files with no avail as to where I&#39;m supposed to find that stupid &quot;administration&quot; file. So I&#39;m beyond confused right now, and too tired to care about having too much pride to ask for help. 

So here I am asking for help, heck I don&#39;t even know if  I posted this in the right place :/ I&#39;m really sorry if I didn&#39;t, I&#39;m new but a quick learner and ready and willing to learn. So help me out here and I&#39;ll be extremely grateful![br][size=1]Posted at: November 06, 2006, 01:45:30 AM[/size][hr]Alright someone please help me. I&#39;m beginning to think its my router but the tuts I&#39;ve read have not helped me at ALL with my router.[br][size=1]Posted at: November 06, 2006, 12:41:59 PM[/size][hr]I know ya&#39;ll can help me with this.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 08 Nov 2006 02:01:55 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/ya-i-need-a-bit-of-help-with-private-servers/22687.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Ya I need a bit of help with private servers</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@jason_x jason_x]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/jason_x">@jason_x</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>oh lol no you downloaded his source that dosent mean your on his server he made it but he didnt change any of the menus or anything you have to do that yourself lol. if you would have said something sooner i would have been able to help more.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/ya-i-need-a-bit-of-help-with-private-servers/22687/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/ya-i-need-a-bit-of-help-with-private-servers/22687/6</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 08 Nov 2006 02:01:55 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-22687-6</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/ya-i-need-a-bit-of-help-with-private-servers/22687.rss">Ya I need a bit of help with private servers</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Ya I need a bit of help with private servers</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@blayde9999 blayde9999]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/blayde9999">@blayde9999</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Basically what its doing is saying that I got logged onto “testscape made by vi divid” or w/e that guys name is. Than it continues to list his mods and player mods of that testscape. So this is just beyond confusing to me :/[br][size=1]Posted at: November 06, 2006, 02:24:39 PM[/size][hr]<br>
Blayde<br>
Under<br>
Massive<br>
Pain -,- helllllp</p>
<p>bump</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/ya-i-need-a-bit-of-help-with-private-servers/22687/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/ya-i-need-a-bit-of-help-with-private-servers/22687/5</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2006 01:54:31 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-22687-5</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/ya-i-need-a-bit-of-help-with-private-servers/22687.rss">Ya I need a bit of help with private servers</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Ya I need a bit of help with private servers</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@jason_x jason_x]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/jason_x">@jason_x</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>hmmm i guess i would recomend whitescape since you cannot get p16. and i have no clue why its sending you to someone elses server</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/ya-i-need-a-bit-of-help-with-private-servers/22687/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/ya-i-need-a-bit-of-help-with-private-servers/22687/4</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2006 00:41:23 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-22687-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/ya-i-need-a-bit-of-help-with-private-servers/22687.rss">Ya I need a bit of help with private servers</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Ya I need a bit of help with private servers</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@blayde9999 blayde9999]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/blayde9999">@blayde9999</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Ok this is a pain in the butt but when I tried to download P16 it did NOT work, when I clicked on the newest version it said “page cannot be found”, when I went to the version under that one, it downloaded yet I couldn’t pull it up -,-. I’ll try again, and what should I download? Which one would you most highly recommend? Cheezscape? p16? Or whitescape?</p>
<p>I have been trying the local host but its not helping, its still sending me to someone elses testscape.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/ya-i-need-a-bit-of-help-with-private-servers/22687/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/ya-i-need-a-bit-of-help-with-private-servers/22687/3</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2006 00:34:44 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-22687-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/ya-i-need-a-bit-of-help-with-private-servers/22687.rss">Ya I need a bit of help with private servers</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Ya I need a bit of help with private servers</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@jason_x jason_x]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/jason_x">@jason_x</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>ok i got that once use a different source like p16 or cheezscape or make sure you dont have like your compile open and your runserver and as for theip thing use the term localhost as your ip and youll be able to log into it hope that helped.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/ya-i-need-a-bit-of-help-with-private-servers/22687/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/ya-i-need-a-bit-of-help-with-private-servers/22687/2</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2006 00:27:35 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-22687-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/ya-i-need-a-bit-of-help-with-private-servers/22687.rss">Ya I need a bit of help with private servers</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Ya I need a bit of help with private servers</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@blayde9999 blayde9999]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/blayde9999">@blayde9999</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>If you flame me you will not get a reply. People who flame newbs for being NEW at something are just noobs themselves. Now I’m not incompentant, I’ve been searching for 2 straight days all over this site and others trying to figure out what the hell I’m supposed to do and am still stuck. So here’s my problem…</p>
<p>I have no-ip, and hamachi, I have testscape, I’m willing to download w/e, delete w/e, but everytime I try to log onto the private server, it logs me onto someone elses <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/confused.png?v=9" title=":confused:" class="emoji" alt=":confused:"></p>
<p>(BTW These errors have occered on both my hamachi and no-ip.)</p>
<p>So heres the thing, I’ve read tons of those tut’s on how to make a private server, and I’ve got testscape up and running, got the 0.0.0.0.43594 up and running. So I try to log on with that up and running and it’ll say “Error: unable to starup listener on 43594 - port already in use?” That’s what it says on running bot. So here I am, just really really confused, as for the administration stuff, try to help me out on that or w/e but I’ve searched all over test scape and hybridscape files with no avail as to where I’m supposed to find that stupid “administration” file. So I’m beyond confused right now, and too tired to care about having too much pride to ask for help.</p>
<p>So here I am asking for help, heck I don’t even know if  I posted this in the right place <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/confused.png?v=9" title=":confused:" class="emoji" alt=":confused:"> I’m really sorry if I didn’t, I’m new but a quick learner and ready and willing to learn. So help me out here and I’ll be extremely grateful![br][size=1]Posted at: November 06, 2006, 01:45:30 AM[/size][hr]Alright someone please help me. I’m beginning to think its my router but the tuts I’ve read have not helped me at ALL with my router.[br][size=1]Posted at: November 06, 2006, 12:41:59 PM[/size][hr]I know ya’ll can help me with this.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/ya-i-need-a-bit-of-help-with-private-servers/22687/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/ya-i-need-a-bit-of-help-with-private-servers/22687/1</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2006 00:07:02 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-22687-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/ya-i-need-a-bit-of-help-with-private-servers/22687.rss">Ya I need a bit of help with private servers</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
