<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Who will be the next president? Good or bad?</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/who-will-be-the-next-president-good-or-bad/454137</link>
    <description>So recently I have been watching how both Obama and the other guy have been battling it out in their campaigns.

I am honestly lost who to vote for. 

On one side Obama has destroyed the economy worse than anybody else I know of could had. He has also forced it so we have to BUY medical insurance.(which I personally believe goes into my personal liberties ) 

On the other side, I am disgusted with the other candidate for a couple of reasons. First off, he blatantly states and I quote that &quot;the poor have a  safety net&quot; Maybe if he got his face out of his ass he would see that people are starving to death, burning/freezing to death, the total amount of people who are homeless because of the economy, etc. There is no safety net unless that net is death. Secondly, his vice was announced to be that Ryans guy. From what I have been able to gather from him he wants to pretty much screw over our elders, the older people(seniors).

So like I said I really am in a debatable time right now as to who to vote for. 

In one sense ... can&#39;t get much worse than Obama right? He spent more money than any other president! 

On the other hand...not sure I could stay in a country where our liberties are took away more, and our seniors privileges are stolen right from beneath them.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 26 Oct 2012 00:33:26 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>General Discussion</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/who-will-be-the-next-president-good-or-bad/454137.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Who will be the next president? Good or bad?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@bowserjr2 Bowser jr]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/bowserjr2">@bowserjr2</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p><div class="lazyYT" data-youtube-id="fUspLVStPbk" data-youtube-title="Every Sperm is Sacred - Monty Python's The Meaning of Life" data-width="480" data-height="270" data-parameters="feature=oembed&amp;wmode=opaque"></div><br>
This is why Moparisthebest is busy, all those kids he need to take care of.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/who-will-be-the-next-president-good-or-bad/454137/91">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/who-will-be-the-next-president-good-or-bad/454137/91</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 26 Oct 2012 00:33:26 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-454137-91</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/who-will-be-the-next-president-good-or-bad/454137.rss">Who will be the next president? Good or bad?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Who will be the next president? Good or bad?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@TheCyberMan TheCyberMan]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/thecyberman">@TheCyberMan</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“amy_webb, post:89, topic:454137”]So if abortion is murder, is ejaculation after masturbation murder too? I mean, you’re letting all of those potential human beings die for your own satisfaction. Had they been ejaculated into a females vagina they would at LEAST have a chance to develop, right? Just think about how many emotions they could of felt and the happiness if you had just done the natural thing, instead of jerking off.</p>
<p>It is up to the women to chose what she wishes to do with her unborn baby, no president, nor opinionated person should be able to stop that. It is her body, and therefore she has rights to chose. How would you like for people to take the rights to your body away because of their “religious values”?[/quote]</p>
<p>Religiously speaking (at least for Catholics), masturbation is condemned for being lustful and wasting potential life. Looks like we’re all going to hell, lol :rolleyes:</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/who-will-be-the-next-president-good-or-bad/454137/90">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/who-will-be-the-next-president-good-or-bad/454137/90</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 26 Oct 2012 00:08:07 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-454137-90</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/who-will-be-the-next-president-good-or-bad/454137.rss">Who will be the next president? Good or bad?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Who will be the next president? Good or bad?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@amy_webb1 amy_webb]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/amy_webb1">@amy_webb1</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>So if abortion is murder, is ejaculation after masturbation murder too? I mean, you’re letting all of those potential human beings die for your own satisfaction. Had they been ejaculated into a females vagina they would at LEAST have a chance to develop, right? Just think about how many emotions they could of felt and the happiness if you had just done the natural thing, instead of jerking off.</p>
<p>It is up to the women to chose what she wishes to do with her unborn baby, no president, nor opinionated person should be able to stop that. It is her body, and therefore she has rights to chose. How would you like for people to take the rights to your body away because of their “religious values”?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/who-will-be-the-next-president-good-or-bad/454137/89">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/who-will-be-the-next-president-good-or-bad/454137/89</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 23 Oct 2012 11:05:21 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-454137-89</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/who-will-be-the-next-president-good-or-bad/454137.rss">Who will be the next president? Good or bad?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Who will be the next president? Good or bad?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Rodgerwilco Rodgerwilco]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/rodgerwilco">@Rodgerwilco</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>“Abortion is advocated only by persons who have themselves been born.” Ronald Reagan</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/who-will-be-the-next-president-good-or-bad/454137/88">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/who-will-be-the-next-president-good-or-bad/454137/88</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 23 Oct 2012 07:36:41 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-454137-88</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/who-will-be-the-next-president-good-or-bad/454137.rss">Who will be the next president? Good or bad?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Who will be the next president? Good or bad?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@The_Un-Named The Un-Named]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/the_un-named">@The_Un-Named</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote" data-post="76" data-topic="454137">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/imsuperman05/40/5_e05bb34c421432ee4d40de30c10af3e5.png" class="avatar"> imsuperman05:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Rape is horrible, but why should the child pay for the sins (wrong doing) of another? The baby is innocent of the offense and his life should not be taken because of the act of another.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>bla bla bla, all I hear is why the FOETUS should and not the MOTHER as if to completely disregard the fact that women STILL DIE IN CHILDBIRTH</p>
<p>hell, on the topic of women dying in childbirth, mitt romney in the past told a woman not to abort a foetus that if carried to birth would have killed the mother, did I mention the foetus would not have survived the pregnancy regardless? this is quite fucking literally stone age barbarism due to religious beliefs and is quite literally ignoring medical science, this is not for the cause of preventing abortion to save a foetus, it is the cause of banning abortion for personal religious beliefs</p>
<aside class="quote quote-modified" data-post="76" data-topic="454137">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/imsuperman05/40/5_e05bb34c421432ee4d40de30c10af3e5.png" class="avatar"> imsuperman05:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Yes, because that’s the purpose of sex: to create human life.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>yeah well that’s just like your opinion man</p>
<p>proven fact: teens regularly cannot support a family without assistance from the state or their own family<br>
proven fact: a PROPER sex education reduces the number of teen pregnancies, std transmission<br>
proven fact: contraceptives reduce the number of teen pregnancies<br>
proven fact: condoms reduce the number of teen pregnancies, std transmission<br>
proven fact: sticking your head in a bucket of sand results in higher std transmission and higher teen pregnancy</p>
<p>I’m willing to bet you’re the kind of person who would fight tooth and nail to prevent women from having abortions but wouldn’t want to give your tax dollars to programs like welfare to support those babies once born</p>
<p>love the foetus but throw the baby in a trash can, amirite?</p>
<p>[quote=“imsuperman05, post:76, topic:454137”]This disregards the fact that the nature of the life is human. It has human DNA and is alive. How can its nature not be human if it is alive and has human DNA?</p>
<p>This asserts a false premise that someone is not human until he/she is fully developed.  What constitutes full development? One hour before birth or one hour after? Is there really a difference?[/quote]</p>
<p>no no no BAD</p>
<p>|<span class="bbcode-i">A straw man, also known in the UK as an Aunt Sally,[1][2] is a type of argument and is an informal fallacy based on misrepresentation of an opponent’s position.[3] To “attack a straw man” is to create the illusion of having refuted a proposition by replacing it with a superficially similar yet unequivalent proposition (the “straw man”), and refuting it, without ever having actually refuted the original position.[3][4]</span></p>
<p>I never said embryos or foetuses weren’t human, you are not attacking my position</p>
<aside class="quote quote-modified" data-post="76" data-topic="454137">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/imsuperman05/40/5_e05bb34c421432ee4d40de30c10af3e5.png" class="avatar"> imsuperman05:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>This is simply begging the question. You assume it isn’t human, even though it is alive and has human DNA, and then pass judgment that it is not a person.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>no no no BAD</p>
<p>|<span class="bbcode-i">A straw man, also known in the UK as an Aunt Sally,[1][2] is a type of argument and is an informal fallacy based on misrepresentation of an opponent’s position.[3] To “attack a straw man” is to create the illusion of having refuted a proposition by replacing it with a superficially similar yet unequivalent proposition (the “straw man”), and refuting it, without ever having actually refuted the original position.[3][4]</span></p>
<p>I never said embryos or foetuses weren’t human, you are not attacking my position</p>
<aside class="quote" data-post="76" data-topic="454137">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/imsuperman05/40/5_e05bb34c421432ee4d40de30c10af3e5.png" class="avatar"> imsuperman05:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>The fetus is alive and death injures it.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>the foetus is no more “alive” than skin cells or sperm, it is not a developed human being, injuring implies harm or pain was felt which is impossible before the 3rd trimester because the nerves and brain functions to recognise pain have not been developed</p>
<aside class="quote quote-modified" data-post="80" data-topic="454137">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/imsuperman05/40/5_e05bb34c421432ee4d40de30c10af3e5.png" class="avatar"> imsuperman05:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>So you’d rather kill the chance of a human life only because the mother has to “suffer” for 18 years?  Even if she does have an abortion, she will still have to live with killing another human being <span class="bbcode-i">and</span> the rape that caused it.  Don’t you think that is much worse?  Then that means the mother has no feelings about the life that has been removed from her womb, that wonderful place that only a woman in her nature has. Countless women are psychologically harmed when they kill the child in their womb.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>abortion is NOT the act of KILLING a human being, it is the act of PREVENTING A FOETUS FROM DEVELOPING</p>
<p>here’s an idea though, if abortion is murder, should all the women that do not carry a foetus to term be charged with manslaughter?</p>
<p>if abortion is murder, should women who smoke or drink be charged with negligence? if abortion is murder, should we bubble wrap women for 9 months just in case any harm comes to the baby due to not being bubble wrapped?</p>
<aside class="quote quote-modified" data-post="80" data-topic="454137">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/imsuperman05/40/5_e05bb34c421432ee4d40de30c10af3e5.png" class="avatar"> imsuperman05:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>It is not a “group of cells,” because after eighteen days the baby’s heart is already beating, probably pumping a different blood type than the mothers.  And so on and so forth, the baby starts to develop brain function and ability to react to certain things.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>“higher” brain function does NOT start until at least the 3rd trimester, abortions are generally legal UP UNTIL the 3rd trimester where the only legally recognised abortions are ones deemed medically necessarily</p>
<p>[quote=“imsuperman05, post:80, topic:454137”]“Does the baby feel pain during an abortion?”<br>
“Most likely yes. From six weeks the baby has sensation around its face and mouth. At seven weeks the baby can feel a needle stick and draw back. Even at that time if you put a little probe or instrument in the baby’s hand it will curl up its hand around it, so it feels things.”</p>
<p><a href="http://www.friendsoftheunborn.org/html/abortion_facts.html%5B/quote%5D" class="onebox" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">http://www.friendsoftheunborn.org/html/abortion_facts.html[/quote]</a></p>
<p>except that is completely FALSE and this is why you should NOT get information from BIASED WEBSITES</p>
<p>the nerve circuitry to recognise PAIN does NOT develop until around 26 weeks, or the 3rd trimester, and even then the ability to recognise pain depends on several other factors such as conciousness</p>
<p>since you are arguing that foetuses “feel” from 6 weeks as a position against abortion, I am going to propose the argument that because foetuses do not feel PAIN  until 26 weeks we should be able to abort them, hey it’s your logic pal</p>
<p>[quote=“imsuperman05, post:80, topic:454137”]Not to mention that an abortion hurts the mother too:<br>
“Does an abortion hurt?”<br>
“Yes it hurts because dilating the cervix. or the neck of the womb, has to be done causing cramping pain. Usually medication is given to help relieve this but the patient is usually awake. A local anesthetic is injected into the cervix to numb it up. This helps some.”[/quote]</p>
<p>see, if you had taken a proper sex-ed class you would have known this already</p>
<p>here’s an idea: women don’t get abortions so atheists can eat babies, women (usually) get abortions because they cannot financially or emotionally support a baby</p>
<aside class="quote quote-modified" data-post="82" data-topic="454137">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/imsuperman05/40/5_e05bb34c421432ee4d40de30c10af3e5.png" class="avatar"> imsuperman05:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>I would say a better option is to put the baby up for adoption, if the parents can’t handle it.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>and this is coming from someone who will NEVER have to carry a foetus for 9 months, give birth to it, raise that child for at least a few weeks and then have to go through the emotional blackmail of putting it up for adoption because you cannot support it</p>
<p>this is also coming from someone who presumably was not put up for adoption</p>
<p>this is also coming from someone who presumably was born into a family that could sustain a baby and had relatively few hardships</p>
<p>but correct me if I’m wrong</p>
<p>it must be so hard being a male of the race, not having to deal with any emotional or moral issues such as “can I financially support a baby that was forced upon me and if I do not does that make me a bad human being?”</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/who-will-be-the-next-president-good-or-bad/454137/87">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/who-will-be-the-next-president-good-or-bad/454137/87</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 23 Oct 2012 06:46:01 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-454137-87</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/who-will-be-the-next-president-good-or-bad/454137.rss">Who will be the next president? Good or bad?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Who will be the next president? Good or bad?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@reyx7 reyx7]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/reyx7">@reyx7</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote quote-modified" data-post="85" data-topic="454137">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/purestmage74/40/5_e05bb34c421432ee4d40de30c10af3e5.png" class="avatar"> purestmage74:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Romney’s already been decided 4 months ago (i heard)</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>For what, president? He’s had the nomination the longest. If you mean president stop smoking what you’re smoking. This is going to Obama, Romney’s messed up to many times on national TV.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/who-will-be-the-next-president-good-or-bad/454137/86">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/who-will-be-the-next-president-good-or-bad/454137/86</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 23 Oct 2012 01:34:42 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-454137-86</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/who-will-be-the-next-president-good-or-bad/454137.rss">Who will be the next president? Good or bad?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Who will be the next president? Good or bad?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@purestmage74 purestmage74]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/purestmage74">@purestmage74</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Romney’s already been decided 4 months ago (i heard)</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/who-will-be-the-next-president-good-or-bad/454137/85">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/who-will-be-the-next-president-good-or-bad/454137/85</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 23 Oct 2012 01:17:33 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-454137-85</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/who-will-be-the-next-president-good-or-bad/454137.rss">Who will be the next president? Good or bad?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Who will be the next president? Good or bad?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@eyeownyew Eyeownyew]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/eyeownyew">@eyeownyew</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“Bowser jr, post:83, topic:454137”][quote author=imsuperman05 link=topic=557009.msg4129950#msg4129950 date=1350950410]<br>
Where are you getting 18 years from?  Oh you’re assuming that the parents will keep the child until the child can live on its own.  I would say a better option is to put the baby up for adoption, if the parents can’t handle it.<br>
[/quote]<br>
Because it is so popular to adopt American children. You might be a superpower, but China beats you in have cute children.[/quote]<br>
I would say it is pretty popular to adopt American children… Especially in America, where 75% of the children are American children… /facepalm</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/who-will-be-the-next-president-good-or-bad/454137/84">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/who-will-be-the-next-president-good-or-bad/454137/84</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 23 Oct 2012 01:09:57 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-454137-84</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/who-will-be-the-next-president-good-or-bad/454137.rss">Who will be the next president? Good or bad?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Who will be the next president? Good or bad?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@bowserjr2 Bowser jr]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/bowserjr2">@bowserjr2</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote quote-modified" data-post="82" data-topic="454137">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/imsuperman05/40/5_e05bb34c421432ee4d40de30c10af3e5.png" class="avatar"> imsuperman05:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Where are you getting 18 years from?  Oh you’re assuming that the parents will keep the child until the child can live on its own.  I would say a better option is to put the baby up for adoption, if the parents can’t handle it.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Because it is so popular to adopt American children. You might be a superpower, but China beats you in have cute children.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/who-will-be-the-next-president-good-or-bad/454137/83">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/who-will-be-the-next-president-good-or-bad/454137/83</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 23 Oct 2012 00:04:02 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-454137-83</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/who-will-be-the-next-president-good-or-bad/454137.rss">Who will be the next president? Good or bad?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Who will be the next president? Good or bad?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@imsuperman05 imsuperman05]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/imsuperman05">@imsuperman05</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Where are you getting 18 years from?  Oh you’re assuming that the parents will keep the child until the child can live on its own.  I would say a better option is to put the baby up for adoption, if the parents can’t handle it.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/who-will-be-the-next-president-good-or-bad/454137/82">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/who-will-be-the-next-president-good-or-bad/454137/82</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 23 Oct 2012 00:00:10 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-454137-82</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/who-will-be-the-next-president-good-or-bad/454137.rss">Who will be the next president? Good or bad?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Who will be the next president? Good or bad?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@JavaTC JavaTC]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/javatc">@JavaTC</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <blockquote>So you'd rather kill the chance of a human life only because the mother has to "suffer" for 18 years?  Even if she does have an abortion, she will still have to live with killing another human being and the rape that caused it.  Don't you think that is much worse?  Then that means the mother has no feelings about the life that has been removed from her womb, that wonderful place that only a woman in her nature has. Countless women are psychologically harmed when they kill the child in their womb.</blockquote>
<p>So you’re saying raising children is a walk in the park?  Especially as a single mother of a rape baby?  Raising a child in the average family is absolute hell for the first while, whether it be monetary problems, depriving of sleep, worrying about the child, any alterations that may have occurred that pop up, etc.  It’s 100% dependent on the mother, so if she doesn’t think she can handle it, why should she put the child though the emotionally scarring roller coaster of adoption?</p>
<p>Although some may find it difficult, it’s their choice to keep it or not.  It’s a bit like they know what some people think about it, but they themselves would be much happier if they didn’t have to go though with it.  Like I said, the child is completely dependent on them during pregnancy, and the key rule to nature is survival of the fittest anyway.  I guess it’s also wrong when newborn animals are killed because they’re a easy and quick meal for predators?  They don’t care, they do it because they have to.</p>
<blockquote>he value of human life should not depend on the amount of people.  Children cannot work until the age of 12, according to the laws, so why would the birth of one child affect the availability of jobs?  What if that child were to grew up and start their own business, thus creating more jobs?</blockquote>
<p>I’m saying that one person leaving isn’t worth much if theirs millions of others to take their place.  You’re saying that killing one human is wrong and yet people die and people are born every day, and the population is still <a href="http://www.census.gov/main/www/popclock.html" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">growing by the minute.</a>  I’m not saying killing people is a good thing, but I’m saying potentially avoiding unnecessary suffering is.  According to those who are religious, the child would apparently go to a much better place than earth anyway.</p>
<blockquote>It is not a "group of cells," because after eighteen days the baby's heart is already beating, probably pumping a different blood type than the mothers.  And so on and so forth, the baby starts to develop brain function and ability to react to certain things.</blockquote>
<p>I’m no biologist, like I said, I was just going of the slight understanding of everything during pregnancy I have.</p>
<blockquote>"Does the baby feel pain during an abortion?"
"Most likely yes. From six weeks the baby has sensation around its face and mouth. At seven weeks the baby can feel a needle stick and draw back. Even at that time if you put a little probe or instrument in the baby's hand it will curl up its hand around it, so it feels things."
<p><a href="http://www.friendsoftheunborn.org/html/abortion_facts.html" class="onebox" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">http://www.friendsoftheunborn.org/html/abortion_facts.html</a></p>
<p>Not to mention that an abortion hurts the mother too:<br>
“Does an abortion hurt?”<br>
“Yes it hurts because dilating the cervix. or the neck of the womb, has to be done causing cramping pain. Usually medication is given to help relieve this but the patient is usually awake. A local anesthetic is injected into the cervix to numb it up. This helps some.”</p>
</blockquote>
<p>I’d say waiting until you’re ready both financially and emotionally and going though a couple days of cramps is much better than 18 years of emotional stress and financial trouble (not to mention when it comes time for labor).</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/who-will-be-the-next-president-good-or-bad/454137/81">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/who-will-be-the-next-president-good-or-bad/454137/81</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 22 Oct 2012 22:53:13 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-454137-81</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/who-will-be-the-next-president-good-or-bad/454137.rss">Who will be the next president? Good or bad?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Who will be the next president? Good or bad?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@imsuperman05 imsuperman05]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/imsuperman05">@imsuperman05</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote quote-modified" data-post="79" data-topic="454137">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/javatc/40/5_e05bb34c421432ee4d40de30c10af3e5.png" class="avatar"> JavaTC:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>[quote]Rape is horrible, but why should the child pay for the sins (wrong doing) of another? The baby is innocent of the offense and his life should not be taken because of the act of another.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>A loss of one life is better than 18 years of potential suffering of 2, is it not?  Especially considering the one being lost can contribute nothing for years and will take disable another (Taking care of the child, pregnancy and birth, after effects of both, etc)[/quote]So you’d rather kill the chance of a human life only because the mother has to “suffer” for 18 years?  Even if she does have an abortion, she will still have to live with killing another human being <span class="bbcode-i">and</span> the rape that caused it.  Don’t you think that is much worse?  Then that means the mother has no feelings about the life that has been removed from her womb, that wonderful place that only a woman in her nature has. Countless women are psychologically harmed when they kill the child in their womb.</p>
<aside class="quote quote-modified" data-post="79" data-topic="454137">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/javatc/40/5_e05bb34c421432ee4d40de30c10af3e5.png" class="avatar"> JavaTC:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>[quote]Since when does the value of human life depend upon how many people there are? Besides, if the number of people is the issue, maybe they should start getting rid of the sick and old. Maybe they should get rid of those who aren’t intelligent or good looking. Where will it stop?</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>The ‘value’ of a a human life defiantly depends on the current population.  A good example is the fact that there are only so many jobs available and so many that can be created due to Manual Labor requirements and those who are more intelligent.  If we have 10 million people but can only use 5, then that party clearly has no use for the extra 5 million, therefore only the most useful people will get the jobs and the rest will be unemployed.</p>
<p>My point being that the only thing that would come of this is using even more of our limited resources and create the suffering of more people.  Everyone has the right to have children, and they also have the choice to not have them should the situation present itself.[/quote]The value of human life should not depend on the amount of people.  Children cannot work until the age of 12, according to the laws, so why would the birth of one child affect the availability of jobs?  What if that child were to grew up and start their own business, thus creating more jobs?</p>
<aside class="quote quote-modified" data-post="79" data-topic="454137">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/javatc/40/5_e05bb34c421432ee4d40de30c10af3e5.png" class="avatar"> JavaTC:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>[quote]This disregards the fact that the nature of the life is human. It has human DNA and is alive. How can its nature not be human if it is alive and has human DNA?</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>You don’t understand what’s considered for a human to be alive.  If you get shot in the head, you die, correct?  But this does not mean that every single human cell in your body instantly dies with you.  They continue their functions until finally they run of whatever’s require to survive (I’m no biologist).  But we still say the human is dead, despite having living cells in it’s body, because they have clearly lost all brain function.</p>
<p>In the early stages, the baby has no brain function at all as far as I know, but rather it’s a group of cells forming into a new organism using what DNA was passed on from it’s parents.  So by the human standard, it’s not alive until it actually has a brain function, you’re only killing human cells with you do to yourself every day anyway.[/quote]It is not a “group of cells,” because after eighteen days the baby’s heart is already beating, probably pumping a different blood type than the mothers.  And so on and so forth, the baby starts to develop brain function and ability to react to certain things.</p>
<p>[quote=“JavaTC, post:79, topic:454137”][quote]This is simply begging the question. You assume it isn’t human, even though it is alive and has human DNA, and then pass judgment that it is not a person</p>
<p>The fetus is alive and death injures it.[/quote]<br>
I already answered this above.  And no, it doesn’t injure it as it has no sense of pain.  Even after birth, infants know nothing about general feelings and for a while, can’t tell the difference between pain and relief.  This is a brief period after birth I believe but it’s still there.[/quote]<br>
“Does the baby feel pain during an abortion?”<br>
“Most likely yes. From six weeks the baby has sensation around its face and mouth. At seven weeks the baby can feel a needle stick and draw back. Even at that time if you put a little probe or instrument in the baby’s hand it will curl up its hand around it, so it feels things.”</p>
<p><a href="http://www.friendsoftheunborn.org/html/abortion_facts.html" class="onebox" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">http://www.friendsoftheunborn.org/html/abortion_facts.html</a></p>
<p>Not to mention that an abortion hurts the mother too:<br>
“Does an abortion hurt?”<br>
“Yes it hurts because dilating the cervix. or the neck of the womb, has to be done causing cramping pain. Usually medication is given to help relieve this but the patient is usually awake. A local anesthetic is injected into the cervix to numb it up. This helps some.”</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/who-will-be-the-next-president-good-or-bad/454137/80">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/who-will-be-the-next-president-good-or-bad/454137/80</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 22 Oct 2012 14:47:19 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-454137-80</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/who-will-be-the-next-president-good-or-bad/454137.rss">Who will be the next president? Good or bad?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Who will be the next president? Good or bad?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@JavaTC JavaTC]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/javatc">@JavaTC</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Not trying to jump into an argument, but I just have to comment on this.</p>
<blockquote>Rape is horrible, but why should the child pay for the sins (wrong doing) of another? The baby is innocent of the offense and his life should not be taken because of the act of another.</blockquote>
A loss of one life is better than 18 years of potential suffering of 2, is it not?  Especially considering the one being lost can contribute nothing for years and will take disable another (Taking care of the child, pregnancy and birth, after effects of both, etc)
<blockquote>Since when does the value of human life depend upon how many people there are? Besides, if the number of people is the issue, maybe they should start getting rid of the sick and old. Maybe they should get rid of those who aren't intelligent or good looking. Where will it stop?</blockquote>
The 'value' of a a human life defiantly depends on the current population.  A good example is the fact that there are only so many jobs available and so many that can be created due to Manual Labor requirements and those who are more intelligent.  If we have 10 million people but can only use 5, then that party clearly has no use for the extra 5 million, therefore only the most useful people will get the jobs and the rest will be unemployed.
<p>My point being that the only thing that would come of this is using even more of our limited resources and create the suffering of more people.  Everyone has the right to have children, and they also have the choice to not have them should the situation present itself.</p>
<blockquote>This disregards the fact that the nature of the life is human. It has human DNA and is alive. How can its nature not be human if it is alive and has human DNA?</blockquote>
You don't understand what's considered for a human to be alive.  If you get shot in the head, you die, correct?  But this does not mean that every single human cell in your body instantly dies with you.  They continue their functions until finally they run of whatever's require to survive (I'm no biologist).  But we still say the human is dead, despite having living cells in it's body, because they have clearly lost all brain function.  
<p>In the early stages, the baby has no brain function at all as far as I know, but rather it’s a group of cells forming into a new organism using what DNA was passed on from it’s parents.  So by the human standard, it’s not alive until it actually has a brain function, you’re only killing human cells with you do to yourself every day anyway.</p>
<blockquote>This asserts a false premise that someone is not human until he/she is fully developed.  What constitutes full development? One hour before birth or one hour after? Is there really a difference?</blockquote>
And yet, by your own logic, you're assuming that they are fully human before their body is fully developed.
<blockquote>This is simply begging the question. You assume it isn't human, even though it is alive and has human DNA, and then pass judgment that it is not a person
<p>The fetus is alive and death injures it.</p>
</blockquote><br>
I already answered this above.  And no, it doesn’t injure it as it has no sense of pain.  Even after birth, infants know nothing about general feelings and for a while, can’t tell the difference between pain and relief.  This is a brief period after birth I believe but it’s still there.
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/who-will-be-the-next-president-good-or-bad/454137/79">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/who-will-be-the-next-president-good-or-bad/454137/79</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 22 Oct 2012 08:38:19 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-454137-79</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/who-will-be-the-next-president-good-or-bad/454137.rss">Who will be the next president? Good or bad?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Who will be the next president? Good or bad?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Rodgerwilco Rodgerwilco]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/rodgerwilco">@Rodgerwilco</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote" data-post="77" data-topic="454137">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 KroniKz_:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>anyone see obama 2016</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>waste of time to watch</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/who-will-be-the-next-president-good-or-bad/454137/78">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/who-will-be-the-next-president-good-or-bad/454137/78</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 22 Oct 2012 01:51:57 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-454137-78</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/who-will-be-the-next-president-good-or-bad/454137.rss">Who will be the next president? Good or bad?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Who will be the next president? Good or bad?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@kronixz kronikz]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/kronixz">@kronixz</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>anyone see obama 2016</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/who-will-be-the-next-president-good-or-bad/454137/77">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/who-will-be-the-next-president-good-or-bad/454137/77</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 21 Oct 2012 20:49:12 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-454137-77</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/who-will-be-the-next-president-good-or-bad/454137.rss">Who will be the next president? Good or bad?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Who will be the next president? Good or bad?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@imsuperman05 imsuperman05]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/imsuperman05">@imsuperman05</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote quote-modified" data-post="71" data-topic="454137">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 Niall:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>[quote author=imsuperman05 link=topic=557009.msg4128342#msg4128342 date=1350759235]You can bring all this scientific shit back, but it’s still murder.  Why should the baby have to be blamed for what the parents did?  Even if it was rape.  </p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>and this is why your argument is retarded beyond belief, you value the life of an unborn baby that may not even survive the pregnancy over a living human being, the mother, and why do you do this? because herp derp</p>
<p>“the baby should not be blamed for the parents actions” how about “the parent should not be <span class="bbcode-b">forced</span> to carry to term a rape baby enduring ridiculous physical and emotional stress for the length of the pregnancy and then face the emotional blackmail of keeping a rapebaby or giving it up for adoption”[/quote]Rape is horrible, but why should the child pay for the sins (wrong doing) of another? The baby is innocent of the offense and his life should not be taken because of the act of another.</p>
<aside class="quote quote-modified" data-post="71" data-topic="454137">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 Niall:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>[quote author=imsuperman05 link=topic=557009.msg4128342#msg4128342 date=1350759235]The answer to the debate of abortion is to educate teenagers about safe sex in order to not have to have an abortion.  It should be illegal and I will stand by that.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>then I guess it’s just too fucking bad that the majority of people who are anti-abortion are also anti-contraceptive and anti-sex ed and anti-sex in general unless for procreation because that’s what the bible says !![/quote]Yes, because that’s the purpose of sex: to create human life.</p>
<aside class="quote quote-modified" data-post="71" data-topic="454137">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 Niall:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>[quote author=Muroth link=topic=557009.msg4128367#msg4128367 date=1350762315]Think of when it’s born, even if you give it up for adoption, maybe because you can’t afford one, or maybe some other reason, you know you brought life into this world. Whether it’s a good life for them, or a bad one, they still had a life, and eventually one day they might have kids, and a new family would start. </p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>yes, just what this planet needs, more humans</p>
<p>we’re not overpopulated or anything[/quote]Since when does the value of human life depend upon how many people there are? Besides, if the number of people is the issue, maybe they should start getting rid of the sick and old. Maybe they should get rid of those who aren’t intelligent or good looking. Where will it stop?</p>
<p>[quote=“Niall, post:65, topic:454137”]that is an embryo at 5-6 weeks in, yes it may have a heartbeat, yes it may have some extremely limited brain functions but it is not a developed brain, and the language used to say “our brains are always developing” can either be interpreted as deceptive or blatantly wrong, yes, our brains may be developing in the sense that we can learn new information but they are not developing in the sense that new brain regions are being formed that are required for things like pain</p>
<p>it is the general scientific consensus that things like pain don’t develop until at LEAST 28 weeks in, and past 28 weeks is where most of the magic really happens, and you can disagree if you want but for the love of god don’t claim that embryos have brains at 6 weeks in[/quote]This disregards the fact that the nature of the life is human. It has human DNA and is alive. How can its nature not be human if it is alive and has human DNA?</p>
<p>This asserts a false premise that someone is not human until he/she is fully developed.  What constitutes full development? One hour before birth or one hour after? Is there really a difference?</p>
<p>[quote=“Niall, post:42, topic:454137”]it nearly could have been me been but that’s not the point and I’m still here saying abortion SHOULD be legal</p>
<p>the general scientific consensus is that embryos don’t feel pain before the 3rd trimester, and generally countries don’t allow abortions during the 3rd trimester unless it’s a medical necessity, does meaning the embryo doesn’t feel pain make it right? hell no, but given the alternative it’s the most humane thing to do, the alternative being FORCING the mother to carry it to term to then raise it or put her through the emotional blackmail of either giving it up or keeping it, for it to probably be born into a low income household where the child may not have a good life</p>
<p>but this is of course assuming that most abortions are done around 20-24 weeks which they generally aren’t, abortions are generally done early on when there really isn’t much in the way that can be called human[/quote]This is simply begging the question. You assume it isn’t human, even though it is alive and has human DNA, and then pass judgment that it is not a person.</p>
<p>The fetus is alive and death injures it.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/who-will-be-the-next-president-good-or-bad/454137/76">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/who-will-be-the-next-president-good-or-bad/454137/76</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 21 Oct 2012 16:26:43 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-454137-76</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/who-will-be-the-next-president-good-or-bad/454137.rss">Who will be the next president? Good or bad?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Who will be the next president? Good or bad?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@bowserjr2 Bowser jr]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/bowserjr2">@bowserjr2</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote" data-post="74" data-topic="454137">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 the elve age:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Electoral College is baaad.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>You don’t say…</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/who-will-be-the-next-president-good-or-bad/454137/75">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/who-will-be-the-next-president-good-or-bad/454137/75</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 21 Oct 2012 03:09:24 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-454137-75</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/who-will-be-the-next-president-good-or-bad/454137.rss">Who will be the next president? Good or bad?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Who will be the next president? Good or bad?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@the_elve_age the elve age]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/the_elve_age">@the_elve_age</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Electoral College is baaad.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/who-will-be-the-next-president-good-or-bad/454137/74">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/who-will-be-the-next-president-good-or-bad/454137/74</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 21 Oct 2012 03:05:31 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-454137-74</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/who-will-be-the-next-president-good-or-bad/454137.rss">Who will be the next president? Good or bad?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Who will be the next president? Good or bad?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@JavaTC JavaTC]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/javatc">@JavaTC</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I don’t see what’s so bad about abortion considering it’s basically human cells that will eventually form into a human being, however it’s only a clump of cells, it’s not like we’re smashing an infant’s head in, it has nothing it can contribute.  It has a chance to grow into a human but there’s no guarantee that it (or it’s mother) will survive the pregnancy anyway.</p>
<p>[quote=“Davidi2, post:72, topic:454137”]the answer is clear…</p>
<p>David Insley for write in candidate 2012[/quote]<br>
yes</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/who-will-be-the-next-president-good-or-bad/454137/73">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/who-will-be-the-next-president-good-or-bad/454137/73</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 21 Oct 2012 02:21:55 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-454137-73</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/who-will-be-the-next-president-good-or-bad/454137.rss">Who will be the next president? Good or bad?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Who will be the next president? Good or bad?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@davidi2 Davidi2]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/davidi2">@davidi2</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>the answer is clear…</p>
<p>David Insley for write in candidate 2012</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/who-will-be-the-next-president-good-or-bad/454137/72">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/who-will-be-the-next-president-good-or-bad/454137/72</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 21 Oct 2012 02:13:45 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-454137-72</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/who-will-be-the-next-president-good-or-bad/454137.rss">Who will be the next president? Good or bad?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Who will be the next president? Good or bad?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@The_Un-Named The Un-Named]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/the_un-named">@The_Un-Named</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote quote-modified" data-post="66" data-topic="454137">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/imsuperman05/40/5_e05bb34c421432ee4d40de30c10af3e5.png" class="avatar"> imsuperman05:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>You can bring all this scientific shit back, but it’s still murder.  Why should the baby have to be blamed for what the parents did?  Even if it was rape. </p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>and this is why your argument is retarded beyond belief, you value the life of an unborn baby that may not even survive the pregnancy over a living human being, the mother, and why do you do this? because herp derp</p>
<p>“the baby should not be blamed for the parents actions” how about “the parent should not be <span class="bbcode-b">forced</span> to carry to term a rape baby enduring ridiculous physical and emotional stress for the length of the pregnancy and then face the emotional blackmail of keeping a rapebaby or giving it up for adoption”</p>
<aside class="quote" data-post="66" data-topic="454137">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/imsuperman05/40/5_e05bb34c421432ee4d40de30c10af3e5.png" class="avatar"> imsuperman05:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>The answer to the debate of abortion is to educate teenagers about safe sex in order to not have to have an abortion.  It should be illegal and I will stand by that.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>then I guess it’s just too fucking bad that the majority of people who are anti-abortion are also anti-contraceptive and anti-sex ed and anti-sex in general unless for procreation because that’s what the bible says !!</p>
<aside class="quote quote-modified" data-post="67" data-topic="454137">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/muroth/40/5_e05bb34c421432ee4d40de30c10af3e5.png" class="avatar"> Muroth:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Think of when it’s born, even if you give it up for adoption, maybe because you can’t afford one, or maybe some other reason, you know you brought life into this world. Whether it’s a good life for them, or a bad one, they still had a life, and eventually one day they might have kids, and a new family would start.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>yes, just what this planet needs, more humans</p>
<p>we’re not overpopulated or anything</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/who-will-be-the-next-president-good-or-bad/454137/71">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/who-will-be-the-next-president-good-or-bad/454137/71</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 21 Oct 2012 01:25:54 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-454137-71</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/who-will-be-the-next-president-good-or-bad/454137.rss">Who will be the next president? Good or bad?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Who will be the next president? Good or bad?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@imsuperman05 imsuperman05]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/imsuperman05">@imsuperman05</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“eyeownyew, post:69, topic:454137”]This topic has gotten very far off-track… A mod might want to clean it up, or move the off-topic posts to a new thread[/quote]No it hasn’t.  Abortion is one of the reasons as to why some people vote for president and why i makes a president “good” or “bad”.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/who-will-be-the-next-president-good-or-bad/454137/70">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/who-will-be-the-next-president-good-or-bad/454137/70</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 20 Oct 2012 22:58:42 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-454137-70</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/who-will-be-the-next-president-good-or-bad/454137.rss">Who will be the next president? Good or bad?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Who will be the next president? Good or bad?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@eyeownyew Eyeownyew]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/eyeownyew">@eyeownyew</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>This topic has gotten very far off-track… A mod might want to clean it up, or move the off-topic posts to a new thread</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/who-will-be-the-next-president-good-or-bad/454137/69">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/who-will-be-the-next-president-good-or-bad/454137/69</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 20 Oct 2012 22:30:15 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-454137-69</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/who-will-be-the-next-president-good-or-bad/454137.rss">Who will be the next president? Good or bad?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Who will be the next president? Good or bad?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@imsuperman05 imsuperman05]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/imsuperman05">@imsuperman05</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>So you’re going to let Obama fuck up 4 years more?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/who-will-be-the-next-president-good-or-bad/454137/68">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/who-will-be-the-next-president-good-or-bad/454137/68</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 20 Oct 2012 20:38:53 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-454137-68</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/who-will-be-the-next-president-good-or-bad/454137.rss">Who will be the next president? Good or bad?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Who will be the next president? Good or bad?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Muroth Muroth]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/muroth">@Muroth</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“imsuperman05, post:66, topic:454137”][quote author=Niall link=topic=557009.msg4080361#msg4080361 date=1345314621]</p>
<aside class="quote">
<blockquote>
<aside class="quote">
<blockquote>
<aside class="quote">
<blockquote>
<p>No. If the mother truly doesn’t want the baby then she can put it up for adoption.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>so the mother of the child should be FORCED to carry that child to term, enduring physical and emotional stress for 9 months and then go through the emotional blackmail of keeping the baby or putting it up for adoption?</p>
<aside class="quote">
<blockquote>
<p>All humans have rights.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>cept you’re ignoring the mothers right to terminate the pregnancy when it is deemed medically safe to do so all because of your religious beliefs</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Yes, because that baby has as much right to live as the mother. The mother doesn’t have the right to kill another human being.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>so an embryo has just as much right to live inside the mother, who is a fully developed member of society who may bear physical and emotional stress from carrying the baby (in the case of rape/incest) who may not be in a financial position to support the baby, who may not be medically fit to carry the baby etc</p>
<p>unless you also support legislation requiring state funded care for the embryo until development into a fetus, childbirth and a childhood stages until they reach adulthood (and no, foster care isn’t a valid option) then all you are doing is giving the shitty end of the stick to the mother and the shittier end of the stick to the child</p>
<p>it’s all fine and dandy saying “people should be responsible” but people aren’t responsible and mistakes do happen and you are giving people absolutely no way to correct those mistakes and are placing an absolutely ridiculous burden on people by forcing them to live with those mistakes that you yourself will never be required to bear</p>
<aside class="quote">
<blockquote>
<p>All human brains are developing. As we speak your brain is developing and so is mine. A fetuses brain begins developing at 40 days. It may not be able to understand but it’s brain most certainly does work. At week 6 it’s heart is pumping blood and it’s brain is working.[/quote]</p>
<p>that really is deceptive</p>
<p><a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/File:Tubal_Pregnancy_with_embryo.jpg" rel="nofollow noopener">http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/File:Tubal_Pregnancy_with_embryo.jpg</a></p>
<p>that is an embryo at 5-6 weeks in, yes it may have a heartbeat, yes it may have some extremely limited brain functions but it is not a developed brain, and the language used to say “our brains are always developing” can either be interpreted as deceptive or blatantly wrong, yes, our brains may be developing in the sense that we can learn new information but they are not developing in the sense that new brain regions are being formed that are required for things like pain</p>
<p>it is the general scientific consensus that things like pain don’t develop until at LEAST 28 weeks in, and past 28 weeks is where most of the magic really happens, and you can disagree if you want but for the love of god don’t claim that embryos have brains at 6 weeks in</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>i wanna bring this debate back so here goes.</p>
<p>You can bring all this scientific shit back, but it’s still murder.  Why should the baby have to be blamed for what the parents did?  Even if it was rape.  The answer to the debate of abortion is to educate teenagers about safe sex in order to not have to have an abortion.  It should be illegal and I will stand by that.[/quote]<br>
Although i’m not against abortion, i’m not for it. I’m leaning more on against it though. If I were to get a girl pregnant right now, and she wanted an abortion, I wouldn’t let her. I’d try my hardest to change her mind to keep the baby. Think of when it’s born, even if you give it up for adoption, maybe because you can’t afford one, or maybe some other reason, you know you brought life into this world. Whether it’s a good life for them, or a bad one, they still had a life, and eventually one day they might have kids, and a new family would start.</p>
<p>As for the presidential debate, I wouldn’t choose either, but I think Obama’s our best choice. Even though he’s fucked up alot, I wouldn’t let Mitt Romney take over.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/who-will-be-the-next-president-good-or-bad/454137/67">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/who-will-be-the-next-president-good-or-bad/454137/67</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 20 Oct 2012 19:45:15 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-454137-67</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/who-will-be-the-next-president-good-or-bad/454137.rss">Who will be the next president? Good or bad?</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
