<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>RedDwarfServer</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/reddwarfserver/442456</link>
    <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;RedDwarf Server is a horizontally scalable application server for low latency applications such as online games, virtual worlds, and social networking applications.  It is the official community fork for Project Darkstar, previously sponsored by Sun Microsystems, Inc.  RedDwarf is a server side technology written in Java that radically simplifies the development of online games and lowers the barrier to entry into the MMOG market.

Why are you forking Project Darkstar?

Sun&#39;s (now Oracle&#39;s) investment in Project Darkstar was discontinued immediately upon the close of the Oracle-Sun acquisition.  This left Project Darkstar in an awkward, limbo state where contributions, development, and releases were controlled by Oracle, but there were no resources devoted to managing this effort.  Rather than leaving Project Darkstar to whither and splinter off in many directions, we have organized a centralized community fork to continue development where Oracle left off.

What are the goals for RedDwarf?

From a technical standpoint, RedDwarf&#39;s objectives remain similar to that laid out for Project Darkstar.  The &quot;version 1.0&quot; milestone will be a complete multi-node implementation that provides true transparent, horizontal scalability to support large virtual worlds, thousands of simultaneous connections, and intelligent load balancing.

What&#39;s &quot;different&quot; about RedDwarf as opposed to other network game frameworks?

Unlike most network game frameworks, RedDwarf is more than just an infrastructure for communications.  It is a completely multi-threaded, event-driven transactional system that provides automatic data persistence.  Much like other Java application containers, RedDwarf maintains data consistency and integrity for your server side application state while providing a persistent database backend that protects against server crashes and network failures.  However, unlike most application containers (such as J2EE containers), RedDwarf is engineered and tuned to ensure low-latency response time, a must for games.

How do I build a game with RedDwarf?

RedDwarf is a server side technology.  Your server side game state is completely managed and executed in the RedDwarf environment when you develop against the RedDwarf server API and deploy and boot up your game in the RedDwarf server.  The server must be written completely in Java.  On the client side, however, RedDwarf is completely language agnostic.  There are a number of available client APIs that provide the communications endpoint to communicate with a RedDwarf server.  RedDwarf does not provide any other client side tools (such as graphics engines, physics engines, etc), but it is flexible enough to be integrated with just about anything that you want.

What license is RedDwarf available under?

RedDwarf is continuing with an identical licensing scheme as Project Darkstar.  RedDwarf server is distributed under GPLv2 with the server APIs being made specially available under GPLv2 + classpath exception.  The Java client and the C client APIs available as part of the RedDwarf project are distributed under a BSD license.&lt;/blockquote&gt;

http://www.reddwarfserver.org/

Thoughts?</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 17 May 2012 19:11:18 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>General Programming</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/reddwarfserver/442456.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>RedDwarfServer</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@slavemaster veer]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/slavemaster">@slavemaster</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Lothy toyed with SGS/DarkStar for a while… it’s not easy to adjust it for use in an RS server. RedDwarf is just the community fork started after Oracle shut-down the project in early 2010. I’ve done plenty of research into the seemingly interesting parts and posted extensively on them in the past, so you must’ve missed all that to be just now considering it. The only specifically interesting parts are its Berkeley ObjectDB database for persisting all game state, and the transaction layer implemented above this – but it isn’t readily pluggable into the typical game server model you’re thinking of.<br>
There’s another framework which is similar to DarkStar but after 20 minutes of googling I’ve been unable to come up with anything in particular.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/reddwarfserver/442456/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/reddwarfserver/442456/4</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 17 May 2012 19:11:18 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-442456-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/reddwarfserver/442456.rss">RedDwarfServer</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>RedDwarfServer</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Rodgerwilco Rodgerwilco]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/rodgerwilco">@Rodgerwilco</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Lothy incorporated RedDwarftServer with RSC in 2009.</p>
<p>I believe, if I can remember correctly, it was Suns open source projects and then called it quits and atm the project is dead (development wise). Edit : Oh wait, if I read the op my memory is correct <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/smiley.png?v=5" title=":smiley:" class="emoji" alt=":smiley:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/reddwarfserver/442456/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/reddwarfserver/442456/3</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 17 May 2012 15:58:15 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-442456-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/reddwarfserver/442456.rss">RedDwarfServer</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>RedDwarfServer</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@_s11 s1gma]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/_s11">@_s11</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>sounds like someone gutted a game engine and didn’t take the ‘useful’ label off</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/reddwarfserver/442456/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/reddwarfserver/442456/2</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 17 May 2012 15:20:26 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-442456-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/reddwarfserver/442456.rss">RedDwarfServer</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>RedDwarfServer</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@sinisoul sini]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/sinisoul">@sinisoul</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <blockquote>RedDwarf Server is a horizontally scalable application server for low latency applications such as online games, virtual worlds, and social networking applications.  It is the official community fork for Project Darkstar, previously sponsored by Sun Microsystems, Inc.  RedDwarf is a server side technology written in Java that radically simplifies the development of online games and lowers the barrier to entry into the MMOG market.
<p>Why are you forking Project Darkstar?</p>
<p>Sun’s (now Oracle’s) investment in Project Darkstar was discontinued immediately upon the close of the Oracle-Sun acquisition.  This left Project Darkstar in an awkward, limbo state where contributions, development, and releases were controlled by Oracle, but there were no resources devoted to managing this effort.  Rather than leaving Project Darkstar to whither and splinter off in many directions, we have organized a centralized community fork to continue development where Oracle left off.</p>
<p>What are the goals for RedDwarf?</p>
<p>From a technical standpoint, RedDwarf’s objectives remain similar to that laid out for Project Darkstar.  The “version 1.0” milestone will be a complete multi-node implementation that provides true transparent, horizontal scalability to support large virtual worlds, thousands of simultaneous connections, and intelligent load balancing.</p>
<p>What’s “different” about RedDwarf as opposed to other network game frameworks?</p>
<p>Unlike most network game frameworks, RedDwarf is more than just an infrastructure for communications.  It is a completely multi-threaded, event-driven transactional system that provides automatic data persistence.  Much like other Java application containers, RedDwarf maintains data consistency and integrity for your server side application state while providing a persistent database backend that protects against server crashes and network failures.  However, unlike most application containers (such as J2EE containers), RedDwarf is engineered and tuned to ensure low-latency response time, a must for games.</p>
<p>How do I build a game with RedDwarf?</p>
<p>RedDwarf is a server side technology.  Your server side game state is completely managed and executed in the RedDwarf environment when you develop against the RedDwarf server API and deploy and boot up your game in the RedDwarf server.  The server must be written completely in Java.  On the client side, however, RedDwarf is completely language agnostic.  There are a number of available client APIs that provide the communications endpoint to communicate with a RedDwarf server.  RedDwarf does not provide any other client side tools (such as graphics engines, physics engines, etc), but it is flexible enough to be integrated with just about anything that you want.</p>
<p>What license is RedDwarf available under?</p>
<p>RedDwarf is continuing with an identical licensing scheme as Project Darkstar.  RedDwarf server is distributed under GPLv2 with the server APIs being made specially available under GPLv2 + classpath exception.  The Java client and the C client APIs available as part of the RedDwarf project are distributed under a BSD license.</p>
</blockquote>
<p><a href="http://www.reddwarfserver.org/" class="onebox" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">http://www.reddwarfserver.org/</a></p>
<p>Thoughts?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/reddwarfserver/442456/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/reddwarfserver/442456/1</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 17 May 2012 05:42:09 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-442456-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/reddwarfserver/442456.rss">RedDwarfServer</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
