<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Need a Partner For a Game</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/need-a-partner-for-a-game/403196</link>
    <description>Not sure if this is allowed never seen a post here, its not advertising, more like requesting for assistance.
Anyways I play wow and I want to level up a paladin tank really fast, and by doing (RaF) recruit a friend, me and the player im recruiting get benefits. Basically you get 4x exp rate which is insane EXP rate and this bonus works all the way up to level 80 (out of 85). You also can summon each other in-case the new player gets lost. All you have to do is let me know if you want in, Ill send you an invitation asking you to join wow. Your account will then be linked to mine. All you have to do from there is by the game at a local game store and enter the CD code on your account to upgrade it. Or you can purchase the game online on their website. Either way you buy it the first game is only 10 bucks I think and it comes with a month free. Anyways I want to level this guy really fast, and I couldn&#39;t find anyone on WoW to do it because theirs new content and everyone busy. Heres info on it: http://us.battle.net/wow/en/services/recruit-a-friend/  . So yeah if your interested add me on MSN: acrodox@yahoo.com

again if this is not allowed im sorry.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 09 Jul 2011 03:59:44 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>General Discussion</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/need-a-partner-for-a-game/403196.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Need a Partner For a Game</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Acrodox Acrodox]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/acrodox">@Acrodox</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Not sure if this is allowed never seen a post here, its not advertising, more like requesting for assistance.<br>
Anyways I play wow and I want to level up a paladin tank really fast, and by doing (RaF) recruit a friend, me and the player im recruiting get benefits. Basically you get 4x exp rate which is insane EXP rate and this bonus works all the way up to level 80 (out of 85). You also can summon each other in-case the new player gets lost. All you have to do is let me know if you want in, Ill send you an invitation asking you to join wow. Your account will then be linked to mine. All you have to do from there is by the game at a local game store and enter the CD code on your account to upgrade it. Or you can purchase the game online on their website. Either way you buy it the first game is only 10 bucks I think and it comes with a month free. Anyways I want to level this guy really fast, and I couldn’t find anyone on WoW to do it because theirs new content and everyone busy. Heres info on it: <a href="http://us.battle.net/wow/en/services/recruit-a-friend/" rel="nofollow noopener">http://us.battle.net/wow/en/services/recruit-a-friend/</a>  . So yeah if your interested add me on MSN: <a href="mailto:acrodox@yahoo.com">acrodox@yahoo.com</a></p>
<p>again if this is not allowed im sorry.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/need-a-partner-for-a-game/403196/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/need-a-partner-for-a-game/403196/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 09 Jul 2011 03:59:44 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-403196-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/need-a-partner-for-a-game/403196.rss">Need a Partner For a Game</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
