<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Question about how to Deob Bot client</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/question-about-how-to-deob-bot-client/478998</link>
    <description>Ok so I have a client with no source files. It&#39;s a bot client. I need to change the version of the client because it is updated. I am no good at Deob and I dont think there are any programs to deob a rsc bot client. I would really love to deob the client so I can mess with all the src files but like i said I do not know exactly where to start. I do know to get the class files I open the jar file in winrar and can see everything. I then can put all the class files in a folder but when I edit the class file with the client version I do not know how to even begin to compile that 1 file because i have no build.xml or whatever i need to be able to compile. I have tried to do a online compiler but it wants a server also. If someone can help I can compensate somehow.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 22 Jan 2013 04:47:18 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/question-about-how-to-deob-bot-client/478998.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Question about how to Deob Bot client</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Stealmojo Stealmojo]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/stealmojo">@Stealmojo</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Ok so I have a client with no source files. It’s a bot client. I need to change the version of the client because it is updated. I am no good at Deob and I dont think there are any programs to deob a rsc bot client. I would really love to deob the client so I can mess with all the src files but like i said I do not know exactly where to start. I do know to get the class files I open the jar file in winrar and can see everything. I then can put all the class files in a folder but when I edit the class file with the client version I do not know how to even begin to compile that 1 file because i have no build.xml or whatever i need to be able to compile. I have tried to do a online compiler but it wants a server also. If someone can help I can compensate somehow.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/question-about-how-to-deob-bot-client/478998/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/question-about-how-to-deob-bot-client/478998/1</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jan 2013 04:47:18 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-478998-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/question-about-how-to-deob-bot-client/478998.rss">Question about how to Deob Bot client</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
