<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Slackintosh puts Slackware on PPC Macs</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/slackintosh-puts-slackware-on-ppc-macs/126109</link>
    <description>[center]Aptly-named Slackintosh version 12, just released, updates this unofficial version of Slackware Linux that targets PowerPC-based Macintosh computers, such as the iBook. Based on a 2.6.21.5 kernel, the distribution&#39;s brief release statement noted that version 12 includes KDE 3.5.7 and glibc 2.5.

[img]http://www.desktoplinux.com/files/misc/slackintosh_screenshot.jpg[/img]

Slackintosh screenshot
(Click to enlarge; source: Slackintosh project)

Spread the word:
digg this story
Slackintosh has developed a small following since the project&#39;s take off in mid-2005. The port is designed for PowerPC-based Macintosh computers and won&#39;t work on Intel-based Apple hardware. The team, headed by Adiran Ulrich in Switzerland and Marco Bonetti in Italy, maintains a general discussion site here. In an FAQ, Ulrich claims Slackintosh is &quot;Almost&quot; real Slack, stating &quot;I used the sources + SlackBuild files... but I had to make a few changes.&quot;

The full package list for this release is buried in a readme file on the distribution, so you&#39;ll have to download to read it. The ISO for DVD is 3.8G; CD ISO&#39;s (four) are also provided. ISO downloads and packages are available from the project&#39;s download page, here.

Interestingly, the download server is a MacMini &quot;running the latest version of Slackintosh Linux,&quot; according to project&#39;s website.[/center]

http://www.desktoplinux.com/news/NS4685749611.html</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 22 Jul 2007 21:39:53 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Technology</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/slackintosh-puts-slackware-on-ppc-macs/126109.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Slackintosh puts Slackware on PPC Macs</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@mwiebelhaus mwiebelhaus]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/mwiebelhaus">@mwiebelhaus</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[center]Aptly-named Slackintosh version 12, just released, updates this unofficial version of Slackware Linux that targets PowerPC-based Macintosh computers, such as the iBook. Based on a 2.6.21.5 kernel, the distribution’s brief release statement noted that version 12 includes KDE 3.5.7 and glibc 2.5.</p>
<p><img src="http://www.desktoplinux.com/files/misc/slackintosh_screenshot.jpg" alt width="" height=""></p>
<p>Slackintosh screenshot<br>
(Click to enlarge; source: Slackintosh project)</p>
<p>Spread the word:<br>
digg this story<br>
Slackintosh has developed a small following since the project’s take off in mid-2005. The port is designed for PowerPC-based Macintosh computers and won’t work on Intel-based Apple hardware. The team, headed by Adiran Ulrich in Switzerland and Marco Bonetti in Italy, maintains a general discussion site here. In an FAQ, Ulrich claims Slackintosh is “Almost” real Slack, stating “I used the sources + SlackBuild files… but I had to make a few changes.”</p>
<p>The full package list for this release is buried in a readme file on the distribution, so you’ll have to download to read it. The ISO for DVD is 3.8G; CD ISO’s (four) are also provided. ISO downloads and packages are available from the project’s download page, here.</p>
<p>Interestingly, the download server is a MacMini “running the latest version of Slackintosh Linux,” according to project’s website.[/center]</p>
<p><a href="http://www.desktoplinux.com/news/NS4685749611.html" class="onebox" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">http://www.desktoplinux.com/news/NS4685749611.html</a></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/slackintosh-puts-slackware-on-ppc-macs/126109/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/slackintosh-puts-slackware-on-ppc-macs/126109/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 22 Jul 2007 21:39:53 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-126109-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/slackintosh-puts-slackware-on-ppc-macs/126109.rss">Slackintosh puts Slackware on PPC Macs</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
