<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>布里斯班驾照翻译 Submariner Automatic 18K Two Tone Plated with Gray Dial-Blue Ceramic Bezel Replica Watches</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/submariner-automatic-18k-two-tone-plated-with-gray-dial-blue-ceramic-bezel-replica-watches/535288</link>
    <description>Many trolling motors can be raised or lowered vertically as necessary to ensure sufficient operating depth for the propeller.
The base needs to rest evenly so that the motor can be raised onto the deck and locked down for transport without binding.
3 Ways to Mount a Trolling Motor
Schmidt, electric trolling motors allow fishermen to maneuver their boats at slower speeds than trolling speed with an outboard motor and with greater control than with a paddle or oars. They are also an option for propelling boats across lakes where &quot;no wake&quot; rules are in effect or in most lakes where gasoline powered outboard motors are not allowed. Trolling motors are available for both freshwater and saltwater fishing and can be mounted in 1 of 3  places: on the transom (stern), on the engine itself, [url=https://www.facebook.com/aufanyi]Brisbane驾照翻译[/url]
 or on the bow. The trolling motor should be placed as close to the center of the [url=https://www.facebook.com/professionaltranslator]Melbourne驾照翻译[/url]
 stern as possible without interfering with the operation of the main motor, if there is one. Turn the clamps clockwise (to the right) as far as they will go, so that the motor won&#39;t vibrate loose while in operation.
Transom mounted trolling motors should be positioned so that the center of the motor section is at least 9 inches (22.5 cm) under water while the motor is running to keep the propeller from breaking the water&#39;s surface. The anti cavitation [url=https://www.facebook.com/professionaltranslator]墨尔本文件翻译[/url]
 is a horizontal plate above the propeller on either an outboard motor or the outboard unit of an inboard outboard motor that keeps the propeller from breaking the water&#39;s surface as it pushes the boat forward. The mounting bracket is designed so that when the boat is &quot;on plane&quot; (the bow lifts out of the water as the boat skims across its surface), the https://www.facebook.com/aufanyi
 trolling motor does break the water&#39;s surface. Bow mounted electric trolling motors are designed to be used on boats with flat, raised forward decks. You should place the mount base somewhere where it can accommodate the motor both when it is pulling the boat and when it is stowed on [url=https://www.facebook.com/aufanyi]Brisbane驾照翻译[/url]
 deck while the boat&#39;s main motor pushes it through https://www.facebook.com/professionaltranslator
 the water. Use a sharp bit to drill to a depth of 1/4 inch (6.5 mm) and clear out any debris after drilling. You&#39;ll want to hold the washers in position with your fingers as you move the mount https://www.facebook.com/aufanyi
 base over the holes you drilled in the deck. If it doesn&#39;t, you&#39;ll need to add more rubber washers under those bolts where the base wobbles to level it.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 06 Nov 2013 04:43:44 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Uncategorized</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/submariner-automatic-18k-two-tone-plated-with-gray-dial-blue-ceramic-bezel-replica-watches/535288.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>布里斯班驾照翻译 Submariner Automatic 18K Two Tone Plated with Gray Dial-Blue Ceramic Bezel Replica Watches</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@tqzhwatchtf tqzhwatchtf]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/tqzhwatchtf">@tqzhwatchtf</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Many trolling motors can be raised or lowered vertically as necessary to ensure sufficient operating depth for the propeller.<br>
The base needs to rest evenly so that the motor can be raised onto the deck and locked down for transport without binding.<br>
3 Ways to Mount a Trolling Motor<br>
Schmidt, electric trolling motors allow fishermen to maneuver their boats at slower speeds than trolling speed with an outboard motor and with greater control than with a paddle or oars. They are also an option for propelling boats across lakes where “no wake” rules are in effect or in most lakes where gasoline powered outboard motors are not allowed. Trolling motors are available for both freshwater and saltwater fishing and can be mounted in 1 of 3  places: on the transom (stern), on the engine itself, <a href="https://www.facebook.com/aufanyi" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">Brisbane驾照翻译</a><br>
or on the bow. The trolling motor should be placed as close to the center of the <a href="https://www.facebook.com/professionaltranslator" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">Melbourne驾照翻译</a><br>
stern as possible without interfering with the operation of the main motor, if there is one. Turn the clamps clockwise (to the right) as far as they will go, so that the motor won’t vibrate loose while in operation.<br>
Transom mounted trolling motors should be positioned so that the center of the motor section is at least 9 inches (22.5 cm) under water while the motor is running to keep the propeller from breaking the water’s surface. The anti cavitation <a href="https://www.facebook.com/professionaltranslator" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">墨尔本文件翻译</a><br>
is a horizontal plate above the propeller on either an outboard motor or the outboard unit of an inboard outboard motor that keeps the propeller from breaking the water’s surface as it pushes the boat forward. The mounting bracket is designed so that when the boat is “on plane” (the bow lifts out of the water as the boat skims across its surface), the <a href="https://www.facebook.com/aufanyi" rel="nofollow noopener">https://www.facebook.com/aufanyi</a><br>
trolling motor does break the water’s surface. Bow mounted electric trolling motors are designed to be used on boats with flat, raised forward decks. You should place the mount base somewhere where it can accommodate the motor both when it is pulling the boat and when it is stowed on <a href="https://www.facebook.com/aufanyi" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">Brisbane驾照翻译</a><br>
deck while the boat’s main motor pushes it through <a href="https://www.facebook.com/professionaltranslator" rel="nofollow noopener">https://www.facebook.com/professionaltranslator</a><br>
the water. Use a sharp bit to drill to a depth of 1/4 inch (6.5 mm) and clear out any debris after drilling. You’ll want to hold the washers in position with your fingers as you move the mount <a href="https://www.facebook.com/aufanyi" rel="nofollow noopener">https://www.facebook.com/aufanyi</a><br>
base over the holes you drilled in the deck. If it doesn’t, you’ll need to add more rubber washers under those bolts where the base wobbles to level it.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/submariner-automatic-18k-two-tone-plated-with-gray-dial-blue-ceramic-bezel-replica-watches/535288/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/submariner-automatic-18k-two-tone-plated-with-gray-dial-blue-ceramic-bezel-replica-watches/535288/1</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 06 Nov 2013 04:43:44 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-535288-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/submariner-automatic-18k-two-tone-plated-with-gray-dial-blue-ceramic-bezel-replica-watches/535288.rss">布里斯班驾照翻译 Submariner Automatic 18K Two Tone Plated with Gray Dial-Blue Ceramic Bezel Replica Watches</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
