<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>I need help with my server!</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/i-need-help-with-my-server/107398</link>
    <description>well, i don&#39;t know what my problem is, but i&#39;ve gotten my server to the point by updating it where there&#39;s nothing more to do before i bring it online. so i got my no-ip [alanscape.no-ip.info] and i [owner] log in as localhost, but my friends when i check the box and click run server aren&#39;t able to log in, and i can&#39;t manage my server into the server list, because it tells me it&#39;s not online, but i can still log in.. port fowarding doesn&#39;t work because when i got to my default gateway it tells me that i need a password &amp; user, so i looked up my default on portfoward.com and my default didn&#39;t work.. so i&#39;m having trouble bringing my server online. can anyone help me? it&#39;ll be GREATLY appriciated.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 08 Jun 2007 01:19:20 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/i-need-help-with-my-server/107398.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>I need help with my server!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Alan Alan]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/alan">@Alan</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>well, i don’t know what my problem is, but i’ve gotten my server to the point by updating it where there’s nothing more to do before i bring it online. so i got my no-ip [alanscape.no-ip.info] and i [owner] log in as localhost, but my friends when i check the box and click run server aren’t able to log in, and i can’t manage my server into the server list, because it tells me it’s not online, but i can still log in… port fowarding doesn’t work because when i got to my default gateway it tells me that i need a password &amp; user, so i looked up my default on <a href="http://portfoward.com" rel="nofollow noopener">portfoward.com</a> and my default didn’t work… so i’m having trouble bringing my server online. can anyone help me? it’ll be GREATLY appriciated.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/i-need-help-with-my-server/107398/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/i-need-help-with-my-server/107398/1</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Jun 2007 01:19:20 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-107398-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/i-need-help-with-my-server/107398.rss">I need help with my server!</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
