<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Hamachi...just look plz</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/hamachi-just-look-plz/334119</link>
    <description>can someone explain to me exactly some tips about hamachi like what it does and why people use it or have to use it... i don&#39;t use hamachi but i want further experiance on it...

thanks to all that help..</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 25 Mar 2010 18:04:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/hamachi-just-look-plz/334119.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Hamachi...just look plz</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@mangalover51 mangalover51]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/mangalover51">@mangalover51</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>lol replied already? (lets make this post big? lol maybe more people will ready it?) haha so… we can get more people to learn alittle hamachi here… i still kinda don’t get it you got it online tho and copied and pasted but still i didn’t have to find it thx agin lol</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/hamachi-just-look-plz/334119/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/hamachi-just-look-plz/334119/5</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 25 Mar 2010 18:04:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-334119-5</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/hamachi-just-look-plz/334119.rss">Hamachi...just look plz</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Hamachi...just look plz</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@ILOVEJAVA ILOVEJAVA]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/ilovejava">@ILOVEJAVA</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>any time bro, any time.  ;D</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/hamachi-just-look-plz/334119/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/hamachi-just-look-plz/334119/4</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 25 Mar 2010 18:02:58 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-334119-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/hamachi-just-look-plz/334119.rss">Hamachi...just look plz</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Hamachi...just look plz</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@mangalover51 mangalover51]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/mangalover51">@mangalover51</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>holy sht thx… i didn’t read yet but you typed alot thx… yo ucan have your firewalls on and still run a server if you have hamachi?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/hamachi-just-look-plz/334119/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/hamachi-just-look-plz/334119/3</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 25 Mar 2010 18:02:31 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-334119-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/hamachi-just-look-plz/334119.rss">Hamachi...just look plz</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Hamachi...just look plz</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@ILOVEJAVA ILOVEJAVA]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/ilovejava">@ILOVEJAVA</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Hamachi is a zero-configuration virtual private network (VPN) shareware application capable of establishing direct links between computers that are behind NAT firewalls without requiring reconfiguration (in most cases); in other words, it establishes a connection over the Internet that very closely emulates the connection that would exist if the computers were connected over a local area network. Currently available as a production version for Microsoft Windows.<br>
Each client establishes and maintains a control connection to the server cluster. When the connection is established, the client goes through a login sequence, followed by the discovery process and state synchronization. The login step authenticates the client to the server and vice versa. The discovery is used to determine the topology of client’s Internet connection, specifically to detect the presence of NAT and firewall devices on its route to the Internet. The synchronization step brings a client’s view of its private networks in sync with other members of these networks.</p>
<p>When a member of a network goes online or offline, the server instructs other network peers to either establish or tear down tunnels to the former. When establishing tunnels between the peers, Hamachi uses a server-assisted NAT traversal technique, similar to UDP hole punching. Detailed information on how it works has not been made public. The vendor claims “…to successfully mediate P2P connections in roughly 95% of all cases …” This process does not work on certain combinations of NAT devices, requiring the user to explicitly set up a port forward. Additionally 1.0 series of client software are capable of relaying traffic through vendor-maintained ‘relay servers’.</p>
<p>In the event of unexpectedly losing a connection to the server, the client retains all its tunnels and starts actively checking their status. When the server unexpectedly loses client’s connection, it informs client’s peers about the fact and expects them to also start liveliness checks. This enables Hamachi tunnels to withstand transient network problems on the route between the client and the server as well as short periods of complete server unavailability.</p>
<p>Each Hamachi client is assigned an IP address from the 5.0.0.0/8 address block. This address is assigned when the client logs into the system for the first time, and is henceforth associated with the client’s public crypto key. As long as the client retains its key, it can log into the system and use this 5.x.x.x IP address.</p>
<p>The 5.0.0.0/8 network is used to avoid collisions with private IP networks that might already be in use on the client side. Specifically - 10.0.0.0/8, 172.16.0.0/12 and 192.168.0.0/16. The 5.0.0.0/8 address block is reserved by IANA and is not currently in use in the Internet routing domain, but this is not guaranteed to continue. For example in January 2010 the address range 1.0.0.0/8 “used” by AnoNet became allocated. The IANA free pool is expected to be exhausted by February 2011.[1] If this range is allocated, Hamachi users will not be able to connect to any Internet IP addresses within the range as long as the Hamachi client is running.</p>
<p>Additionally, using a separate network prefix creates a single broadcast domain between all clients. This makes it possible to use LAN protocols that rely on IP broadcasts for discovery and announcement services over Hamachi networks. Hamachi is frequently used for gaming and remote administration. The vendor provides free basic service and extra features for a fee.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/hamachi-just-look-plz/334119/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/hamachi-just-look-plz/334119/2</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 25 Mar 2010 18:01:10 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-334119-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/hamachi-just-look-plz/334119.rss">Hamachi...just look plz</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Hamachi...just look plz</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@mangalover51 mangalover51]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/mangalover51">@mangalover51</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>can someone explain to me exactly some tips about hamachi like what it does and why people use it or have to use it… i don’t use hamachi but i want further experiance on it…</p>
<p>thanks to all that help…</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/hamachi-just-look-plz/334119/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/hamachi-just-look-plz/334119/1</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 25 Mar 2010 17:47:16 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-334119-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/hamachi-just-look-plz/334119.rss">Hamachi...just look plz</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
