<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Self-motivation?</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/self-motivation/260214</link>
    <description>Are there are good ways that I can use to help force myself to put in more effort at college? I&#39;m really starting to slack a bit, mainly because I&#39;m really lazy, and need some ideas on how to build up some motivation and start actually working. I&#39;m also finding it reallly hard to concentrate in classes, so any other good ways to stay focused in a lesson will be a big help.
 
thanks to any ideas or input.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2009 15:45:29 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>General Discussion</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/self-motivation/260214.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Self-motivation?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Fishstix Fishstix]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/fishstix">@Fishstix</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>The most simplest and best one there is out there is to make something of your self and make some money.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/self-motivation/260214/19">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/self-motivation/260214/19</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2009 15:45:29 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-260214-19</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/self-motivation/260214.rss">Self-motivation?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Self-motivation?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@sup000 sup000]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/sup000">@sup000</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>stop toking</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/self-motivation/260214/18">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/self-motivation/260214/18</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2009 09:01:21 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-260214-18</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/self-motivation/260214.rss">Self-motivation?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Self-motivation?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Javacisnotrecognized _^_]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/javacisnotrecognized">@Javacisnotrecognized</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <blockquote>Why was the blonde looking so intently at the orange juice carton? Because it said “concentrate” Grin
<p>Concentration problems stem from not understanding what concentration actually is.</p>
<p>First you must accept that concentrating by sheer force of will is impossible. The fact is, the human mind likes to wander, and although you may start with the best of intentions of concentrating on your piece, very soon you will be thinking about what happened on the TV soap yesterday. So, rather than fight this tendency of the human mind – a fight you will eventually loose – use it for your own ends. Let your mind wander, but keep its wanderings within the work you are doing at the moment</p>
<p>I will give you a simple example. Look at you right hand. Try to keep your thoughts concentrated in your hand. You will probably find that after a few seconds, your mind starts to think of something else, quite unrelated. You may even completely forget that you were supposed to be concentrating on your hand.</p>
<p>Now try again looking at your hand and focussing your thoughts on it. But this time, let your mind wander around your hand: think of its shape. Examine the size of your nails (do they need cutting? Pianist have short nails!). Consider how your thumb opposes the other fingers, and how this allows you to grasp objects. See that the fingers have different sizes and different strengths. Look at the shape of your hand and fingers. Is it squarish? Or roundish? Or pointed?</p>
<p>By letting your mind wander around your hand like that you will be able to keep your thoughts focussed in your hand for quite long periods of time. And your mind is nowhere as interesting as your piano scales! Or as your new piece!</p>
<p>So, do not wait for your mind to wander on its own. From the very beginning encourage your mind to wander, but control its meanderings by keeping it around your subject. And of course you can apply this little trick to anything, including that boring lesson at school!</p>
<p>If you keep using this strategy consistently, very soon you will discover that it becomes a subconscious habit: you will be concentrating without effort and without thinking about it, and everyone will be amazed at your powers of focus and concentration.</p>
<p>Then you can try two meditation techniques. One is to observe your breath (sit on a chair with a straight back, closed eyes, and put your awareness on the several breathing sensations, how it warms up as it gets in, how the air cools down as it goes out, where can you feel the air – nose, trachea – lungs, etc. this is really a variation of the “let your mind wander but control its meanderings). This should improve your concentration. Then you can try a more advanced one: Think of nothing. In fact, you will not be able to do it (no one can do it). Thoughts will arise. Your job is to observe the thoughts without following them. Think of thoughts as clouds in the sky. You want to keep your sights on the blue sky. If a cloud passes by, notice it, but do not let your sight follow it. These are long term disciplines that will work wonders not only for concentration as for performance nerves and stress. Smiley</p>
<p>Best wishes,<br>
Bernhard.</p>
</blockquote>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/self-motivation/260214/17">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/self-motivation/260214/17</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2009 03:25:47 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-260214-17</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/self-motivation/260214.rss">Self-motivation?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Self-motivation?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@goatee goatee]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/goatee">@goatee</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>The visualization technique really helps for starting something, like exercise, a repetitive chore or just getting off your arse. But I don’t think it helps when it comes to revision, sure it gets you to a computer/book to begin the revision but it doesn’t help you concentrate or prevent you from getting distracted.</p>
<p>So after reading that information I think it helps the motional section of the brain and not the intellectual section. Keep looking?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/self-motivation/260214/16">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/self-motivation/260214/16</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2009 21:44:56 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-260214-16</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/self-motivation/260214.rss">Self-motivation?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Self-motivation?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Original_Daniel Original Daniel]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/original_daniel">@Original_Daniel</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>be more selfish about your career. after all, nobody else gives a shit whether you succeed or fail.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/self-motivation/260214/15">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/self-motivation/260214/15</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2009 00:04:34 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-260214-15</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/self-motivation/260214.rss">Self-motivation?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Self-motivation?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Mr.Chris Mr.Chris]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/mr.chris">@Mr.Chris</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“Fat Cookies, post:11, topic:260214”][quote author=Davidude link=topic=343539.msg2653819#msg2653819 date=1233705636]<br>
I feel the same way Mr.Chris, it’s just so hard to settle down and do revision. I haven’t found a way yet. =[<br>
[/quote]<br>
Whenever I try to revise using a computer i suddenly remember all these random things i have always wanted to to and kinda forget what im was supposed to do in the first place!</p>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p>I can’t actually believe that that visualisation technique actually works</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>What exactly did you imagine[/quote]<br>
lol yeh. i sit down to do some work and end up looking at 100 vids on youtube.</p>
<p>Will try that visualization thing when getting up to go to college. thats the worst part - not a morning person.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/self-motivation/260214/14">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/self-motivation/260214/14</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2009 21:17:31 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-260214-14</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/self-motivation/260214.rss">Self-motivation?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Self-motivation?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Javacisnotrecognized _^_]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/javacisnotrecognized">@Javacisnotrecognized</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“Fat Cookies, post:11, topic:260214”][quote author=Davidude link=topic=343539.msg2653819#msg2653819 date=1233705636]<br>
I feel the same way Mr.Chris, it’s just so hard to settle down and do revision. I haven’t found a way yet. =[<br>
[/quote]<br>
Whenever I try to revise using a computer i suddenly remember all these random things i have always wanted to to and kinda forget what im was supposed to do in the first place![/quote]</p>
<p>Ok, try this: When you remember all these things, RIGHT THEN create a new document for them, write them all down in one go, save it, close it, and then let them just completely float out of your head. Then all you have to do is revise that document into a list of things you CAN do. When you go to revise it, if you remember anything else, you can just write it down.</p>
<p>Right now I am writing a webpage (Real simple) that will serve as my to do list from now on. I’m going to set it as my homepage when I finish. You’ll be able to add, update, and delete tasks. I’ll send you a copy.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/self-motivation/260214/13">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/self-motivation/260214/13</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2009 19:33:19 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-260214-13</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/self-motivation/260214.rss">Self-motivation?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Self-motivation?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@R.I.P_RSC R.I.P RSC]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/r.i.p_rsc">@R.I.P_RSC</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote no-group" data-post="11" data-topic="260214">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 Fat Cookies:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>What exactly did you imagine</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>You should imagine to read the rest of his post, maybe you’ll find out!</p>
<p>I’m in an odd vicious circle. So let’s start the bragging shall we? I enjoy the classes I follow, which result in good grades. I hardly ever learn more then 2-3 hours per test. I sometimes get grades of about 9+/10. It sounds great, but then you realize something. If 2 hours of learning gets you a 9.5, what would 1 hour get you?</p>
<p>So good grades aren’t motivating either.</p>
<p>But to answer your question: first try that visualization thing. It surely helps in many occasions. And something else, which may sound like a cliché: don’t think about the profit you get from your education now, but about the profit you get in the future. I know it can be boring, and hanging around with mates all they long can be fun. But that won’t get you anywhere.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/self-motivation/260214/12">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/self-motivation/260214/12</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2009 17:58:09 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-260214-12</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/self-motivation/260214.rss">Self-motivation?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Self-motivation?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Fat_Cookies Fat Cookies]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/fat_cookies">@Fat_Cookies</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote no-group quote-modified" data-post="6" data-topic="260214">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 Davidude:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>I feel the same way Mr.Chris, it’s just so hard to settle down and do revision. I haven’t found a way yet. =[</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Whenever I try to revise using a computer i suddenly remember all these random things i have always wanted to to and kinda forget what im was supposed to do in the first place!</p>
<aside class="quote no-group quote-modified" data-post="10" data-topic="260214">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/goatee/40/5_6bca9977b612b7aeef77ba1ec1cd67b3.png" class="avatar"> goatee:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>I can’t actually believe that that visualisation technique actually works</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>What exactly did you imagine</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/self-motivation/260214/11">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/self-motivation/260214/11</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2009 16:53:24 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-260214-11</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/self-motivation/260214.rss">Self-motivation?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Self-motivation?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@goatee goatee]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/goatee">@goatee</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I can’t actually believe that that visualisation technique actually works… but it does. I couldn’t be arsed to walk my dog… then i imagined doing it and now i actually want to go and do it. So I’m off niggers!</p>
<p>TY for this because I’m sure alot of people have trouble with laziness.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/self-motivation/260214/10">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/self-motivation/260214/10</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2009 15:36:21 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-260214-10</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/self-motivation/260214.rss">Self-motivation?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Self-motivation?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Ske Ske]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/ske">@Ske</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>There! Another auto-suggesting method.</p>
<p>“down to earth” my ass!!</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/self-motivation/260214/9">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/self-motivation/260214/9</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2009 14:41:23 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-260214-9</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/self-motivation/260214.rss">Self-motivation?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Self-motivation?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Javacisnotrecognized _^_]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/javacisnotrecognized">@Javacisnotrecognized</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <blockquote>Consider that the human body/mind has these three functions (there are more, but these three are the ones that interest us for the moment being): emotional, intellectual and motional.
<p>The emotional function works on the basis of: I like it I hate it. There is no argument or explanation, just a feeling of attraction or of repulsion. It is very quick to react to various stimuli. Emotional responses (like/dislike) are almost immediate.</p>
<p>The intellectual function works on the basis of comparisons. It takes a long time for all that comparing to take place. It also has nothing to do with likes or dislikes. If you are in intellectual mode you may do something you dislike deeply (e.g. washing the dishes) because you have reasoned yourself into it. But you will be resentful and unhappy about it. And eventually you will stop doing it.</p>
<p>The motional function has to do with your movements and with the five (+) senses: your sensual perception. The motional function is amazingly fast: much faster than the emotional, which is itself much faster than the intellectual. Piano playing at the physical level is done purely with the motional function. If – as you play – you start “thinking” – that is using your intellectual function – about what you are doing it will all fall apart. Also, the only way to learn motional tasks is by imitation. You cannot use an intellectual approach (making comparisons and analysis). Try to learn how to dance by telling yourself to step this way, turn to the left, turn to the right and so on and so forth. It will not work. Instead find the best dancer in the hall and imitate what s/he is doing. You have to be in a certain state of mindlessness to do that: all your attention must be directed outwards. If you are not used to it, you will find it really hard to concentrate on pure imitation. Chances are you will slip into intellectual mode and flop it.</p>
<p>The emotional function does not learn. It just likes or dislikes. It is pretty much useless in genera land is always causing trouble. However it does have a very important function to fulfil: It is the emotional that will make you do anything. You can sit down and reason to yourself all night why you should practise everyday (intellectual function).  You can even sit down at the piano and go through the movements of practice (motional function). But unless you come to like practice , that is unless you succeed in engaging your emotional function in a positive way, you will not practice. It is as simple as that.</p>
<p>So all this long preamble to explain this obvious fact: quick progress is a result of deeply enjoying what you are doing. In other words, if you succeed in engaging the emotional function, the student will go through heel and fire to follow your instructions. And all the pedagogy in the whole world will not change this simple, but mostly ignored fact. Your teaching system can be very logical (intellectually well reasoned), it can be incredibly efficient and correct technically (motionally appropriate), but if the student dislike it intensely that is it.</p>
<p>Now to make the above relevant to your question:</p>
<p>It is only by engaging the emotional function (like/dislike) that you will be able to go through with nay activity/plan. In short, laziness is always the result of emotional detachment/indifference. No amount of intellectual reasoning will see you through a piece unless you can engage your emotion sot your intellectual decision.</p>
<p>So all you need to do is to engage your emotional function to your good intentions to change (which are basically intellectual, and therefore completely ineffective). Think of your intelectual decisions as a train wagon. However good to transport passengers and goods, it will only move if you can link it to the locomotive of your emotions.</p>
<p>Now that you understand the problem, sit down for the solution, for it will make you weak at the knees.</p>
<p>The only way to engage the emotional function to your intellectual decisions is by visualising it.</p>
<p>Yes, that is right. You must see in your mind the process by which you must achieve your goals. Once you see it, it will create an irresistible compulsion to do it.</p>
<p>It is that simple. Just try it. Do you have a pile of dirty dishes in the kitchen sink, and you are just too lazy to get out of the armchair to wash it? Just sit there, and start seeing yourself  in your mind going through the process of washing the dishes. I assure you that you will not be able to sit idly for too long. Soon you will feel this violent compulsion to tackle the dishes.</p>
<p>But you must guard yourself against two mistakes most uninitiated make:</p>
<ol>
<li>
<pre><code> They visualise the goal, not the process. It is no good to sit in front of the TV and visualise the dishes sparkling clean in the cupboard. This is the goal. What you must visualise is the complete process that leads to that goal: getting up form the armchair, going to the kitchen, turning the water, soaping the dishes, drying the dishes, storing the dishes. The more detailed you can make this visualisation; the strongest will be the compulsion to fulfil it. Likewise, it is no good to visualise yourself playing Rach3 and bowing to the applause of the audience. This is the goal, not the process. Instead visualise the process of practising it in as much detail as possible and you will be unable to resist the compulsion to go and practise.
</code></pre>
</li>
<li>
<pre><code> It is important to distinguish between two kinds of visualisation: associated and dissociated.
</code></pre>
</li>
</ol>
<p>i.      Dissociated visualisation is when you see yourself from the outside, so to speak. One way to create this kind of visualisation is to imagine yourself sitting at a cinema, and then see yourself as the main actor in a movie. This way you are seeing yourself form the outside. This is the kind of visualisation you want to avoid when dealing with laziness, because it disengages the emotional function. However this is very useful in certain circumstances when the emotional function would be a hindrance (this is the sort of think surgeons do when operating so that they can maintain their cool).</p>
<p>ii.      In associated visualisations you actually go “inside yourself” so you see through your eyes, so to speak. This is the visualisation that engages the emotional function. That is the one you want to apply to your laziness.</p>
<ol start="3">
<li>One last word. We all do these visualisations all the time, but they are done haphazardly, chaotically and mostly at the unconscious level. Most of the time we start practising and unconsciously start visualising watching TV or playing some video game. The compulsion to do so results and practise becomes boring, so we have to watch TV.  This is also a very typical pattern with people who are trying to stop smoking, for instance. They say I will stop smoking now, And then they unconsciously visualise having a very last cigarette. Next thing they know they have gone through a whole pack. The only way to counter such unconscious visualisations is to consciously visualise the process that will lead you to your goal. In the case of the cigarette addict , he must visualise himself actually refusing a cigarette, or even better, visualising himself doing something else. This explains why we have such constant shifts of mood and energy. What I am suggesting here is that you start to do it in a methodical and pre-planned way. (Oh crap, I forgot you are lazy, you are never going to do it!)</li>
</ol>
<p>So, since you never seem to finish a piece, set yourself a goal that demands a finished piece. The best one is of course a performance of some sort. Then visualise regularly the process (or steps of the process) that will lead you to that goal.</p>
<p>And the other suggestions in the thread are also good, but you will only be able to implement them after you have dealt with the laziness issue.</p>
<p>Best wishes,<br>
Bernhard.</p>
</blockquote>
<p>The quoted post talks about something different than your example here, but if you are not a complete fucking moron you should be able to replace “practicing” with “college” and get the idea.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/self-motivation/260214/8">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/self-motivation/260214/8</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2009 13:13:43 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-260214-8</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/self-motivation/260214.rss">Self-motivation?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Self-motivation?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Ske Ske]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/ske">@Ske</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“Mr.Chris, post:3, topic:260214”]BUY THIS NEW BOOK FROM DR FIXALOT! 100% PROVEN TO BE THE BEST SELF MOTIVATOR!</p>
<p>im looking for down to earth, first hand methods.[/quote]<br>
I didnt say you need to buy books.<br>
Probably the best thing you’re going to find anyway.</p>
<p>Do some research about the basics.<br>
Auto-suggestion, self-suggestion…</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/self-motivation/260214/7">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/self-motivation/260214/7</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2009 11:44:06 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-260214-7</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/self-motivation/260214.rss">Self-motivation?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Self-motivation?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@davidude36 Brolapse]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/davidude36">@davidude36</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I feel the same way Mr.Chris, it’s just so hard to settle down and do revision. I haven’t found a way yet. =[</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/self-motivation/260214/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/self-motivation/260214/6</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2009 00:00:36 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-260214-6</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/self-motivation/260214.rss">Self-motivation?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Self-motivation?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Unhandled Unhandled]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/unhandled">@Unhandled</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Leaving this website forever would probably do wonders for your motivation, health, and mental well being. Unfortunately, that would require a lot of motivation, so you are somewhat stuck in an infinite paradox.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/self-motivation/260214/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/self-motivation/260214/5</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2009 22:12:54 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-260214-5</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/self-motivation/260214.rss">Self-motivation?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Self-motivation?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@chrisn2323 chrisn2323]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/chrisn2323">@chrisn2323</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>start cutting yourself.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/self-motivation/260214/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/self-motivation/260214/4</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2009 21:57:01 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-260214-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/self-motivation/260214.rss">Self-motivation?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Self-motivation?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Mr.Chris Mr.Chris]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/mr.chris">@Mr.Chris</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>BUY THIS NEW BOOK FROM DR FIXALOT! 100% PROVEN TO BE THE BEST SELF MOTIVATOR!</p>
<p>im looking for down to earth, first hand methods.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/self-motivation/260214/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/self-motivation/260214/3</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2009 21:54:32 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-260214-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/self-motivation/260214.rss">Self-motivation?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Self-motivation?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Ske Ske]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/ske">@Ske</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Auto-suggestion stuff!</p>
<p>Don’t be lazy and search on google.</p>
<p>[size=2pt]I will search on google. I  will search on google.  I  will search on google. I  will search on google. I  will search on google.[/size]</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/self-motivation/260214/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/self-motivation/260214/2</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2009 19:50:27 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-260214-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/self-motivation/260214.rss">Self-motivation?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Self-motivation?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Mr.Chris Mr.Chris]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/mr.chris">@Mr.Chris</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Are there are good ways that I can use to help force myself to put in more effort at college? I’m really starting to slack a bit, mainly because I’m really lazy, and need some ideas on how to build up some motivation and start actually working. I’m also finding it reallly hard to concentrate in classes, so any other good ways to stay focused in a lesson will be a big help.</p>
<p>thanks to any ideas or input.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/self-motivation/260214/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/self-motivation/260214/1</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2009 19:03:43 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-260214-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/self-motivation/260214.rss">Self-motivation?</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
