<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Someone pleaseeeeee help meeeee!</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/someone-pleaseeeeee-help-meeeee/381232</link>
    <description>Ok, so I got my server running and crap, but there are some things I don&#39;t know at all. I have looked and looked and hopefully someone here can help me. I will list out the issues and questions.

1.)During research: I came on here and went to download files and stuff. I clicked on the moparscape 4.1 forum link and it in then turned me to the play moparscape link. Before that, there was a &quot;start programming&quot; link that I clicked on. It then opened a download window which i downloaded to my &quot;downloads&quot; folder on my computer. The folder contained 2 server .jar files and 2 client .jar files, as well as the moparscape.jar file. There were 2 text files and another folder called META_INF. Then, I started up my server through no-ip and port forwarded and all that jazz. I started playing and testing characters, but all of them were &quot;owners&quot;. So I didn&#39;t know how to change character rights. I then found another folder under my users called &quot;.moparscape&quot;, which included a &quot;servers&quot; folder that had a characters folder in it, of which I could change the rights of new characters. After playing for a bit, logging in and out and stuff, it started saying like &quot;account allready logged in&quot; and crap. I fixed it but don&#39;t remember. question:

Question: When moparscape opens, do I need to click on new server under the file menu, then hit start server? Do I just log in? How do I prevent that error of &quot;account allready logged in&quot;.


2.) What files do I edit in order to effect my in game features? Do I need to add .java files into the folder with the characters options? Or do I put it in the folder I downloaded when I went to that website above? What files do I edit and where do I access them from?

3.) The number 2 problem is really important, I need to know how to change the game. Like changing the spawn point, adding teleports, mini games, just in-game features. PLEASE ANSWER THAT ONE.

4.) Do I need a compile file and a run file? if so where do I put it? WHERE WHERE WHERE. that is my main issue, where to find things, and if I need to add them?



-Bob Matt</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 05 Feb 2011 00:30:37 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/someone-pleaseeeeee-help-meeeee/381232.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Someone pleaseeeeee help meeeee!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Woopzpkedu Woopzpkedu]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/woopzpkedu">@Woopzpkedu</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>lol…but anyways 1. i dont get wat u asking 2.yes u need to add java files for minigames and shit then  make it all work 3.search the coords then change em at client.java or w/e it is for me its in config so idk 4. WTF?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/someone-pleaseeeeee-help-meeeee/381232/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/someone-pleaseeeeee-help-meeeee/381232/2</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 05 Feb 2011 00:30:37 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-381232-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/someone-pleaseeeeee-help-meeeee/381232.rss">Someone pleaseeeeee help meeeee!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Someone pleaseeeeee help meeeee!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@mawang mawang]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/mawang">@mawang</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Ok, so I got my server running and crap, but there are some things I don’t know at all. I have looked and looked and hopefully someone here can help me. I will list out the issues and questions.</p>
<p>1.)During research: I came on here and went to download files and stuff. I clicked on the moparscape 4.1 forum link and it in then turned me to the play moparscape link. Before that, there was a “start programming” link that I clicked on. It then opened a download window which i downloaded to my “downloads” folder on my computer. The folder contained 2 server .jar files and 2 client .jar files, as well as the moparscape.jar file. There were 2 text files and another folder called META_INF. Then, I started up my server through no-ip and port forwarded and all that jazz. I started playing and testing characters, but all of them were “owners”. So I didn’t know how to change character rights. I then found another folder under my users called “.moparscape”, which included a “servers” folder that had a characters folder in it, of which I could change the rights of new characters. After playing for a bit, logging in and out and stuff, it started saying like “account allready logged in” and crap. I fixed it but don’t remember. question:</p>
<p>Question: When moparscape opens, do I need to click on new server under the file menu, then hit start server? Do I just log in? How do I prevent that error of “account allready logged in”.</p>
<p>2.) What files do I edit in order to effect my in game features? Do I need to add .java files into the folder with the characters options? Or do I put it in the folder I downloaded when I went to that website above? What files do I edit and where do I access them from?</p>
<p>3.) The number 2 problem is really important, I need to know how to change the game. Like changing the spawn point, adding teleports, mini games, just in-game features. PLEASE ANSWER THAT ONE.</p>
<p>4.) Do I need a compile file and a run file? if so where do I put it? WHERE WHERE WHERE. that is my main issue, where to find things, and if I need to add them?</p>
<p>-Bob Matt</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/someone-pleaseeeeee-help-meeeee/381232/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/someone-pleaseeeeee-help-meeeee/381232/1</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 04 Feb 2011 23:56:53 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-381232-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/someone-pleaseeeeee-help-meeeee/381232.rss">Someone pleaseeeeee help meeeee!</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
