<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Excellscape 667</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/excellscape-667/439250</link>
    <description>[img]http://filebeam.com/0c1ad1454450c828ddb8f100ee2fa852.jpg[/img]
SERVER STATUS:ALPHA
Development-Server completely unplayable, all skills are not fully trainable, no content.
Alpha-Server is available for live testing, basic frame is being worked on, some ideas from plan are being implemented, still pretty buggy.
Beta-Server is available for live testing, and the basic frame of the idea is implemented. Starting to implement main features from plan, some content from plan already available.
Open-All things described in the plan below are implemented and the server is 100% ready for players

===================================================
WELCOME TO THE OFFICIAL EXCELL SCAPE 667 DEVELOPMENT THREAD
===================================================

[b]-Are you using matrix you n00bz0r?[/b]
Comic Sans MS&quot;]Im going to be honest and say yes, BUT before raging about how this is another stupid leech of matrix&#39;s work, read through what our plans are for the server.

===================================================
SERVER PLAN:
===================================================

[b]-General Features:[/b]

[ul][*]Unique Training Caves Containing Many Sought-After Monsters
[*]Epic Donator Zone And Dungeons (Further Explained Below)
[*]Unique summoning system (Further Explained Below)
[*]Working Dungeoneering With Multiple Complexity Levels
[*]Lots of minigames for players to engage in PvP and/or PvM combat
[*]Fun PvP with perfected switching
[*]Unique shops to ease obtaining the most essential items
[*]An engaging set-up geared towards a skill based game-play like real RS
[*]Nearly open world, nearly all locations accessible and spawned like real RS
[*]Tokens dropped by bosses to be exchanged for prized gear and skilling tools.
[*]Most mini-games working (Clanwars, Castlewars, Dominion Tower, Pest Controll, Fight Pits and more...)
[*]All skills working (with the possible exception of construction...)[/ul]

[b]-PvP In Further Detail:[/b]
Even though the server will be geared towards skill based gameplay (items, rewards, money and etc... obtained via skills) we plan to make a fun PvP supported environment for players to engage in brutal combat whether via the Dual Arena, Minigamers or, The Wilderness.
[u]We plan to perfect combat by introducing: fully working magics, proper projectile scripture, near perfect switching using rs-like formulas and timing and proper gear-statistics[/u] to aid in a fair combat situation.

[b]-PvM In Further Detail:[/b]
The fact that we plan to be nearly open world, means that we also have to present a quality PvM experience, don&#39;t we?
This means, that apart from our custom Training Caverns and Donator Zone/Dungeon and the Home Area, we plan to have the world spawned out just like runescape. We aim towards being able to present most if not all popular NPCs such as rare monsters and bosses to be available for players to slaughter and loot  XD 
And with the bosses will obviously come a revamped drop system, allowing for Tokens to be dropped, to be exchanged for prized gear and skilling resources/tools. Which is made even more awesome with working minigames, allowing the players to engage in more game-time, playing the mini games to be able to harvest more than the default rewards.

===================================================
FURTHER DETAILS:
===================================================

[b]-Summoning In Detail:[/b]
We wish to create a simple, lightweight yet powerful summoning system to aid players via simplicity. We plan to have access to the obelisk below Pickupstix&#39;s house at which the player will be able to infuse pouches, just like in RS. We will also provide a Summoning Shop for players to purchase blank pouches, spirit shards, and basic materials from. The charms after gold, will be dropped by monsters once again aimed at an engaging PvM experience. Upon obtaining all necessary materials, the player will be able to infuse pouches and summon familiars once they have obtained the pouch.[/color]

[b]-Donator Benefits In Detail:[/b]
We plan to offer a unique donation benefit set. Based on Legit RS gold and account donations. We plan to offer month based donations via RS gold and life-time donations via RS accounts. The donation benefits will include access to the donator zone, containing all the necessities for skilling (altars, trees, rocks, anvils, fishing pond, farming patches, obelisks, ovens and etc...) plus an array of shops providing the rarest armours, auras and drops at a price of guthix tokens (normal players will have to grind bosses for the drops, donators can just buy them with tokens. Donators will also gain access to the donator dungeon, in which all monsters will drop tokens used for the store mentioned above, plus superior loot including cool rare items, recoloured items and noted skilling resources.

===================================================
WHAT MAKES US UNIQUE:
===================================================

We aim to not only fit, but lead the image of a good RS private server experience, which means we have to be unique in our doings. And with that being said, to add onto the features mentioned above, we are currently planning to offer monthly events encouraging PvP, resulting in rewards for the #1 PKer on the high-scores, each month. This does not mean that ALL the events we do will be PvP based, there will be many hide-n-seek events and in-game rewards for top posters on our forums. Unlike many servers, we actually listen to what the players want and bring up every single suggestion posted on our forums, at our regular staff meetings resulting in many implements being made regularly, fitting our server to the player&#39;s tastes. Also, we try to keep the image of the server as professional by housing an elite staff team, many servers have abusive owners, poorly trained staff and inexperienced management, not to mention that most servers do not have the financial or technical resources to provide for their players. We on the other hand are lucky to have been accepted to be a part of our mother-community, Excell Gaming. They offer premium connection hosting for their servers and a good amount of support for their players. 

===================================================
HOW YOU CAN HELP
===================================================

Yes, you too can take a part in this project, we are in need of beta players, to hastily discover bugs, imperfections and general improvements to be made.
You can join us on our forums linked below.
As another way to support this project, you can copy the image linked below and set is as your signature. Suggestions and good-luck wishes are fully welcome :)
MEDIA WILL BE ADDED SOON

*</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 12 Apr 2012 00:46:38 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/excellscape-667/439250.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Excellscape 667</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Nelson_x Nelson_x]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/nelson_x">@Nelson_x</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>i am superior</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/excellscape-667/439250/8">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/excellscape-667/439250/8</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 12 Apr 2012 00:46:38 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-439250-8</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/excellscape-667/439250.rss">Excellscape 667</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Excellscape 667</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Chrisl1924 Chrisl1924]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/chrisl1924">@Chrisl1924</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Nelson, may I ask how you are affiliated with Excell?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/excellscape-667/439250/7">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/excellscape-667/439250/7</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 11 Apr 2012 22:55:32 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-439250-7</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/excellscape-667/439250.rss">Excellscape 667</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Excellscape 667</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Nelson_x Nelson_x]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/nelson_x">@Nelson_x</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>&lt;3 thx bro</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/excellscape-667/439250/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/excellscape-667/439250/6</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 11 Apr 2012 21:48:54 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-439250-6</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/excellscape-667/439250.rss">Excellscape 667</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Excellscape 667</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Chrisl1924 Chrisl1924]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/chrisl1924">@Chrisl1924</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Nolan, I’ve been playing it, and they’ve changed it enough that it’s starting to become unique. I can’t wait until they’ve had a prolonged period of time to fix it up and make it their own.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/excellscape-667/439250/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/excellscape-667/439250/5</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 11 Apr 2012 19:52:56 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-439250-5</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/excellscape-667/439250.rss">Excellscape 667</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Excellscape 667</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@nolan2131 nolan2131]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/nolan2131">@nolan2131</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Matrix is shit, good luck. Hope you make something out of it.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/excellscape-667/439250/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/excellscape-667/439250/4</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 11 Apr 2012 19:18:34 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-439250-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/excellscape-667/439250.rss">Excellscape 667</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Excellscape 667</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Nelson_x Nelson_x]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/nelson_x">@Nelson_x</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>u can play <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=5" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"> but we still are coding on it <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=5" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/excellscape-667/439250/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/excellscape-667/439250/3</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 11 Apr 2012 17:16:21 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-439250-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/excellscape-667/439250.rss">Excellscape 667</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Excellscape 667</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Chrisl1924 Chrisl1924]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/chrisl1924">@Chrisl1924</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Wonderful, I simply love the community that you have going on. Can’t wait to get on and play!</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/excellscape-667/439250/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/excellscape-667/439250/2</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 11 Apr 2012 02:25:37 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-439250-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/excellscape-667/439250.rss">Excellscape 667</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Excellscape 667</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Nelson_x Nelson_x]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/nelson_x">@Nelson_x</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p><img src="http://filebeam.com/0c1ad1454450c828ddb8f100ee2fa852.jpg" alt width="" height=""><br>
SERVER STATUS:ALPHA<br>
Development-Server completely unplayable, all skills are not fully trainable, no content.<br>
Alpha-Server is available for live testing, basic frame is being worked on, some ideas from plan are being implemented, still pretty buggy.<br>
Beta-Server is available for live testing, and the basic frame of the idea is implemented. Starting to implement main features from plan, some content from plan already available.<br>
Open-All things described in the plan below are implemented and the server is 100% ready for players</p>
<h1>===================================================<br>
WELCOME TO THE OFFICIAL EXCELL SCAPE 667 DEVELOPMENT THREAD</h1>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">-Are you using matrix you n00bz0r?</span><br>
Comic Sans MS"]Im going to be honest and say yes, BUT before raging about how this is another stupid leech of matrix’s work, read through what our plans are for the server.</p>
<h1>===================================================<br>
SERVER PLAN:</h1>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">-General Features:</span></p>
<p>[ul][<em>]Unique Training Caves Containing Many Sought-After Monsters<br>
[</em>]Epic Donator Zone And Dungeons (Further Explained Below)<br>
[<em>]Unique summoning system (Further Explained Below)<br>
[</em>]Working Dungeoneering With Multiple Complexity Levels<br>
[<em>]Lots of minigames for players to engage in PvP and/or PvM combat<br>
[</em>]Fun PvP with perfected switching<br>
[<em>]Unique shops to ease obtaining the most essential items<br>
[</em>]An engaging set-up geared towards a skill based game-play like real RS<br>
[<em>]Nearly open world, nearly all locations accessible and spawned like real RS<br>
[</em>]Tokens dropped by bosses to be exchanged for prized gear and skilling tools.<br>
[<em>]Most mini-games working (Clanwars, Castlewars, Dominion Tower, Pest Controll, Fight Pits and more…)<br>
[</em>]All skills working (with the possible exception of construction…)[/ul]</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">-PvP In Further Detail:</span><br>
Even though the server will be geared towards skill based gameplay (items, rewards, money and etc… obtained via skills) we plan to make a fun PvP supported environment for players to engage in brutal combat whether via the Dual Arena, Minigamers or, The Wilderness.<br>
<span class="bbcode-u">We plan to perfect combat by introducing: fully working magics, proper projectile scripture, near perfect switching using rs-like formulas and timing and proper gear-statistics</span> to aid in a fair combat situation.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">-PvM In Further Detail:</span><br>
The fact that we plan to be nearly open world, means that we also have to present a quality PvM experience, don’t we?<br>
This means, that apart from our custom Training Caverns and Donator Zone/Dungeon and the Home Area, we plan to have the world spawned out just like runescape. We aim towards being able to present most if not all popular NPCs such as rare monsters and bosses to be available for players to slaughter and loot  XD<br>
And with the bosses will obviously come a revamped drop system, allowing for Tokens to be dropped, to be exchanged for prized gear and skilling resources/tools. Which is made even more awesome with working minigames, allowing the players to engage in more game-time, playing the mini games to be able to harvest more than the default rewards.</p>
<h1>===================================================<br>
FURTHER DETAILS:</h1>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">-Summoning In Detail:</span><br>
We wish to create a simple, lightweight yet powerful summoning system to aid players via simplicity. We plan to have access to the obelisk below Pickupstix’s house at which the player will be able to infuse pouches, just like in RS. We will also provide a Summoning Shop for players to purchase blank pouches, spirit shards, and basic materials from. The charms after gold, will be dropped by monsters once again aimed at an engaging PvM experience. Upon obtaining all necessary materials, the player will be able to infuse pouches and summon familiars once they have obtained the pouch.[/color]</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">-Donator Benefits In Detail:</span><br>
We plan to offer a unique donation benefit set. Based on Legit RS gold and account donations. We plan to offer month based donations via RS gold and life-time donations via RS accounts. The donation benefits will include access to the donator zone, containing all the necessities for skilling (altars, trees, rocks, anvils, fishing pond, farming patches, obelisks, ovens and etc…) plus an array of shops providing the rarest armours, auras and drops at a price of guthix tokens (normal players will have to grind bosses for the drops, donators can just buy them with tokens. Donators will also gain access to the donator dungeon, in which all monsters will drop tokens used for the store mentioned above, plus superior loot including cool rare items, recoloured items and noted skilling resources.</p>
<h1>===================================================<br>
WHAT MAKES US UNIQUE:</h1>
<p>We aim to not only fit, but lead the image of a good RS private server experience, which means we have to be unique in our doings. And with that being said, to add onto the features mentioned above, we are currently planning to offer monthly events encouraging PvP, resulting in rewards for the <span class="hashtag">#1</span> PKer on the high-scores, each month. This does not mean that ALL the events we do will be PvP based, there will be many hide-n-seek events and in-game rewards for top posters on our forums. Unlike many servers, we actually listen to what the players want and bring up every single suggestion posted on our forums, at our regular staff meetings resulting in many implements being made regularly, fitting our server to the player’s tastes. Also, we try to keep the image of the server as professional by housing an elite staff team, many servers have abusive owners, poorly trained staff and inexperienced management, not to mention that most servers do not have the financial or technical resources to provide for their players. We on the other hand are lucky to have been accepted to be a part of our mother-community, Excell Gaming. They offer premium connection hosting for their servers and a good amount of support for their players.</p>
<h1>===================================================<br>
HOW YOU CAN HELP</h1>
<p>Yes, you too can take a part in this project, we are in need of beta players, to hastily discover bugs, imperfections and general improvements to be made.<br>
You can join us on our forums linked below.<br>
As another way to support this project, you can copy the image linked below and set is as your signature. Suggestions and good-luck wishes are fully welcome <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=5" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"><br>
MEDIA WILL BE ADDED SOON</p>
<ul>
<li>
</li>
</ul>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/excellscape-667/439250/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/excellscape-667/439250/1</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 11 Apr 2012 01:12:09 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-439250-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/excellscape-667/439250.rss">Excellscape 667</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
