<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Mouse movement learning?</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/mouse-movement-learning/410069</link>
    <description>I came up with a theory yesterday regarding the idea of using prerecorded mouse paths to generate new mouse paths. I record a series of data points representing the movement of a mouse, and then linearly interpolate between the points to fill in the holes. I then compare this data set to a curve (right now, just a line) and determine a deviation value of how much different the dataset is from the curve. The curve has an orientation of using either independent x values, or independent y values (determined based on whether y or x deviates more in the dataset, respectively). I calculate the &quot;progress&quot; along the curve by taking the distance from the start point to the current point, divided by the distance between the endpoints. This creates a percentage of how far along the curve I am. I then map this percentage to the deviation value for each point in the curve.

When I want to generate a new dataset, I can create the same curve between any two datapoints, and then use my progress along that curve to gather a new deviation value from the deviation table. If the percentage cannot be exactly matched, the deviation values for the next percentage lower than the inputted percentage and the next percentage higher than the inputted percentage are interpolated. The new deviation value becomes an estimate in a scaled (or rather, irregular) curve. This means I can create any sort of mouse movement I want, and then produce any sort of point a to point b dataset, no matter how its size or orientation compares to the original mouse movement.

The program I made implements this algorithm along with an idea of randomness. I store a new table for each input mouse movement, then have a means of switching between tables in the runtime of the generation algorithm. Basically, it&#39;s currently setup to randomly pick one of any of the created tables, then generate the line with a 50% chance in the course of the algorithm to randomly switch to any other table, thus combining two entirely separate mouse movement schemas into one.

Another idea to develop this algorithm is I theorized the behavior of generating new datasets would differ greatly if one used a curve other than a line, and interpolated nonlinearly. For example, generating a bezier curve and calculating differentiation based on that, then creating a new bezier curve to grab the deviation values would create a system of far more curved behavior, obviously. One could also interpolate values from the table using cosine or a cubic approach. There is a lot of room for customization in how the algorithm actually determines the table and determines new datasets. I propose these customizations for what some people have called &quot;profiles&quot; of certain behavior. A linear approach is a much more direct means of finding the point, whereas a bezier curve approach would represent people taking their time to move their mouse from point a to point b. One could even create a noisy linear approach for people that are really slow at moving their mouse, and tend to have a ridiculous about of zigzagging in their pathway.

But anyway, here is a picture that hopefully illustrates my algorithm better:

[img]http://img855.imageshack.us/img855/5271/mousecurvefit.png[/img]

Here you have a red curve with a blue dataset of points, assumed to have been made by a mouse. This particular line progresses faster along the y-axis, thereby making the y values of the line the independent variable, and the x values dependent. This implies x differs far more nonlinearly in the dataset than y does, which obviously is true. So, we progress along the line and compare the x values, acquiring deviations from the line to the dataset (these values are seen on the right). I also calculate the progress along the line, which can be thought of as a percentage complete (these values are seen on the left). This allows me to approximate any dataset based on another line, by simply comparing the progress values to the deviation values in a table.

Moving onto the actual program I wrote. I did it rather poorly, so don&#39;t immediately crucify me. My program does employ my theory in the most crudest and simplest of forms. It does a poor job, overall, but it gets the job done. There are much better solutions than the ones I have, and I hope they can be used by someone else in place of mine. I am simply proposing a theory and hoping it&#39;s unique. My program sometimes messes up on creating the curves (especially when you record really wild ones), and the result curves are usually really noisy (easily fixable with a smooth filter). Here are some pictures of it being used, nevertheless:

recording a simple mouse path:
[img]http://img30.imageshack.us/img30/6152/mlearning1.png[/img]

recording a more complex mouse path (obnoxious and will probably fuck up generation later on):
[img]http://img709.imageshack.us/img709/8022/mlearning2.png[/img]

recording a much more direct path (to balance the last one, but also show the nice linearity of some pathways):
[img]http://img192.imageshack.us/img192/1706/mlearning3.png[/img]

generating a new path (the red dots represent where the last recorded curve was; the following curve was also generated only based on the last curve recorded, being the one in picture 3):
[img]http://img818.imageshack.us/img818/1590/mlearning4.png[/img]

generating a randomized path (as predicted, it fucks up a bit from the complexity of mouse path 2, but we can still see two different mouse paths being used as sources):
[img]http://img534.imageshack.us/img534/9561/mlearning5.png[/img]

Controls for the program:

[ul][li]F1 - switches program mode to recording, where a click starts a path and another click ends it (the program then corrects the path, so don&#39;t be surprised if it looks different afterward)[/li]
[li]F2 - switches program mode to generating, where a click starts a path and another click ends it. The program generates this path based on the last path recorded, with no random switching to other paths (though there is still minor randomization added, where the interpolation ratio is slightly randomized to add random touchups to the final product).[/li]
[li]F3 - switches program mode to randomized generating where, as explained above, it will choose a random dataset to source the new path on, and then have a 50% chance of switching to another one midpath.[/li][/ul]


Attached is the program and the source. I apologize for lack of documentation. I simply came up with a theory and went ahead crudely implementing it.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 15 Aug 2011 20:35:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>General Programming</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/mouse-movement-learning/410069.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Mouse movement learning?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@lawl lawl]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/lawl">@lawl</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“slavemaster, post:1, topic:410306”][quote author=lawl_temp link=topic=511337.msg3712032#msg3712032 date=1313416674]<br>
wall of text</p>
<p>use a neural network<br>
[/quote]<br>
That’s cute. It’s fun to suggest something randomly that seems partially related. Can you explain how you would apply a neural network here, though?[/quote]<br>
no i cant</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/mouse-movement-learning/410069/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/mouse-movement-learning/410069/6</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 15 Aug 2011 20:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-410069-6</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/mouse-movement-learning/410069.rss">Mouse movement learning?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Mouse movement learning?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@lawl lawl]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/lawl">@lawl</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>wall of text</p>
<p>use a neural network</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/mouse-movement-learning/410069/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/mouse-movement-learning/410069/5</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 15 Aug 2011 13:57:54 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-410069-5</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/mouse-movement-learning/410069.rss">Mouse movement learning?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Mouse movement learning?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@moparisthebest Moparisthebest]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/moparisthebest">@moparisthebest</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I think to make it decent you are going to have to take into account many more than just one mouse movement.  Maybe more like 100 or so would yield a more accurate result?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/mouse-movement-learning/410069/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/mouse-movement-learning/410069/4</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 14 Aug 2011 23:30:05 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-410069-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/mouse-movement-learning/410069.rss">Mouse movement learning?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Mouse movement learning?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@mod_taharok Taharok]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/mod_taharok">@mod_taharok</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote quote-modified" data-post="2" data-topic="410069">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/eczema3/40/5_e05bb34c421432ee4d40de30c10af3e5.png" class="avatar"> eczema3:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>It needs smoothing out, there’s no way a realistic mouse movement would EVER be that jagged.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Indeed, I mentioned that. <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/wink.png?v=5" title=":wink:" class="emoji" alt=":wink:"> Smoothing is trivial. This post is meant to explore the theory, not a perfect result.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/mouse-movement-learning/410069/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/mouse-movement-learning/410069/3</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 14 Aug 2011 14:26:56 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-410069-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/mouse-movement-learning/410069.rss">Mouse movement learning?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Mouse movement learning?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@eczema3 eczema3]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/eczema3">@eczema3</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>It needs smoothing out, there’s no way a realistic mouse movement would EVER be that jagged.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/mouse-movement-learning/410069/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/mouse-movement-learning/410069/2</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 14 Aug 2011 13:48:08 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-410069-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/mouse-movement-learning/410069.rss">Mouse movement learning?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Mouse movement learning?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@mod_taharok Taharok]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/mod_taharok">@mod_taharok</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I came up with a theory yesterday regarding the idea of using prerecorded mouse paths to generate new mouse paths. I record a series of data points representing the movement of a mouse, and then linearly interpolate between the points to fill in the holes. I then compare this data set to a curve (right now, just a line) and determine a deviation value of how much different the dataset is from the curve. The curve has an orientation of using either independent x values, or independent y values (determined based on whether y or x deviates more in the dataset, respectively). I calculate the “progress” along the curve by taking the distance from the start point to the current point, divided by the distance between the endpoints. This creates a percentage of how far along the curve I am. I then map this percentage to the deviation value for each point in the curve.</p>
<p>When I want to generate a new dataset, I can create the same curve between any two datapoints, and then use my progress along that curve to gather a new deviation value from the deviation table. If the percentage cannot be exactly matched, the deviation values for the next percentage lower than the inputted percentage and the next percentage higher than the inputted percentage are interpolated. The new deviation value becomes an estimate in a scaled (or rather, irregular) curve. This means I can create any sort of mouse movement I want, and then produce any sort of point a to point b dataset, no matter how its size or orientation compares to the original mouse movement.</p>
<p>The program I made implements this algorithm along with an idea of randomness. I store a new table for each input mouse movement, then have a means of switching between tables in the runtime of the generation algorithm. Basically, it’s currently setup to randomly pick one of any of the created tables, then generate the line with a 50% chance in the course of the algorithm to randomly switch to any other table, thus combining two entirely separate mouse movement schemas into one.</p>
<p>Another idea to develop this algorithm is I theorized the behavior of generating new datasets would differ greatly if one used a curve other than a line, and interpolated nonlinearly. For example, generating a bezier curve and calculating differentiation based on that, then creating a new bezier curve to grab the deviation values would create a system of far more curved behavior, obviously. One could also interpolate values from the table using cosine or a cubic approach. There is a lot of room for customization in how the algorithm actually determines the table and determines new datasets. I propose these customizations for what some people have called “profiles” of certain behavior. A linear approach is a much more direct means of finding the point, whereas a bezier curve approach would represent people taking their time to move their mouse from point a to point b. One could even create a noisy linear approach for people that are really slow at moving their mouse, and tend to have a ridiculous about of zigzagging in their pathway.</p>
<p>But anyway, here is a picture that hopefully illustrates my algorithm better:</p>
<p><img src="http://img855.imageshack.us/img855/5271/mousecurvefit.png" alt width="" height=""></p>
<p>Here you have a red curve with a blue dataset of points, assumed to have been made by a mouse. This particular line progresses faster along the y-axis, thereby making the y values of the line the independent variable, and the x values dependent. This implies x differs far more nonlinearly in the dataset than y does, which obviously is true. So, we progress along the line and compare the x values, acquiring deviations from the line to the dataset (these values are seen on the right). I also calculate the progress along the line, which can be thought of as a percentage complete (these values are seen on the left). This allows me to approximate any dataset based on another line, by simply comparing the progress values to the deviation values in a table.</p>
<p>Moving onto the actual program I wrote. I did it rather poorly, so don’t immediately crucify me. My program does employ my theory in the most crudest and simplest of forms. It does a poor job, overall, but it gets the job done. There are much better solutions than the ones I have, and I hope they can be used by someone else in place of mine. I am simply proposing a theory and hoping it’s unique. My program sometimes messes up on creating the curves (especially when you record really wild ones), and the result curves are usually really noisy (easily fixable with a smooth filter). Here are some pictures of it being used, nevertheless:</p>
<p>recording a simple mouse path:<br>
<img src="http://img30.imageshack.us/img30/6152/mlearning1.png" alt width="" height=""></p>
<p>recording a more complex mouse path (obnoxious and will probably fuck up generation later on):<br>
<img src="http://img709.imageshack.us/img709/8022/mlearning2.png" alt width="" height=""></p>
<p>recording a much more direct path (to balance the last one, but also show the nice linearity of some pathways):<br>
<img src="http://img192.imageshack.us/img192/1706/mlearning3.png" alt width="" height=""></p>
<p>generating a new path (the red dots represent where the last recorded curve was; the following curve was also generated only based on the last curve recorded, being the one in picture 3):<br>
<img src="http://img818.imageshack.us/img818/1590/mlearning4.png" alt width="" height=""></p>
<p>generating a randomized path (as predicted, it fucks up a bit from the complexity of mouse path 2, but we can still see two different mouse paths being used as sources):<br>
<img src="http://img534.imageshack.us/img534/9561/mlearning5.png" alt width="" height=""></p>
<p>Controls for the program:</p>
<p>[ul][li]F1 - switches program mode to recording, where a click starts a path and another click ends it (the program then corrects the path, so don’t be surprised if it looks different afterward)[/li]<br>
[li]F2 - switches program mode to generating, where a click starts a path and another click ends it. The program generates this path based on the last path recorded, with no random switching to other paths (though there is still minor randomization added, where the interpolation ratio is slightly randomized to add random touchups to the final product).[/li]<br>
[li]F3 - switches program mode to randomized generating where, as explained above, it will choose a random dataset to source the new path on, and then have a 50% chance of switching to another one midpath.[/li][/ul]</p>
<p>Attached is the program and the source. I apologize for lack of documentation. I simply came up with a theory and went ahead crudely implementing it.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/mouse-movement-learning/410069/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/mouse-movement-learning/410069/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 14 Aug 2011 13:35:15 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-410069-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/mouse-movement-learning/410069.rss">Mouse movement learning?</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
