<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>EasyRsc</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/easyrsc/441234</link>
    <description>Okay, so here is my issue. I&#39;m still quite new to this whole rsps business, I&#39;ve figured most of the stuff out but one thing. I&#39;m trying to add armor, npcs, and drops, but here is my issue. I put the same code in on both the server side and client side, I know that the server side needs edited and complied to  gzip file. My issue is with the client side. Because its an rscd file, I don&#39;t know what type of file to compile it under after I&#39;ve made my changes. I&#39;m currently using 7zip, and any information would be much appreciated.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 03 May 2012 01:05:12 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/easyrsc/441234.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>EasyRsc</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@professionalnoob professionalnoob]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/professionalnoob">@professionalnoob</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Okay, so here is my issue. I’m still quite new to this whole rsps business, I’ve figured most of the stuff out but one thing. I’m trying to add armor, npcs, and drops, but here is my issue. I put the same code in on both the server side and client side, I know that the server side needs edited and complied to  gzip file. My issue is with the client side. Because its an rscd file, I don’t know what type of file to compile it under after I’ve made my changes. I’m currently using 7zip, and any information would be much appreciated.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/easyrsc/441234/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/easyrsc/441234/1</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 03 May 2012 01:05:12 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-441234-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/easyrsc/441234.rss">EasyRsc</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
