<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Rune-Demon #317</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rune-demon-317/372095</link>
    <description>[center]
[anchor=top]
[img]http://i55.tinypic.com/34ih1c4.jpg[/img]


Hello guys,

Time for a project eh, Well i have decided to start this project as known that i have been wanting to work on work continuely for a long time, So i have decied to make &quot;Rune-Demon&quot; Which i hope will be a very big success...

I have started working on this about 3 days ago and i know that it&#39;s going to work out pretty well and i have done alot mainly client sided and it&#39;s working out great!

[u]Be sure to sign up on our popular forum to check more updates:[/u]
http://rune-demon.org


[ul][b]Navigation[/b]
[list][li][iurl=#about]About Rune-Demon[/iurl][/li]
[li][iurl=#features]Features[/iurl][/li]
[li][iurl=#qs]The Quest System[/iurl][/li]
[li][iurl=#demon]The Demon Quest[/iurl][/li]
[li][iurl=#621]Loading 621 Items[/iurl][/li]
[li][iurl=#economy]Economy[/iurl][/li]
[li][iurl=#images]Images[/iurl][/li]
[li][iurl=#credits]Credits[/iurl][/li][/list]

[anchor=about]
[b]About Rune-Demon[/b]
Rune-Demon is a Development server in progress, The server is based around Economy. We are working to make the server the most Quality and fun experience you will have. We will be working hard to make the server Unique and very effective. Alot has been put into this server and hopefully alot to gain. Now i think this may be one of my best project on Moparscape and i plan for it to be one of my best servers of all time. I have just started using Project Insanity and i&#39;ve progressed well on it, it is turning out to be a very good success for me and i hope to develop this alot Further.

[anchor=features]
[b]
Features:[/b][/ul]
[code]-Transparency click on item icons.
-Loading 621 items
-Fixed animation header.
-508 NPC&#39;s packed but not added yet.
-New home entranna
-Added a Quest System
-Added a Demon Quest.
-Added Firemaking
-Fixed Staking
-Fixed all Trade Dupes
-Added Cooks Assistant.[/code]
-Fixed PlayerRights System.
More coming Soon...

[anchor=qs]
[u]The Quest System[/u]
The quest system is very unique, It loads from seperate classes packed into 2 directorys. It&#39;s mainly loading using ints, And has Requirments and everything packed into it ect.
I&#39;ve added the interface for it to be perfect for the quests, And i have made my own custom quest dedicated to the server called Demon Killers, It&#39;s based around the home area.

[anchor=demon]
[u]The Demon Killer (Quest):[/u]
The Demon Killer is a custom quest made for Rune-Demon, It starts by speaking to vannaka and he tells you to go get jungle demons located of the rear end of home, And it is the requirment to kill them and get 5 ourg bones. When you Return to vannaka he will say thanks ect, And ask you to go talk to The Runescape guide to give you your starter items, When you return to Vannaka he will Reward you with Experience and 20M.

[anchor=621]
[u]Loading 621 Models:[/u]
Well Today i packed the 621 models into the client but not yet the cache, It&#39;s loading most 621 models but not all of them yet. Some of the models are an invisable icon and don&#39;t show which i am soon to fix. It is very friendly and bug free on the models that do work and look very effective, Check a picture below to see...

[anchor=economy]
[u]Economy:[/u]
Economy on Rune-Demon is very powerfull to the server, We have alot of Ecomical ways of treating the servers, Their is theiving on the other side of home and their are the minigames to work on based for money making/item getting, These ways of making money i would say is the best, And there is all 21 skills added so you can make money from them also.

[anchor=images]
[b]Images:[/b]
[u]Inventory Click Transparency (Preview not my pic but is exactly the same.)[/u]
[img]http://img252.imageshack.us/img252/2724/0151.gif[/img]
[u]Loading some 621 Models.[/u]
[img]http://i64.servimg.com/u/f64/15/94/88/92/newmod10.jpg[/img]

[anchor=credits]
[b]Credits:[/b]
Sanity (Project Insanity)
Dust R I P (Teaching me of the cache)
Lsm1107 (Programmer/Development)

[iurl=#top]Back to the Top.[/iurl]

[/center]</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2010 14:20:41 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rune-demon-317/372095.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Rune-Demon #317</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Lsm1107 Lsm1107]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/lsm1107">@Lsm1107</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[center]<br>
[anchor=top]<br>
<img src="http://i55.tinypic.com/34ih1c4.jpg" alt width="140" height="120"></p>
<p>Hello guys,</p>
<p>Time for a project eh, Well i have decided to start this project as known that i have been wanting to work on work continuely for a long time, So i have decied to make “Rune-Demon” Which i hope will be a very big success…</p>
<p>I have started working on this about 3 days ago and i know that it’s going to work out pretty well and i have done alot mainly client sided and it’s working out great!</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-u">Be sure to sign up on our popular forum to check more updates:</span><br>
<a href="http://rune-demon.org" class="onebox" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">http://rune-demon.org</a></p>
<p>[ul]<span class="bbcode-b">Navigation</span><br>
[list][li][iurl=#about]About Rune-Demon[/iurl][/li]<br>
[li][iurl=#features]Features[/iurl][/li]<br>
[li][iurl=#qs]The Quest System[/iurl][/li]<br>
[li][iurl=#demon]The Demon Quest[/iurl][/li]<br>
[li][iurl=#621]Loading 621 Items[/iurl][/li]<br>
[li][iurl=#economy]Economy[/iurl][/li]<br>
[li][iurl=#images]Images[/iurl][/li]<br>
[li][iurl=#credits]Credits[/iurl][/li][/list]</p>
<p>[anchor=about]<br>
<span class="bbcode-b">About Rune-Demon</span><br>
Rune-Demon is a Development server in progress, The server is based around Economy. We are working to make the server the most Quality and fun experience you will have. We will be working hard to make the server Unique and very effective. Alot has been put into this server and hopefully alot to gain. Now i think this may be one of my best project on Moparscape and i plan for it to be one of my best servers of all time. I have just started using Project Insanity and i’ve progressed well on it, it is turning out to be a very good success for me and i hope to develop this alot Further.</p>
<p>[anchor=features]<br>
<span class="bbcode-b"><br>
Features:</span>[/ul]</p>
<p><code>-Transparency click on item icons.
-Loading 621 items
-Fixed animation header.
-508 NPC's packed but not added yet.
-New home entranna
-Added a Quest System
-Added a Demon Quest.
-Added Firemaking
-Fixed Staking
-Fixed all Trade Dupes
-Added Cooks Assistant.</code><br>
-Fixed PlayerRights System.<br>
More coming Soon…</p>
<p>[anchor=qs]<br>
<span class="bbcode-u">The Quest System</span><br>
The quest system is very unique, It loads from seperate classes packed into 2 directorys. It’s mainly loading using ints, And has Requirments and everything packed into it ect.<br>
I’ve added the interface for it to be perfect for the quests, And i have made my own custom quest dedicated to the server called Demon Killers, It’s based around the home area.</p>
<p>[anchor=demon]<br>
<span class="bbcode-u">The Demon Killer (Quest):</span><br>
The Demon Killer is a custom quest made for Rune-Demon, It starts by speaking to vannaka and he tells you to go get jungle demons located of the rear end of home, And it is the requirment to kill them and get 5 ourg bones. When you Return to vannaka he will say thanks ect, And ask you to go talk to The Runescape guide to give you your starter items, When you return to Vannaka he will Reward you with Experience and 20M.</p>
<p>[anchor=621]<br>
<span class="bbcode-u">Loading 621 Models:</span><br>
Well Today i packed the 621 models into the client but not yet the cache, It’s loading most 621 models but not all of them yet. Some of the models are an invisable icon and don’t show which i am soon to fix. It is very friendly and bug free on the models that do work and look very effective, Check a picture below to see…</p>
<p>[anchor=economy]<br>
<span class="bbcode-u">Economy:</span><br>
Economy on Rune-Demon is very powerfull to the server, We have alot of Ecomical ways of treating the servers, Their is theiving on the other side of home and their are the minigames to work on based for money making/item getting, These ways of making money i would say is the best, And there is all 21 skills added so you can make money from them also.</p>
<p>[anchor=images]<br>
<span class="bbcode-b">Images:</span><br>
<span class="bbcode-u">Inventory Click Transparency (Preview not my pic but is exactly the same.)</span><br>
<img src="http://img252.imageshack.us/img252/2724/0151.gif" alt width="" height=""><br>
<span class="bbcode-u">Loading some 621 Models.</span><br>
<img src="http://i64.servimg.com/u/f64/15/94/88/92/newmod10.jpg" alt width="484" height="298"></p>
<p>[anchor=credits]<br>
<span class="bbcode-b">Credits:</span><br>
Sanity (Project Insanity)<br>
Dust R I P (Teaching me of the cache)<br>
Lsm1107 (Programmer/Development)</p>
<p>[iurl=#top]Back to the Top.[/iurl]</p>
<p>[/center]</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rune-demon-317/372095/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rune-demon-317/372095/1</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2010 14:20:41 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-372095-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rune-demon-317/372095.rss">Rune-Demon #317</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
