<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Hey there</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/hey-there/31073</link>
    <description>Howdy everybody.

I&#39;m new to the whole &#39;MoparScape&#39; concept, I heard of it when I saw some noobs trying to &#39;sell&#39; a private server because it was &#39;rare&#39; for 500m RS gp. I thought I recognized the name &#39;Mopar&#39;; I&#39;m a big fan of his work ever since the SCAR Scripts on Kaitnieks forums. (Too bad about that  :( )

I&#39;m not exactly an uber-coder, so bear with my nooby questions  :)

So lemme see...I&#39;ve set up a server, (using Hamachi). It&#39;s the most basic server you can have, I just used the TestScape source and changed it all to my servername. So my first question is:

1) I&#39;ve noticed that several of the actions requiring animations (e.g. slashing webs, opening doors, skills) do not work. I&#39;ve seen several tutorials about adding skills etc, but how would you make something like a door open, or how would you make yourself be able to speak to an NPC, for example the barbershop in Falador, that kind of stuff?

2) I&#39;m familiar with some Java basics, but what is a &#39;Public void&#39;?  :o

3) If someone could point me to a tutorial which explains how to make Range and Magic/Ancient Magic work, that would be very helpful (I&#39;ve looked for one, but I can&#39;t seem to find one that works.)

4) Where could I get a copy of &#39;PimpScape&#39; and other such sources (RealityScape, etc)? (you&#39;ll probably know by now that I use TestScape)

I think that just about covers it for now, thank you all very much for helping me out  :)

~Philo

[br][size=1]Posted at: November 30, 2006, 09:39:49 AM[/size][hr]Oh, I remembered another question..

Are the latest caches kept somewhere, or on some other site? And would these include the RS holiday events?[br][size=1]Posted at: November 30, 2006, 12:17:09 PM[/size][hr]I found the place to get the other sources, NVM about that.

~Philo[br][size=1]Posted at: November 30, 2006, 12:57:24 PM[/size][hr] :(</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2006 00:52:02 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/hey-there/31073.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Hey there</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@pkedpker pkedpker]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/pkedpker">@pkedpker</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Well first of all you posted in the wrong section this is to ask questions about moparscape which is the client I guess i dont think anyone will help you here try posting in the</p>
<p>RS2 Server Development/Help<br>
Show off what you have done, help with errors and so forth.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/hey-there/31073/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/hey-there/31073/2</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2006 00:52:02 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-31073-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/hey-there/31073.rss">Hey there</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Hey there</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Philosophica Philosophica]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/philosophica">@Philosophica</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Howdy everybody.</p>
<p>I’m new to the whole ‘MoparScape’ concept, I heard of it when I saw some noobs trying to ‘sell’ a private server because it was ‘rare’ for 500m RS gp. I thought I recognized the name ‘Mopar’; I’m a big fan of his work ever since the SCAR Scripts on Kaitnieks forums. (Too bad about that  <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/frowning.png?v=6" title=":frowning:" class="emoji" alt=":frowning:"> )</p>
<p>I’m not exactly an uber-coder, so bear with my nooby questions  <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=6" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
<p>So lemme see…I’ve set up a server, (using Hamachi). It’s the most basic server you can have, I just used the TestScape source and changed it all to my servername. So my first question is:</p>
<ol>
<li>
<p>I’ve noticed that several of the actions requiring animations (e.g. slashing webs, opening doors, skills) do not work. I’ve seen several tutorials about adding skills etc, but how would you make something like a door open, or how would you make yourself be able to speak to an NPC, for example the barbershop in Falador, that kind of stuff?</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>I’m familiar with some Java basics, but what is a ‘Public void’?  :o</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>If someone could point me to a tutorial which explains how to make Range and Magic/Ancient Magic work, that would be very helpful (I’ve looked for one, but I can’t seem to find one that works.)</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Where could I get a copy of ‘PimpScape’ and other such sources (RealityScape, etc)? (you’ll probably know by now that I use TestScape)</p>
</li>
</ol>
<p>I think that just about covers it for now, thank you all very much for helping me out  <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=6" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
<p>~Philo</p>
<p>[br][size=1]Posted at: November 30, 2006, 09:39:49 AM[/size][hr]Oh, I remembered another question…</p>
<p>Are the latest caches kept somewhere, or on some other site? And would these include the RS holiday events?[br][size=1]Posted at: November 30, 2006, 12:17:09 PM[/size][hr]I found the place to get the other sources, NVM about that.</p>
<p>~Philo[br][size=1]Posted at: November 30, 2006, 12:57:24 PM[/size][hr] <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/frowning.png?v=6" title=":frowning:" class="emoji" alt=":frowning:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/hey-there/31073/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/hey-there/31073/1</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2006 19:37:05 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-31073-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/hey-there/31073.rss">Hey there</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
