<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>718 Runeportal/Quest Tab</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/718-runeportal-quest-tab/554913</link>
    <description>Hi Guys,

I&#39;ve been working on a 718 to get the feel of how things are coded compared to the 317 revision and i&#39;m quickly getting my head around things following some basic tutorials, now that i have a good base to work with to learn on i&#39;m going about cleaning up some things.

I&#39;m currently having an issue with the 506 interface for the quest tab, where RunePortal class is called upon replacing the quest tab entirely with player commands, tele&#39;s etc, while it is a nice idea i would like to revert back to the tab calling out the quests - my quest manager and relevant files are there but for the life of me can not work out what i need to be replacing in the buttonhandler etc, if someone could point me in the right direction it would be very much appreciated, i&#39;m not requesting to be spoon fed and sorry if a search will provide the answer but i&#39;m having no luck other than finding tutorials on how to add a custom tab with the RunePortal class.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 04 Mar 2016 15:08:16 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/718-runeportal-quest-tab/554913.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>718 Runeportal/Quest Tab</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Jarvistude Jarvistude]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/jarvistude">@Jarvistude</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Perfect, thanks sk8rdude, i thought that was the case, but i just wasn’t 100% whether as it was calling in that class whether i needed to take it out and recall the quest manager class etc.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/718-runeportal-quest-tab/554913/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/718-runeportal-quest-tab/554913/3</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 04 Mar 2016 15:08:16 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-554913-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/718-runeportal-quest-tab/554913.rss">718 Runeportal/Quest Tab</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>718 Runeportal/Quest Tab</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@sk8rdude461 sk8rdude461]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/sk8rdude461">@sk8rdude461</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>What you would first do is remove the code making the runeportal show up.</p>
<p>Then you need to get the ids of the text components and etc so you can replace those strings/data with your own.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/718-runeportal-quest-tab/554913/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/718-runeportal-quest-tab/554913/2</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 03 Mar 2016 23:21:03 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-554913-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/718-runeportal-quest-tab/554913.rss">718 Runeportal/Quest Tab</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>718 Runeportal/Quest Tab</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Jarvistude Jarvistude]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/jarvistude">@Jarvistude</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Hi Guys,</p>
<p>I’ve been working on a 718 to get the feel of how things are coded compared to the 317 revision and i’m quickly getting my head around things following some basic tutorials, now that i have a good base to work with to learn on i’m going about cleaning up some things.</p>
<p>I’m currently having an issue with the 506 interface for the quest tab, where RunePortal class is called upon replacing the quest tab entirely with player commands, tele’s etc, while it is a nice idea i would like to revert back to the tab calling out the quests - my quest manager and relevant files are there but for the life of me can not work out what i need to be replacing in the buttonhandler etc, if someone could point me in the right direction it would be very much appreciated, i’m not requesting to be spoon fed and sorry if a search will provide the answer but i’m having no luck other than finding tutorials on how to add a custom tab with the RunePortal class.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/718-runeportal-quest-tab/554913/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/718-runeportal-quest-tab/554913/1</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 03 Mar 2016 15:30:44 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-554913-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/718-runeportal-quest-tab/554913.rss">718 Runeportal/Quest Tab</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
