<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Deaths a bitch and then you wait</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/deaths-a-bitch-and-then-you-wait/251202</link>
    <description>Well this is a novel im working on for the sheer boredom that i constantly get, here is the first 3 pages of it, i&#39;ll post more when i write more
&lt;blockquote&gt;Dieing isn’t a particularly pleasant experience, many say it’s something to postpone at all costs. Whereas others decide that they should get it over and done with, like pulling a plaster off a hairy patch of skin. Murphy Baker had decided that dieing was definitely not for him as soon as his car had careened off the road and into to an army assault course. Naturally they had looked upon his as a terrorist and fired without command. His dieing words were: “If only my name had been Will.” That was the past as Murphy liked to think of it, a simpler time. Now however he was waiting inside his own brain, waiting for his chance to exit the current life and enter the after life. Had he not had an ounce of faith in any religion he would be very bored, but as it was, he believed mildly in Christianity. That being said he also believed in his right to party and if the two ever collided Jesus and his pals took a back seat. As his thoughts wandered wildly, the classic line “Have I left the oven on?” suddenly popped into his unconscious ramblings. He dismissed this thought quickly, what the hell did he care? He was dead. So as he flew around his own bubble of thought he decided on two things: One, that he was getting impatient and that he wished someone would come save him from his boredom. And two, he hoped the after life had a buffet, he was starving. 
The minutes passed, they eventually turned to hours and, for the sake of prolonging my poor characters boredom, then days. Finally, as Murphy was just about to start considering committing unconscious suicide to see if he could get to the second afterlife because the first was bloody boring, a light entered his bubble of thought. It steadily grew brighter and shone with an extraordinary brightness. A shadowy figure stepped from the light and reached out a hand. Disregarding all of the lessons he had learned when he was younger, Murphy grabbed the strangers hand and went on into the light. The first thing Murphy noticed was that he was now, once again, in control of his extremities. Instantly his insatiable libido starting gnawing at his mind. He quashed it and turned to see his new surroundings. It was a small box shaped room, whitewashed walls and an MDF door, also whitewashed. There was a small potted planet in the corner. Which, by the looks of things, had expired many moons ago. The stranger stood next to him. He was wearing a white suit with a golden tie. A satchel slung over one shoulder and a driver cap atop his short hair. Embroidered on the satchel was a picture of a man running and the name ‘St Peters Soul Snatchers.’ “So, you St. Peter?” asked Murphy.
“No,” snorted the man.
“Who are you then?”
“Soul Snatcher, ‘nuff said”
“Grouchy,” Murphy mumbled. The man checked his watch, he looked at the door and then stared at Murphy. “So what the hell is going on?”
“Didn’t you listen to the Herpe?” A Herpe is an informant of the afterlife, these are not to be confused with Herpes which is an STD, however to become a Herpe you must have had Herpes. 
“Normally when I get an STD I rub some cream on it and hope for the best,” the man slapped his forehead. “You dumb ass, they are instructors, not something you get from a dirty weekend in Essex.” 
“Regardless, I got neither after I died.”
“Damn Herpe relation office, they are always on strike.”
“So, I’m still none the wiser”
“Cheeky little sod you are. Basically, we, that is to say the Soul Snatchers, come and pick you up from your death, then we drop you off into the judgement room.”
“So where’s this judgement room?”
“As soon as the door flashes a white light, its time to go into the judgement room.” As if by some sort of pre-scripted magic (because you guys would never accuse me of that) the door started to flash slowly with a white light.
“That’s more of a pulse” protested Murphy.
“Like it matters.” The man kicked the door hard and watched it swing inwards. They now stood in what looked like an airport terminal. It was a huge whitewashed room with a glass domed ceiling. There were sofas dotted around and a line of booths separating the main room from a long corridor. At the booths were a bunch of tired looking men and women. There was even a Starbucks in the far corner (not satisfied with domination of the world, Starbucks decided that the moon needed at least one per crater. That still not being enough, the marketing manager committed suicide to instantly started setting up a new branch in the afterlife. What the dead did before this magical move of capitalist coffee shops we’ll never know.) It all seemed quiet lovely, all except for the queue that wound from the booths all the way around the room and then out of two corridors and came back in. There was a sign above the booths ‘Now serving numbers 9,657,230,069 – 9,658,230,069. If you one of these numbers please cue up.’ “Right you,” said the man “get a ticket and I go on my break and get some food, I am starving.” There was a ticket machine right by their door. Murphy reached for it. A women flew over with some white wings, and slapped a sign over the machine ‘Out of order, suck it.’ “Oh you mother-” the man cuffed Murphy before he could finish his abusive language. “Don’t swear in the judgement room.”
“That’s Bullshi-” the man cuffed him again.
“You don’t learn, do you?”
“What?” Murphy retorted.
“I said no swearing, you want me to start getting abusive? I will taser you if necessary.”
“No need ma brother from another mother, don’t get those knickers of yours in a twist.”
“Are you black?”
“Quite obviously not.”
“Then don’t speak as if you are,” the man cuffed Murphy again.
“Whatever, so what do I do now this ticket machine is screwed?”
“Take a seat like the rest of those people, then get a ticket when the machine is working again, savvy?”
“That’s going to take ages”
“Well your afterlife not mine, bye.” And with that the man walked off through the booths with a flash of a white passport. 
Now thoroughly miffed Murphy walked off towards a seating arrangement on the other side of the room. As he neared it, he could see balconies above with signs saying ‘Rent while you wait! 5,000 units of ectoplasm per Century. Hurry this offer must end soon’ Along from those balconies were shops and entertainment complexes, quite obviously he was going to be waiting a long time. Taking a seat in one of the (cheap might I add) burgundy seats and lent over to his left where a long wooden table covered in magazines stood. Picking one up he glanced at the cover ‘Perfect dental health’ flicking idly through the pages. He lost interest when he realised the magazine was older than he was. Murphy scanned the table for a more modern magazine, some titles leapt out at him such as: ‘Wet ‘n’ Wild Girls’ and ‘Naughty Maids Uncovered’ others such as ‘Erectile Dysfunction, what to do and when’ and ‘How to recognize when the corpse needs heating first.’ Deciding that reading was probably not the best way to pass the possibly millennium wait he just sat there idly thinking. A bit of light filtered in through the domed ceiling, it was promptly blocked by a man approaching Murphy. He was fairly tall with long hair and a fairly long beard. It was greying at parts and he had a Starbucks cinnamon bun clutched in his hand. “Mind if I sit down?”
“Free country.” Not thinking before he spoke Murphy realised that this probably wasn’t a country.
“Thanks.” They sat in relative silence for at least 5 minutes (I say relative, because the stranger was a noisy eater, you know the kind.) “So tell me a bit about yourself,” the man took another huge bite of the bun. “Well my name is Murphy and I’m dead. How ‘bout you?”
“That was extremely vague,” the stranger frowned “I’ll start and then you can try again ok?”
“Sure be my guest,” at least he wasn’t alone in this limbo. Possibly the man would be interesting. “ Well my name is José, I was born around about 2000 years ago in the little town of Bethlehem and my parents were called Mary and Joseph. Do I sound like anyone you might recognize?”
“Oh yeah some guy walked on water or some shit” Murphy said unenthusiastically, maybe solitude was better.
“You weren’t very cultured as a live person were you? You might know me as Jesus, but that book about me was a load of bullshit. A few friends of mine got a bit drunk one night at the tavern and decided it would be a good idea to sell me as an icon to twelve different people. Well as you can guess they were illiterate and extremely arrogant and my story grew until someone could be arsed to write it down and know people follow me like sheep.”
“So what did you do when you were alive?” Murphy was a little intrigued now.
“Made furniture out of wood for posh knobs at the castles and courts,” José replied.
Now Murphy was bored once again, José wasn’t that interesting. You would’ve that a global icon would at least give some good banter but quite evidently not. Maybe Ronald McDonald would be more interesting? He was a global icon and was worshipped by children everywhere. 
A thought suddenly struck Murphy; it was completely un-related to the bird dropping that had also struck him. “How long have you been waiting to go through the gates?”
“Well the ticket machine has been screwed for about 10,000 years now, either that or the idiots that run this place like tormenting me.”
“Damn it, I can’t be bothered to wait that long. I just want to get to my destination and then get severely drunk,” Murphy replied, sinking lower in his seat at this news.
“Well get in line mate, its not likely you’ll be going anywhere for some time.”&lt;/blockquote&gt;</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 24 Mar 2009 05:12:17 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>General Discussion</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/deaths-a-bitch-and-then-you-wait/251202.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Deaths a bitch and then you wait</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Ollie Ollie]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/ollie">@Ollie</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>It’s more a script than story.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/deaths-a-bitch-and-then-you-wait/251202/7">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/deaths-a-bitch-and-then-you-wait/251202/7</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 24 Mar 2009 05:12:17 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-251202-7</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/deaths-a-bitch-and-then-you-wait/251202.rss">Deaths a bitch and then you wait</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Deaths a bitch and then you wait</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@R.I.P_RSC R.I.P RSC]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/r.i.p_rsc">@R.I.P_RSC</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>There’s too much conversation going on. You need to describe the feelings of the characters, not just what they say. The problem with books are that you don’t see the characters. So you, the writer, has to describe them in such a way that the reader can imagine what they look like, and they have to be able to ‘read’ the emotions of the characters.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/deaths-a-bitch-and-then-you-wait/251202/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/deaths-a-bitch-and-then-you-wait/251202/6</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 22 Mar 2009 15:16:32 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-251202-6</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/deaths-a-bitch-and-then-you-wait/251202.rss">Deaths a bitch and then you wait</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Deaths a bitch and then you wait</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@ranger_squad ranger squad]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/ranger_squad">@ranger_squad</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“the bank, post:3, topic:251202”][quote author=ranger squad link=topic=331508.msg2715868#msg2715868 date=1237651600]<br>
Two mistakes:<br>
It says “It all looked quiet lovely” instead of “quite lovely”.<br>
And it says that José died 2000 years ago, but has been in the afterlife for 10000 years. WTF?</p>
<p>Other than that, its quite funny <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=6" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"><br>
[/quote]No, the ticket machine has been broken for 10000 years, doesn’t mean he has been there that long, someone could have told him.[/quote]</p>
<p>Oops, misread.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/deaths-a-bitch-and-then-you-wait/251202/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/deaths-a-bitch-and-then-you-wait/251202/5</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 22 Mar 2009 14:30:55 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-251202-5</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/deaths-a-bitch-and-then-you-wait/251202.rss">Deaths a bitch and then you wait</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Deaths a bitch and then you wait</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@ThAt0n36Uy Elijah]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/that0n36uy">@ThAt0n36Uy</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Way to start a novel with an incorrect spelling. Failure before it even began.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/deaths-a-bitch-and-then-you-wait/251202/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/deaths-a-bitch-and-then-you-wait/251202/4</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 22 Mar 2009 03:32:42 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-251202-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/deaths-a-bitch-and-then-you-wait/251202.rss">Deaths a bitch and then you wait</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Deaths a bitch and then you wait</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@the_bank the bank]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/the_bank">@the_bank</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“ranger squad, post:2, topic:251202”]Two mistakes:<br>
It says “It all looked quiet lovely” instead of “quite lovely”.<br>
And it says that José died 2000 years ago, but has been in the afterlife for 10000 years. WTF?</p>
<p>Other than that, its quite funny :)[/quote]No, the ticket machine has been broken for 10000 years, doesn’t mean he has been there that long, someone could have told him.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/deaths-a-bitch-and-then-you-wait/251202/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/deaths-a-bitch-and-then-you-wait/251202/3</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 21 Mar 2009 20:15:21 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-251202-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/deaths-a-bitch-and-then-you-wait/251202.rss">Deaths a bitch and then you wait</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Deaths a bitch and then you wait</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@ranger_squad ranger squad]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/ranger_squad">@ranger_squad</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Two mistakes:<br>
It says “It all looked quiet lovely” instead of “quite lovely”.<br>
And it says that José died 2000 years ago, but has been in the afterlife for 10000 years. WTF?</p>
<p>Other than that, its quite funny <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=6" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/deaths-a-bitch-and-then-you-wait/251202/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/deaths-a-bitch-and-then-you-wait/251202/2</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 21 Mar 2009 16:06:40 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-251202-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/deaths-a-bitch-and-then-you-wait/251202.rss">Deaths a bitch and then you wait</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Deaths a bitch and then you wait</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@sanga282 sanga282]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/sanga282">@sanga282</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Well this is a novel im working on for the sheer boredom that i constantly get, here is the first 3 pages of it, i’ll post more when i write more</p>
<blockquote>Dieing isn’t a particularly pleasant experience, many say it’s something to postpone at all costs. Whereas others decide that they should get it over and done with, like pulling a plaster off a hairy patch of skin. Murphy Baker had decided that dieing was definitely not for him as soon as his car had careened off the road and into to an army assault course. Naturally they had looked upon his as a terrorist and fired without command. His dieing words were: “If only my name had been Will.” That was the past as Murphy liked to think of it, a simpler time. Now however he was waiting inside his own brain, waiting for his chance to exit the current life and enter the after life. Had he not had an ounce of faith in any religion he would be very bored, but as it was, he believed mildly in Christianity. That being said he also believed in his right to party and if the two ever collided Jesus and his pals took a back seat. As his thoughts wandered wildly, the classic line “Have I left the oven on?” suddenly popped into his unconscious ramblings. He dismissed this thought quickly, what the hell did he care? He was dead. So as he flew around his own bubble of thought he decided on two things: One, that he was getting impatient and that he wished someone would come save him from his boredom. And two, he hoped the after life had a buffet, he was starving. 
The minutes passed, they eventually turned to hours and, for the sake of prolonging my poor characters boredom, then days. Finally, as Murphy was just about to start considering committing unconscious suicide to see if he could get to the second afterlife because the first was bloody boring, a light entered his bubble of thought. It steadily grew brighter and shone with an extraordinary brightness. A shadowy figure stepped from the light and reached out a hand. Disregarding all of the lessons he had learned when he was younger, Murphy grabbed the strangers hand and went on into the light. The first thing Murphy noticed was that he was now, once again, in control of his extremities. Instantly his insatiable libido starting gnawing at his mind. He quashed it and turned to see his new surroundings. It was a small box shaped room, whitewashed walls and an MDF door, also whitewashed. There was a small potted planet in the corner. Which, by the looks of things, had expired many moons ago. The stranger stood next to him. He was wearing a white suit with a golden tie. A satchel slung over one shoulder and a driver cap atop his short hair. Embroidered on the satchel was a picture of a man running and the name ‘St Peters Soul Snatchers.’ “So, you St. Peter?” asked Murphy.
“No,” snorted the man.
“Who are you then?”
“Soul Snatcher, ‘nuff said”
“Grouchy,” Murphy mumbled. The man checked his watch, he looked at the door and then stared at Murphy. “So what the hell is going on?”
“Didn’t you listen to the Herpe?” A Herpe is an informant of the afterlife, these are not to be confused with Herpes which is an STD, however to become a Herpe you must have had Herpes. 
“Normally when I get an STD I rub some cream on it and hope for the best,” the man slapped his forehead. “You dumb ass, they are instructors, not something you get from a dirty weekend in Essex.” 
“Regardless, I got neither after I died.”
“Damn Herpe relation office, they are always on strike.”
“So, I’m still none the wiser”
“Cheeky little sod you are. Basically, we, that is to say the Soul Snatchers, come and pick you up from your death, then we drop you off into the judgement room.”
“So where’s this judgement room?”
“As soon as the door flashes a white light, its time to go into the judgement room.” As if by some sort of pre-scripted magic (because you guys would never accuse me of that) the door started to flash slowly with a white light.
“That’s more of a pulse” protested Murphy.
“Like it matters.” The man kicked the door hard and watched it swing inwards. They now stood in what looked like an airport terminal. It was a huge whitewashed room with a glass domed ceiling. There were sofas dotted around and a line of booths separating the main room from a long corridor. At the booths were a bunch of tired looking men and women. There was even a Starbucks in the far corner (not satisfied with domination of the world, Starbucks decided that the moon needed at least one per crater. That still not being enough, the marketing manager committed suicide to instantly started setting up a new branch in the afterlife. What the dead did before this magical move of capitalist coffee shops we’ll never know.) It all seemed quiet lovely, all except for the queue that wound from the booths all the way around the room and then out of two corridors and came back in. There was a sign above the booths ‘Now serving numbers 9,657,230,069 – 9,658,230,069. If you one of these numbers please cue up.’ “Right you,” said the man “get a ticket and I go on my break and get some food, I am starving.” There was a ticket machine right by their door. Murphy reached for it. A women flew over with some white wings, and slapped a sign over the machine ‘Out of order, suck it.’ “Oh you mother-” the man cuffed Murphy before he could finish his abusive language. “Don’t swear in the judgement room.”
“That’s Bullshi-” the man cuffed him again.
“You don’t learn, do you?”
“What?” Murphy retorted.
“I said no swearing, you want me to start getting abusive? I will taser you if necessary.”
“No need ma brother from another mother, don’t get those knickers of yours in a twist.”
“Are you black?”
“Quite obviously not.”
“Then don’t speak as if you are,” the man cuffed Murphy again.
“Whatever, so what do I do now this ticket machine is screwed?”
“Take a seat like the rest of those people, then get a ticket when the machine is working again, savvy?”
“That’s going to take ages”
“Well your afterlife not mine, bye.” And with that the man walked off through the booths with a flash of a white passport. 
Now thoroughly miffed Murphy walked off towards a seating arrangement on the other side of the room. As he neared it, he could see balconies above with signs saying ‘Rent while you wait! 5,000 units of ectoplasm per Century. Hurry this offer must end soon’ Along from those balconies were shops and entertainment complexes, quite obviously he was going to be waiting a long time. Taking a seat in one of the (cheap might I add) burgundy seats and lent over to his left where a long wooden table covered in magazines stood. Picking one up he glanced at the cover ‘Perfect dental health’ flicking idly through the pages. He lost interest when he realised the magazine was older than he was. Murphy scanned the table for a more modern magazine, some titles leapt out at him such as: ‘Wet ‘n’ Wild Girls’ and ‘Naughty Maids Uncovered’ others such as ‘Erectile Dysfunction, what to do and when’ and ‘How to recognize when the corpse needs heating first.’ Deciding that reading was probably not the best way to pass the possibly millennium wait he just sat there idly thinking. A bit of light filtered in through the domed ceiling, it was promptly blocked by a man approaching Murphy. He was fairly tall with long hair and a fairly long beard. It was greying at parts and he had a Starbucks cinnamon bun clutched in his hand. “Mind if I sit down?”
“Free country.” Not thinking before he spoke Murphy realised that this probably wasn’t a country.
“Thanks.” They sat in relative silence for at least 5 minutes (I say relative, because the stranger was a noisy eater, you know the kind.) “So tell me a bit about yourself,” the man took another huge bite of the bun. “Well my name is Murphy and I’m dead. How ‘bout you?”
“That was extremely vague,” the stranger frowned “I’ll start and then you can try again ok?”
“Sure be my guest,” at least he wasn’t alone in this limbo. Possibly the man would be interesting. “ Well my name is José, I was born around about 2000 years ago in the little town of Bethlehem and my parents were called Mary and Joseph. Do I sound like anyone you might recognize?”
“Oh yeah some guy walked on water or some shit” Murphy said unenthusiastically, maybe solitude was better.
“You weren’t very cultured as a live person were you? You might know me as Jesus, but that book about me was a load of bullshit. A few friends of mine got a bit drunk one night at the tavern and decided it would be a good idea to sell me as an icon to twelve different people. Well as you can guess they were illiterate and extremely arrogant and my story grew until someone could be arsed to write it down and know people follow me like sheep.”
“So what did you do when you were alive?” Murphy was a little intrigued now.
“Made furniture out of wood for posh knobs at the castles and courts,” José replied.
Now Murphy was bored once again, José wasn’t that interesting. You would’ve that a global icon would at least give some good banter but quite evidently not. Maybe Ronald McDonald would be more interesting? He was a global icon and was worshipped by children everywhere. 
A thought suddenly struck Murphy; it was completely un-related to the bird dropping that had also struck him. “How long have you been waiting to go through the gates?”
“Well the ticket machine has been screwed for about 10,000 years now, either that or the idiots that run this place like tormenting me.”
“Damn it, I can’t be bothered to wait that long. I just want to get to my destination and then get severely drunk,” Murphy replied, sinking lower in his seat at this news.
“Well get in line mate, its not likely you’ll be going anywhere for some time.”</blockquote>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/deaths-a-bitch-and-then-you-wait/251202/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/deaths-a-bitch-and-then-you-wait/251202/1</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2008 17:39:38 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-251202-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/deaths-a-bitch-and-then-you-wait/251202.rss">Deaths a bitch and then you wait</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
