<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>508 Big tips/help need</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/508-big-tips-help-need/308386</link>
    <description>1.There Is a  big magic/attack bug in my server! you can attack people with magic in wild. even if you jump the ditch in edgeville and be in safe your still able to mage them. with melee and range you can&#39;t do them. it will say your not able to attack person in safe!
2. my server is a pking server with spawing. some people want to also train skills in there! and in quest list if your a starter a option called &quot;master&quot; will appears, how can i make it so that only it only levels up attack strength defence range mage prayer and summoning? when you click master it will disconnect and you have to relog.
3.my stupid server autorestarter is not functioning! please help me! when ever i come back i see it like always dced and players can&#39;t move![br][br][size=1]Posted on: October 13, 2009, 04:50:01 pm[/size][hr]4. How Do i Fix Friends List And Ingore List! When You Relog, It Deletes Everyone In The list![br][br][size=1]Posted on: October 13, 2009, 05:02:21 pm[/size][hr]omg i answered everyones  question but no1 can answer mine :(</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 13 Oct 2009 22:13:27 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/508-big-tips-help-need/308386.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>508 Big tips/help need</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@sonicforce41 sonicforce41]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/sonicforce41">@sonicforce41</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>1.There Is a  big magic/attack bug in my server! you can attack people with magic in wild. even if you jump the ditch in edgeville and be in safe your still able to mage them. with melee and range you can’t do them. it will say your not able to attack person in safe!<br>
2. my server is a pking server with spawing. some people want to also train skills in there! and in quest list if your a starter a option called “master” will appears, how can i make it so that only it only levels up attack strength defence range mage prayer and summoning? when you click master it will disconnect and you have to relog.<br>
3.my stupid server autorestarter is not functioning! please help me! when ever i come back i see it like always dced and players can’t move![br][br][size=1]Posted on: October 13, 2009, 04:50:01 pm[/size][hr]4. How Do i Fix Friends List And Ingore List! When You Relog, It Deletes Everyone In The list![br][br][size=1]Posted on: October 13, 2009, 05:02:21 pm[/size][hr]omg i answered everyones  question but no1 can answer mine <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/frowning.png?v=5" title=":frowning:" class="emoji" alt=":frowning:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/508-big-tips-help-need/308386/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/508-big-tips-help-need/308386/1</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 13 Oct 2009 22:13:27 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-308386-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/508-big-tips-help-need/308386.rss">508 Big tips/help need</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
