<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Guthans || Quality || Oldschool||ECO/PK ||</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/guthans-quality-oldschool-eco-pk/549268</link>
    <description>[center][img]http://guthans.com/forums/images/logo.png[/img]

[u][b]Quick Links:[/b][/u]
[img]http://i.imgur.com/9eAt7MP.png[/img][url=http://www.guthans.com/forums]Forums[/url]
[img]http://i.imgur.com/fC6mT3t.png[/img][url=http://guthans.com/forums/pages.php?page=play]Play Webclient[/url]
[img]http://cdn2.iconfinder.com/data/icons/splashyIcons/download.png[/img][url=http://www.guthans.com/Launcher.jar]Download Launcher[/url]
[img]http://www.tradearcadepro.com/images/CheckIconSmall.png[/img][url=http://guthans.com/forums/pages.php?page=vote]Vote[/url]

[B]Introduction[/B]
Hello And welcome to my project thread guys and I am going to start a new project that is based on skill
You know how on runescape you get these items like fire cape. Takes a few hours to get that fire cape and when you do get it you&#39;re awesome yea. I&#39;m going to be starting a project Where you can&#39;t just easily obtain your so-called power (virtues, bandos etc. etc.) you need to gain your power, almost like gaining a fire cape, the hard long hours of doing jad, he is strong. You need to be slightly skilled at praying if you know what I mean. Gaining the powerful items, boss killing, quests, pking, Mini Games. The items we&#39;re going to be adding to our server And when i say our server I mean the community&#39;s server. Are going to be all based on what our server community wants. So this server will be skilful. Skilful players will have the best items. Money will be used a different way. Make it so everyone can gain these items. Might take awhile, if you&#39;re a dedicated gamer you will get all these items.

[B]Economy[/B]

Servers nowadays have items worth &#39;10b&#39; you don&#39;t get that amount of cash so my economy plans will be very worked out. How I am planning the economy is low cash rates. Hard to get cash but a lot of this will be cheap. Shops will only have a limited supply of the product like runes. 
Rares will be the most expensive items along with other Armours you can sell.
all the powerful weapons/armour is  tradeable and will be gained with skill and long hours of combat or quests.
Some of the top class items will possibly degrade. Chaotics, torva etc. but will take a long time to degrade, you will be able to repair them at a price from a npc like the infamous Bob.
There will be donor only items like a XP boost ring or something along the lines, I really don&#39;t want to see donators have a huge advantage.
Upto Barrows will be sellable Just need a few suggestions

[B]Gameplay[/B]

Quest will become ideal but for now, Won&#39;t be any added. All skills will be added to help bring the economy up. You will have the choice of picking your xp rates, 4 modes or 5 each giving a unique ability. Player titles just to make the game that bit nicer.
Daily updates to make the players entertained
A grand and excellent slayer system. A lot of us love slayer and doing slayer brings good money.
Excellent features like working ring of wealth etc..
I think I may be adding in a prestige system. Some items require a certain prestige to wear. Only for certain game modes, for example the easiest game mode I will require 5th prestige to wear torva, on hardest I don&#39;t require any prestige. This is to keep the players a goal to become something of themselves cause honestly, If the game doesn&#39;t have something to keep the players occupied then why play?

[B]Pvm[/B]


There will be countless bosses. Most unique and adapted to their environment e.g. Spawning minions.
Countless monsters over the world to gain items
Bosses will Give you a good challenge, Some easy, Some hard.
Single and Multi Bosses. Bosses to make you want to practically rage quit but not exactly.
Monster drops for every NPC from a single rat to bandos will be coded like-wise to RS but easier, with a touch of guthans to fit the gameplay.
There will be a wide variety of monster to choose from, Especially the slayer monsters. You will require to wear the correct equipment when fighting The NPC, If you do not wear They either - Hit higher or you can&#39;t attack them altogether or well you would of wished you did..

[B]Pvp[/B]

Player vs player will be the most worked on. People will be Pking in all sorts of gear due to the &#39;can&#39;t buy power&#39; this will give Pking a great advantage to everyone, if you&#39;re rich you can buy armour to Pk but them items will hopefully be hard to obtain or a challenge. So everyone is fair, Cause really, Spending money on a game to get a good advantage isn&#39;t much fair. Killing will get you Pk points which could lead to good rewards ofc.
The combat system will be redone to Your standards of the players.

[B]Skilling[/B]

Skilling will now become useful and will be a main part of the eco system for all players to have. It will help with mainly Bringing a better economy like crafting Dragon bolts (e) For pkers to buy, Fishing food to sell and make profits. It will actually be useful on a private server for one. Each skill will become a key part of the game either for quests or money making.
[/CENTER]

Features:
- Flawless skills, excluding Agility and Farming
- Perfect Duel Arena
- Custom Barrows Minigame
- Custom PK system where you can turn in your PK Points for various rewards
- Friendly Staff and Active staff from all over the globe.
- Hundreds of PVM and PVP opportunities with countless rewards
- Custom Whips Including Lava and Lime whip
- Perfect PKing with flawless switching and perfect hybriding
- Clans in Single and Multi
- Every working special attack you can think of
- Quick, Fast, Reliable auto donation system
- Custom Donator Islands with lots of helpful donation perks!
- MYBB Forums
-Custom Wilderness teleports</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2015 04:06:27 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/guthans-quality-oldschool-eco-pk/549268.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Guthans || Quality || Oldschool||ECO/PK ||</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@stCky stCky]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/stcky">@stCky</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Wooo GuthixScape! Looking cool as buddo.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/guthans-quality-oldschool-eco-pk/549268/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/guthans-quality-oldschool-eco-pk/549268/5</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2015 04:06:27 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-549268-5</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/guthans-quality-oldschool-eco-pk/549268.rss">Guthans || Quality || Oldschool||ECO/PK ||</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Guthans || Quality || Oldschool||ECO/PK ||</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@GuthansRSPS GuthansRSPS]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/guthansrsps">@GuthansRSPS</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Bump for our server!</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/guthans-quality-oldschool-eco-pk/549268/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/guthans-quality-oldschool-eco-pk/549268/4</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2015 02:55:26 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-549268-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/guthans-quality-oldschool-eco-pk/549268.rss">Guthans || Quality || Oldschool||ECO/PK ||</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Guthans || Quality || Oldschool||ECO/PK ||</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@pk99ranger1 pk99ranger1]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/pk99ranger1">@pk99ranger1</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Love the Server!</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/guthans-quality-oldschool-eco-pk/549268/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/guthans-quality-oldschool-eco-pk/549268/3</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2015 13:20:27 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-549268-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/guthans-quality-oldschool-eco-pk/549268.rss">Guthans || Quality || Oldschool||ECO/PK ||</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Guthans || Quality || Oldschool||ECO/PK ||</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Ix_Soulcist_xI Soulcist]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/ix_soulcist_xi">@Ix_Soulcist_xI</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Add some media that would attract a player base that you would want. Not many people are going to download the cache, wait the extra time to do so and then log in to explore.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/guthans-quality-oldschool-eco-pk/549268/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/guthans-quality-oldschool-eco-pk/549268/2</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2015 06:38:47 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-549268-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/guthans-quality-oldschool-eco-pk/549268.rss">Guthans || Quality || Oldschool||ECO/PK ||</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Guthans || Quality || Oldschool||ECO/PK ||</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@GuthansRSPS GuthansRSPS]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/guthansrsps">@GuthansRSPS</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[center]<img src="http://guthans.com/forums/images/logo.png" alt width="" height=""></p>
<p><span class="bbcode-u"><span class="bbcode-b">Quick Links:</span></span><br>
<img src="http://i.imgur.com/9eAt7MP.png" alt width="" height=""><a href="http://www.guthans.com/forums" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">Forums</a><br>
<img src="http://i.imgur.com/fC6mT3t.png" alt width="" height=""><a href="http://guthans.com/forums/pages.php?page=play" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">Play Webclient</a><br>
<img src="http://cdn2.iconfinder.com/data/icons/splashyIcons/download.png" alt width="" height=""><a href="http://www.guthans.com/Launcher.jar" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">Download Launcher</a><br>
<img src="http://www.tradearcadepro.com/images/CheckIconSmall.png" alt width="" height=""><a href="http://guthans.com/forums/pages.php?page=vote" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">Vote</a></p>
<p>[B]Introduction[/B]<br>
Hello And welcome to my project thread guys and I am going to start a new project that is based on skill<br>
You know how on runescape you get these items like fire cape. Takes a few hours to get that fire cape and when you do get it you’re awesome yea. I’m going to be starting a project Where you can’t just easily obtain your so-called power (virtues, bandos etc. etc.) you need to gain your power, almost like gaining a fire cape, the hard long hours of doing jad, he is strong. You need to be slightly skilled at praying if you know what I mean. Gaining the powerful items, boss killing, quests, pking, Mini Games. The items we’re going to be adding to our server And when i say our server I mean the community’s server. Are going to be all based on what our server community wants. So this server will be skilful. Skilful players will have the best items. Money will be used a different way. Make it so everyone can gain these items. Might take awhile, if you’re a dedicated gamer you will get all these items.</p>
<p>[B]Economy[/B]</p>
<p>Servers nowadays have items worth ‘10b’ you don’t get that amount of cash so my economy plans will be very worked out. How I am planning the economy is low cash rates. Hard to get cash but a lot of this will be cheap. Shops will only have a limited supply of the product like runes.<br>
Rares will be the most expensive items along with other Armours you can sell.<br>
all the powerful weapons/armour is  tradeable and will be gained with skill and long hours of combat or quests.<br>
Some of the top class items will possibly degrade. Chaotics, torva etc. but will take a long time to degrade, you will be able to repair them at a price from a npc like the infamous Bob.<br>
There will be donor only items like a XP boost ring or something along the lines, I really don’t want to see donators have a huge advantage.<br>
Upto Barrows will be sellable Just need a few suggestions</p>
<p>[B]Gameplay[/B]</p>
<p>Quest will become ideal but for now, Won’t be any added. All skills will be added to help bring the economy up. You will have the choice of picking your xp rates, 4 modes or 5 each giving a unique ability. Player titles just to make the game that bit nicer.<br>
Daily updates to make the players entertained<br>
A grand and excellent slayer system. A lot of us love slayer and doing slayer brings good money.<br>
Excellent features like working ring of wealth etc…<br>
I think I may be adding in a prestige system. Some items require a certain prestige to wear. Only for certain game modes, for example the easiest game mode I will require 5th prestige to wear torva, on hardest I don’t require any prestige. This is to keep the players a goal to become something of themselves cause honestly, If the game doesn’t have something to keep the players occupied then why play?</p>
<p>[B]Pvm[/B]</p>
<p>There will be countless bosses. Most unique and adapted to their environment e.g. Spawning minions.<br>
Countless monsters over the world to gain items<br>
Bosses will Give you a good challenge, Some easy, Some hard.<br>
Single and Multi Bosses. Bosses to make you want to practically rage quit but not exactly.<br>
Monster drops for every NPC from a single rat to bandos will be coded like-wise to RS but easier, with a touch of guthans to fit the gameplay.<br>
There will be a wide variety of monster to choose from, Especially the slayer monsters. You will require to wear the correct equipment when fighting The NPC, If you do not wear They either - Hit higher or you can’t attack them altogether or well you would of wished you did…</p>
<p>[B]Pvp[/B]</p>
<p>Player vs player will be the most worked on. People will be Pking in all sorts of gear due to the ‘can’t buy power’ this will give Pking a great advantage to everyone, if you’re rich you can buy armour to Pk but them items will hopefully be hard to obtain or a challenge. So everyone is fair, Cause really, Spending money on a game to get a good advantage isn’t much fair. Killing will get you Pk points which could lead to good rewards ofc.<br>
The combat system will be redone to Your standards of the players.</p>
<p>[B]Skilling[/B]</p>
<p>Skilling will now become useful and will be a main part of the eco system for all players to have. It will help with mainly Bringing a better economy like crafting Dragon bolts (e) For pkers to buy, Fishing food to sell and make profits. It will actually be useful on a private server for one. Each skill will become a key part of the game either for quests or money making.<br>
[/CENTER]</p>
<p>Features:</p>
<ul>
<li>Flawless skills, excluding Agility and Farming</li>
<li>Perfect Duel Arena</li>
<li>Custom Barrows Minigame</li>
<li>Custom PK system where you can turn in your PK Points for various rewards</li>
<li>Friendly Staff and Active staff from all over the globe.</li>
<li>Hundreds of PVM and PVP opportunities with countless rewards</li>
<li>Custom Whips Including Lava and Lime whip</li>
<li>Perfect PKing with flawless switching and perfect hybriding</li>
<li>Clans in Single and Multi</li>
<li>Every working special attack you can think of</li>
<li>Quick, Fast, Reliable auto donation system</li>
<li>Custom Donator Islands with lots of helpful donation perks!</li>
<li>MYBB Forums<br>
-Custom Wilderness teleports</li>
</ul>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/guthans-quality-oldschool-eco-pk/549268/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/guthans-quality-oldschool-eco-pk/549268/1</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2015 05:18:25 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-549268-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/guthans-quality-oldschool-eco-pk/549268.rss">Guthans || Quality || Oldschool||ECO/PK ||</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
