<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Fallout: New Vegas and my thoughts</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/fallout-new-vegas-and-my-thoughts/365487</link>
    <description>[center][img]http://img163.imageshack.us/img163/7854/falloutbanner0days.png[/img]
[/center]October 19, Fallout: New Vegas, a game developed by Obsidian Entertainment was released. Another game in one of the greatest RPG series of all time. This game features many changes such as the ability to look down the iron sights of your gun, a feature that the previous game, Fallout 3, lacked. There is many other interesting additions such as creation of chems, foods, and ammunition, rather than relying on the wasteland and creatures for your items.

[center][url=http://img254.imageshack.us/img254/5209/screen22b.jpg][img]http://img513.imageshack.us/img513/9267/screen22s.jpg[/img] [/url][url=http://img705.imageshack.us/img705/9320/screen21b.jpg][img]http://img713.imageshack.us/img713/7689/screen21s.jpg[/img] [/url][url=http://img145.imageshack.us/img145/5540/screen20b.jpg][img]http://img829.imageshack.us/img829/228/screen20s.jpg[/img][/url]
[url=http://img94.imageshack.us/img94/4480/screen19b.jpg][img]http://img832.imageshack.us/img832/1042/screen19s.jpg[/img] [/url][url=http://img835.imageshack.us/img835/1452/screen18b.jpg][img]http://img225.imageshack.us/img225/6028/screen18s.jpg[/img] [/url][url=http://img257.imageshack.us/img257/4857/screen17b.jpg][img]http://img257.imageshack.us/img257/8471/screen17s.jpg[/img][/url]
[/center][u]
My review[/u]

I think the game could have been great. I don&#39;t believe in sequels having to be &#39;bigger and better&#39; than their previous title. This game is alright overall, but not anything special. The voice acting sounds like a gargling asshole filtered with the moist cloth of a thousand orphan tears. It&#39;s worse than Fallout 3&#39;s (where every character was voiced by like three dudes).

The iron sights are nothing to look forward to, they are just a let-down; when you go to look down the sight of your gun, your hand teleports to the middle of the screen and when you release the sights, it displays a smooth animation of your hand going back to it&#39;s regular position on the screen. Why is this? Did they not check this game for quality? It feels like I&#39;m playing Fallout 3 with a shitty iron sight mod. The sad thing is, iron sight mods for Fallout 3 are better than the iron sights included in this game.

Ammo creation is alright, but it&#39;s unorganized in a way that you can easily mess up and end up losing ammunition. Basically it&#39;s just a big unfiltered list of names. Examples of the list could be &quot;9mm ammo&quot; and &quot;Breakdown 9mm ammo.&quot; A new player isn&#39;t going to understand what the fuck this means, and nobody reads the damn help. It should be user-friendly. At first I thought &quot;Breakdown 9mm ammo&quot; was some sort of hardcore 9mm ammo, but no, I just ended up breaking open some bullets, getting some resources and then make 9mm ammo again, except less. The menu is confusing also because you can&#39;t click on any of the lit up options, you have to hover over it, and then press the accept button. Why can&#39;t I just click the goddamn option, is it really necessary for me to precisely hover over it and then click accept?

I don&#39;t have much to say about chem/food creation. To me it&#39;s not particularly useful. Maybe it is in hardcore mode, I haven&#39;t tried. From the looks of it, it is just like the ammo creation interface and you can make stuff like cooked gecko hide steak. Cool story bra.

The new weapons are crap, they left in older weapons, but added new weapons that do not match the old ones. For example, there is a 9mm pistol that actually looks like a damn pistol from our time and the 10mm pistol from Fallout 3 that looks like a futuristic handgun. It feels like they slapped together this game rather quickly and it just doesn&#39;t work. Modding weapons is sloppy, to mod your weapon you buy the part from people throughout the game and then go into your Pipboy&#39;s weapon menu, find the weapon you want to mod, hover over it, and press the mod key (default X on PC) and then select the part. It&#39;s very uncreative and I wouldn&#39;t doubt that there is a mod for Fallout 3 that adds this feature much better than this.

The storyline is uninteresting and just overall boring. Shot in the head, and now you want to find this fucker and shake hands with him? The only thing I really like about this game is the character Victor. He&#39;s a cowboy robot and extremely friendly. Seriously, out of this entire game, that is the thing I enjoy the most.

The intro to the game is worse than Fallout 3&#39;s. First you wake up in a creepy dude&#39;s house and he starts talking to you. It&#39;s like he raped you while sleeping. Do you remember the GOAT exam from Fallout 3? Well the quiz is even worse. You just reply with retarded responses &quot;Smelly cheese.&quot; You can just select random shit and choose your tag skills afterward, like the GOAT exam. He has a mustache.

Fallout: New Vegas is bug ridden, even worse than Fallout 3. More crashes to desktop on PC, and they actually managed to fuck up the &quot;Continue&quot; button on the intro screen sadly enough. NPCs around the world can randomly fly through roofs, and [url=http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ToKIkw3LIoQ]heads can go into exorcist mode and start spinning around[/url]. Walking paths are also messed up and creatures get stuck in boulders.

Overall, I&#39;m just going to go back to Fallout 3 and play it over and over until the next game comes out. Maybe it won&#39;t be made by careless dicks.



What did you guys think of New Vegas?</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 23 Oct 2010 02:39:33 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>General Discussion</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/fallout-new-vegas-and-my-thoughts/365487.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Fallout: New Vegas and my thoughts</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@krackkid Krackkid]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/krackkid">@krackkid</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“Errorist, post:7, topic:365487”][quote author=krackkid link=topic=461687.msg3377512#msg3377512 date=1287758737]<br>
I still am waiting to get o.o, I don’t got the money for it right now. But I will be getting for the 360 I know fallout was always bad on computers from what I heard. I will make a honest review when I get it.<br>
[/quote]<br>
If you didn’t play Fallout 2 in the 90’s then you can’t say it was a bad game. Same goes for Warcraft 1 and 2.[/quote]What the fuck are you on about? I said <span class="bbcode-b">from what I heard</span>, I didn’t say I think there bad.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/fallout-new-vegas-and-my-thoughts/365487/9">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/fallout-new-vegas-and-my-thoughts/365487/9</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 23 Oct 2010 02:39:33 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-365487-9</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/fallout-new-vegas-and-my-thoughts/365487.rss">Fallout: New Vegas and my thoughts</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Fallout: New Vegas and my thoughts</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Frell Frell]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/frell">@Frell</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“Errorist, post:7, topic:365487”][quote author=krackkid link=topic=461687.msg3377512#msg3377512 date=1287758737]<br>
I still am waiting to get o.o, I don’t got the money for it right now. But I will be getting for the 360 I know fallout was always bad on computers from what I heard. I will make a honest review when I get it.<br>
[/quote]<br>
If you didn’t play Fallout 2 in the 90’s then you can’t say it was a bad game. Same goes for Warcraft 1 and 2.[/quote]<br>
Wasnt bad, just not popular.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/fallout-new-vegas-and-my-thoughts/365487/8">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/fallout-new-vegas-and-my-thoughts/365487/8</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 23 Oct 2010 02:18:56 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-365487-8</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/fallout-new-vegas-and-my-thoughts/365487.rss">Fallout: New Vegas and my thoughts</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Fallout: New Vegas and my thoughts</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Errorist Errorist]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/errorist">@Errorist</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote no-group quote-modified" data-post="2" data-topic="365487">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/krackkid/40/5_1887921562df0dabfae55079ddabeb03.png" class="avatar"> krackkid:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>I still am waiting to get o.o, I don’t got the money for it right now. But I will be getting for the 360 I know fallout was always bad on computers from what I heard. I will make a honest review when I get it.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>If you didn’t play Fallout 2 in the 90’s then you can’t say it was a bad game. Same goes for Warcraft 1 and 2.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/fallout-new-vegas-and-my-thoughts/365487/7">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/fallout-new-vegas-and-my-thoughts/365487/7</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 23 Oct 2010 01:57:57 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-365487-7</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/fallout-new-vegas-and-my-thoughts/365487.rss">Fallout: New Vegas and my thoughts</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Fallout: New Vegas and my thoughts</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Ix_Soulcist_xI Soulcist]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/ix_soulcist_xi">@Ix_Soulcist_xI</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>At least there not quiting. As far as Fallout series, I didn’t like the series because I thought there was a lot of talking which made me bored after awhile.</p>
<p>Fallout 3 was the time I played the game and it bored me, nothing was interesting to me. Friend thinks I should attempt to try out the new one; I don’t want to but I’m going to give it a chance.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/fallout-new-vegas-and-my-thoughts/365487/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/fallout-new-vegas-and-my-thoughts/365487/6</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 22 Oct 2010 22:47:13 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-365487-6</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/fallout-new-vegas-and-my-thoughts/365487.rss">Fallout: New Vegas and my thoughts</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Fallout: New Vegas and my thoughts</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Frell Frell]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/frell">@Frell</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“T3arful, post:4, topic:365487”][quote author=Frell link=topic=461687.msg3377571#msg3377571 date=1287767104]<br>
This game vegas was NEVER hit by any nukes, yet everything is still blown up…? I guess no repairs to infrastructure could cause this but eh.<br>
[/quote]<br>
As far as I know, only the actual Vegas area wasn’t effected by a nuke, the areas outside of Vegas were effected.[/quote]<br>
Thats what i thought, but it isnt true. They might aswell call the game Faction Wars - Vegas</p>
<blockquote>Written by John Gonzalez,[10] Fallout: New Vegas takes place during the year 2281, four years after the estimated end of Fallout 3, and 204 years after the Great War of 2077, making this installment chronologically the latest in the series thus far.[11] The game is set in post-apocalyptic Las Vegas, Nevada and the Mojave Desert known as the "Mojave Wasteland" which is roughly the same size as the "Capital Wasteland" in Fallout 3.[11] Unlike other cities in the Fallout series, [b]Las Vegas was not struck directly by a nuclear attack. Its buildings remain intact, and mutation of its inhabitants is minimal.[/b][11] The city is divided between various factions, most notably the New California Republic (NCR), the slave-driving Caesar's Legion, and the various factions of New Vegas itself.[9][12] Landmarks featured in Fallout: New Vegas include the Hoover Dam that supplies power to the city[12] and the Helios 1 solar energy plant.[13]</blockquote>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/fallout-new-vegas-and-my-thoughts/365487/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/fallout-new-vegas-and-my-thoughts/365487/5</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 22 Oct 2010 19:54:56 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-365487-5</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/fallout-new-vegas-and-my-thoughts/365487.rss">Fallout: New Vegas and my thoughts</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Fallout: New Vegas and my thoughts</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@T3arful T3arful]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/t3arful">@T3arful</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>At the moment, the game is very buggy. The console versions have performance issues at the moment, and yeah, it does seem as if it was just slapped together really quickly, but it’s biting them on the ass because they’re having to hurry up and patch all the bugs.</p>
<p>I just got it today, and I think it’s okay, though I haven’t played it enough to be able to write a proper opinion about it.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group quote-modified" data-post="3" data-topic="365487">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/frell/40/5_1887921562df0dabfae55079ddabeb03.png" class="avatar"> Frell:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>This game vegas was NEVER hit by any nukes, yet everything is still blown up…? I guess no repairs to infrastructure could cause this but eh.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>As far as I know, only the actual Vegas area wasn’t effected by a nuke, the areas outside of Vegas were effected.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/fallout-new-vegas-and-my-thoughts/365487/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/fallout-new-vegas-and-my-thoughts/365487/4</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 22 Oct 2010 18:27:01 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-365487-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/fallout-new-vegas-and-my-thoughts/365487.rss">Fallout: New Vegas and my thoughts</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Fallout: New Vegas and my thoughts</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Frell Frell]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/frell">@Frell</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Its pretty decent, but it lacks what i loved about fallout 3 so much. The fact that DC was nuked, walking around was like “oshit look at the washington monument… damn”. This game vegas was NEVER hit by any nukes, yet everything is still blown up…? I guess no repairs to infrastructure could cause this but eh.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group quote-modified" data-post="1" data-topic="365487">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/kihomura/40/5_1887921562df0dabfae55079ddabeb03.png" class="avatar"> Kihomura:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>The new weapons are crap, they left in older weapons, but added new weapons that do not match the old ones. For example, there is a 9mm pistol that actually looks like a damn pistol from our time and the 10mm pistol from Fallout 3 that looks like a futuristic handgun. It feels like they slapped together this game rather quickly and it just doesn’t work. Modding weapons is sloppy, to mod your weapon you buy the part from people throughout the game and then go into your Pipboy’s weapon menu, find the weapon you want to mod, hover over it, and press the mod key (default X on PC) and then select the part. It’s very uncreative and I wouldn’t doubt that there is a mod for Fallout 3 that adds this feature much better than this.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>They got the weapon mod idea from over at nexus.</p>
<p>Remember, Bethesda has been developing Fallout 4 (cant wait) since Fallout 3 ended, and Obsidian (known for making games that look unfinished and are glitchy) Made Fallout New Vegas at the same time. People thought new vegas would be better because “its da serm ppl dat made first 2” No it isnt, just 2 people that manage the team were from the first games.</p>
<p>Oh yea, and the map being “roughly” as big as fallout 3? Bullshit. I dont know how these people could be so proud of such a shit game. Had Fallout 3 not been such a success they wouldnt have dick money (good thing bethesda got most of it). I hope this lump of horse shit doesnt hurt Fallout 4’s rep, which i think will be in NY btw.</p>
<p>I would go back to Fallout 3… but ive played through it so much that i cant think of anything worth doing and i get bored in a few minutes.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/fallout-new-vegas-and-my-thoughts/365487/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/fallout-new-vegas-and-my-thoughts/365487/3</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 22 Oct 2010 17:05:04 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-365487-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/fallout-new-vegas-and-my-thoughts/365487.rss">Fallout: New Vegas and my thoughts</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Fallout: New Vegas and my thoughts</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@krackkid Krackkid]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/krackkid">@krackkid</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I still am waiting to get o.o, I don’t got the money for it right now. But I will be getting for the 360 I know fallout was always bad on computers from what I heard. I will make a honest review when I get it.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/fallout-new-vegas-and-my-thoughts/365487/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/fallout-new-vegas-and-my-thoughts/365487/2</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 22 Oct 2010 14:45:37 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-365487-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/fallout-new-vegas-and-my-thoughts/365487.rss">Fallout: New Vegas and my thoughts</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Fallout: New Vegas and my thoughts</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@kihomura Kihomura]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/kihomura">@kihomura</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[center]<img src="http://img163.imageshack.us/img163/7854/falloutbanner0days.png" alt width="" height=""><br>
[/center]October 19, Fallout: New Vegas, a game developed by Obsidian Entertainment was released. Another game in one of the greatest RPG series of all time. This game features many changes such as the ability to look down the iron sights of your gun, a feature that the previous game, Fallout 3, lacked. There is many other interesting additions such as creation of chems, foods, and ammunition, rather than relying on the wasteland and creatures for your items.</p>
<p>[center]<a href="http://img254.imageshack.us/img254/5209/screen22b.jpg" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener"><img src="http://img513.imageshack.us/img513/9267/screen22s.jpg" alt width="" height=""> </a><a href="http://img705.imageshack.us/img705/9320/screen21b.jpg" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener"><img src="http://img713.imageshack.us/img713/7689/screen21s.jpg" alt width="" height=""> </a><a href="http://img145.imageshack.us/img145/5540/screen20b.jpg" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener"><img src="http://img829.imageshack.us/img829/228/screen20s.jpg" alt width="" height=""></a><br>
<a href="http://img94.imageshack.us/img94/4480/screen19b.jpg" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener"><img src="http://img832.imageshack.us/img832/1042/screen19s.jpg" alt width="" height=""> </a><a href="http://img835.imageshack.us/img835/1452/screen18b.jpg" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener"><img src="http://img225.imageshack.us/img225/6028/screen18s.jpg" alt width="" height=""> </a><a href="http://img257.imageshack.us/img257/4857/screen17b.jpg" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener"><img src="http://img257.imageshack.us/img257/8471/screen17s.jpg" alt width="" height=""></a><br>
[/center]<span class="bbcode-u"><br>
My review</span></p>
<p>I think the game could have been great. I don’t believe in sequels having to be ‘bigger and better’ than their previous title. This game is alright overall, but not anything special. The voice acting sounds like a gargling asshole filtered with the moist cloth of a thousand orphan tears. It’s worse than Fallout 3’s (where every character was voiced by like three dudes).</p>
<p>The iron sights are nothing to look forward to, they are just a let-down; when you go to look down the sight of your gun, your hand teleports to the middle of the screen and when you release the sights, it displays a smooth animation of your hand going back to it’s regular position on the screen. Why is this? Did they not check this game for quality? It feels like I’m playing Fallout 3 with a shitty iron sight mod. The sad thing is, iron sight mods for Fallout 3 are better than the iron sights included in this game.</p>
<p>Ammo creation is alright, but it’s unorganized in a way that you can easily mess up and end up losing ammunition. Basically it’s just a big unfiltered list of names. Examples of the list could be “9mm ammo” and “Breakdown 9mm ammo.” A new player isn’t going to understand what the fuck this means, and nobody reads the damn help. It should be user-friendly. At first I thought “Breakdown 9mm ammo” was some sort of hardcore 9mm ammo, but no, I just ended up breaking open some bullets, getting some resources and then make 9mm ammo again, except less. The menu is confusing also because you can’t click on any of the lit up options, you have to hover over it, and then press the accept button. Why can’t I just click the goddamn option, is it really necessary for me to precisely hover over it and then click accept?</p>
<p>I don’t have much to say about chem/food creation. To me it’s not particularly useful. Maybe it is in hardcore mode, I haven’t tried. From the looks of it, it is just like the ammo creation interface and you can make stuff like cooked gecko hide steak. Cool story bra.</p>
<p>The new weapons are crap, they left in older weapons, but added new weapons that do not match the old ones. For example, there is a 9mm pistol that actually looks like a damn pistol from our time and the 10mm pistol from Fallout 3 that looks like a futuristic handgun. It feels like they slapped together this game rather quickly and it just doesn’t work. Modding weapons is sloppy, to mod your weapon you buy the part from people throughout the game and then go into your Pipboy’s weapon menu, find the weapon you want to mod, hover over it, and press the mod key (default X on PC) and then select the part. It’s very uncreative and I wouldn’t doubt that there is a mod for Fallout 3 that adds this feature much better than this.</p>
<p>The storyline is uninteresting and just overall boring. Shot in the head, and now you want to find this fucker and shake hands with him? The only thing I really like about this game is the character Victor. He’s a cowboy robot and extremely friendly. Seriously, out of this entire game, that is the thing I enjoy the most.</p>
<p>The intro to the game is worse than Fallout 3’s. First you wake up in a creepy dude’s house and he starts talking to you. It’s like he raped you while sleeping. Do you remember the GOAT exam from Fallout 3? Well the quiz is even worse. You just reply with retarded responses “Smelly cheese.” You can just select random shit and choose your tag skills afterward, like the GOAT exam. He has a mustache.</p>
<p>Fallout: New Vegas is bug ridden, even worse than Fallout 3. More crashes to desktop on PC, and they actually managed to fuck up the “Continue” button on the intro screen sadly enough. NPCs around the world can randomly fly through roofs, and <a href="http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ToKIkw3LIoQ" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">heads can go into exorcist mode and start spinning around</a>. Walking paths are also messed up and creatures get stuck in boulders.</p>
<p>Overall, I’m just going to go back to Fallout 3 and play it over and over until the next game comes out. Maybe it won’t be made by careless dicks.</p>
<p>What did you guys think of New Vegas?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/fallout-new-vegas-and-my-thoughts/365487/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/fallout-new-vegas-and-my-thoughts/365487/1</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 22 Oct 2010 14:01:19 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-365487-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/fallout-new-vegas-and-my-thoughts/365487.rss">Fallout: New Vegas and my thoughts</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
