<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>[Hyperion] NPC Combat</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/hyperion-npc-combat/462713</link>
    <description>I have a good player versus player system (using [url=http://www.rune-server.org/runescape-development/google/downloads/305655-hyperion-perfect-oldschool-base.html]this[/url] source), but no player versus NPC combat. I have just loaded up NPCs because it didn&#39;t come with the base, but I need to know how difficult it would be to implement attacking an NPC with regards to the fact I already have a good PVP combat system.

I&#39;ve never been able to do combat in any server. Is it a matter of changing a couple of things or do you have to have one system for players and a whole new system for NPCs? It&#39;s entity based so I assume it&#39;s a matter of telling the server what to do when you click the attack packet and that is it? Just need some insight before I dive in.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 01 Oct 2012 02:47:17 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/hyperion-npc-combat/462713.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>[Hyperion] NPC Combat</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Broken_Britain Broken Britain]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/broken_britain">@Broken_Britain</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I have a good player versus player system (using <a href="http://www.rune-server.org/runescape-development/google/downloads/305655-hyperion-perfect-oldschool-base.html" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">this</a> source), but no player versus NPC combat. I have just loaded up NPCs because it didn’t come with the base, but I need to know how difficult it would be to implement attacking an NPC with regards to the fact I already have a good PVP combat system.</p>
<p>I’ve never been able to do combat in any server. Is it a matter of changing a couple of things or do you have to have one system for players and a whole new system for NPCs? It’s entity based so I assume it’s a matter of telling the server what to do when you click the attack packet and that is it? Just need some insight before I dive in.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/hyperion-npc-combat/462713/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/hyperion-npc-combat/462713/1</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 01 Oct 2012 02:47:17 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-462713-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/hyperion-npc-combat/462713.rss">[Hyperion] NPC Combat</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
