<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Minecraft - How to edit the Client/Server!</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/minecraft-how-to-edit-the-client-server/405241</link>
    <description>Hey guys and gals,

I have always lurked these forums, and never really made any DECENT posts. So i decided to give you all some information that may be very handy in your Minecraft server/client development =)

What I will be explaining today is how to edit the constant pool of a class file without any vast knowledge of BCEL, or other forms of library that can modify the code of a java class.

Now, recently in my adventure around the internet, I came accross a very nice little program called &quot;ClassEditor&quot;. this program, written in java, allows the user to change most of the data within the class file, such as string references, etc.

I will write a brief tutorial on how this can benifit you, and how it has also been a major benifit me =)

For this tutorial, I am just going to use the example of the &quot;Unlicensed Copy&quot; post that is in this section. for some strange reason i was under the impression that CoonHunter was decompiling the minecraft client to make these modifications (from what i read anyway..  :| ). This way is FAR more simple, and will work 100% of the time when done correctly. lets get started.

These are the steps we will follow:

[ul][li]decompile minecraft jar.[/li]
[li]search for the string.[/li]
[li]open the [b]class[/b] file in CE.[/li]
[li]modify constant pool.[/li]
[li]insert back into client.[/li][/ul]


[b]--Decompile the main Minecraft jar.[/b]
so. First step is first. We want to decompile the main Minecraft jar file (this is commonly stored in the appdata folder for windows users. i am unsure of the location for linux based OS&#39;s).
I use a program called JD which stands for JavaDecompiler. this can be found from their website [url=http://java.decompiler.free.fr/]http://java.decompiler.free.fr/[/url]

So once you have downloaded that, or you have opened your favorite decompiler, we can move on.
open the minecraft.jar file found commonly in the appdata directory on most microsoft computers. you can get there fast by typing %appdata% into either the start button search bar, or the bar where it shows your current directory path. once open you wish to export the entire source like so:

[center][img]http://i56.tinypic.com/k9hvz7.png[/img][/center]
once you have done that we can move on to step 2.

[b]--Search for the String.[/b]
So, this is the string that we wish to modify(in this case, we are removing it all together). so lets go ahead and use a program such as Z-FileSearcher to find us what files contain the string we wish to edit.

so we search for &quot;Unlicensed Copy&quot;, and we should find that (in update 1.7.3) the file we are looking for is VU.class.
now we have identified this, we are on to step 3.

[b]--open the class file in CE.[/b]
please note that that says Class file. to be able to do this, we will need to extract the minecraft.jar to a smart location. I have just left mine in the %appdata%/.minecraft/bin/ folder with the main jar file for ease of access.
once you have extracted it (using 7zip or winzip or some other form of compression tool), we need to find the class file inside the newly extracted file.

we will be using CE which can be found here: [url=http://classeditor.sourceforge.net/]http://classeditor.sourceforge.net/[/url]
once you have downloaded the latest version of CE, extract it to a location such as your desktop, lets begin.
we were looking for vu.class. so lets navigate to the folder and open the class. it will look like this:
(NOTE: we can also use the search box in CE to find the strings. I forgot to hghlight that in the image :|. just remember that it searched from your current location, so if yu wish to find all occurences, remember to scroll to the top of the lit and click on the 1st line.).
[center][img]http://i54.tinypic.com/2ibgpc0.png[/img][/center]

the main points i have highlighted in the picture are:

--modify mode needs to be turned to ON.

--we want to be looking in the Constant Pool tab. (if you dont understand how a java class works, it isn&#39;t necisary to completely understand... but its definately good to read up on things).

--we need to find all the strings that we need to edit, but there is a bit of a catch. they will appear 2 times in the constant pool each. one of the references points to the other.

--Navigate. this is where this reference is POINTING to.

now we semi-understand the layout, time for the next step.

[b]--Modifying the Constant Pool.[/b]
as you can see in the image, i have found one of the pointers to a string i wish to edit out. the Navigate section has a number in it, so I know where it is getting pointed to. Before we click the &quot;go&quot; button, we need to remember where this line is, so take note of the number 7.. we need to come back here soon.

go ahead and hit the GO button in the navigtor section. once you have done so we will end up where it was pointing to (in my case, line 164). Here is where we are going to modify the text.

because I wish to remove this message all together, I will want to set the &quot;value&quot; of the string:
[center][img]http://i52.tinypic.com/2w7fm0w.png[/img][/center]

so we set the &quot;value&quot; to be empty (just remove everything) then click modify.
if you dont see the line at 164 change, click on it.. if it still doesnt change you need to click the modify button again.
NOW we need to go back to the line that was pointing to here (YES! it was line 7).
once here, all we need to do is click the modify button, and it should change to what ever text you entered into the value section.

repeat this process with the other strings you wish to remove.

[b]--Inserting files Back into the Client.[/b]
ok. after we have modified the class and we have clicked the save button in CE, we will want to pack this file back into the client.
first off, MAKE A BACKUP of your minecraft.jar file. i have messed things up many times, and its a pain in the ass if you didn&#39;t make a backup.. so.. JUST DO IT.

second step. we open minecraft.jar with 7zip or winzip (or similar). we DO NOT want to be extracting the file, but rather OPENING it so we can see the content of the jar.

first things first, we need to delete the MANIFEST folder. this folder contains all the checksums for the class files, and seeing as we modified them, we don&#39;t want it to be making any checks regarding this. SO we remove it.
once done, we drag and drop our EDITED class file into the archive program. it should replace the old one.
once done, close and test :D

load up the minecraft loader, enter user + pass, then see if the minecraft applet has changed!. if the applet runs, then there usually has been no error, and your changes will be effective :D

heres a quick SS of my custom MineCraft client:
[center][img]http://i55.tinypic.com/vqks9s.png[/img][/center]
nothing special as of yet (Visually), but i have created my own Authorisation server with MySQL database, a few PHP files and methods that i explained in this tutorial.
Interested in this project?.. want me to post another tutorial on how to set up your own Auth server for your minecraft client and server? leave a post saying so.


this brings my tutorial to an end. Hopefully some people have learnt how you can modify a java class file without the need to decompile/recompile, and i hope that it will help this community.
all constructive critisism is welcome.
(please excuse any bad grammar or spelling mistakes. I was making this up as I went along. it should still all make sense though..)</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 21 Jul 2011 09:24:16 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Minecraft</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/minecraft-how-to-edit-the-client-server/405241.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Minecraft - How to edit the Client/Server!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@k4den k4den]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/k4den">@k4den</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>thanks =)</p>
<p>and I mean, what I was doing with my client wasn’t hard at all. I wasn’t trying to customise it as such, but was really just testing stuff out =P</p>
<p>I just thought I would post so that anyone who was interested in it could test things out themselves. I sure know that when I didn’t have the knowledge, I found it very hard to find information and teach myself… So I decided to give back a little, and hopefully help someone learn something that I have always been interested in.</p>
<p>Next step for me will be some sort of Reflection/BCEL class loader that will modify the URL’s or something for me… Would be a cool little tool if I ever released my Auth server to the public (and not just to Mopar =P)</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/minecraft-how-to-edit-the-client-server/405241/9">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/minecraft-how-to-edit-the-client-server/405241/9</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jul 2011 09:24:16 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-405241-9</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/minecraft-how-to-edit-the-client-server/405241.rss">Minecraft - How to edit the Client/Server!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Minecraft - How to edit the Client/Server!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@reyx7 reyx7]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/reyx7">@reyx7</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Custom minecraft clients eh? Sounds like a pattern another popular server hosting thing went through not to long ago…<br>
Anyway nice job on this, was really easy to follow.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/minecraft-how-to-edit-the-client-server/405241/8">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/minecraft-how-to-edit-the-client-server/405241/8</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jul 2011 06:23:26 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-405241-8</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/minecraft-how-to-edit-the-client-server/405241.rss">Minecraft - How to edit the Client/Server!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Minecraft - How to edit the Client/Server!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@k4den k4den]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/k4den">@k4den</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Sent you a PM with all the details and files Mopar =)<br>
I was never planning on opening it as a Minecraft server, so it will be good if it gets used =P</p>
<p>oh one thing i forgot to add, you might want to supress the warnings from the POST and GET requests in the PHP files… I forgot to do that  :(… it just looks more professional if someone is snooping around the filesystem and finds the php files xD</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/minecraft-how-to-edit-the-client-server/405241/7">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/minecraft-how-to-edit-the-client-server/405241/7</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jul 2011 02:49:43 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-405241-7</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/minecraft-how-to-edit-the-client-server/405241.rss">Minecraft - How to edit the Client/Server!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Minecraft - How to edit the Client/Server!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@moparisthebest Moparisthebest]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/moparisthebest">@moparisthebest</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Do you mind posting your ‘authorization server’ code?  I’ve been meaning to look into something like that for moparcraft.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/minecraft-how-to-edit-the-client-server/405241/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/minecraft-how-to-edit-the-client-server/405241/6</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 20 Jul 2011 23:21:32 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-405241-6</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/minecraft-how-to-edit-the-client-server/405241.rss">Minecraft - How to edit the Client/Server!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Minecraft - How to edit the Client/Server!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@k4den k4den]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/k4den">@k4den</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>From my experience of decompiling obfuscated code, I always seem to get errors when it comes to recompiling. then you run into certain errors where class names are reserved names for internal functions (such as the most recent example of the class do, which would require you to refractor/deobfuscate it yourself)… it just seems like a lot of effort =P</p>
<p>And JAD is an alright decompiler, but I have had better experiance with the decompiler i use in the tutorial… just personal prefrence I guess =P… unless it isn’t just a decompiler… then please, enlighten me of its other uses <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=5" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
<p>thanks for the feedback, hope it comes in helpful  :rolleyes:</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/minecraft-how-to-edit-the-client-server/405241/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/minecraft-how-to-edit-the-client-server/405241/5</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 20 Jul 2011 16:47:27 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-405241-5</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/minecraft-how-to-edit-the-client-server/405241.rss">Minecraft - How to edit the Client/Server!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Minecraft - How to edit the Client/Server!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@CoonHunter CoonHunter]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/coonhunter">@CoonHunter</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I don’t really see how my way was complicated (from how you put it) lol. Anyways, most people would still rather just download a pre-patched class file rather than doing this themselves. The ‘Class Editor’ program will come in handy so I will be keeping this around. There is a program called JAD that is ran via the command line. I know for a fact there are windows and linux copies available, and possibly mac.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/minecraft-how-to-edit-the-client-server/405241/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/minecraft-how-to-edit-the-client-server/405241/4</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 20 Jul 2011 14:53:47 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-405241-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/minecraft-how-to-edit-the-client-server/405241.rss">Minecraft - How to edit the Client/Server!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Minecraft - How to edit the Client/Server!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@k4den k4den]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/k4den">@k4den</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>oooh   <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=5" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"><br>
didn’t even know that existed. that would be pretty handy =P</p>
<p>aw well… this is still helpful for most java when there isnt a deobfuscator/decompiler available. Its also easy for those quick fixes you need to do… it is a lot of hasstle to decompile, edit, recompile… its just as easy to edit class &gt; add to the archive =P</p>
<p>thanks for the feedback.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/minecraft-how-to-edit-the-client-server/405241/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/minecraft-how-to-edit-the-client-server/405241/3</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 20 Jul 2011 09:59:34 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-405241-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/minecraft-how-to-edit-the-client-server/405241.rss">Minecraft - How to edit the Client/Server!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Minecraft - How to edit the Client/Server!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@whattehp406 whattehp406]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/whattehp406">@whattehp406</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Very nice tutorial, but you should look up the Minecraft Coder Pack.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/minecraft-how-to-edit-the-client-server/405241/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/minecraft-how-to-edit-the-client-server/405241/2</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 20 Jul 2011 09:22:33 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-405241-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/minecraft-how-to-edit-the-client-server/405241.rss">Minecraft - How to edit the Client/Server!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Minecraft - How to edit the Client/Server!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@k4den k4den]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/k4den">@k4den</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Hey guys and gals,</p>
<p>I have always lurked these forums, and never really made any DECENT posts. So i decided to give you all some information that may be very handy in your Minecraft server/client development =)</p>
<p>What I will be explaining today is how to edit the constant pool of a class file without any vast knowledge of BCEL, or other forms of library that can modify the code of a java class.</p>
<p>Now, recently in my adventure around the internet, I came accross a very nice little program called “ClassEditor”. this program, written in java, allows the user to change most of the data within the class file, such as string references, etc.</p>
<p>I will write a brief tutorial on how this can benifit you, and how it has also been a major benifit me =)</p>
<p>For this tutorial, I am just going to use the example of the “Unlicensed Copy” post that is in this section. for some strange reason i was under the impression that CoonHunter was decompiling the minecraft client to make these modifications (from what i read anyway…  <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/expressionless.png?v=5" title=":expressionless:" class="emoji" alt=":expressionless:"> ). This way is FAR more simple, and will work 100% of the time when done correctly. lets get started.</p>
<p>These are the steps we will follow:</p>
<p>[ul][li]decompile minecraft jar.[/li]<br>
[li]search for the string.[/li]<br>
[li]open the <span class="bbcode-b">class</span> file in CE.[/li]<br>
[li]modify constant pool.[/li]<br>
[li]insert back into client.[/li][/ul]</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">–Decompile the main Minecraft jar.</span><br>
so. First step is first. We want to decompile the main Minecraft jar file (this is commonly stored in the appdata folder for windows users. i am unsure of the location for linux based OS’s).<br>
I use a program called JD which stands for JavaDecompiler. this can be found from their website <a href="http://java.decompiler.free.fr/" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">http://java.decompiler.free.fr/</a></p>
<p>So once you have downloaded that, or you have opened your favorite decompiler, we can move on.<br>
open the minecraft.jar file found commonly in the appdata directory on most microsoft computers. you can get there fast by typing %appdata% into either the start button search bar, or the bar where it shows your current directory path. once open you wish to export the entire source like so:</p>
<p>[center]<img src="http://i56.tinypic.com/k9hvz7.png" alt width="" height="">[/center]<br>
once you have done that we can move on to step 2.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">–Search for the String.</span><br>
So, this is the string that we wish to modify(in this case, we are removing it all together). so lets go ahead and use a program such as Z-FileSearcher to find us what files contain the string we wish to edit.</p>
<p>so we search for “Unlicensed Copy”, and we should find that (in update 1.7.3) the file we are looking for is VU.class.<br>
now we have identified this, we are on to step 3.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">–open the class file in CE.</span><br>
please note that that says Class file. to be able to do this, we will need to extract the minecraft.jar to a smart location. I have just left mine in the %appdata%/.minecraft/bin/ folder with the main jar file for ease of access.<br>
once you have extracted it (using 7zip or winzip or some other form of compression tool), we need to find the class file inside the newly extracted file.</p>
<p>we will be using CE which can be found here: <a href="http://classeditor.sourceforge.net/" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">http://classeditor.sourceforge.net/</a><br>
once you have downloaded the latest version of CE, extract it to a location such as your desktop, lets begin.<br>
we were looking for vu.class. so lets navigate to the folder and open the class. it will look like this:<br>
(NOTE: we can also use the search box in CE to find the strings. I forgot to hghlight that in the image :|. just remember that it searched from your current location, so if yu wish to find all occurences, remember to scroll to the top of the lit and click on the 1st line.).<br>
[center]<img src="http://i54.tinypic.com/2ibgpc0.png" alt width="" height="">[/center]</p>
<p>the main points i have highlighted in the picture are:</p>
<p>–modify mode needs to be turned to ON.</p>
<p>–we want to be looking in the Constant Pool tab. (if you dont understand how a java class works, it isn’t necisary to completely understand… but its definately good to read up on things).</p>
<p>–we need to find all the strings that we need to edit, but there is a bit of a catch. they will appear 2 times in the constant pool each. one of the references points to the other.</p>
<p>–Navigate. this is where this reference is POINTING to.</p>
<p>now we semi-understand the layout, time for the next step.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">–Modifying the Constant Pool.</span><br>
as you can see in the image, i have found one of the pointers to a string i wish to edit out. the Navigate section has a number in it, so I know where it is getting pointed to. Before we click the “go” button, we need to remember where this line is, so take note of the number 7… we need to come back here soon.</p>
<p>go ahead and hit the GO button in the navigtor section. once you have done so we will end up where it was pointing to (in my case, line 164). Here is where we are going to modify the text.</p>
<p>because I wish to remove this message all together, I will want to set the “value” of the string:<br>
[center]<img src="http://i52.tinypic.com/2w7fm0w.png" alt width="" height="">[/center]</p>
<p>so we set the “value” to be empty (just remove everything) then click modify.<br>
if you dont see the line at 164 change, click on it… if it still doesnt change you need to click the modify button again.<br>
NOW we need to go back to the line that was pointing to here (YES! it was line 7).<br>
once here, all we need to do is click the modify button, and it should change to what ever text you entered into the value section.</p>
<p>repeat this process with the other strings you wish to remove.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">–Inserting files Back into the Client.</span><br>
ok. after we have modified the class and we have clicked the save button in CE, we will want to pack this file back into the client.<br>
first off, MAKE A BACKUP of your minecraft.jar file. i have messed things up many times, and its a pain in the ass if you didn’t make a backup… so… JUST DO IT.</p>
<p>second step. we open minecraft.jar with 7zip or winzip (or similar). we DO NOT want to be extracting the file, but rather OPENING it so we can see the content of the jar.</p>
<p>first things first, we need to delete the MANIFEST folder. this folder contains all the checksums for the class files, and seeing as we modified them, we don’t want it to be making any checks regarding this. SO we remove it.<br>
once done, we drag and drop our EDITED class file into the archive program. it should replace the old one.<br>
once done, close and test <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/smiley.png?v=5" title=":smiley:" class="emoji" alt=":smiley:"></p>
<p>load up the minecraft loader, enter user + pass, then see if the minecraft applet has changed!. if the applet runs, then there usually has been no error, and your changes will be effective <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/smiley.png?v=5" title=":smiley:" class="emoji" alt=":smiley:"></p>
<p>heres a quick SS of my custom MineCraft client:<br>
[center]<img src="http://i55.tinypic.com/vqks9s.png" alt width="" height="">[/center]<br>
nothing special as of yet (Visually), but i have created my own Authorisation server with MySQL database, a few PHP files and methods that i explained in this tutorial.<br>
Interested in this project?.. want me to post another tutorial on how to set up your own Auth server for your minecraft client and server? leave a post saying so.</p>
<p>this brings my tutorial to an end. Hopefully some people have learnt how you can modify a java class file without the need to decompile/recompile, and i hope that it will help this community.<br>
all constructive critisism is welcome.<br>
(please excuse any bad grammar or spelling mistakes. I was making this up as I went along. it should still all make sense though…)</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/minecraft-how-to-edit-the-client-server/405241/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/minecraft-how-to-edit-the-client-server/405241/1</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 20 Jul 2011 06:58:21 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-405241-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/minecraft-how-to-edit-the-client-server/405241.rss">Minecraft - How to edit the Client/Server!</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
