<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Some Java term definitions</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/some-java-term-definitions/347275</link>
    <description>[u][b]Contents[/b][/u]-use control-F to navigate
Chapter 1
1.1 basics
Chapter 2
2.1 Value Type
2.2 Method Parameters and Return Values.
2.3 Number types:
2.4 Constructing Objects:
2.5 Test programs:
2.6 API documentation
2.7 Object reference
Chapter 3
3.1 Implementing classes
3.2 Commenting the public interface
3.3 Instance fields
3.4 Implementing Constructors and Methods
...more to come about implicit and explicit method parameters
[size=14pt][u][b]Introduction[/b][/u][/size]

This is part of my notes I made myself for the purpose of learning Java. Almost all definitions are word for word copied from &quot;Big Java&quot; by Cay Horstamann. 3rd edition. The entire book is 1000+ pages. This guide attempt to summarize some key information and omit some explanations and &quot;extra&quot; facts. Like the book, this tutorial follows the same layout. 

This guide list some common Java terms and they are listed as their relevant topics came up.

I will update more, plz pm me for corrections or need for clarifications.
[size=18pt][b]
JAVA TERMS[/b][/size]

[size=12pt][b]Chapter 1 [/b][/size]
•	Java has a free-form layout, (doesn’t matter how many spaces or lines you make your statements). However, it is case sensitive. (lower-case needs to be in lower-case, upper case needs to be in uppercase). 
•	[b]Classes[/b] are the fundamental building blocks of Java programs. (more on classes, method and objects in chapter 2)
•	Each class contains [u]definitions [/u]of methods. Each method contains a sequence of instructions. (more on definitions later) 
•	Every Java application contains a class with a [b]main method[/b]. When the application starts, the instructions in the main method are executed.
       o	For example: look at this statement  [i]System.out.println(“Hello”);[/i] with the method [i]println[/i].
       o	What this statement does is print out “Hello” in the console display window. 
       o	The display window or System.out is the object.
              	“[i]out[/i]” is an [b]object[/b], in this case, the display window.
              	“[i]System[/i]” is a class file that describes where the object [i]out [/i]is found. 
              	“[i]println[/i]” is the method name.
              	“Hello” is an input of the method println, it is called a [b]parameter [/b]of the method “println”. 
       o	A [b]method [/b]is called by specifying an [b]object[/b], the method name, and the parameters. 
•	A [b]syntax error[/b] is a violation of the rules of the programming language. The compiler detects syntax errors.
•	A [b]logic error[/b] causes a program to take an action that the programmer did not intend. 
       o	Programs called [b]debuggers [/b]help find logic errors or bugs. 
•	An [b]editor[/b] is a program for entering and modifying text, such as a Java program.
       o	Notepad, Textpad and word can all be used for this task.
•	A [b]Java compiler[/b] translates source code into class files that contain instructions for the Java virtual machine.
       o	The compiler translates the statements that you wrote in an editor (aka the [b]source code[/b]) into class files. 
       o	[b]Class files[/b] have the .class extension and consist of virtual machine instructions and other information that is required for execution.
       o	The class files have only the instructions that you wrote. Often times, that alone is not enough to run your program. Your class files will often need instructions from other class files written by someone else. These class files compose Java’s huge library. 
              	A [b]library[/b] is a collection of code that has been programmed and translated by someone else, ready for you to use in your program.
       o	The [b]Java Virtual Machine[/b] loads program instructions from class files and library files.
[b]
[size=14pt]Chapter 2[/size][/b]
[b][u]2.1Value types.[/u][/b]
•	-In java, every [b]value [/b]has a [b]type[/b].
       o	“hello” is a [i]value[/i] that has type [i]string[/i]. 
              	A string is a sequence of characters contained in quotation marks.
       o	The integer 100 is a value that has type [i][b]int[/b][/i].
       o	It is an error to store a value whose class does not match the type of variable.
              	E.g. String variablename =”Hello”; is correct
              	E.g. String variablename = 100; is incorrect, because the value 100 is type int. 
•	You use [b]variables [/b]to store values that you want to use at a later time. 
       o	Variables in Java have to be [b]defined [/b]and [b]initialized [/b]first before you can use it in your program.
              	Define the variable: int thetimeofday;
              	Initialize the variable: thetimeofday = 50;
              	You can define and initialize a variable like this: int thetimeofday =50;
•	The name of the variable is called an [b]identifier[/b]. 
       o	E.g. String variablename =”Hello”;  variablename is an identifier. 
•	An identifier is the name of a variable, method, or class. 
       o	The [u]rules for identifiers[/u] are the following.
              	Identifiers can be made up of letters, digits, and the underscore (_) and dollar sign ($) characters. 
              	They cannot start with a digit.
              	Other symbols are not allowed such as ?, % ! etc…
              	No spaces
              	No [b]reserved words[/b] can be used for identifiers, such as [i]public[/i], because they hold special meaning in Java.
              	Identifiers are case sensitive. The identifiers, Variablename, variablename, VarIaBlename are all different identifiers and can store different variables.
              	But this doesn’t mean that you should. Good programming notations dictate that you should make variable and method names start with a lowercase letter and class names start with an uppercase letter.
•	Use the [b]assignment operator (=)[/b] to change the value of a variable.
[u][b]2.2 Objects[/b][/u]
•	An [b]object [/b]is an entity that you can manipulate in your program by calling methods.
       o	[i]System.out.println(“Hello”);[/i]
              	You manipulate the object [i]System.out[/i], by calling the method [i]println[/i]. This tells the Java Virtual machine to print the word Hello in the system output (aka, the display window).
•	A class defines the methods that you can apply to its objects. 
       o	“Hello” is an object that belongs to the class string.
       o	System.out is an object that belongs to the class PrintStream.
       o	[i]String greeting= “Hello”;[/i]
       o	[i]int n= greeting.length();[/i]
       o	For the object &quot;Hello”, method such as greeting.length() can be applied. This method get the length of the string greeting. Which is the length of Hello. So n= 5. 
       o	Another method that can be applied to objects that belong to the String class is toUpperCase().
       o	The statement:
 [i]             	String greeting= “Hello”;
              	String biggreeting= greeting.toUpperCase();[/i]
       o	This makes the variable biggreeting “HELLO”.
       o	The methods for the class strings cannot be applied to the class int or the class PrintStream and vice versa.
       o	The class of an object defines what methods can be applied to it!
•	The method forms the [b]public interface[/b] of the class. 
       o	This tells you what you can do with the objects.
•	A class also defines a [b]private implementation[/b], describing the data inside [i]its [/i]objects and the instructions for its methods. Those details are hidden from the programmers who use objects and call methods. 

[u][b]2.3 Method Parameters and Return Values.[/b][/u]
•	Some methods require inputs that give details about the work it needs to do. 
       o	A [b]parameter [/b]is an input to a method. 
•	[b]Implicit vs explicit parameters:[/b]
       o	Considering the statement: System.out.println(greeting);
              	The greeting parameter is an [b]explicit parameter[/b] of the println method.
              	The object System.out (aka, the display window), is an [b]implicit parameter[/b] of the method println. 
              	The [b]implicit parameter[/b] of the method call is the object on which the method is invoked.
              	Some methods need many explicit parameters, other needs no explicit parameters. 
•	The [b]return value[/b] of a method is a result that the method has computed for use by the code that called it. 
       o	For example, the method “length” returns the value of the length of characters in a string.  
       o	The statement: “int n = greeting.length();” , where the number of characters in greeting or the return value of the method length is stored in the integer n.
       o	Not all method has a return value. 
       o	Does the print.ln method have a return value? No, because print.ln only interacts with the console window and gives instructions to display texts, it does not have a return value.
       o	You can use the return value of a method, (aka, the results of a method call) as a parameter for another method. 
              	For example: System.out.println(greeting.length());
              	greeting.length() gives the value 5, 5 is the return value of the method greeting.length and also the explicit parameter of the method println.
•	When a method is defined in a class, the [b]definition [/b]specifies the types of the explicit parameters and the return value. 
       o	For example, the [i]String class[/i] defines the [i]length [/i]method as public int length()
•	The type of the implicit parameter is the class that defines the method. (more on methods and method definitions later)
•	When a method returns no value, the return type is declared with the word void.
•	For example the method println, which have no return value is defined by PrintStream class as “[i]public void println(int output) [/i]or [i]public void println(String output).[/i]
       o	The class PrintStream defines 2 methods with the same method name (println). One can print string types, the other integer types.
       o	Method names that refer to 2 or more methods are called [b]overloaded[/b]. 
              	The method name println is over loaded.
Number types:
•	Numbers in java can be [b]integer [/b]types which are whole numbers or [b]floating-point numbers[/b], which contain fractions. 
•	The double type denotes the floating-point numbers that can have fractional parts.
       o	double fractionarecool= 1.4353
       o	int integerarethebomb= 5
•	int, double are [b]primitive types[/b], not classes. Numbers are not objects, number types are not classes.
•	Numbers can be combined by arithmetic operators such as +, -, *, /
[b][u]2.4 Constructing Objects:
[/u][/b]•	Use the [b]new [/b]operator, followed by a class name and parameters, to construct new objects.
       o	E.g. [i]Rectangle [/i]box = new Rectangle (5, 10 ,20, 30);
       o	[i]Rectangle [/i]is the name of the class from the java library. (you needed to define the [u]type [/u]of variables before you can use them.)
       o	[i]box [/i]is the variable where with the type class.
       o	[i]new [/i]is an operator and makes a Rectangle object. (note, not an actual rectangle, but just a set of numbers that describe a rectangle.)
       o	[i](5, 10, 20, 30,) [/i]are construction parameters , they describe a rectangle at coordinates x= 5, y =10, that is 20 pixels in width and 30 pixels in height.
•	Constructor are not like methods: the following will result in a syntax error:
       o	Box.Rectangle(20,35,20,30);
       o	You have to make a new one “box= new Rectangle(20, 35, 20, 30);”
•	Accessor vs Mutator methods
       o	An [b]accessor method[/b] does not change the state of its implicit parameter. A [b]mutator method[/b] changes the state. 
[b][u]2.5 Test programs:[/u][/b]
•	Determining the expected result in advance is an important part of testing.
•	Java classes are grouped into [b]packages[/b]. Use the [b]import [/b]statement to use classes that are defined in other packages. 
       o	Example: you need to import the rectangle class to be able to construct a rectangle. 
       o	To do that write: “import packageName.ClassName;” in this case: “import java.awt.Rectangle;”
[u][b]2.6 API documentation[/b][/u]
•	The Application Programming Interface documentation lists the classes and methods of the Java library. 
[b][u]2.7 Object References:[/u][/b]
•	A variable whose type is a class does not actually hold an object, it hold the [b]memory location[/b] of an object. 
•	[b]Object reference[/b] denotes the memory location of an object.
•	When a variable that contains the memory location of an object, we say that it [b]refers [/b]to an object. 
       o	For example, in the statement “Rectangle box = new Rectangle (5, 10 ,20, 30);”
       o	The new operator returned a [b]reference [/b]of the new object and that reference is stored in the variable box. 
              	Hint: the new object is (Rectangle (5, 10 ,20, 30))
•	Multiple object variables can contain references to the same object.
•	Number variables store numbers. Object variables store references. 
       o	What this means is that if you make a copy of an [b]object variable[/b], the 2 variables refer to the same object.  So if you change the object, both variables are also changed, since they refered to the same object. But number variables will actually store numbers. 
•	Object variable are references because objects takes up more memory than numbers, using object variables to store memory location takes up less memory than objects stored in variables.  
[b][size=14pt]Chapter 3[/size][/b]
•	a[b] black box[/b] is a device, system or object which can be viewed solely in terms of its input, output and transfer characteristics without any knowledge of its internal workings.
•	An object has an internal structure-perhaps, sometimes composed of other objects. For runescape players, their black boxes are objects which made your client. For beginning developers, black boxes might be the base used to construct the server. 
•	For example, a computer user uses a computer program which are constructed by objects (black boxes to him or her) designed by application programmers. In turn, the application programmers uses object designed by other application programmers. And in turn, those objects may be designed by system programmers. 
•	In object oriented programming, you will design objects that you use to construct other objects and you those to develop your applications. In other words, you will be the application programmer and also the system programmer at the same time.
[b][u]
3.1 Specifying the public interface of a class[/u][/b]
•	In order to implement a class, you first need to know which methods are required.
•	A method definition contains an access specifier (usually public), a return type, a method name, parameters, and the method body. 
       o	Example: public void eatpie (double pieces) {method body}
       o	The method name is eatpie and it is an accessor method. Therefore, the The return type is “void”, which means no return value.
       o	Public is the access specifier
       o	(), whatever are in brackets are parameters of the method eatpie.
              	A parameter of a method definition must have a name and a type. In this case, double is the type and pieces is the name of the parameter. 
•	The [b]constructors [/b]contain instructions to initialize objects. The constructor name is always the same as the class name. 
o	A constructor is similar to a method, except for 2 differences. Constructors have no return type, (not even void) and the name of the constructor is always the same name as the name of the class.
•	Just like methods, a constructor also has a [b]body[/b], which are a sequence of statements that is executed when a new object is constructed. 
•	Constructors can take on different parameters, that is how they are differentiated since all constructors in the same class have the same name. (more on constructors later)
•	The public methods and constructors of a class makes up its public interface.
[u][b]3.2 Commenting the public interface[/b][/u]
•	A [u][b]documentation comment[/b][/u] is placed before the class or method definition that is being documented. It starts with a /**, a special comment delimeter used by the javadoc utility. Then you describe the method’s purpose. Then, for each method parameter, you supply a line that starts with [b]@param[/b], followed by the parameter name and a short explanation. Finally you supply a line that starts with [b]@return[/b], describing the return value. You omit the @param tag for methods that have no parameters, and you omit the @return tag for methods whose return type is void. 
•	The [b]javadoc [/b]utility copies the first sentence of each comment to a summary table in the HTML documentation. 
•	Use documentation comments to describe the classes and public methods of your program.
•	Provide documentation comments for every class, every method, every parameter, and every return value. 
[u][b]3.3 Instance fields[/b][/u]
•	An object stores its data in [b]instance fields[/b].
•	A [b]field [/b]is the storage location inside a block of memory.
•	An [b]instance [/b]of a class is an object of the class. 
•	The class declaration specifies the instance fields. An instance field declaration consists of:
       o	An access specifier (usually [i]private[/i])
              	Private means that the method can only be accessed by methods of the same class.
       o	The type of the instance field (such as [i]double[/i])
       o	The name of the instance field (such as [i]balance[/i])
•	By making instance fields private, all data access must occur through public methods.
•	They are effectively hidden from the programmer who uses a class. 
•	The process of hiding the data and providing methods for data access is called encapsulation. 
[u][b]3.4 Implementing Constructors and Methods[/b][/u]
•	Constructors contain instructions to initialize the instance fields of an object. 
       o	Often times you will need 2 constructors, one that sets all fields to a default and one that sets them to user-supplied values. 
•	Use the [b]return [/b]statement to specify the value that a method returns to its caller.
       o	The return statement instructs the method to terminate and return an output to the statement that called the method.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2010 06:29:50 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/some-java-term-definitions/347275.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Some Java term definitions</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@PvPTurf PvPTurf]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/pvpturf">@PvPTurf</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Very nice. Thanks for posting it. I will refer to it from time to time. I’d ++rep you, but I don’t have enough rank yet.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/some-java-term-definitions/347275/7">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/some-java-term-definitions/347275/7</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2010 06:29:50 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-347275-7</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/some-java-term-definitions/347275.rss">Some Java term definitions</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Some Java term definitions</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@j19283746 j19283746]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/j19283746">@j19283746</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Hey now… I liked it.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/some-java-term-definitions/347275/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/some-java-term-definitions/347275/6</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2010 05:38:48 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-347275-6</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/some-java-term-definitions/347275.rss">Some Java term definitions</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Some Java term definitions</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Ruppich Ruppich]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/ruppich">@Ruppich</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Looks like something that should go on MoparIsTheBest(:</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/some-java-term-definitions/347275/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/some-java-term-definitions/347275/5</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 04 Jul 2010 23:32:21 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-347275-5</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/some-java-term-definitions/347275.rss">Some Java term definitions</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Some Java term definitions</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Wayra Wayra]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/wayra">@Wayra</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>you are welcome</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/some-java-term-definitions/347275/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/some-java-term-definitions/347275/4</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 04 Jul 2010 22:34:41 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-347275-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/some-java-term-definitions/347275.rss">Some Java term definitions</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Some Java term definitions</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@j19283746 j19283746]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/j19283746">@j19283746</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>This is very nice for beginners like me <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=5" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"> Thanks.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/some-java-term-definitions/347275/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/some-java-term-definitions/347275/3</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 04 Jul 2010 15:02:10 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-347275-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/some-java-term-definitions/347275.rss">Some Java term definitions</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Some Java term definitions</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@spy_man47 spy man47]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/spy_man47">@spy_man47</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Wow nice… You learning Java?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/some-java-term-definitions/347275/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/some-java-term-definitions/347275/2</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 04 Jul 2010 14:13:19 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-347275-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/some-java-term-definitions/347275.rss">Some Java term definitions</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Some Java term definitions</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Wayra Wayra]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/wayra">@Wayra</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p><span class="bbcode-u"><span class="bbcode-b">Contents</span></span>-use control-F to navigate<br>
Chapter 1<br>
1.1 basics<br>
Chapter 2<br>
2.1 Value Type<br>
2.2 Method Parameters and Return Values.<br>
2.3 Number types:<br>
2.4 Constructing Objects:<br>
2.5 Test programs:<br>
2.6 API documentation<br>
2.7 Object reference<br>
Chapter 3<br>
3.1 Implementing classes<br>
3.2 Commenting the public interface<br>
3.3 Instance fields<br>
3.4 Implementing Constructors and Methods<br>
…more to come about implicit and explicit method parameters<br>
[size=14pt]<span class="bbcode-u"><span class="bbcode-b">Introduction</span></span>[/size]</p>
<p>This is part of my notes I made myself for the purpose of learning Java. Almost all definitions are word for word copied from “Big Java” by Cay Horstamann. 3rd edition. The entire book is 1000+ pages. This guide attempt to summarize some key information and omit some explanations and “extra” facts. Like the book, this tutorial follows the same layout.</p>
<p>This guide list some common Java terms and they are listed as their relevant topics came up.</p>
<p>I will update more, plz pm me for corrections or need for clarifications.<br>
[size=18pt]<span class="bbcode-b"><br>
JAVA TERMS</span>[/size]</p>
<p>[size=12pt]<span class="bbcode-b">Chapter 1 </span>[/size]<br>
•	Java has a free-form layout, (doesn’t matter how many spaces or lines you make your statements). However, it is case sensitive. (lower-case needs to be in lower-case, upper case needs to be in uppercase).<br>
•	<span class="bbcode-b">Classes</span> are the fundamental building blocks of Java programs. (more on classes, method and objects in chapter 2)<br>
•	Each class contains <span class="bbcode-u">definitions </span>of methods. Each method contains a sequence of instructions. (more on definitions later)<br>
•	Every Java application contains a class with a <span class="bbcode-b">main method</span>. When the application starts, the instructions in the main method are executed.<br>
o	For example: look at this statement  <span class="bbcode-i">System.out.println(“Hello”);</span> with the method <span class="bbcode-i">println</span>.<br>
o	What this statement does is print out “Hello” in the console display window.<br>
o	The display window or System.out is the object.<br>
	“<span class="bbcode-i">out</span>” is an <span class="bbcode-b">object</span>, in this case, the display window.<br>
	“<span class="bbcode-i">System</span>” is a class file that describes where the object <span class="bbcode-i">out </span>is found.<br>
	“<span class="bbcode-i">println</span>” is the method name.<br>
	“Hello” is an input of the method println, it is called a <span class="bbcode-b">parameter </span>of the method “println”.<br>
o	A <span class="bbcode-b">method </span>is called by specifying an <span class="bbcode-b">object</span>, the method name, and the parameters.<br>
•	A <span class="bbcode-b">syntax error</span> is a violation of the rules of the programming language. The compiler detects syntax errors.<br>
•	A <span class="bbcode-b">logic error</span> causes a program to take an action that the programmer did not intend.<br>
o	Programs called <span class="bbcode-b">debuggers </span>help find logic errors or bugs.<br>
•	An <span class="bbcode-b">editor</span> is a program for entering and modifying text, such as a Java program.<br>
o	Notepad, Textpad and word can all be used for this task.<br>
•	A <span class="bbcode-b">Java compiler</span> translates source code into class files that contain instructions for the Java virtual machine.<br>
o	The compiler translates the statements that you wrote in an editor (aka the <span class="bbcode-b">source code</span>) into class files.<br>
o	<span class="bbcode-b">Class files</span> have the .class extension and consist of virtual machine instructions and other information that is required for execution.<br>
o	The class files have only the instructions that you wrote. Often times, that alone is not enough to run your program. Your class files will often need instructions from other class files written by someone else. These class files compose Java’s huge library.<br>
	A <span class="bbcode-b">library</span> is a collection of code that has been programmed and translated by someone else, ready for you to use in your program.<br>
o	The <span class="bbcode-b">Java Virtual Machine</span> loads program instructions from class files and library files.<br>
<span class="bbcode-b"><br>
[size=14pt]Chapter 2[/size]</span><br>
<span class="bbcode-b"><span class="bbcode-u">2.1Value types.</span></span><br>
•	-In java, every <span class="bbcode-b">value </span>has a <span class="bbcode-b">type</span>.<br>
o	“hello” is a <span class="bbcode-i">value</span> that has type <span class="bbcode-i">string</span>.<br>
	A string is a sequence of characters contained in quotation marks.<br>
o	The integer 100 is a value that has type <span class="bbcode-i"><span class="bbcode-b">int</span></span>.<br>
o	It is an error to store a value whose class does not match the type of variable.<br>
	E.g. String variablename =”Hello”; is correct<br>
	E.g. String variablename = 100; is incorrect, because the value 100 is type int.<br>
•	You use <span class="bbcode-b">variables </span>to store values that you want to use at a later time.<br>
o	Variables in Java have to be <span class="bbcode-b">defined </span>and <span class="bbcode-b">initialized </span>first before you can use it in your program.<br>
	Define the variable: int thetimeofday;<br>
	Initialize the variable: thetimeofday = 50;<br>
	You can define and initialize a variable like this: int thetimeofday =50;<br>
•	The name of the variable is called an <span class="bbcode-b">identifier</span>.<br>
o	E.g. String variablename =”Hello”;  variablename is an identifier.<br>
•	An identifier is the name of a variable, method, or class.<br>
o	The <span class="bbcode-u">rules for identifiers</span> are the following.<br>
	Identifiers can be made up of letters, digits, and the underscore (_) and dollar sign ($) characters.<br>
	They cannot start with a digit.<br>
	Other symbols are not allowed such as ?, % ! etc…<br>
	No spaces<br>
	No <span class="bbcode-b">reserved words</span> can be used for identifiers, such as <span class="bbcode-i">public</span>, because they hold special meaning in Java.<br>
	Identifiers are case sensitive. The identifiers, Variablename, variablename, VarIaBlename are all different identifiers and can store different variables.<br>
	But this doesn’t mean that you should. Good programming notations dictate that you should make variable and method names start with a lowercase letter and class names start with an uppercase letter.<br>
•	Use the <span class="bbcode-b">assignment operator (=)</span> to change the value of a variable.<br>
<span class="bbcode-u"><span class="bbcode-b">2.2 Objects</span></span><br>
•	An <span class="bbcode-b">object </span>is an entity that you can manipulate in your program by calling methods.<br>
o	<span class="bbcode-i">System.out.println(“Hello”);</span><br>
	You manipulate the object <span class="bbcode-i">System.out</span>, by calling the method <span class="bbcode-i">println</span>. This tells the Java Virtual machine to print the word Hello in the system output (aka, the display window).<br>
•	A class defines the methods that you can apply to its objects.<br>
o	“Hello” is an object that belongs to the class string.<br>
o	System.out is an object that belongs to the class PrintStream.<br>
o	<span class="bbcode-i">String greeting= “Hello”;</span><br>
o	<span class="bbcode-i">int n= greeting.length();</span><br>
o	For the object "Hello”, method such as greeting.length() can be applied. This method get the length of the string greeting. Which is the length of Hello. So n= 5.<br>
o	Another method that can be applied to objects that belong to the String class is toUpperCase().<br>
o	The statement:<br>
<span class="bbcode-i">             	String greeting= “Hello”;<br>
	String biggreeting= greeting.toUpperCase();</span><br>
o	This makes the variable biggreeting “HELLO”.<br>
o	The methods for the class strings cannot be applied to the class int or the class PrintStream and vice versa.<br>
o	The class of an object defines what methods can be applied to it!<br>
•	The method forms the <span class="bbcode-b">public interface</span> of the class.<br>
o	This tells you what you can do with the objects.<br>
•	A class also defines a <span class="bbcode-b">private implementation</span>, describing the data inside <span class="bbcode-i">its </span>objects and the instructions for its methods. Those details are hidden from the programmers who use objects and call methods.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-u"><span class="bbcode-b">2.3 Method Parameters and Return Values.</span></span><br>
•	Some methods require inputs that give details about the work it needs to do.<br>
o	A <span class="bbcode-b">parameter </span>is an input to a method.<br>
•	<span class="bbcode-b">Implicit vs explicit parameters:</span><br>
o	Considering the statement: System.out.println(greeting);<br>
	The greeting parameter is an <span class="bbcode-b">explicit parameter</span> of the println method.<br>
	The object System.out (aka, the display window), is an <span class="bbcode-b">implicit parameter</span> of the method println.<br>
	The <span class="bbcode-b">implicit parameter</span> of the method call is the object on which the method is invoked.<br>
	Some methods need many explicit parameters, other needs no explicit parameters.<br>
•	The <span class="bbcode-b">return value</span> of a method is a result that the method has computed for use by the code that called it.<br>
o	For example, the method “length” returns the value of the length of characters in a string.<br>
o	The statement: “int n = greeting.length();” , where the number of characters in greeting or the return value of the method length is stored in the integer n.<br>
o	Not all method has a return value.<br>
o	Does the print.ln method have a return value? No, because print.ln only interacts with the console window and gives instructions to display texts, it does not have a return value.<br>
o	You can use the return value of a method, (aka, the results of a method call) as a parameter for another method.<br>
	For example: System.out.println(greeting.length());<br>
	greeting.length() gives the value 5, 5 is the return value of the method greeting.length and also the explicit parameter of the method println.<br>
•	When a method is defined in a class, the <span class="bbcode-b">definition </span>specifies the types of the explicit parameters and the return value.<br>
o	For example, the <span class="bbcode-i">String class</span> defines the <span class="bbcode-i">length </span>method as public int length()<br>
•	The type of the implicit parameter is the class that defines the method. (more on methods and method definitions later)<br>
•	When a method returns no value, the return type is declared with the word void.<br>
•	For example the method println, which have no return value is defined by PrintStream class as “<span class="bbcode-i">public void println(int output) </span>or <span class="bbcode-i">public void println(String output).</span><br>
o	The class PrintStream defines 2 methods with the same method name (println). One can print string types, the other integer types.<br>
o	Method names that refer to 2 or more methods are called <span class="bbcode-b">overloaded</span>.<br>
	The method name println is over loaded.<br>
Number types:<br>
•	Numbers in java can be <span class="bbcode-b">integer </span>types which are whole numbers or <span class="bbcode-b">floating-point numbers</span>, which contain fractions.<br>
•	The double type denotes the floating-point numbers that can have fractional parts.<br>
o	double fractionarecool= 1.4353<br>
o	int integerarethebomb= 5<br>
•	int, double are <span class="bbcode-b">primitive types</span>, not classes. Numbers are not objects, number types are not classes.<br>
•	Numbers can be combined by arithmetic operators such as +, -, *, /<br>
<span class="bbcode-b"><span class="bbcode-u">2.4 Constructing Objects:<br>
</span></span>•	Use the <span class="bbcode-b">new </span>operator, followed by a class name and parameters, to construct new objects.<br>
o	E.g. <span class="bbcode-i">Rectangle </span>box = new Rectangle (5, 10 ,20, 30);<br>
o	<span class="bbcode-i">Rectangle </span>is the name of the class from the java library. (you needed to define the <span class="bbcode-u">type </span>of variables before you can use them.)<br>
o	<span class="bbcode-i">box </span>is the variable where with the type class.<br>
o	<span class="bbcode-i">new </span>is an operator and makes a Rectangle object. (note, not an actual rectangle, but just a set of numbers that describe a rectangle.)<br>
o	<span class="bbcode-i">(5, 10, 20, 30,) </span>are construction parameters , they describe a rectangle at coordinates x= 5, y =10, that is 20 pixels in width and 30 pixels in height.<br>
•	Constructor are not like methods: the following will result in a syntax error:<br>
o	Box.Rectangle(20,35,20,30);<br>
o	You have to make a new one “box= new Rectangle(20, 35, 20, 30);”<br>
•	Accessor vs Mutator methods<br>
o	An <span class="bbcode-b">accessor method</span> does not change the state of its implicit parameter. A <span class="bbcode-b">mutator method</span> changes the state.<br>
<span class="bbcode-b"><span class="bbcode-u">2.5 Test programs:</span></span><br>
•	Determining the expected result in advance is an important part of testing.<br>
•	Java classes are grouped into <span class="bbcode-b">packages</span>. Use the <span class="bbcode-b">import </span>statement to use classes that are defined in other packages.<br>
o	Example: you need to import the rectangle class to be able to construct a rectangle.<br>
o	To do that write: “import packageName.ClassName;” in this case: “import java.awt.Rectangle;”<br>
<span class="bbcode-u"><span class="bbcode-b">2.6 API documentation</span></span><br>
•	The Application Programming Interface documentation lists the classes and methods of the Java library.<br>
<span class="bbcode-b"><span class="bbcode-u">2.7 Object References:</span></span><br>
•	A variable whose type is a class does not actually hold an object, it hold the <span class="bbcode-b">memory location</span> of an object.<br>
•	<span class="bbcode-b">Object reference</span> denotes the memory location of an object.<br>
•	When a variable that contains the memory location of an object, we say that it <span class="bbcode-b">refers </span>to an object.<br>
o	For example, in the statement “Rectangle box = new Rectangle (5, 10 ,20, 30);”<br>
o	The new operator returned a <span class="bbcode-b">reference </span>of the new object and that reference is stored in the variable box.<br>
	Hint: the new object is (Rectangle (5, 10 ,20, 30))<br>
•	Multiple object variables can contain references to the same object.<br>
•	Number variables store numbers. Object variables store references.<br>
o	What this means is that if you make a copy of an <span class="bbcode-b">object variable</span>, the 2 variables refer to the same object.  So if you change the object, both variables are also changed, since they refered to the same object. But number variables will actually store numbers.<br>
•	Object variable are references because objects takes up more memory than numbers, using object variables to store memory location takes up less memory than objects stored in variables.<br>
<span class="bbcode-b">[size=14pt]Chapter 3[/size]</span><br>
•	a<span class="bbcode-b"> black box</span> is a device, system or object which can be viewed solely in terms of its input, output and transfer characteristics without any knowledge of its internal workings.<br>
•	An object has an internal structure-perhaps, sometimes composed of other objects. For runescape players, their black boxes are objects which made your client. For beginning developers, black boxes might be the base used to construct the server.<br>
•	For example, a computer user uses a computer program which are constructed by objects (black boxes to him or her) designed by application programmers. In turn, the application programmers uses object designed by other application programmers. And in turn, those objects may be designed by system programmers.<br>
•	In object oriented programming, you will design objects that you use to construct other objects and you those to develop your applications. In other words, you will be the application programmer and also the system programmer at the same time.<br>
<span class="bbcode-b"><span class="bbcode-u"><br>
3.1 Specifying the public interface of a class</span></span><br>
•	In order to implement a class, you first need to know which methods are required.<br>
•	A method definition contains an access specifier (usually public), a return type, a method name, parameters, and the method body.<br>
o	Example: public void eatpie (double pieces) {method body}<br>
o	The method name is eatpie and it is an accessor method. Therefore, the The return type is “void”, which means no return value.<br>
o	Public is the access specifier<br>
o	(), whatever are in brackets are parameters of the method eatpie.<br>
	A parameter of a method definition must have a name and a type. In this case, double is the type and pieces is the name of the parameter.<br>
•	The <span class="bbcode-b">constructors </span>contain instructions to initialize objects. The constructor name is always the same as the class name.<br>
o	A constructor is similar to a method, except for 2 differences. Constructors have no return type, (not even void) and the name of the constructor is always the same name as the name of the class.<br>
•	Just like methods, a constructor also has a <span class="bbcode-b">body</span>, which are a sequence of statements that is executed when a new object is constructed.<br>
•	Constructors can take on different parameters, that is how they are differentiated since all constructors in the same class have the same name. (more on constructors later)<br>
•	The public methods and constructors of a class makes up its public interface.<br>
<span class="bbcode-u"><span class="bbcode-b">3.2 Commenting the public interface</span></span><br>
•	A <span class="bbcode-u"><span class="bbcode-b">documentation comment</span></span> is placed before the class or method definition that is being documented. It starts with a /**, a special comment delimeter used by the javadoc utility. Then you describe the method’s purpose. Then, for each method parameter, you supply a line that starts with <span class="bbcode-b"><a class="mention" href="/u/param">@param</a></span>, followed by the parameter name and a short explanation. Finally you supply a line that starts with <span class="bbcode-b"><a class="mention" href="/u/return">@return</a></span>, describing the return value. You omit the <a class="mention" href="/u/param">@param</a> tag for methods that have no parameters, and you omit the <a class="mention" href="/u/return">@return</a> tag for methods whose return type is void.<br>
•	The <span class="bbcode-b">javadoc </span>utility copies the first sentence of each comment to a summary table in the HTML documentation.<br>
•	Use documentation comments to describe the classes and public methods of your program.<br>
•	Provide documentation comments for every class, every method, every parameter, and every return value.<br>
<span class="bbcode-u"><span class="bbcode-b">3.3 Instance fields</span></span><br>
•	An object stores its data in <span class="bbcode-b">instance fields</span>.<br>
•	A <span class="bbcode-b">field </span>is the storage location inside a block of memory.<br>
•	An <span class="bbcode-b">instance </span>of a class is an object of the class.<br>
•	The class declaration specifies the instance fields. An instance field declaration consists of:<br>
o	An access specifier (usually <span class="bbcode-i">private</span>)<br>
	Private means that the method can only be accessed by methods of the same class.<br>
o	The type of the instance field (such as <span class="bbcode-i">double</span>)<br>
o	The name of the instance field (such as <span class="bbcode-i">balance</span>)<br>
•	By making instance fields private, all data access must occur through public methods.<br>
•	They are effectively hidden from the programmer who uses a class.<br>
•	The process of hiding the data and providing methods for data access is called encapsulation.<br>
<span class="bbcode-u"><span class="bbcode-b">3.4 Implementing Constructors and Methods</span></span><br>
•	Constructors contain instructions to initialize the instance fields of an object.<br>
o	Often times you will need 2 constructors, one that sets all fields to a default and one that sets them to user-supplied values.<br>
•	Use the <span class="bbcode-b">return </span>statement to specify the value that a method returns to its caller.<br>
o	The return statement instructs the method to terminate and return an output to the statement that called the method.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/some-java-term-definitions/347275/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/some-java-term-definitions/347275/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 04 Jul 2010 13:41:29 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-347275-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/some-java-term-definitions/347275.rss">Some Java term definitions</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
