<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>&quot;Error loading your profile. Please contact Customer Support.&quot; Please help!</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/error-loading-your-profile-please-contact-customer-support-please-help/553718</link>
    <description>Ok so I can log in just fine for the first time but then when I try to log back in for a second time a message pops up where it usually says &quot;Invalid username/password&quot; and stuff but for me it says &quot;Error loading your profile. Please contact Customer Support.&quot; and in the server dialog it says

&quot;log4j: WARN No appenders could be found for logger (org.apache.mina.filter.executor.ExectutorFilter). &quot;
&quot;log4j: WARN Please initialize the log4j system properly.&quot;

i&#39;ve tryed fixing on my own and searching online for solutions but came up with nothing so any help would be appreciated!

Please atleast be respectful even if you dont want to help I left rune-server because the people over there were straight up fucking dicks and staff were as useless as a fucking rock. Sorry had to get that off chest... well mind i guess seeing how i didnt say it in real life lol :)</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 01 Nov 2015 05:00:11 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/error-loading-your-profile-please-contact-customer-support-please-help/553718.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>&quot;Error loading your profile. Please contact Customer Support.&quot; Please help!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@vancepm vancepm]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/vancepm">@vancepm</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Ok so I can log in just fine for the first time but then when I try to log back in for a second time a message pops up where it usually says “Invalid username/password” and stuff but for me it says “Error loading your profile. Please contact Customer Support.” and in the server dialog it says</p>
<p>"log4j: WARN No appenders could be found for logger (org.apache.mina.filter.executor.ExectutorFilter). "<br>
“log4j: WARN Please initialize the log4j system properly.”</p>
<p>i’ve tryed fixing on my own and searching online for solutions but came up with nothing so any help would be appreciated!</p>
<p>Please atleast be respectful even if you dont want to help I left rune-server because the people over there were straight up fucking dicks and staff were as useless as a fucking rock. Sorry had to get that off chest… well mind i guess seeing how i didnt say it in real life lol <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=5" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/error-loading-your-profile-please-contact-customer-support-please-help/553718/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/error-loading-your-profile-please-contact-customer-support-please-help/553718/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 01 Nov 2015 05:00:11 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-553718-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/error-loading-your-profile-please-contact-customer-support-please-help/553718.rss">&quot;Error loading your profile. Please contact Customer Support.&quot; Please help!</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
