<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Claws of Guthix</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/claws-of-guthix/518861</link>
    <description>[center]https://twitter.com/Claws_of_Guthix
[/center]


Claws of Guthix is and has been a unique concept that I have been working on privately for the last several months. I am using a heavily modified moparclassic revision and client which enables security and complete control over the server and content yadayadayada. 

[b]Introduction[/b]
Claws of Guthix is intended to pursue a different &#39;world&#39; compared to the traditional RSC private servers we have all played. Upon registering players get to choose which god they want to represent (Sara, Zammy, Guthix). Each god has their own homeland that you share with other members. As a team you can assemble your homeland any way you would like. You can buy defensive npcs that protect your god and these npcs can even be upgraded (l1 - men, l2 - guards, l3 - knights, l4 - Paladins). 

If you&#39;re not interested in the combat aspects of things you can certainly train skills, you can even buy your homeland a furnace (quest required to purchase) Don&#39;t worry only one member of your team needs to complete the quest! If you&#39;re not interested in smithing you can always buy your homeland a spinning wheel! Each homeland is unique in it&#39;s own different way relevant to each god. You as a player will learn that your homeland is limited and the ultimate treasure is out in the mysterious world. You will discover new quests, new monsters and rivals.

[b]Safe Zones[/b]
Playing the game you will notice that you can attack anyone you want (other than the people on your own team ofc). You can fight off other teams anywhere on the map except quest locations and banks. 

[b]Point System[/b]
The point system revolves around each team and their capability to work as a team. As a team you will complete tasks that will reward points. Points are added up after after each game session the winning team is announced along side some prizes. Oh, you can also gain points by killing other god members or invading homelands.

[b]&#39;Game Session&#39;?[/b]
Unfortunately all good things come to an end. We all know rsc servers die, it just happens. COG will rely on game sessions (more like &#39;seasons&#39;) to determine winning teams. I am unsure if a wipe will be needed, up to the players.

[b]Misc[/b]
-10-20x exp rate
-New updated projectile sprites
-Changed around weapons so the 2hs are not top dog.
-8 Completely new quests.
-114 edited npcs
-Homeland and upgrade system
-Team chat
-Minimap shows colors of players in relationship to team.
-Safe zones
-Drop rates completed (similar to last stand but better)</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2013 15:39:51 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/claws-of-guthix/518861.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Claws of Guthix</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@waj waj]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/waj">@waj</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>DRAGON PARTIES??</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/claws-of-guthix/518861/16">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/claws-of-guthix/518861/16</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2013 15:39:51 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-518861-16</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/claws-of-guthix/518861.rss">Claws of Guthix</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Claws of Guthix</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@nacional nacional]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/nacional">@nacional</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>anytime bro</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/claws-of-guthix/518861/15">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/claws-of-guthix/518861/15</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2013 02:49:30 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-518861-15</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/claws-of-guthix/518861.rss">Claws of Guthix</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Claws of Guthix</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Rodgerwilco Rodgerwilco]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/rodgerwilco">@Rodgerwilco</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Active project is active. Thanks to nacional for inspiring me to push through the dreaded landscape of rsc…</p>
<p><img src="http://i.imgur.com/VfJ8leK.png" alt width="562" height="442"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/claws-of-guthix/518861/14">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/claws-of-guthix/518861/14</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2013 02:47:39 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-518861-14</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/claws-of-guthix/518861.rss">Claws of Guthix</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Claws of Guthix</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Crooks Crooks]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/crooks">@Crooks</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>You got it bro, the whole concept will be amazing and hopefully some new faces, not the same twats over and over…</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/claws-of-guthix/518861/13">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/claws-of-guthix/518861/13</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2013 14:44:32 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-518861-13</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/claws-of-guthix/518861.rss">Claws of Guthix</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Claws of Guthix</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Rodgerwilco Rodgerwilco]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/rodgerwilco">@Rodgerwilco</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>‘Haters’… anyone who trolls the dead rsc scene really needs to reconstruct their life so they can be more productive to society. This project has been a vision of mine for a few years now and is finally at a realistic stage. I’d say because back in 2008 I didn’t have the knowledge of how to properly achieve what I wanted. Yes, I ran a few servers even moderated some of the ‘decent’ ones.</p>
<p>Then I would also say that it is extremely difficult to break away from the traditional rsc server. With 3hits Realm of Asgard we experienced this first hand and I really thought about a lot of the issues that we dealt with. People, especially rsc vets hate change. I would say we had the most innovative server ever, it just never polled in the player base it needed to thrive.</p>
<p>The timing is right. Since the scene has truly hit rock bottom I feel like this is the perfect time to release a server with a complete new story line and world. In the past few days I began the work of three additional skills and a player movement system that is controlled by mouse keys.</p>
<p>I am not going to ‘market’ this server towards the people that have been around the rsc scene forever nor will I ever care to attempt to recruit them. I am going to really just branch out and attempt to bring in fresh new players who never played a day in their life. I know RSCE has attempted this with the ‘paid advertisements’ but I feel that every server has stuck to the traditional group of people. Fortunately, I know exactly how to break this trend.</p>
<p>If anybody wants to do some landscape work for some donation$, let me know <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=5" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/claws-of-guthix/518861/12">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/claws-of-guthix/518861/12</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2013 06:14:27 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-518861-12</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/claws-of-guthix/518861.rss">Claws of Guthix</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Claws of Guthix</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Stunninhigh Stunninhigh]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/stunninhigh">@Stunninhigh</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Sounds pretty cool man, dont listen to the haters, You got a good thing goin on here.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/claws-of-guthix/518861/11">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/claws-of-guthix/518861/11</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2013 01:26:42 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-518861-11</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/claws-of-guthix/518861.rss">Claws of Guthix</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Claws of Guthix</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Rodgerwilco Rodgerwilco]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/rodgerwilco">@Rodgerwilco</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote" data-post="8" data-topic="518861">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 No Effn Lime:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>This sounds pretty badass. You should post some screenshots</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Like I mentioned before, do you have any specific features you would like to see?</p>
<aside class="quote" data-post="9" data-topic="518861">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 -So Kurupt-:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>do you want me to finish the COG landscape that i half done for you? skype me</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Skype me.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/claws-of-guthix/518861/10">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/claws-of-guthix/518861/10</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2013 00:44:24 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-518861-10</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/claws-of-guthix/518861.rss">Claws of Guthix</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Claws of Guthix</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@So_Kurupt1 -So Kurupt-]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/so_kurupt1">@So_Kurupt1</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>do you want me to finish the COG landscape that i half done for you? skype me</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/claws-of-guthix/518861/9">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/claws-of-guthix/518861/9</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 12 May 2013 04:47:20 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-518861-9</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/claws-of-guthix/518861.rss">Claws of Guthix</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Claws of Guthix</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@No_Effn_Lime No Effn Lime]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/no_effn_lime">@No_Effn_Lime</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>This sounds pretty badass. You should post some screenshots</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/claws-of-guthix/518861/8">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/claws-of-guthix/518861/8</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2013 21:25:21 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-518861-8</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/claws-of-guthix/518861.rss">Claws of Guthix</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Claws of Guthix</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Rodgerwilco Rodgerwilco]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/rodgerwilco">@Rodgerwilco</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote" data-post="3" data-topic="518861">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/waj/40/5_e05bb34c421432ee4d40de30c10af3e5.png" class="avatar"> waj:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Not sure if to take this serious or not, seen too many posts like this from you.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I would like to first say that it’s not difficult to do what I am doing, basic edits at most.</p>
<p>This project is just those posts finally <span class="bbcode-i">near</span> complete. Same concept and same ideas expressed earlier. I would love to run the server but I just can’t for two reasons. The first reason is because I need to actually play the server, I have to get out of the administrators mind set and play it legit. This way I can see exactly what the players enjoy, what they hate and how I could improve the overall game play. I have been around the scene for several years now and  I have experienced and witnessed the limited abilities of an admins. They don’t understand a players mind set and I hope to eliminate this problem by finding someone (mature, friendly, experienced) who is willing to help.</p>
<p>The second reason is simply because the RSC scene is full of the same scumbags since day one. I do enjoy some of the players but the RSC scene tends to have a bunch of assholes who just troll. There is no patience or comprehension on the players end when updates or real life events create drastic times for server owners/moderators. Like our entire purpose is to sit behind a computer and serve our players 24/7 breakfast lunch and dinner. They nit pick every little detail (which is beneficial in some cases). It’s not much of a problem until you realize they have been doing this for several years to every owner.</p>
<p>I don’t intend to make any money from this nor would I ever think about making money from a RSC server. I have always been for the community and really ask for nothing in return. I am willing to fund the project out of my own pockets just so a few players can experience what I have been working on. I don’t care if this gets 10 players or 100 players, that’s not the point. The point is and always has been to do something unique and out of the box with RSC. It truly is unique, you don’t know what is around the next corner. There are no quest guides, no help involved. As a team you will conquer new monsters, obstacles and find new treasures. I wanted to revamp that original RSC feeling where you first log in and you have no idea what the hell is going on and I finally feel like I am close to accomplishing it.</p>
<p>The only huge thing right now is the landscape, I need someone who has some free time on their hands and we can discuss other concerns privately. If I can’t find someone who is willing to help I will continue to work on this with my very limited free time and hopefully… just hopefully launch it later.</p>
<aside class="quote" data-post="2" data-topic="518861">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/tigerclan/40/5_e05bb34c421432ee4d40de30c10af3e5.png" class="avatar"> tigerclan:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Wow, this actual sounds amazing. Any screenies?</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Anything specific you would like me to post? I will also be launching a trailer on youtube briefly showing the new features and content (when the landscape is complete)</p>
<aside class="quote quote-modified" data-post="6" data-topic="518861">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/tomorroww/40/5_e05bb34c421432ee4d40de30c10af3e5.png" class="avatar"> Tomorroww:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Sounds like a good concept if it actually takes off. You may think about lowering the XP rate though. If it’s 10-20x and the max stat is 60ish before unlocking stuff you will achieve max stats in 30 minutes.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>A concern I had with the exp rate is what if someone new joined the team in a later stage of the game? They would be required to no-life to catch up to even be considered a help. 10x exp rate is what I felt comfortable with when testing it out but it can always be changed. After level 75 in a skill the exp rate became 20x to stop the deathly grind. Just do keep in mind it was set this way for testing purposes and can be changed.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/claws-of-guthix/518861/7">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/claws-of-guthix/518861/7</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2013 20:22:04 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-518861-7</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/claws-of-guthix/518861.rss">Claws of Guthix</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Claws of Guthix</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Tomorroww Tomorroww]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/tomorroww">@Tomorroww</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Sounds like a good concept if it actually takes off. You may think about lowering the XP rate though. If it’s 10-20x and the max stat is 60ish before unlocking stuff you will achieve max stats in 30 minutes.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/claws-of-guthix/518861/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/claws-of-guthix/518861/6</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2013 15:04:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-518861-6</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/claws-of-guthix/518861.rss">Claws of Guthix</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Claws of Guthix</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@imthenull imthenull]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/imthenull">@imthenull</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“RSCShadow, post:4, topic:518861”][quote author=waj link=topic=637129.msg4295737#msg4295737 date=1368193125]<br>
Not sure if to take this serious or not, seen too many posts like this from you.<br>
[/quote]Yeah I wouldn’t worry about it.[/quote]qft</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/claws-of-guthix/518861/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/claws-of-guthix/518861/5</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2013 15:02:21 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-518861-5</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/claws-of-guthix/518861.rss">Claws of Guthix</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Claws of Guthix</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@RSCShadow RSCShadow]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/rscshadow">@RSCShadow</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“waj, post:3, topic:518861”]Not sure if to take this serious or not, seen too many posts like this from you.[/quote]Yeah I wouldn’t worry about it.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/claws-of-guthix/518861/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/claws-of-guthix/518861/4</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2013 13:39:20 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-518861-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/claws-of-guthix/518861.rss">Claws of Guthix</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Claws of Guthix</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@waj waj]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/waj">@waj</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Not sure if to take this serious or not, seen too many posts like this from you.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/claws-of-guthix/518861/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/claws-of-guthix/518861/3</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2013 13:38:45 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-518861-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/claws-of-guthix/518861.rss">Claws of Guthix</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Claws of Guthix</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@tigerclan tigerclan]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/tigerclan">@tigerclan</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Wow, this actual sounds amazing. Any screenies?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/claws-of-guthix/518861/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/claws-of-guthix/518861/2</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2013 10:24:45 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-518861-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/claws-of-guthix/518861.rss">Claws of Guthix</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Claws of Guthix</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Rodgerwilco Rodgerwilco]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/rodgerwilco">@Rodgerwilco</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[center]<a href="https://twitter.com/Claws_of_Guthix" rel="nofollow noopener">https://twitter.com/Claws_of_Guthix</a><br>
[/center]</p>
<p>Claws of Guthix is and has been a unique concept that I have been working on privately for the last several months. I am using a heavily modified moparclassic revision and client which enables security and complete control over the server and content yadayadayada.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Introduction</span><br>
Claws of Guthix is intended to pursue a different ‘world’ compared to the traditional RSC private servers we have all played. Upon registering players get to choose which god they want to represent (Sara, Zammy, Guthix). Each god has their own homeland that you share with other members. As a team you can assemble your homeland any way you would like. You can buy defensive npcs that protect your god and these npcs can even be upgraded (l1 - men, l2 - guards, l3 - knights, l4 - Paladins).</p>
<p>If you’re not interested in the combat aspects of things you can certainly train skills, you can even buy your homeland a furnace (quest required to purchase) Don’t worry only one member of your team needs to complete the quest! If you’re not interested in smithing you can always buy your homeland a spinning wheel! Each homeland is unique in it’s own different way relevant to each god. You as a player will learn that your homeland is limited and the ultimate treasure is out in the mysterious world. You will discover new quests, new monsters and rivals.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Safe Zones</span><br>
Playing the game you will notice that you can attack anyone you want (other than the people on your own team ofc). You can fight off other teams anywhere on the map except quest locations and banks.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Point System</span><br>
The point system revolves around each team and their capability to work as a team. As a team you will complete tasks that will reward points. Points are added up after after each game session the winning team is announced along side some prizes. Oh, you can also gain points by killing other god members or invading homelands.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">‘Game Session’?</span><br>
Unfortunately all good things come to an end. We all know rsc servers die, it just happens. COG will rely on game sessions (more like ‘seasons’) to determine winning teams. I am unsure if a wipe will be needed, up to the players.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Misc</span><br>
-10-20x exp rate<br>
-New updated projectile sprites<br>
-Changed around weapons so the 2hs are not top dog.<br>
-8 Completely new quests.<br>
-114 edited npcs<br>
-Homeland and upgrade system<br>
-Team chat<br>
-Minimap shows colors of players in relationship to team.<br>
-Safe zones<br>
-Drop rates completed (similar to last stand but better)</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/claws-of-guthix/518861/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/claws-of-guthix/518861/1</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2013 10:19:57 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-518861-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/claws-of-guthix/518861.rss">Claws of Guthix</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
