<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>End Point - Apocalyptic Survival</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/end-point-apocalyptic-survival/538728</link>
    <description>[CENTER][IMG]http://i.cubeupload.com/B1FD9w.png[/img]

• Introduction: While developing Enigma, I&#39;ve been playing lots of Zombie FPS, it came to me that instead of developing a typical PVP server, why not develop a Survival server? This is because I don&#39;t see much servers out involving the aspect so I thought I&#39;d incorporate the features already implemented into Enigma and transforming it into an Apocalyptic Survival. The goal of the game is to survive, obvious right? but it&#39;s a bit harder than you&#39;d expect. The open world is applicable to all players, you can fight off hordes of zombies in order to protect yourself and to earn gear to upper your skill in the world of destruction. Safe Zones will be provided within specific regions for you lye down and relax while resupplying yourself. The danger of running of from these zones can cause catastrophic results, Players will be able to hunt you for your arsenal and loot them off you, or you can team up with them and provide heavy support for one another. Aside from surviving, you have a problem, you are poisoned along the game, to keep alive and resist turning into a mutated infection, you must cook the animals you kill in order to feed yourself and keep yourself well. Much more to be said but so little time to say it. Are you ready?



• Server Layout &amp; Features: Open World, NPC Dependent, Poisoned, PVP, Clans, Safe Zones, Regions, Different Classes of Monsters, Bosses, Specific Regions with Specific Items to encourage transport and PVP., Markets, Guards, Diaries, Quests, Much more!


• Overall Goal: This server is meant to give a unique gaming experience to those who haven&#39;t had one, it will be a friendly but competitive community that deals with smooth game play, innovative knowledge, and definite memories for those who want them. Everyone talks of past experiences that define memorable things that cannot be upheld once more, but to hell with the old experiences we can fabricate new ones and allow them to be better than those of our preterit ones.


• Development Log:

[CODE] 
• 1/1/2014: Started End Point
• 1/1/2014: Home is: Port Phasmatys
• 1/1/2014: Diaries Base Complete
• 1/2/2014: Skeletal Apes on Crash Island Invasion Complete
• 1/3/2014: Cooking Base Done
• 1/3/2014: Fishing Base Done
• 1/3/2014: Skeletal Horror Added
• 1/3/2014: Poison Base Added
• 1/6/2014: Dialogue Progression
• 1/6/2014: Fishing Configurations Progressed
• 1/7/2014: Thirst &amp; Hunger System Done
• 1/8/2014: Scavenger Feature Done
• 1/9/2014: Removed Indication of: NPCs, Players, etc. on Minimap
• 1/10/2014: Barricade Base Added
• 1/11/2014: Mystery Boxes Added
• 1/14/2014: Slash Bash Added
• 1/16/2014: Pet System Done. 
• 1/17/2014: Resumed Fletching Progression
[/CODE]


[IMG]http://i.cubeupload.com/sHYpQj.png[/img]


[IMG]http://i.cubeupload.com/w5sPeH.png[/img]
[IMG]http://i.cubeupload.com/tzcojv.png[/img]
[IMG]http://i.cubeupload.com/EqX7AM.png[/img]
[IMG]http://gyazo.com/c63b23e3143b67a964087410ef5b70c9.png[/img]
[IMG]http://i.cubeupload.com/4lS9YL.png[/img]
[IMG]http://static1.wikia.nocookie.net/__cb20111122012516/runescape/images/9/9d/Glider_map.png[/img]
[IMG]http://i.cubeupload.com/bhinKl.png[/img]
[IMG]http://i.cubeupload.com/98WuIg.png[/img]
[IMG]http://i.cubeupload.com/FuEvTD.png[/img]
[IMG]http://i.cubeupload.com/1umAnm.png[/img]
[IMG]http://i.cubeupload.com/nxmUtl.png[/img]
[IMG]http://i.cubeupload.com/OQbzug.png[/img]
[IMG]http://i.cubeupload.com/ul406e.png[/img]
[IMG]http://i.cubeupload.com/hS3Qkm.png[/img]
[IMG]http://i.cubeupload.com/woZxe3.png[/img]
[img]http://i.cubeupload.com/Dwy61k.png[/img]
[IMG]http://i.cubeupload.com/rh5Ip2.png[/img]
[IMG]http://i.cubeupload.com/sXLtUg.png[/img]
[IMG]http://i.cubeupload.com/DSbGMm.png[/img]
[IMG]http://i.cubeupload.com/6DNqXi.png[/img]
[IMG]http://i.cubeupload.com/MakeB9.png[/img]
[IMG]http://i.cubeupload.com/6xA90z.png[/img]


[/CENTER]</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2014 04:42:39 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/end-point-apocalyptic-survival/538728.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>End Point - Apocalyptic Survival</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Synergize Synergize]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/synergize">@Synergize</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[CENTER]<img src="http://i.cubeupload.com/TN09Z7.png" alt width="" height=""></p>
<p>Moar Progression with Fletching</p>
<p>• Fletching Step 2: Well, since we’re progressing with Fletching, I fixed up Flax Picking, Flax Picking features Object Deletion for a little bit until it re spawns to avoid Spam Clicking, also Timers have been developed, proper emotes are given to when you pick it up. Along with this comes the Spinning Wheel which’ll give Crafting EXP, you are now able to Spin Flax for Bow Strings, more improvements to come like Magic Root Spinning, first gotta research for its use, EXP rates, etc.</p>
<p>• Pet System Improvement: Clipped Pets via Region Clipping, your pet will get stuck in between Obstacles that you can overcome, however, not to worry, upon logging out and in they’ll be back, they’ll just be lost until you do so.</p>
<p>• Support Signatures: <img src="http://i.cubeupload.com/dPTq2d.png" alt width="" height=""></p>
<p><img src="http://i.cubeupload.com/kh8MoP.png" alt width="" height=""><br>
<img src="http://i.cubeupload.com/gkKCmV.png" alt width="" height=""><br>
<img src="http://i.cubeupload.com/EiGFXm.png" alt width="" height=""></p>
<hr>
<p><img src="http://i.cubeupload.com/q76T3U.png" alt width="" height=""></p>
<p>Hey guys, I’m here with some End Point Progression News! <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=5" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
<p>• Client Search: As of right now, I’m working on providing my players a High Definition experience in End Point. I’m searching through old clients to see what fits best for my likings, I am debating whether which Data to go with, but both clients are of high quality and sustains many features to ensure a memorable, enjoyable experience for the players! <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=5" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
<p>• Client Features and Options:</p>
<ul>
<li>High Definition Texturing for Both Clients.</li>
<li>508 Data Includes: GFX, Animations, Maps, NPCs, Items, etc.</li>
<li>562 Data Includes: GFX, Animations, Maps, NPCs, Items, etc.</li>
</ul>
<p>• What the Client soon will have:</p>
<ul>
<li>Sounds/Music</li>
<li>Fixed White Walls within certain areas</li>
<li>Day &amp; Night via Game Time</li>
<li>Much More!</li>
</ul>
<p><img src="http://i.cubeupload.com/UZs1if.png" alt width="" height=""><br>
<img src="http://i.cubeupload.com/0OSxn4.png" alt width="" height=""><br>
<img src="http://i.cubeupload.com/1VAiMk.png" alt width="" height=""><br>
<img src="http://i.cubeupload.com/YMzIqk.png" alt width="" height=""><br>
<img src="http://i.cubeupload.com/K0lvxY.png" alt width="" height=""></p>
<hr>
<p><img src="http://i.cubeupload.com/TN09Z7.png" alt width="" height=""></p>
<p>• Crafting Base: Started working on Crafting, right now the base should be almost done aside from the easy ClickingButtons part. But I’ll detail the base later on. Worked on Jewelery Carving, Leather Crafting, and a few more configurations.</p>
<p>• Client: I decided to go with the 317 Loading 562 Data, however, consider that many aspects of 508 will also be present to satisfy both worlds. Bugs and Client Errors are still currently being fixed as of now so keep up with more news. Although it is progressing I still have to properly allign the client Icons so that’ll also be done, disregard the cIcons for now.</p>
<p><img src="http://i.cubeupload.com/kqguid.png" alt width="" height=""></p>
<p><img src="http://i.cubeupload.com/UzeC0Q.png" alt width="" height=""></p>
<p><img src="http://i.cubeupload.com/ypMZvW.png" alt width="" height=""></p>
<p><img src="http://i.cubeupload.com/6hp13N.png" alt width="" height=""></p>
<hr>
<p><img src="http://i.cubeupload.com/TN09Z7.png" alt width="" height=""></p>
<p>• Client Base: Fixed Many Errors Today Thanks To My Helper Logic. Crashing is fixed as far as I know. But, still Client Testing is undergoing to ensure proper stability.</p>
<p>So far Bugs Fixed:</p>
<ul>
<li>Pink Hair Fixed</li>
<li>IDK Non-Glitchy Now</li>
<li>Repacked Some Maps To Decrease White Walls (Draynor)</li>
</ul>
<p>• Client Updates (Other):</p>
<ul>
<li>Zoomed Camera View in on Client to make it harder to know what’s around you. With this said I still have to fix up Characters upon being Zoomed in.</li>
<li>Players can now access New Player Clothes upon registration. The IDK has been updated to be with 562 Data, along with the clothes comes different Hair Styles as well.</li>
</ul>
<p>NOTE: Still Have To Fix Hitmask Updating</p>
<p>• Server Bug Note: Must Fix Up Player Updating to Server Sided</p>
<p><img src="http://i.cubeupload.com/aD1Mo3.png" alt width="" height=""></p>
<p><img src="http://i.cubeupload.com/Cqu0pX.png" alt width="" height=""></p>
<hr>
<p><img src="http://i.cubeupload.com/TN09Z7.png" alt width="" height=""></p>
<p>• Woodcutting Base: Working on the Woodcutting Base right now. Woodcutting will be essential to a players in order to benefit from its uses. Barricade Making will soon be implemented so you’ll need Wood in order to fabricate it. It will also be for some use to make fires in order to cook your food.</p>
<p>Right now Key Features Woodcutting Has:</p>
<ul>
<li>Bronze Axes, Iron Axes, Black Axes, Mithril Axes, Adamant Axes, Rune Axes, Dragon Axes &amp; Inferno Adze Support</li>
<li>Wood Stumps Upon Cutting A Trey Down</li>
<li>Proper Respawning</li>
<li>Decent Timers</li>
<li>Main Trees Support: Dead Trees, Trees, Oaks, Willows, Maples, Yews, Magics</li>
</ul>
<p>Features Soon To Be Implemented:</p>
<ul>
<li>Inferno Adze Effect</li>
<li>Other Uncommon Trees</li>
<li>Lumberjack Outfit Bonuses</li>
<li>Bird Nests</li>
</ul>
<p>These Additional Features will be found during either Beta or Public Release.</p>
<p><img src="http://i.cubeupload.com/5Gwmvx.png" alt width="" height=""></p>
<p><img src="http://i.cubeupload.com/Xiel7y.png" alt width="" height=""></p>
<p><img src="http://i.cubeupload.com/mOivzr.png" alt width="" height=""></p>
<p><img src="http://i.cubeupload.com/mGNaFl.png" alt width="" height=""></p>
<p>IF YOU HADN’T JOIN OUR FORUMS JOIN NOW! <a href="http://endpoint-survival.com/" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">http://endpoint-survival.com/</a> For the Latest News!</p>
<hr>
<p><img src="http://i.cubeupload.com/TN09Z7.png" alt width="" height=""></p>
<p>• Mining Base: Finished Mining Base as well. Mining will be used to fabricate weapons alongside with the Smithing/Smelting Skill. A few things need to be fixed but other than it’s done. Took a little time because I had to Update Objects as I didn’t want Old Rock Models, so after implementing them I feel better, but just in case, I have it compatible with Old Models as well.</p>
<p>Right now Key Features Woodcutting Has:</p>
<ul>
<li>New Rock Models</li>
<li>Old Rock Compatibility</li>
<li>Smelting</li>
<li>Most If Not All Rocks Work</li>
<li>Prospecting</li>
<li>Inferno Adze Support</li>
</ul>
<p>Things to be looked at (Notes):</p>
<ul>
<li>Slow Down Timers</li>
<li>Fix Unnecessary Numbers in Smelting Interface</li>
<li>Global Smelting Objects</li>
</ul>
<p>These Additional Features will be found during either Beta or Public Release.</p>
<p><img src="http://i.cubeupload.com/zxWmGn.png" alt width="" height=""></p>
<p><img src="http://i.cubeupload.com/xWmAEY.png" alt width="" height=""></p>
<p><img src="http://i.cubeupload.com/8WX4BX.png" alt width="" height=""></p>
<p>IF YOU HADN’T JOIN OUR FORUMS JOIN NOW! <a href="http://endpoint-survival.com/" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">http://endpoint-survival.com/</a> For the Latest News!</p>
<hr>
<p><img src="http://i.cubeupload.com/TN09Z7.png" alt width="" height=""></p>
<p>• Herblore Base: As of now the Herblore Base is Finished, Herblore will be a skill dependent of the player as you will need them every time you die. Why? As you die, your player becomes weak and hour and a half, drained from 20 Levels in ALL Skills you’ll regain it within the time that passes. Restores will be a hard item to find and make as they’re only dropped by Zombies for now. I’ll find other ways for players to acquire it!</p>
<p>• Herblore Features:</p>
<ul>
<li>Extreme Potion Making</li>
<li>Most Animations</li>
<li>Overload Making</li>
<li>Normal Potion Making</li>
<li>Interface For Potion Making</li>
</ul>
<p>• Prayer Base: So Far, Normal Prayer Effects are done, however still have to implement Head Icons and deactivation when one prayer intrudes the other.</p>
<p>• Client Base: Lots of Fixing to do, But so far, I added Player Chat Heads, as now we are loading 562 Data. So Newer Heads are loaded, just got to have them animated while in dialogue. But, for now, It’s a still frame. Also, I got to find Port Sarim Map-Data, so far, I can’t seem to find an uploaded Version of it, but I’ll continue to search for it.</p>
<p>Here’s some progressive Media Atm.</p>
<p><img src="http://i.cubeupload.com/leuORp.png" alt width="" height=""></p>
<p><img src="http://i.cubeupload.com/6ExlGD.png" alt width="" height=""></p>
<p><img src="http://i.cubeupload.com/jYpLXz.png" alt width="" height=""></p>
<p><img src="http://i.cubeupload.com/Iu5LKY.png" alt width="" height=""></p>
<p><img src="http://i.cubeupload.com/ZSfUZv.png" alt width="" height=""></p>
<p><img src="http://i.cubeupload.com/yK0S0w.png" alt width="" height=""></p>
<p><img src="http://i.cubeupload.com/Lgppz5.png" alt width="" height=""></p>
<p><img src="http://i.cubeupload.com/rqzs9X.png" alt width="" height=""></p>
<p>IF YOU HADN’T JOIN OUR FORUMS JOIN NOW! <a href="http://endpoint-survival.com/" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">http://endpoint-survival.com/</a> For the Latest News! AND YOU CAN RECEIVE VETERAN STATUS IF YOU REGISTER BEFORE ALPHA 2.0’s Release</p>
<hr>
<p><img src="http://i.cubeupload.com/TN09Z7.png" alt width="" height=""></p>
<p>• Building Exploration Base: To Add on to the Explorer Effect in End Point, I’m starting to add Stair Climbing, This so you, the players can explore the open world and explore buildings to find belongings! Or perhaps use them as a shelter to relax. I still have much stairs to add and places to access. I’m still debating whether you’ll see Building Exploration in Alpha or Beta. Relevance will be seen within each building as they have special items for you to receive. For Example: The Cooking Guild will have Cooked and Raw Foods for you to take along with your journey, and so on. Progressive Media is below.</p>
<p>• Barricade Base Progression: Started Barricade Making along with the Barricades posted back a bit back then. As of now, Players are able to now conduct the ingredients to make Barricades. It’s a bit relevant to Runescape’s Plank system. Basically, it requires 75 Crafting to Saw Logs into planks. You need 3 Normal Logs and a Saw to make one plank. You require 3 Planks to ‘Receive’ a Barricade. After you have 3 Planks you must talk to an NPC near the Wildy behind the counter (Where you Pay for Planks on Real RS) It will cost you a certain price for him to make you a barricade, you will also need rope for him to tie it together.</p>
<p>• Texture Toggling: Currently Working on Client Toggling Features for those who don’t have exceptional PC’s. As of now I added Texture Toggling to remove a bit of lag for those who may experience it in the near future. <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=5" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
<p><img src="http://i.cubeupload.com/uNNEsG.png" alt width="" height=""></p>
<p><img src="http://i.cubeupload.com/vR2MUW.png" alt width="" height=""></p>
<p><img src="http://i.cubeupload.com/cO8Rg4.png" alt width="" height=""></p>
<p><img src="http://i.cubeupload.com/zJmpiR.png" alt width="" height=""></p>
<p><img src="http://i.cubeupload.com/cKg7du.png" alt width="" height=""></p>
<p><img src="http://i.cubeupload.com/eQsls7.png" alt width="" height=""></p>
<p><img src="http://i.cubeupload.com/Efo3YS.png" alt width="" height=""></p>
<p>IF YOU HADN’T JOIN OUR FORUMS JOIN NOW! <a href="http://endpoint-survival.com/" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">http://endpoint-survival.com/</a> For the Latest News!</p>
<p>If that link doesn’t work use the Subdomain (Talked to host about fixing this): endpoint.x10.mx/index.php[/center]</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/end-point-apocalyptic-survival/538728/8">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/end-point-apocalyptic-survival/538728/8</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2014 04:42:39 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-538728-8</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/end-point-apocalyptic-survival/538728.rss">End Point - Apocalyptic Survival</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>End Point - Apocalyptic Survival</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Kodiak Kodiak]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/kodiak">@Kodiak</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Bump. Updates coming.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/end-point-apocalyptic-survival/538728/7">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/end-point-apocalyptic-survival/538728/7</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 26 Jan 2014 07:38:54 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-538728-7</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/end-point-apocalyptic-survival/538728.rss">End Point - Apocalyptic Survival</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>End Point - Apocalyptic Survival</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Synergize Synergize]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/synergize">@Synergize</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote" data-post="5" data-topic="538728">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 KroniKz_:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Looks cool!</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Thanks! Expect to see more updates!</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/end-point-apocalyptic-survival/538728/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/end-point-apocalyptic-survival/538728/6</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2014 19:21:29 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-538728-6</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/end-point-apocalyptic-survival/538728.rss">End Point - Apocalyptic Survival</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>End Point - Apocalyptic Survival</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@kronixz kronikz]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/kronixz">@kronixz</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Looks cool!</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/end-point-apocalyptic-survival/538728/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/end-point-apocalyptic-survival/538728/5</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2014 19:03:50 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-538728-5</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/end-point-apocalyptic-survival/538728.rss">End Point - Apocalyptic Survival</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>End Point - Apocalyptic Survival</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Synergize Synergize]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/synergize">@Synergize</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote" data-post="3" data-topic="538728">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 arham 4:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Very nice. I will be tracking this progress.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<aside class="quote" data-post="2" data-topic="538728">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/artem543/40/5_e05bb34c421432ee4d40de30c10af3e5.png" class="avatar"> artem543:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Not bad. Not bad. Good luck.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Thanks guys! <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=5" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/end-point-apocalyptic-survival/538728/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/end-point-apocalyptic-survival/538728/4</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2014 18:41:29 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-538728-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/end-point-apocalyptic-survival/538728.rss">End Point - Apocalyptic Survival</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>End Point - Apocalyptic Survival</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@arham_4 arham 4]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/arham_4">@arham_4</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Very nice. I will be tracking this progress.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/end-point-apocalyptic-survival/538728/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/end-point-apocalyptic-survival/538728/3</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2014 13:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-538728-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/end-point-apocalyptic-survival/538728.rss">End Point - Apocalyptic Survival</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>End Point - Apocalyptic Survival</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@artem543 artem543]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/artem543">@artem543</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Not bad. Not bad. Good luck.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/end-point-apocalyptic-survival/538728/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/end-point-apocalyptic-survival/538728/2</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2014 12:37:53 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-538728-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/end-point-apocalyptic-survival/538728.rss">End Point - Apocalyptic Survival</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>End Point - Apocalyptic Survival</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Synergize Synergize]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/synergize">@Synergize</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[CENTER]<img src="http://i.cubeupload.com/B1FD9w.png" alt width="" height=""></p>
<p>• Introduction: While developing Enigma, I’ve been playing lots of Zombie FPS, it came to me that instead of developing a typical PVP server, why not develop a Survival server? This is because I don’t see much servers out involving the aspect so I thought I’d incorporate the features already implemented into Enigma and transforming it into an Apocalyptic Survival. The goal of the game is to survive, obvious right? but it’s a bit harder than you’d expect. The open world is applicable to all players, you can fight off hordes of zombies in order to protect yourself and to earn gear to upper your skill in the world of destruction. Safe Zones will be provided within specific regions for you lye down and relax while resupplying yourself. The danger of running of from these zones can cause catastrophic results, Players will be able to hunt you for your arsenal and loot them off you, or you can team up with them and provide heavy support for one another. Aside from surviving, you have a problem, you are poisoned along the game, to keep alive and resist turning into a mutated infection, you must cook the animals you kill in order to feed yourself and keep yourself well. Much more to be said but so little time to say it. Are you ready?</p>
<p>• Server Layout &amp; Features: Open World, NPC Dependent, Poisoned, PVP, Clans, Safe Zones, Regions, Different Classes of Monsters, Bosses, Specific Regions with Specific Items to encourage transport and PVP., Markets, Guards, Diaries, Quests, Much more!</p>
<p>• Overall Goal: This server is meant to give a unique gaming experience to those who haven’t had one, it will be a friendly but competitive community that deals with smooth game play, innovative knowledge, and definite memories for those who want them. Everyone talks of past experiences that define memorable things that cannot be upheld once more, but to hell with the old experiences we can fabricate new ones and allow them to be better than those of our preterit ones.</p>
<p>• Development Log:</p>
<p><code> 
• 1/1/2014: Started End Point
• 1/1/2014: Home is: Port Phasmatys
• 1/1/2014: Diaries Base Complete
• 1/2/2014: Skeletal Apes on Crash Island Invasion Complete
• 1/3/2014: Cooking Base Done
• 1/3/2014: Fishing Base Done
• 1/3/2014: Skeletal Horror Added
• 1/3/2014: Poison Base Added
• 1/6/2014: Dialogue Progression
• 1/6/2014: Fishing Configurations Progressed
• 1/7/2014: Thirst &amp; Hunger System Done
• 1/8/2014: Scavenger Feature Done
• 1/9/2014: Removed Indication of: NPCs, Players, etc. on Minimap
• 1/10/2014: Barricade Base Added
• 1/11/2014: Mystery Boxes Added
• 1/14/2014: Slash Bash Added
• 1/16/2014: Pet System Done. 
• 1/17/2014: Resumed Fletching Progression
</code></p>
<p><img src="http://i.cubeupload.com/sHYpQj.png" alt width="" height=""></p>
<p><img src="http://i.cubeupload.com/w5sPeH.png" alt width="" height=""><br>
<img src="http://i.cubeupload.com/tzcojv.png" alt width="" height=""><br>
<img src="http://i.cubeupload.com/EqX7AM.png" alt width="" height=""><br>
<img src="http://gyazo.com/c63b23e3143b67a964087410ef5b70c9.png" alt width="" height=""><br>
<img src="http://i.cubeupload.com/4lS9YL.png" alt width="" height=""><br>
<img src="http://static1.wikia.nocookie.net/__cb20111122012516/runescape/images/9/9d/Glider_map.png" alt width="" height=""><br>
<img src="http://i.cubeupload.com/bhinKl.png" alt width="" height=""><br>
<img src="http://i.cubeupload.com/98WuIg.png" alt width="" height=""><br>
<img src="http://i.cubeupload.com/FuEvTD.png" alt width="" height=""><br>
<img src="http://i.cubeupload.com/1umAnm.png" alt width="" height=""><br>
<img src="http://i.cubeupload.com/nxmUtl.png" alt width="" height=""><br>
<img src="http://i.cubeupload.com/OQbzug.png" alt width="" height=""><br>
<img src="http://i.cubeupload.com/ul406e.png" alt width="" height=""><br>
<img src="http://i.cubeupload.com/hS3Qkm.png" alt width="" height=""><br>
<img src="http://i.cubeupload.com/woZxe3.png" alt width="" height=""><br>
<img src="http://i.cubeupload.com/Dwy61k.png" alt width="" height=""><br>
<img src="http://i.cubeupload.com/rh5Ip2.png" alt width="" height=""><br>
<img src="http://i.cubeupload.com/sXLtUg.png" alt width="" height=""><br>
<img src="http://i.cubeupload.com/DSbGMm.png" alt width="" height=""><br>
<img src="http://i.cubeupload.com/6DNqXi.png" alt width="" height=""><br>
<img src="http://i.cubeupload.com/MakeB9.png" alt width="" height=""><br>
<img src="http://i.cubeupload.com/6xA90z.png" alt width="" height=""></p>
<p>[/CENTER]</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/end-point-apocalyptic-survival/538728/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/end-point-apocalyptic-survival/538728/1</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2014 05:49:05 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-538728-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/end-point-apocalyptic-survival/538728.rss">End Point - Apocalyptic Survival</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
