<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Need help pleaseeeeee :)</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/need-help-pleaseeeeee/400363</link>
    <description>Basically i just need someone to help me fix my firemaking skill. I have it lighting logs (takes a bit longer then hopped), it moves to the west when done, and adds the desired exp lol. What i really need some help with is making it turn back towards the fire after it lights one and how to PREVENT THE NOCLIP BUG when lighting a fire with a wall to the west. If anyone could help me at all, it would be GREATLYYYY appreciated. :D Please and thank you. If you need a copy of my firemaking code I have no problem getting it. Thanks again in advance!!</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 21 Jun 2011 21:03:20 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/need-help-pleaseeeeee/400363.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Need help pleaseeeeee :)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@andy_d_b34st andy d b34st]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/andy_d_b34st">@andy_d_b34st</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Basically i just need someone to help me fix my firemaking skill. I have it lighting logs (takes a bit longer then hopped), it moves to the west when done, and adds the desired exp lol. What i really need some help with is making it turn back towards the fire after it lights one and how to PREVENT THE NOCLIP BUG when lighting a fire with a wall to the west. If anyone could help me at all, it would be GREATLYYYY appreciated. <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/smiley.png?v=5" title=":smiley:" class="emoji" alt=":smiley:"> Please and thank you. If you need a copy of my firemaking code I have no problem getting it. Thanks again in advance!!</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/need-help-pleaseeeeee/400363/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/need-help-pleaseeeeee/400363/1</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 21 Jun 2011 21:03:20 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-400363-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/need-help-pleaseeeeee/400363.rss">Need help pleaseeeeee :)</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
