<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>NVIDIA Provides Physics Technology for PS3</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/nvidia-provides-physics-technology-for-ps3/268005</link>
    <description>http://news.prnewswire.com/DisplayReleaseContent.aspx?ACCT=104&amp;STORY=/www/story/03-17-2009/0004989814&amp;EDATE=

&lt;blockquote&gt;SANTA CLARA, Calif., March 17 /PRNewswire-FirstCall/ -- NVIDIA Corporation today announced that it has signed a tools and middleware license agreement for PLAYSTATION(R)3 (PS3(TM)) with Sony Computer Entertainment Inc (SCEI). As a result, the binary version of the NVIDIA(R) PhysX(R) technology software development kit (SDK) is now available to registered PS3 developers for free download and use on the SCEI Developer Network.

(Logo: http://www.newscom.com/cgi-bin/prnh/20020613/NVDALOGO)

The NVIDIA PhysX software development kit SDK consists of a full-featured API and robust physics engine, designed to give developers, animators, level designers, and artists unprecedented creative control over character and object physical interactions by allowing them to author and preview physics effects in real time. The continued adoption of NVIDIA PhysX technology by the world&#39;s leading content developers is resulting in games that not only look as realistic as possible, but also provides gaming experiences where the world&#39;s literally come to life: environments become highly interactive with effects such as persistent debris, including shattered glass and weapons ammunition, trees that bend in the wind, and water that flows with body and force.

&quot;NVIDIA is proud to support PLAYSTATION 3 as an approved middleware provider,&quot; said Tony Tamasi, senior vice president of content and technology at NVIDIA. &quot;Games developed for the PLAYSTATION 3 using PhysX technology offer a more realistic and lifelike interaction between the games characters and other objects within the game. We look forward to the new games that will redefine reality for a new generation of gamers.&quot;

The PhysX technology source code SDKs for PS3 and all major gaming platforms are available for license directly from NVIDIA. For more information on licensing PhysX SDKs or NVIDIA PhysX technology, please visit: www.nvidia.com/physx.&lt;/blockquote&gt;

One thing you hear developers complain about the PS3 is the development tools, so this can only be a good thing. Right?</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 17 Mar 2009 15:45:20 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Games</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/nvidia-provides-physics-technology-for-ps3/268005.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>NVIDIA Provides Physics Technology for PS3</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@tL tL]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/tl">@tL</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p><a href="http://news.prnewswire.com/DisplayReleaseContent.aspx?ACCT=104&amp;STORY=/www/story/03-17-2009/0004989814&amp;EDATE=" class="onebox" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">http://news.prnewswire.com/DisplayReleaseContent.aspx?ACCT=104&amp;STORY=/www/story/03-17-2009/0004989814&amp;EDATE=</a></p>
<blockquote>SANTA CLARA, Calif., March 17 /PRNewswire-FirstCall/ -- NVIDIA Corporation today announced that it has signed a tools and middleware license agreement for PLAYSTATION(R)3 (PS3(TM)) with Sony Computer Entertainment Inc (SCEI). As a result, the binary version of the NVIDIA(R) PhysX(R) technology software development kit (SDK) is now available to registered PS3 developers for free download and use on the SCEI Developer Network.
<p>(Logo: <a href="http://www.newscom.com/cgi-bin/prnh/20020613/NVDALOGO" rel="nofollow noopener">http://www.newscom.com/cgi-bin/prnh/20020613/NVDALOGO</a>)</p>
<p>The NVIDIA PhysX software development kit SDK consists of a full-featured API and robust physics engine, designed to give developers, animators, level designers, and artists unprecedented creative control over character and object physical interactions by allowing them to author and preview physics effects in real time. The continued adoption of NVIDIA PhysX technology by the world’s leading content developers is resulting in games that not only look as realistic as possible, but also provides gaming experiences where the world’s literally come to life: environments become highly interactive with effects such as persistent debris, including shattered glass and weapons ammunition, trees that bend in the wind, and water that flows with body and force.</p>
<p>“NVIDIA is proud to support PLAYSTATION 3 as an approved middleware provider,” said Tony Tamasi, senior vice president of content and technology at NVIDIA. “Games developed for the PLAYSTATION 3 using PhysX technology offer a more realistic and lifelike interaction between the games characters and other objects within the game. We look forward to the new games that will redefine reality for a new generation of gamers.”</p>
<p>The PhysX technology source code SDKs for PS3 and all major gaming platforms are available for license directly from NVIDIA. For more information on licensing PhysX SDKs or NVIDIA PhysX technology, please visit: <a href="http://www.nvidia.com/physx" rel="nofollow noopener">www.nvidia.com/physx</a>.</p>
</blockquote>
<p>One thing you hear developers complain about the PS3 is the development tools, so this can only be a good thing. Right?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/nvidia-provides-physics-technology-for-ps3/268005/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/nvidia-provides-physics-technology-for-ps3/268005/1</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 17 Mar 2009 15:45:20 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-268005-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/nvidia-provides-physics-technology-for-ps3/268005.rss">NVIDIA Provides Physics Technology for PS3</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
