<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Minor Server Help Required</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/minor-server-help-required/279310</link>
    <description>[s]ZOMG  :eek: :eek: srvr st0ff not wrking[/s]

Recently I&#39;ve been working on making a new server. I&#39;ve seen some tutorials and they often do not go in depth enough. I have some questions I would ask answered,

1. How do I portfoward? I know it&#39;s the step that allows people to connect to the computer, but I don&#39;t know how to do it.

2. How do I get a base and be able to edit it? I have WinRar and I&#39;m able to extract, but what do I do after I extract it.

javac: File not found: *-java
Usage: javac &lt;options&gt; &lt;source files&gt;

Then I get more errors, if I need to post them just say it.

Also I&#39;ve already set the Environmental Variables:

CLASSPATH=C:\Program Files\Java\jdk1.6.0_13\bin;%CLASSPATH%;

That&#39;s my classpath ^^^

C:\Program Files\Java\jdk1.6.0_13\bin;

This is my path ^^^

I haven&#39;t done anything about portfowarding. All I know is that you have to type some IP into the URL bar.

Also regarding two, it won&#39;t help much unless I get a decent base... Can someone post a link to theirs or someone else&#39;s. It would be helpful.

I apologize if I missed anything. If I continue error&#39;s then I will continue posting.

Even if you only answered one question, I will still appreciate it.

Thank you for taking time out of your day to read my post.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 20 May 2009 01:50:12 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/minor-server-help-required/279310.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Minor Server Help Required</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@keyhan3 keyhan3]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/keyhan3">@keyhan3</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p><span class="bbcode-s">ZOMG  :eek: :eek: srvr st0ff not wrking</span></p>
<p>Recently I’ve been working on making a new server. I’ve seen some tutorials and they often do not go in depth enough. I have some questions I would ask answered,</p>
<ol>
<li>
<p>How do I portfoward? I know it’s the step that allows people to connect to the computer, but I don’t know how to do it.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>How do I get a base and be able to edit it? I have WinRar and I’m able to extract, but what do I do after I extract it.</p>
</li>
</ol>
<p>javac: File not found: *-java<br>
Usage: javac  </p>
<p>Then I get more errors, if I need to post them just say it.</p>
<p>Also I’ve already set the Environmental Variables:</p>
<p>CLASSPATH=C:\Program Files\Java\jdk1.6.0_13\bin;%CLASSPATH%;</p>
<p>That’s my classpath ^^^</p>
<p>C:\Program Files\Java\jdk1.6.0_13\bin;</p>
<p>This is my path ^^^</p>
<p>I haven’t done anything about portfowarding. All I know is that you have to type some IP into the URL bar.</p>
<p>Also regarding two, it won’t help much unless I get a decent base… Can someone post a link to theirs or someone else’s. It would be helpful.</p>
<p>I apologize if I missed anything. If I continue error’s then I will continue posting.</p>
<p>Even if you only answered one question, I will still appreciate it.</p>
<p>Thank you for taking time out of your day to read my post.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/minor-server-help-required/279310/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/minor-server-help-required/279310/1</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 20 May 2009 01:50:12 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-279310-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/minor-server-help-required/279310.rss">Minor Server Help Required</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
