<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Hot i fix this error</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/hot-i-fix-this-error/288513</link>
    <description>i wont add me server tovps and make it 24/7
hooow????

client.java:20514: illegal start of expression
        public void startCraft(int actionbutton) {
        ^
1 error
Finished!
Press any key to continue . . .

( any one know</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 13 Jul 2009 11:14:59 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/hot-i-fix-this-error/288513.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Hot i fix this error</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@JavaGuru JavaGuru™]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/javaguru">@JavaGuru</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>K This will be helpfull as i found it on rune-server &lt; You know what i mean.</p>
<p>[code]A lot of people are interested in getting a VPS for there server. So here is a simple guide for starters on how to get and setup there server on a VPS.</p>
<p>*Please Note: If this is in the wrong section, please move it. I wasn’t quite sure where to put it.</p>
<p>Sections:</p>
<ol>
<li>
<p>What is a VPS?</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>How and Where can I buy a VPS?</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>How to I get onto the VPS?</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>How to I get my server up and running on the VPS?</p>
</li>
</ol>
<p>Section 1: What is a VPS?<br>
*Please Note: The term “server” is not referring to your RSPS.</p>
<p>Advanced Definition:<br>
A virtual private server or VPS (also known as a virtual dedicated server, a VDS, or virtual server) is a method of partitioning one physical server into multiple servers. Each one of these servers has the appearance and capabilities (with it’s own allocated resourced) as it if were running it’s own dedicated server. Each VPS can run its own full-fledged operating system, and each server can be independently rebooted.<br>
(Source)</p>
<p>My, more basic definiton:<br>
A VPS is like having a dedicated computer, doing almost nothing but hosting your server. This is what makes it faster than hosting the server on your personal computer, because it doesn’t have other programs etc, hogging all the resources. The difference between a VPS and a dedicated server, is that a VPS is a computer, that is somehow (I’m not exactly sure how they do this), split up into multiple “sections”. It is like it’s very own computer, but there are actually other people running stuff on the same server as you are, they are just using a different part of it. A dedicated server, is an entire computer hosting the server, and is not split up into “sections”. The advantage to having a VPS over a dedicated server, is that it costs much less money.</p>
<p>Section 2: How and Where can I buy a VPS?</p>
<p>First off, to buy a VPS, you need to have money. I recommend using PayPal over a credit/debit card, as it is more secure. You can set up a PayPal account via <a href="http://PayPal.Com" rel="nofollow noopener">PayPal.Com</a>, but BE WARNED: You must confirm your PayPal account before you can spend your money on most things. Confirming your account, requires a Bank Account.</p>
<p>Secondly, you can buy a VPS from many websites, Google It. There are a few websites I can recommend though.</p>
<p><a href="http://OpticVps.Com" class="onebox" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">OpticVps.Com</a><br>
OpticVps is great, their servers have a great internet connection, and are not overly expensive. OpticVps is what I use to host my server, and they have been great so far. If you have $33 or more to spend per month, use them.</p>
<p><a href="http://Profithost.Net" class="onebox" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Profithost.Net</a><br>
Recommended to me by a member of Rune-Server, and they have decent dedicated servers if you have some money to spend.</p>
<p><a href="http://VpsLand.Com" class="onebox" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">VpsLand.Com</a><br>
VpsLand has very cheap VPS’s. If you are on a tight budget, I recommend you use them, but keep in mind, your aren’t going to get a very fast VPS using the Lite kit.<br>
Note: I have also heard from reports Vpsland is very laggy.</p>
<p>Section 3: How to I get onto the VPS?</p>
<p>Once you have purchased you VPS, should receive and e-mail with the IP, username, and password, of your VPS. Once you have that info, open up the Remote Desktop Connection program, I believe it comes by default with any Windows operating system. It should be located in C:\Windows\System32. Once you have that open, type in the IP address that came with the e-mail that was sent to you, then hit Connect. After that it should ask you for a username and password, again, enter the info that came with the e-mail sent to you and hit Ok. It should open up a new window, that looks like a computer. Congratulations, you are now on your VPS.</p>
<p>Section 4: How to I get my server up and running on the VPS?</p>
<p>To get your server up and running on your VPS, you first need to download Java and JDK. So, log into your VPS and download them both. Download Java Here and Download JDK Here.</p>
<p>Next, you need to get your server onto the VPS. I do this by simply minimizing the VPS screen, right clicking the server files on my main computer, clicking copy, then going back onto the VPS, right click on your desktop, and click paste. Walla! You now have your server on your VPS. All you have to do is double click run and your server will be up and running.</p>
<p>*Please Note: If you want a No-Ip, create an account on <a href="http://No-Ip.Com" rel="nofollow noopener">No-Ip.Com</a>, and create a host name/redirect. (Not going to go in-depth).<br>
*Please Note: You do not need to port forward on a VPS<br>
[/code]</p>
<p>Full Credits To Playernt From Rune-Server.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/hot-i-fix-this-error/288513/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/hot-i-fix-this-error/288513/5</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 13 Jul 2009 11:14:59 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-288513-5</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/hot-i-fix-this-error/288513.rss">Hot i fix this error</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Hot i fix this error</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@s3x_4_u_l1f3 s3x 4 u l1f3]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/s3x_4_u_l1f3">@s3x_4_u_l1f3</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>thanks</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/hot-i-fix-this-error/288513/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/hot-i-fix-this-error/288513/4</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 13 Jul 2009 10:25:42 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-288513-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/hot-i-fix-this-error/288513.rss">Hot i fix this error</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Hot i fix this error</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Explisionist Explisionist]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/explisionist">@Explisionist</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>“I want to add my server to a vps, and make it 24/7. how do i do it?”</p>
<p>Please use proper grammar, and find a vps, buy it, and then read the instructions.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/hot-i-fix-this-error/288513/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/hot-i-fix-this-error/288513/3</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 13 Jul 2009 10:24:35 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-288513-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/hot-i-fix-this-error/288513.rss">Hot i fix this error</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Hot i fix this error</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Elven_Dremor Elven Dremor]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/elven_dremor">@Elven_Dremor</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>first of all you need to pay… for the vps<br>
second, it should give you instructions when you buy it</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/hot-i-fix-this-error/288513/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/hot-i-fix-this-error/288513/2</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 13 Jul 2009 10:23:20 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-288513-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/hot-i-fix-this-error/288513.rss">Hot i fix this error</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Hot i fix this error</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@s3x_4_u_l1f3 s3x 4 u l1f3]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/s3x_4_u_l1f3">@s3x_4_u_l1f3</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>i wont add me server tovps and make it 24/7<br>
hooow???</p>
<p>client.java:20514: illegal start of expression<br>
public void startCraft(int actionbutton) {<br>
^<br>
1 error<br>
Finished!<br>
Press any key to continue . . .</p>
<p>( any one know</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/hot-i-fix-this-error/288513/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/hot-i-fix-this-error/288513/1</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 13 Jul 2009 09:37:52 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-288513-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/hot-i-fix-this-error/288513.rss">Hot i fix this error</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
