<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Help, please</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/help-please/278638</link>
    <description>Alright. Well I&#39;ve currently created a Client, and Server. I got two questions.

I want to know if their is a way that I can fix it so it does not show which IP to connect to. Like, you can&#39;t fill it out, but it&#39;s just there. You can click log in, and it will still log you in without typing anything in the IP collum.

Here is a picture of what I mean : 
[IMG]http://i40.tinypic.com/euou8w.jpg[/img]

It shows the IP, but you don&#39;t have to fill it out to connect. Is there a way I can remove that? Because you can&#39;t even fill it out. It automatically connects when you click log in.


Also, my other question is how can I remove items from the shops. I don&#39;t want people to buy claws from the shops. In what file can I fix this? And change prices, all that good stuff...

Thanks in advance![br][br][size=1]Posted on: May 16, 2009, 10:31:59 am[/size][hr]Please, need help, kinda fast. =/[br][br][size=1]Posted on: May 16, 2009, 11:47:27 am[/size][hr]sgfggfdhghgh</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 16 May 2009 17:49:49 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/help-please/278638.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Help, please</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Cuban0_Ftw Cuban0 Ftw]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/cuban0_ftw">@Cuban0_Ftw</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Go into your client’s folder and delete the server IP address. You can edit prices on items in item.cfg, go down to the item you want to edit the price on and change it, the 2nd set of numbers is the one you want to change the price on. Go into shops.cfg and find the shop where the d claws are and delete it.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/help-please/278638/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/help-please/278638/2</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 16 May 2009 17:49:49 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-278638-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/help-please/278638.rss">Help, please</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Help, please</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Rickpwns Rickpwns]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/rickpwns">@Rickpwns</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Alright. Well I’ve currently created a Client, and Server. I got two questions.</p>
<p>I want to know if their is a way that I can fix it so it does not show which IP to connect to. Like, you can’t fill it out, but it’s just there. You can click log in, and it will still log you in without typing anything in the IP collum.</p>
<p>Here is a picture of what I mean :<br>
<img src="http://i40.tinypic.com/euou8w.jpg" alt width="140" height="120"></p>
<p>It shows the IP, but you don’t have to fill it out to connect. Is there a way I can remove that? Because you can’t even fill it out. It automatically connects when you click log in.</p>
<p>Also, my other question is how can I remove items from the shops. I don’t want people to buy claws from the shops. In what file can I fix this? And change prices, all that good stuff…</p>
<p>Thanks in advance![br][br][size=1]Posted on: May 16, 2009, 10:31:59 am[/size][hr]Please, need help, kinda fast. =/[br][br][size=1]Posted on: May 16, 2009, 11:47:27 am[/size][hr]sgfggfdhghgh</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/help-please/278638/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/help-please/278638/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 16 May 2009 16:14:38 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-278638-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/help-please/278638.rss">Help, please</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
