<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Help Please</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/help-please/357229</link>
    <description>Im using an exion&#39;s base server and client which is based off of Project Insanity. I can not find out where to put my models for custom items Ive tryed everywhere there is no models folder I dont even no where the models are that the client supports i have tryed hiding then un hidding it makes no difference the files arent hidden there just not here. All I have found is a file called models.idx which I dont no how or what i need to open idx files because with notepad its a bunch of random stuff and theres another called models.dat which when I try to open in datmaker I get a message that sais invalid file format. Other than that in a folder called data theres a bunch of .dat files but they wont open in datmaker eaither and theres only like 20 so I dont think there the item models but thats the only place where a bunch of .dat files are it doesnt make any sense.

any help is apreciated.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 27 Aug 2010 09:06:43 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/help-please/357229.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Help Please</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@frozon566 frozon566]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/frozon566">@frozon566</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Im using an exion’s base server and client which is based off of Project Insanity. I can not find out where to put my models for custom items Ive tryed everywhere there is no models folder I dont even no where the models are that the client supports i have tryed hiding then un hidding it makes no difference the files arent hidden there just not here. All I have found is a file called models.idx which I dont no how or what i need to open idx files because with notepad its a bunch of random stuff and theres another called models.dat which when I try to open in datmaker I get a message that sais invalid file format. Other than that in a folder called data theres a bunch of .dat files but they wont open in datmaker eaither and theres only like 20 so I dont think there the item models but thats the only place where a bunch of .dat files are it doesnt make any sense.</p>
<p>any help is apreciated.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/help-please/357229/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/help-please/357229/1</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Aug 2010 09:06:43 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-357229-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/help-please/357229.rss">Help Please</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
