<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Help please!</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/help-please/90498</link>
    <description>Hello MoparScape community, I recently came back into playing MoparScape, and I followed this guide and I get a Error from using testscape. here is the guide.

[code] Difficulty: 3/10-1/10. If you follow the guide &#39;Correctly&#39;, and watch the movie, then it will be more like a 1/10.

Assumed Knowledge: How to copy and paste, how to download programs, how to read, as well as watching a movie.

Server Base: Every one.

Modified Material: Many parts/programs on your computer, Win.rar, Moparscape Client, a server file, No-ip, *You might also need to port forward.*

***Introduction***
I. The Movie!
II. Downloading/Installing The Most Recent Form Of Java.
III. The Variables 
III. Getting Win.rar - Extracting Servers/Clients.
IV. Setting Up A Client/Server.
V. Setting Up No-Ip
VI. Port Forwarding.
VII. Creating A Website For Your Server.
VIII Creating A Forum For Your Server.

I. The Movie!
I have gone above and beyond. I have made a movie to show you exactly how to adjust settings on your computer to allow you to run a server. It is a movie that follows the format of this guide. I would advise you to watch the movie first, and then continue on with the rest of this guide, and when you need to refer back to the movie, thats what its there for.

Download the movie here and extract it using win.rar. Then double click on the file that uses the internet to run. A movie will start to run in your internet browser. It should explain everything that you need to know. 

If you find the above part to be complicated, then just play this video. It will show you how to download and play the movie.

To play the how to run the server movie video, &lt;-Click Here-&gt;

II. Downloading/Installing The Most Recent Form Of Java.
Java SE Development Kit 6, also know as JDK 6. IS what most of the private servers you have played on use. To run a server, you need a form of Java. So we will be using the latest version JDK 6.

Download JDK 6.

When you go to download JDK 6. You will see this page.



Click on the download button that I circled in red, and then you will be taken to a new page. There is a part that says accept, and decline, click the accept and the page will be refreshed and then click on the download version I circled in this picture.



Click on the off line download option that best fits your system, and follow the instructions.

III. The Variables 

Now we need to set the variables to allow your computer to run your server, as well as a type of client.

1.) To start off click start menu &gt; go to my computer &gt; right click on my computer &gt;Click properties &gt; then advanced.

You should see a menu such as this;



2.) Now setting the environmental variables. 

Click environmental variables, the button circled in red above. Then click new under system variables. *IMPORTANT DO NOT ADD A NEW &#39;User Variables&#39; ADD A NEW &#39;System Variable&#39;.*

Under System Variables click the New button, and a window will pop up with two sections to fill in. 

In the box that says, Variable Name and type 
Code:
classpathand for the Value, add this in 
Code:
C:\Program Files\Java\Java\jdk1.6.0\bin\Then click ok.

Now look for a SYSTEM VARIABLE called path. Highlight it once by clicking once on it and click edit.

Rename it PATH now for the Variable Value replace the old on with this one 
Code:
%SystemRoot%\system32;%SystemRoot%;%SystemRoot%\Sy stem32\Wbem;C:\Program Files\QuickTime\QTSystem\;C:\Program Files\Java\jdk1.6.0\binClick ok and then click ok on the computer properties screen.
Now it would be best if you restarted your computer now. It might help for the new version of Java to take affect.
Then that should be it for the variables.

IV. Getting Win.rar - Extracting Servers/Clients.
1.) First off, you need to get either of these programs. 
(Q. What do they do?)
(A. They are programs used to extract documents that have been compressed, so that they can be redistributed on-line. When you download a file on-line. It is usually compressed. You need to extract the files so that you can use them. Just download one of the following programs, follow the setup instructions. Then go to the program you downloaded, in our case a client and server, right click it and click on the option that says &#39;extract&#39; And the program should begin to extract the files to where ever the file is. When it is done, you can access the document. There is a picture of an example in this thread.)

a.)win.rar ~ I prefer this program over the other, but either one works.

b.)7zip.rar ~ It does the same thin as win.rar.

Just follow the instructions that the program provides, and you should be good  .

IV. Setting Up A Client/Server. Download Moparscape 3.2 because it is a very reliable source to use.
It will say your download is ready at the bottom of the screen. So scroll down to the bottom and click the part that says download.
Now follow the download instructions.

Now where ever you saved your client, go to it, and start the installation part, it will take a while.

Well done! You now have a client, which enables you to play on a private server!

Now the server!

Today - 4-05-07, there are probably more then a thousand sources to chose from. From my experience most SUX! There are a few that do stand out. My favorite source would be a source called ReenScape. It is just like RuneScape, and is most likely the cleanest source so far. I have put together a list of sources that are decent servers to use, you may chose any one, it doesn&#39;t matter. 

1.) - ReenScape &lt;- Most recent version, a very clean source. Very organized, which makes it easy to edit the server. You do have to know where to look. ~ Just click it to download it.

2.) - Project 16 v3 A very popular source. Great for starters. This is not the most recent version. ~MegaUpload.

3.) - TestScape - One of the most popular servers, most of the tutorials you read for servers are based on this server, or an edited version of it. ~ MegaUpload.

4.) - PimpScape - The most popular pking server around! ~ MegaUpload.

5.) - CheezScape 80 - The base of just about every source out there. ~MegaUpload.

Those are the basic servers, pick any one which you would like to try and follow the rest of the guide.

When the download is complete, the server should look similar to A stack of books. Right click on it and click the option call &quot;extract here&quot; and the server will start to unzip. 

Congratulations you now have a server!

Example of extracting;

Now you want to play on your server? Then follow these instructions.
Once you have your server downloaded you need to extract the files. If you followed the instructions right then go to where ever you told the internet to save the server and you should see this,



Follow the instructions that are included in the picture. If you follow those instructions correctly you should have a folder called &quot;1.4&quot; you should rename this folder to the name you would like your server to be called.

ex. I want my server&#39;s name to be &#39;Bad Scape&#39; so I will rename the folder to &#39;Bad Scape&#39; so that I know what that folder is, and can find my server a little bit more easily.

Now open up your server folder and you should see a few folders, Data, scr, and server. Then there should be a .bat program called compile, and one called run. 

*You will learn how to change names latter on in the tutorial.*

If you downloaded the correct version of Java, and set the variables right, then double click on compile, and a program should pop up. Give it about twenty seconds to load. 

The compile, is like a save button for a server, except it is more advanced. If you make an update in the server you must use the compile after ward so that the update can take effect. If you made a mistake then the compile will tell you what you did and where, so you can easily go in and change what ever you did.
Double click on the file called compile.bat.
After about ten to twenty seconds you should get this message 
Code:
Note: stream.java uses or overrides a deprecated API.
Note: Recompile with -Xlint:deprecation for details.
Press any key to continue . . .Press any key ... and the compile will close. Then double click on run.bat. And you should get a message saying that a port has been started on port 43594.

If you get this message when you click on compile.bat Compiling...

Code:
&#39;javac&#39; is not recognized as an internal or external command,
operable program or batch file.
Press any key to continue . . .Then you do not have Java, or you messed up your Variables. Go back to part one and read over it again.

If you get this message in your compile 
Code:
The system cannot find the path specified.
press any key to continue . . .Then the compile is saying you did not set the variable called &#39;Path&#39; correctly, again go back to part one and read the Variables par again.

Now the fun part for you, bad for people trying to help, The part where you edit your server!
I am just going to tell you how to change the name of your server here, look in the other tutorials to find some cool stuff to add to your server.

To start on changing the name of your server you need to go to your server folder, open it, then open the folder called &#39;Scr&#39; . Now open the document named client.java.
Now hit Ctrl+H and a window will pop up saying &quot;Find what:&quot; and &quot;Replace with:&quot; .

In the place that says &quot;Find what:&quot; add the name of the server you are using, and now in the box that says &quot;Replace with:&quot; add the name you want your server to be called.
[/code] I keep getting a Javac Error or a path not specified error. PLEASE HELP THANK YOu!</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 04 Aug 2009 08:36:27 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/help-please/90498.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Help please!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@hyphy_ftw hyphy ftw]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/hyphy_ftw">@hyphy_ftw</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>This is called gravedigging. Look at the date the last post on the topic was made befor posting on it, like this one, it is over a year old. Why bother?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/help-please/90498/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/help-please/90498/3</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 04 Aug 2009 08:36:27 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-90498-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/help-please/90498.rss">Help please!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Help please!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Turk017 Turk017]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/turk017">@Turk017</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>You have to edit the jdk versions in the .bat files and the enviromental variables part.<br>
(correct me if im wrong :P)</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/help-please/90498/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/help-please/90498/2</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 04 Aug 2009 08:30:29 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-90498-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/help-please/90498.rss">Help please!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Help please!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Sebo Sebo]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/sebo">@Sebo</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Hello MoparScape community, I recently came back into playing MoparScape, and I followed this guide and I get a Error from using testscape. here is the guide.</p>
<p>[code] Difficulty: 3/10-1/10. If you follow the guide ‘Correctly’, and watch the movie, then it will be more like a 1/10.</p>
<p>Assumed Knowledge: How to copy and paste, how to download programs, how to read, as well as watching a movie.</p>
<p>Server Base: Every one.</p>
<p>Modified Material: Many parts/programs on your computer, Win.rar, Moparscape Client, a server file, No-ip, <em>You might also need to port forward.</em></p>
<p><em><strong>Introduction</strong></em><br>
I. The Movie!<br>
II. Downloading/Installing The Most Recent Form Of Java.<br>
III. The Variables<br>
III. Getting Win.rar - Extracting Servers/Clients.<br>
IV. Setting Up A Client/Server.<br>
V. Setting Up No-Ip<br>
VI. Port Forwarding.<br>
VII. Creating A Website For Your Server.<br>
VIII Creating A Forum For Your Server.</p>
<p>I. The Movie!<br>
I have gone above and beyond. I have made a movie to show you exactly how to adjust settings on your computer to allow you to run a server. It is a movie that follows the format of this guide. I would advise you to watch the movie first, and then continue on with the rest of this guide, and when you need to refer back to the movie, thats what its there for.</p>
<p>Download the movie here and extract it using win.rar. Then double click on the file that uses the internet to run. A movie will start to run in your internet browser. It should explain everything that you need to know.</p>
<p>If you find the above part to be complicated, then just play this video. It will show you how to download and play the movie.</p>
<p>To play the how to run the server movie video, &lt;-Click Here-&gt;</p>
<p>II. Downloading/Installing The Most Recent Form Of Java.<br>
Java SE Development Kit 6, also know as JDK 6. IS what most of the private servers you have played on use. To run a server, you need a form of Java. So we will be using the latest version JDK 6.</p>
<p>Download JDK 6.</p>
<p>When you go to download JDK 6. You will see this page.</p>
<p>Click on the download button that I circled in red, and then you will be taken to a new page. There is a part that says accept, and decline, click the accept and the page will be refreshed and then click on the download version I circled in this picture.</p>
<p>Click on the off line download option that best fits your system, and follow the instructions.</p>
<p>III. The Variables</p>
<p>Now we need to set the variables to allow your computer to run your server, as well as a type of client.</p>
<p>1.) To start off click start menu &gt; go to my computer &gt; right click on my computer &gt;Click properties &gt; then advanced.</p>
<p>You should see a menu such as this;</p>
<p>2.) Now setting the environmental variables.</p>
<p>Click environmental variables, the button circled in red above. Then click new under system variables. <em>IMPORTANT DO NOT ADD A NEW ‘User Variables’ ADD A NEW ‘System Variable’.</em></p>
<p>Under System Variables click the New button, and a window will pop up with two sections to fill in.</p>
<p>In the box that says, Variable Name and type<br>
Code:<br>
classpathand for the Value, add this in<br>
Code:<br>
C:\Program Files\Java\Java\jdk1.6.0\bin\Then click ok.</p>
<p>Now look for a SYSTEM VARIABLE called path. Highlight it once by clicking once on it and click edit.</p>
<p>Rename it PATH now for the Variable Value replace the old on with this one<br>
Code:<br>
%SystemRoot%\system32;%SystemRoot%;%SystemRoot%\Sy stem32\Wbem;C:\Program Files\QuickTime\QTSystem;C:\Program Files\Java\jdk1.6.0\binClick ok and then click ok on the computer properties screen.<br>
Now it would be best if you restarted your computer now. It might help for the new version of Java to take affect.<br>
Then that should be it for the variables.</p>
<p>IV. Getting Win.rar - Extracting Servers/Clients.<br>
1.) First off, you need to get either of these programs.<br>
(Q. What do they do?)<br>
(A. They are programs used to extract documents that have been compressed, so that they can be redistributed on-line. When you download a file on-line. It is usually compressed. You need to extract the files so that you can use them. Just download one of the following programs, follow the setup instructions. Then go to the program you downloaded, in our case a client and server, right click it and click on the option that says ‘extract’ And the program should begin to extract the files to where ever the file is. When it is done, you can access the document. There is a picture of an example in this thread.)</p>
<p>a.)win.rar ~ I prefer this program over the other, but either one works.</p>
<p>b.)7zip.rar ~ It does the same thin as win.rar.</p>
<p>Just follow the instructions that the program provides, and you should be good  .</p>
<p>IV. Setting Up A Client/Server. Download Moparscape 3.2 because it is a very reliable source to use.<br>
It will say your download is ready at the bottom of the screen. So scroll down to the bottom and click the part that says download.<br>
Now follow the download instructions.</p>
<p>Now where ever you saved your client, go to it, and start the installation part, it will take a while.</p>
<p>Well done! You now have a client, which enables you to play on a private server!</p>
<p>Now the server!</p>
<p>Today - 4-05-07, there are probably more then a thousand sources to chose from. From my experience most SUX! There are a few that do stand out. My favorite source would be a source called ReenScape. It is just like RuneScape, and is most likely the cleanest source so far. I have put together a list of sources that are decent servers to use, you may chose any one, it doesn’t matter.</p>
<p>1.) - ReenScape &lt;- Most recent version, a very clean source. Very organized, which makes it easy to edit the server. You do have to know where to look. ~ Just click it to download it.</p>
<p>2.) - Project 16 v3 A very popular source. Great for starters. This is not the most recent version. ~MegaUpload.</p>
<p>3.) - TestScape - One of the most popular servers, most of the tutorials you read for servers are based on this server, or an edited version of it. ~ MegaUpload.</p>
<p>4.) - PimpScape - The most popular pking server around! ~ MegaUpload.</p>
<p>5.) - CheezScape 80 - The base of just about every source out there. ~MegaUpload.</p>
<p>Those are the basic servers, pick any one which you would like to try and follow the rest of the guide.</p>
<p>When the download is complete, the server should look similar to A stack of books. Right click on it and click the option call “extract here” and the server will start to unzip.</p>
<p>Congratulations you now have a server!</p>
<p>Example of extracting;</p>
<p>Now you want to play on your server? Then follow these instructions.<br>
Once you have your server downloaded you need to extract the files. If you followed the instructions right then go to where ever you told the internet to save the server and you should see this,</p>
<p>Follow the instructions that are included in the picture. If you follow those instructions correctly you should have a folder called “1.4” you should rename this folder to the name you would like your server to be called.</p>
<p>ex. I want my server’s name to be ‘Bad Scape’ so I will rename the folder to ‘Bad Scape’ so that I know what that folder is, and can find my server a little bit more easily.</p>
<p>Now open up your server folder and you should see a few folders, Data, scr, and server. Then there should be a .bat program called compile, and one called run.</p>
<p><em>You will learn how to change names latter on in the tutorial.</em></p>
<p>If you downloaded the correct version of Java, and set the variables right, then double click on compile, and a program should pop up. Give it about twenty seconds to load.</p>
<p>The compile, is like a save button for a server, except it is more advanced. If you make an update in the server you must use the compile after ward so that the update can take effect. If you made a mistake then the compile will tell you what you did and where, so you can easily go in and change what ever you did.<br>
Double click on the file called compile.bat.<br>
After about ten to twenty seconds you should get this message<br>
Code:<br>
Note: stream.java uses or overrides a deprecated API.<br>
Note: Recompile with -Xlint:deprecation for details.<br>
Press any key to continue . . .Press any key … and the compile will close. Then double click on run.bat. And you should get a message saying that a port has been started on port 43594.</p>
<p>If you get this message when you click on compile.bat Compiling…</p>
<p>Code:<br>
‘javac’ is not recognized as an internal or external command,<br>
operable program or batch file.<br>
Press any key to continue . . .Then you do not have Java, or you messed up your Variables. Go back to part one and read over it again.</p>
<p>If you get this message in your compile<br>
Code:<br>
The system cannot find the path specified.<br>
press any key to continue . . .Then the compile is saying you did not set the variable called ‘Path’ correctly, again go back to part one and read the Variables par again.</p>
<p>Now the fun part for you, bad for people trying to help, The part where you edit your server!<br>
I am just going to tell you how to change the name of your server here, look in the other tutorials to find some cool stuff to add to your server.</p>
<p>To start on changing the name of your server you need to go to your server folder, open it, then open the folder called ‘Scr’ . Now open the document named client.java.<br>
Now hit Ctrl+H and a window will pop up saying “Find what:” and “Replace with:” .</p>
<p>In the place that says “Find what:” add the name of the server you are using, and now in the box that says “Replace with:” add the name you want your server to be called.<br>
[/code] I keep getting a Javac Error or a path not specified error. PLEASE HELP THANK YOu!</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/help-please/90498/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/help-please/90498/1</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 07 May 2007 04:06:35 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-90498-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/help-please/90498.rss">Help please!</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
