<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Skill minigames</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/skill-minigames/538173</link>
    <description>I&#39;m looking for ideas on skill related minigames. The project I&#39;m working on is a different kind of spawn server, so I&#39;m replacing all the item based skills (Prayer, Runecrafting, Herblore, Smithing, Crafting, Fletching, Firemaking, Farming) with minigames. I&#39;m just stuck on ideas.

What I&#39;ve got so far is a prayer minigame that has you in the gravedigger area, finding bones and giving them to the correct NPC based on clues they give you. I also have a herblore minigame that gives you a riddle and you have to guess the ingredient and give it to the guy. So I&#39;m looking for ideas for other skills, any thoughts you guys have that would somewhat match how I&#39;ve done things so far (Simple, short, etc) would be a huge help.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2014 02:10:05 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/skill-minigames/538173.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Skill minigames</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Docent Limits]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/docent">@Docent</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>No problem</p>
<p>1,000th Post!!! Hello Moparian rank@</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/skill-minigames/538173/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/skill-minigames/538173/4</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2014 02:10:05 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-538173-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/skill-minigames/538173.rss">Skill minigames</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Skill minigames</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@n10si_t n10si t]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/n10si_t">@n10si_t</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I have herblore and prayer already, but I really like your ideas, especially the smithing and mining idea. I’ll definitely take these into consideration, thanks a bunch man</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/skill-minigames/538173/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/skill-minigames/538173/3</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2014 02:08:52 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-538173-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/skill-minigames/538173.rss">Skill minigames</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Skill minigames</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Docent Limits]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/docent">@Docent</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Smithing &amp; Mining : Players have 120 seconds (as a team) to mine as much ore as they can and smelt them into bars, then they have 120 seconds to create the most amount of long swords or whatever you’d like.</p>
<p>Herblore. Find a searchable bush and have it give random leaf related items and whoever gets the most unidentified herbs wins.</p>
<p>Prayer: I was thinking something like barrows where if you buried a bone in a certain area an undead creature will spawn and attack you, killing it will reward Prayer experience and a random piece of armor ranging from bronze to rune.</p>
<p>Crafting: An NPC customer gives random orders, (takes place in crafting guild), and the player is required to fulfill each order.</p>
<p>Firemaking &amp; Woodcutting: Clue based, you must cut a certain log and light it on a certain tile to win.</p>
<p>I hope you like em</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/skill-minigames/538173/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/skill-minigames/538173/2</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2014 02:02:41 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-538173-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/skill-minigames/538173.rss">Skill minigames</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Skill minigames</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@n10si_t n10si t]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/n10si_t">@n10si_t</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I’m looking for ideas on skill related minigames. The project I’m working on is a different kind of spawn server, so I’m replacing all the item based skills (Prayer, Runecrafting, Herblore, Smithing, Crafting, Fletching, Firemaking, Farming) with minigames. I’m just stuck on ideas.</p>
<p>What I’ve got so far is a prayer minigame that has you in the gravedigger area, finding bones and giving them to the correct NPC based on clues they give you. I also have a herblore minigame that gives you a riddle and you have to guess the ingredient and give it to the guy. So I’m looking for ideas for other skills, any thoughts you guys have that would somewhat match how I’ve done things so far (Simple, short, etc) would be a huge help.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/skill-minigames/538173/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/skill-minigames/538173/1</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2014 00:48:29 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-538173-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/skill-minigames/538173.rss">Skill minigames</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
