<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Please tell me I&#39;m not a horrible person</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/please-tell-me-im-not-a-horrible-person/3082</link>
    <description>I&#39;m sure some of you remember my thread about me and my girlfriend a while back.

We&#39;ve been dating a year a month and 20 days. However, about 7 months into it we started fighting and stuff. She&#39;s bipolar and gets mad easily so that was the problem and I ignored it. I remember my mom telling me that I didn&#39;t have to put up with her because I&#39;m a good kid and shouldn&#39;t have to deal with that if I don&#39;t want to. She has MANY problems, and her dad doesn&#39;t even take care of her. She has nothing in life, an amount of friends I can count on one hand. We had an amazing time together. Now however, I got to thinking a few days ago. I want someone just like her, but withOUT the problems. I know everyone will fight, but when we fight all I ever hear is I hate you, you&#39;re an asshole, and stfu. She got mad one time because I told her to calm down. We&#39;ve almost broken up a few times. She said things would change, and they did for about a month. Just a few days ago she started again though. She can&#39;t control it.

Well I have this friend named Tricia. She&#39;s a cool girl. We started talking a lot, and we emailed each other in Web Page Design, and commented each other&#39;s myspace uncountable times. My girlfriend, being the jealous person she is, freaked out. Yesteday in school, I was with my girlfriend about to go into Current Issues. Tricia is in that class. So my girlfriend was all like where is she I&#39;m gonna beat her ass and shit. I told her if she&#39;s gonna start interfereing with my friends, I am NOT putting up with it. So I left without a word and went to class. Tricia was like wtf was that and I started telling her. My girlfriend came in and dragged me out just to say she wasn&#39;t serious about that and she&#39;s sorry. The rest of that day all I thought about was when to break up with her. She&#39;s an amazing person, but things WON&#39;T change and we&#39;re always going to fight really bad.

So last night we got in a small fight and I told her that I wasn&#39;t taking this anymore, and it&#39;s over. She begged and begged for me to not, but I did. She told me that I was all she had and she didn&#39;t want to lose me. I told her how it was, and that I&#39;m not going to deal with it anymore. She said that she didn&#39;t change before because she never thought I&#39;d actually break up with her. She said that she CAN change and will. I explained to her that it&#39;s not gonna work out anyways because I feel restricted when I&#39;m around her because I can&#39;t express myself without her getting mad. She said that we can both change and it will work. I told her that I want to be able to be myself, and I&#39;m not when I&#39;m with you. Then she started talking about how we thought we would get married and stuff. She finally accepted it last night. Today she&#39;s coming to give me allll my stuff back, and we&#39;re going to go see Posieden. I&#39;m keeping her stuff though.

Now here&#39;s the bad part. The more I think about her and the times we had, the more I regret my decision. However, when I think of the fights and the things I don&#39;t like, I feel glad I did it. Mixed emotions. This Tricia girl, I like already. I started liking her a few weeks ago, nothing more than I simple crush though. She&#39;s pretty and veryyyy funny. My cheeks hurt from laughing a lot when I&#39;m around her. Am I a horrible person for doing this, and then liking another girl? I&#39;m still really sad about us breaking up, because I&#39;m a huge sucker for sad people. The last thing I wanted to do was this, but I felt like I had to.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 20 May 2006 18:53:34 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>General Discussion</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/please-tell-me-im-not-a-horrible-person/3082.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Please tell me I&#39;m not a horrible person</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Xerxes Xerxes]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/xerxes">@Xerxes</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“Taios, post:3, topic:3082”][quote author=Xerxes link=topic=3534.msg34638#msg34638 date=1148145812]<br>
Wtf.</p>
<p>Get a life yo.</p>
<p>Who the fuck writes a story here about their life.<br>
[/quote]</p>
<p>Usually people who are on a last resort.</p>
<p>Xerxes, ever watched Bambi ? =P[/quote]</p>
<p>OMG U HAVE NO LIFE!1111 <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=9" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/please-tell-me-im-not-a-horrible-person/3082/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/please-tell-me-im-not-a-horrible-person/3082/5</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 20 May 2006 18:53:34 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-3082-5</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/please-tell-me-im-not-a-horrible-person/3082.rss">Please tell me I&#39;m not a horrible person</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Please tell me I&#39;m not a horrible person</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@jme jme]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/jme">@jme</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>If you ask me, that sounds like a pretty normal breakup. I’ve never gone through it like that, but I see it happen all the time. I wouldn’t say your a horrible person.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/please-tell-me-im-not-a-horrible-person/3082/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/please-tell-me-im-not-a-horrible-person/3082/4</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 20 May 2006 17:26:23 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-3082-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/please-tell-me-im-not-a-horrible-person/3082.rss">Please tell me I&#39;m not a horrible person</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Please tell me I&#39;m not a horrible person</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Taios Taios]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/taios">@Taios</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“Xerxes, post:2, topic:3082”]Wtf.</p>
<p>Get a life yo.</p>
<p>Who the fuck writes a story here about their life.[/quote]</p>
<p>Usually people who are on a last resort.</p>
<p>Xerxes, ever watched Bambi ? =P</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/please-tell-me-im-not-a-horrible-person/3082/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/please-tell-me-im-not-a-horrible-person/3082/3</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 20 May 2006 17:25:44 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-3082-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/please-tell-me-im-not-a-horrible-person/3082.rss">Please tell me I&#39;m not a horrible person</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Please tell me I&#39;m not a horrible person</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Xerxes Xerxes]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/xerxes">@Xerxes</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Wtf.</p>
<p>Get a life yo.</p>
<p>Who the fuck writes a story here about their life.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/please-tell-me-im-not-a-horrible-person/3082/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/please-tell-me-im-not-a-horrible-person/3082/2</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 20 May 2006 17:23:32 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-3082-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/please-tell-me-im-not-a-horrible-person/3082.rss">Please tell me I&#39;m not a horrible person</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Please tell me I&#39;m not a horrible person</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@SomethingToHide STH]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/somethingtohide">@SomethingToHide</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I’m sure some of you remember my thread about me and my girlfriend a while back.</p>
<p>We’ve been dating a year a month and 20 days. However, about 7 months into it we started fighting and stuff. She’s bipolar and gets mad easily so that was the problem and I ignored it. I remember my mom telling me that I didn’t have to put up with her because I’m a good kid and shouldn’t have to deal with that if I don’t want to. She has MANY problems, and her dad doesn’t even take care of her. She has nothing in life, an amount of friends I can count on one hand. We had an amazing time together. Now however, I got to thinking a few days ago. I want someone just like her, but withOUT the problems. I know everyone will fight, but when we fight all I ever hear is I hate you, you’re an asshole, and stfu. She got mad one time because I told her to calm down. We’ve almost broken up a few times. She said things would change, and they did for about a month. Just a few days ago she started again though. She can’t control it.</p>
<p>Well I have this friend named Tricia. She’s a cool girl. We started talking a lot, and we emailed each other in Web Page Design, and commented each other’s myspace uncountable times. My girlfriend, being the jealous person she is, freaked out. Yesteday in school, I was with my girlfriend about to go into Current Issues. Tricia is in that class. So my girlfriend was all like where is she I’m gonna beat her ass and shit. I told her if she’s gonna start interfereing with my friends, I am NOT putting up with it. So I left without a word and went to class. Tricia was like wtf was that and I started telling her. My girlfriend came in and dragged me out just to say she wasn’t serious about that and she’s sorry. The rest of that day all I thought about was when to break up with her. She’s an amazing person, but things WON’T change and we’re always going to fight really bad.</p>
<p>So last night we got in a small fight and I told her that I wasn’t taking this anymore, and it’s over. She begged and begged for me to not, but I did. She told me that I was all she had and she didn’t want to lose me. I told her how it was, and that I’m not going to deal with it anymore. She said that she didn’t change before because she never thought I’d actually break up with her. She said that she CAN change and will. I explained to her that it’s not gonna work out anyways because I feel restricted when I’m around her because I can’t express myself without her getting mad. She said that we can both change and it will work. I told her that I want to be able to be myself, and I’m not when I’m with you. Then she started talking about how we thought we would get married and stuff. She finally accepted it last night. Today she’s coming to give me allll my stuff back, and we’re going to go see Posieden. I’m keeping her stuff though.</p>
<p>Now here’s the bad part. The more I think about her and the times we had, the more I regret my decision. However, when I think of the fights and the things I don’t like, I feel glad I did it. Mixed emotions. This Tricia girl, I like already. I started liking her a few weeks ago, nothing more than I simple crush though. She’s pretty and veryyyy funny. My cheeks hurt from laughing a lot when I’m around her. Am I a horrible person for doing this, and then liking another girl? I’m still really sad about us breaking up, because I’m a huge sucker for sad people. The last thing I wanted to do was this, but I felt like I had to.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/please-tell-me-im-not-a-horrible-person/3082/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/please-tell-me-im-not-a-horrible-person/3082/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 20 May 2006 17:22:11 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-3082-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/please-tell-me-im-not-a-horrible-person/3082.rss">Please tell me I&#39;m not a horrible person</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
