<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>RSPS 317 New to Coding</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rsps-317-new-to-coding/453158</link>
    <description>Recently after being banned from a server (RovaScape2.net) I am finally deciding to fulfill my hunger to code and run my own server. I will figure out the Java coding along with everything else that comes into complication with a RSPS, but I just need few questions that can be answered by an experienced coder. I&#39;m not asking you to hold my hand, but just a kick in the ass to get me going.

Q1: Coding with 317 Server and Client is told to be the easiest for newbies, but is it possible to update files such as object, items, and character graphics to 525 or maybe even items up to 525+ for chaotics, torva, SOL&#39;s, and more.

Q2: If so, how?

Q3: Could someone supply me with a really good base Client and Source. I know there is a full post on many (to many  :D) RSPS Source and Clients, but there are just so many posts that don&#39;t support the Source an Client along with many Anti-Leach coding.

Q4: Is Java easy to pick up? I&#39;m enlisting in the Marine Corps in 9 months after taking a year break with my father working for his business and conditioning for boot camp, but is it even possible to have a decent RSPS coded and up and running within those 9 months.

Q5: Are RSPS even profitable and played much any more? One of the main reasons I want to open up my own server is to start understanding the world of a business owner, a RSPS is nothing huge, but a small step for me to understand. Plus Java coding has always intrigued me.

I understand many people come here to MoparScape asking any one to hold their hand through the process of making a RSPS, but I am different. I&#39;m just asking for that boost to get me going. I&#39;ll figure out the rest. If you&#39;d like to help me out a little more just give me some detailed directions (I use Windows Vista, I&#39;ve figured out that steps such as portforwarding are a little different with Vista when it comes to Firewall).

If you&#39;d prefer to keep any information private or just give me a some tips, just send me a forum message. It&#39;s greatly appreciated.

Thanks, Eric</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 07 Aug 2012 01:18:21 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rsps-317-new-to-coding/453158.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>RSPS 317 New to Coding</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@tyb97 tyb97]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/tyb97">@tyb97</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p><a href="http://docs.oracle.com/javase/tutorial/reallybigindex.html" class="onebox" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">http://docs.oracle.com/javase/tutorial/reallybigindex.html</a></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rsps-317-new-to-coding/453158/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rsps-317-new-to-coding/453158/6</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 07 Aug 2012 01:18:21 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-453158-6</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rsps-317-new-to-coding/453158.rss">RSPS 317 New to Coding</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>RSPS 317 New to Coding</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Simplicity_Bliss Simplicity Bliss]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/simplicity_bliss">@Simplicity_Bliss</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote quote-modified" data-post="4" data-topic="453158">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/tyb97/40/5_e05bb34c421432ee4d40de30c10af3e5.png" class="avatar"> tyb97:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>If your looking for a good 525, get the Lumbridge Hyperion, that Linux_ released, I didn’t, I just re posted because his links were dead.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Well I’m downloading it now, but could you point me in the direction of where i’d even start fixing codes for skills and adding other things? Is there like something I can read that will kinda teach me about RSPS coding.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rsps-317-new-to-coding/453158/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rsps-317-new-to-coding/453158/5</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 07 Aug 2012 01:15:46 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-453158-5</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rsps-317-new-to-coding/453158.rss">RSPS 317 New to Coding</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>RSPS 317 New to Coding</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@tyb97 tyb97]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/tyb97">@tyb97</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>If your looking for a good 525, get the Lumbridge Hyperion, that Linux_ released, I didn’t, I just re posted because his links were dead.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rsps-317-new-to-coding/453158/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rsps-317-new-to-coding/453158/4</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 06 Aug 2012 23:18:02 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-453158-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rsps-317-new-to-coding/453158.rss">RSPS 317 New to Coding</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>RSPS 317 New to Coding</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Simplicity_Bliss Simplicity Bliss]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/simplicity_bliss">@Simplicity_Bliss</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Hey thank you, I was actually just looking at one of your clients and server I believe, so I really am shooting for a good 525+ then as I like the graphics better and I simply enjoy having Torva and chaotics as well with an abundance of weapons as it simply adds the choice for people to play different.</p>
<p>Dupe method removed.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rsps-317-new-to-coding/453158/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rsps-317-new-to-coding/453158/3</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 06 Aug 2012 22:15:48 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-453158-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rsps-317-new-to-coding/453158.rss">RSPS 317 New to Coding</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>RSPS 317 New to Coding</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@tyb97 tyb97]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/tyb97">@tyb97</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Please remove the dupe you found, we aren’t a community that’s out to destroy others.</p>
<p>1: Yes, but I don’t recommend it, makes the cache gigantic.<br>
2: That I’ve never been able to figure out, if you don’t mind the glitchyness of running a higher cache on a 317, there are plenty of bases that already have higher cache’s loaded.<br>
3: Hyperion. Apollo if you want to learn scripting as well.<br>
4: It is, if you put the effort into it.<br>
5: It is if you get people that like your server.</p>
<p>Again, remove the dupe info, I could see that getting you infracted.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rsps-317-new-to-coding/453158/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rsps-317-new-to-coding/453158/2</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 06 Aug 2012 22:02:28 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-453158-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rsps-317-new-to-coding/453158.rss">RSPS 317 New to Coding</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>RSPS 317 New to Coding</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Simplicity_Bliss Simplicity Bliss]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/simplicity_bliss">@Simplicity_Bliss</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Recently after being banned from a server (<a href="http://RovaScape2.net" rel="nofollow noopener">RovaScape2.net</a>) I am finally deciding to fulfill my hunger to code and run my own server. I will figure out the Java coding along with everything else that comes into complication with a RSPS, but I just need few questions that can be answered by an experienced coder. I’m not asking you to hold my hand, but just a kick in the ass to get me going.</p>
<p>Q1: Coding with 317 Server and Client is told to be the easiest for newbies, but is it possible to update files such as object, items, and character graphics to 525 or maybe even items up to 525+ for chaotics, torva, SOL’s, and more.</p>
<p>Q2: If so, how?</p>
<p>Q3: Could someone supply me with a really good base Client and Source. I know there is a full post on many (to many  :D) RSPS Source and Clients, but there are just so many posts that don’t support the Source an Client along with many Anti-Leach coding.</p>
<p>Q4: Is Java easy to pick up? I’m enlisting in the Marine Corps in 9 months after taking a year break with my father working for his business and conditioning for boot camp, but is it even possible to have a decent RSPS coded and up and running within those 9 months.</p>
<p>Q5: Are RSPS even profitable and played much any more? One of the main reasons I want to open up my own server is to start understanding the world of a business owner, a RSPS is nothing huge, but a small step for me to understand. Plus Java coding has always intrigued me.</p>
<p>I understand many people come here to MoparScape asking any one to hold their hand through the process of making a RSPS, but I am different. I’m just asking for that boost to get me going. I’ll figure out the rest. If you’d like to help me out a little more just give me some detailed directions (I use Windows Vista, I’ve figured out that steps such as portforwarding are a little different with Vista when it comes to Firewall).</p>
<p>If you’d prefer to keep any information private or just give me a some tips, just send me a forum message. It’s greatly appreciated.</p>
<p>Thanks, Eric</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rsps-317-new-to-coding/453158/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rsps-317-new-to-coding/453158/1</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 06 Aug 2012 21:53:08 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-453158-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rsps-317-new-to-coding/453158.rss">RSPS 317 New to Coding</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
