<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>No postage necessary if mailed in the US</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/no-postage-necessary-if-mailed-in-the-us/195683</link>
    <description>http://officeofstrategicinfluence.com/bulkmailer/

&lt;blockquote&gt;You know those obnoxious &quot;refinance your home&quot; or credit card scams offers that you get in the mail? This is called direct marketing, where marketers use a reduced bulk postal rate to send entire forests of paper mail to you. 

Plenty of people think its cute to put the postage-paid envelopes back into the mail as revenge. But really, that&#39;s a real pussy way of dealing with it. I decided to take it to the next level.

Find a shoebox, or a storage bin, or any cardboard box you have laying around. Fill it up with bricks, big blocks of iron, or maybe cement. Tape the box up with everyday packaging tape. Use a junkmail&#39;s postage-paid envelope and tape it neatly to the top cover of the box. NEATLY. And mail it off. Envelope revenge!

A few days later, your package shows up at the junk mailer&#39;s location, and they have to pay for every cent of delivery. Once the cost outweighs the benefit, they will stop sending out direct mail marketing material. And that is my goal.

Doing this has the following beneficial side effects: 

-Since these companies pay the post office, this lightens the load taxpayers need to pay to keep the post office operating

-This creates employment opportunities. The post office keeps cutting staff because of lack of buisness; this gives the post office a huge source of income from the credit card scam companies. 

-This will lead to more cautious bulk mailing. Maybe these junk mailers simply don&#39;t know they are annoying people? Hopefully they will learn very quickly! 

-This makes me laugh maniacly, like a cartoon supervillan.

-This saves trees. Once enough of us do this, the junk mail companies will stop sending us junk. Or at least they will be more discriminate about it. It will save trees and keep the landfills empty! Yay! 

-If we do this enough, the USPS will make so much money, that they will lower postage costs.&lt;/blockquote&gt;</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2008 02:13:49 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>General Discussion</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/no-postage-necessary-if-mailed-in-the-us/195683.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>No postage necessary if mailed in the US</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@sppt sppt]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/sppt">@sppt</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>this is soooo copied from the people from www.fok.nl who had an action to send boxes with tiles in it to UPC, because they had gotten something which came with a subscription without the people knowing.</p>
<p>always nice, sending out bricks and tiles to companies that try to scam you <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/smiley.png?v=6" title=":smiley:" class="emoji" alt=":smiley:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/no-postage-necessary-if-mailed-in-the-us/195683/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/no-postage-necessary-if-mailed-in-the-us/195683/3</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2008 02:13:49 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-195683-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/no-postage-necessary-if-mailed-in-the-us/195683.rss">No postage necessary if mailed in the US</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>No postage necessary if mailed in the US</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@cooper cooper]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/cooper">@cooper</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p><img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/smiley.png?v=6" title=":smiley:" class="emoji" alt=":smiley:"><br>
I want to try this.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/no-postage-necessary-if-mailed-in-the-us/195683/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/no-postage-necessary-if-mailed-in-the-us/195683/2</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2008 01:39:01 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-195683-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/no-postage-necessary-if-mailed-in-the-us/195683.rss">No postage necessary if mailed in the US</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>No postage necessary if mailed in the US</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@xxlegitxx xxlegitxx]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/xxlegitxx">@xxlegitxx</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p><a href="http://officeofstrategicinfluence.com/bulkmailer/" class="onebox" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">http://officeofstrategicinfluence.com/bulkmailer/</a></p>
<blockquote>You know those obnoxious "refinance your home" or credit card scams offers that you get in the mail? This is called direct marketing, where marketers use a reduced bulk postal rate to send entire forests of paper mail to you. 
<p>Plenty of people think its cute to put the postage-paid envelopes back into the mail as revenge. But really, that’s a real pussy way of dealing with it. I decided to take it to the next level.</p>
<p>Find a shoebox, or a storage bin, or any cardboard box you have laying around. Fill it up with bricks, big blocks of iron, or maybe cement. Tape the box up with everyday packaging tape. Use a junkmail’s postage-paid envelope and tape it neatly to the top cover of the box. NEATLY. And mail it off. Envelope revenge!</p>
<p>A few days later, your package shows up at the junk mailer’s location, and they have to pay for every cent of delivery. Once the cost outweighs the benefit, they will stop sending out direct mail marketing material. And that is my goal.</p>
<p>Doing this has the following beneficial side effects:</p>
<p>-Since these companies pay the post office, this lightens the load taxpayers need to pay to keep the post office operating</p>
<p>-This creates employment opportunities. The post office keeps cutting staff because of lack of buisness; this gives the post office a huge source of income from the credit card scam companies.</p>
<p>-This will lead to more cautious bulk mailing. Maybe these junk mailers simply don’t know they are annoying people? Hopefully they will learn very quickly!</p>
<p>-This makes me laugh maniacly, like a cartoon supervillan.</p>
<p>-This saves trees. Once enough of us do this, the junk mail companies will stop sending us junk. Or at least they will be more discriminate about it. It will save trees and keep the landfills empty! Yay!</p>
<p>-If we do this enough, the USPS will make so much money, that they will lower postage costs.</p>
</blockquote>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/no-postage-necessary-if-mailed-in-the-us/195683/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/no-postage-necessary-if-mailed-in-the-us/195683/1</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2008 00:16:34 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-195683-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/no-postage-necessary-if-mailed-in-the-us/195683.rss">No postage necessary if mailed in the US</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
