<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>VPS help?</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/vps-help/468485</link>
    <description>So I bought a VPS with windows server 2003. I got everything up and running, port 43594 is open, got no-ip, my source on it and runs fine. But when the first person tries to connect after I start running the server, they&#39;ll log in, see the gameframe, but everything else will be black, and then get the &quot;connection lost - attempting to re-establish&quot; thing. After that, I lose internet connection on the VPS. I can&#39;t even browse the internet, BUT I&#39;ll have the little connection icon on the bottom right say I&#39;m still connected. I have the firewall disabled if that makes any difference. Any suggestions? :s</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 14 Nov 2012 19:15:18 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/vps-help/468485.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>VPS help?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@mc_wobbla mc wobbla]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/mc_wobbla">@mc_wobbla</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>So I bought a VPS with windows server 2003. I got everything up and running, port 43594 is open, got no-ip, my source on it and runs fine. But when the first person tries to connect after I start running the server, they’ll log in, see the gameframe, but everything else will be black, and then get the “connection lost - attempting to re-establish” thing. After that, I lose internet connection on the VPS. I can’t even browse the internet, BUT I’ll have the little connection icon on the bottom right say I’m still connected. I have the firewall disabled if that makes any difference. Any suggestions? :s</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/vps-help/468485/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/vps-help/468485/1</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 14 Nov 2012 19:15:18 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-468485-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/vps-help/468485.rss">VPS help?</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
