<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>How to put my server on?</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-put-my-server-on/369697</link>
    <description>Okay I&#39;m using a VPS I recently shut a server down the programs it had running was the sourse obviously, some XAMPP program, and another one called RS2 client which showed who was online.

After I closed these down I went on TeamViewer and somebody else put another client up I&#39;m not sure if they changed any ips. But I know that if I run that source, that server will be up.

I need some help in getting the older server up please. I have the source and the XAMPP program, I can&#39;t find that RS2 client (not sure if I need it).

All help if appreciated, Thanks.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 21 Nov 2010 14:42:58 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-put-my-server-on/369697.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>How to put my server on?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@P_o_s_t_m_a_n P o s t m a n]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/p_o_s_t_m_a_n">@P_o_s_t_m_a_n</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Okay I’m using a VPS I recently shut a server down the programs it had running was the sourse obviously, some XAMPP program, and another one called RS2 client which showed who was online.</p>
<p>After I closed these down I went on TeamViewer and somebody else put another client up I’m not sure if they changed any ips. But I know that if I run that source, that server will be up.</p>
<p>I need some help in getting the older server up please. I have the source and the XAMPP program, I can’t find that RS2 client (not sure if I need it).</p>
<p>All help if appreciated, Thanks.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-put-my-server-on/369697/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-put-my-server-on/369697/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 21 Nov 2010 14:42:58 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-369697-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-put-my-server-on/369697.rss">How to put my server on?</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
