<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Creating a Right-Click Menu?</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/creating-a-right-click-menu/249651</link>
    <description>Hey all... I&#39;m editing the Shop system a guy made on Rune-Server... And I&#39;m adding selling. Problem is, I don&#39;t know what values to send for the right menu. I&#39;ve taken this code and edited it... It&#39;s the Deposit Menu when banking.

[code]        p.stream.createFrame(223);
        p.stream.writeWord(27);
        p.stream.writeWordBigEndianA(0);
        p.stream.writeWordBigEndian(0);
        p.stream.writeWordBigEndian(763);
        p.stream.writeWordBigEndian(1150);
        p.stream.writeWordBigEndian(18);[/code]

And the only thing I&#39;ve found that changes the menu items was the 1150 value... Editing the other values either does nothing, removes the options, or I get dced. I know that the createFrame creates the menu and I&#39;m guessing the other stuff is some sort of word bank... And determines the items.

Honestly I have no idea what I&#39;m doing and tired of experimenting. There must be an easier way to find the values for the shop menus (Buying and Selling).

If I&#39;m wrong about anything, don&#39;t be a dick about it. I was just guessing.

Thanks for helping.

~Lin</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 09 Dec 2008 03:55:11 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/creating-a-right-click-menu/249651.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Creating a Right-Click Menu?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Lin Lin]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/lin">@Lin</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Hey all… I’m editing the Shop system a guy made on Rune-Server… And I’m adding selling. Problem is, I don’t know what values to send for the right menu. I’ve taken this code and edited it… It’s the Deposit Menu when banking.</p>
<p><code>        p.stream.createFrame(223);
        p.stream.writeWord(27);
        p.stream.writeWordBigEndianA(0);
        p.stream.writeWordBigEndian(0);
        p.stream.writeWordBigEndian(763);
        p.stream.writeWordBigEndian(1150);
        p.stream.writeWordBigEndian(18);</code></p>
<p>And the only thing I’ve found that changes the menu items was the 1150 value… Editing the other values either does nothing, removes the options, or I get dced. I know that the createFrame creates the menu and I’m guessing the other stuff is some sort of word bank… And determines the items.</p>
<p>Honestly I have no idea what I’m doing and tired of experimenting. There must be an easier way to find the values for the shop menus (Buying and Selling).</p>
<p>If I’m wrong about anything, don’t be a dick about it. I was just guessing.</p>
<p>Thanks for helping.</p>
<p>~Lin</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/creating-a-right-click-menu/249651/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/creating-a-right-click-menu/249651/1</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 09 Dec 2008 03:55:11 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-249651-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/creating-a-right-click-menu/249651.rss">Creating a Right-Click Menu?</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
