<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Elunity! The Project! Most advanced 317!</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/elunity-the-project-most-advanced-317/534615</link>
    <description>[center][IMG]http://elunity.com/images/elunity.png[/img]

Our advertisement thread: https://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php/topic,653398.0.html
[size=2em]The project! We expect elunity to become the most widly known and played 317 delta to date. 
Follow our progress!
Updates:
[/size][code]
Updates:
10/26
-Lowered Onyx&#39;s in store to only ten. -As suggested by U.
-Added antiDos
-110 magic required for master wand. (For future update)
-Fixed baby d bones (useing on alter) -As suggested by Alex.
-Added developers world. (Dev&#39;s only) No more restarting to test things! Only restart with an actual update or at 120!
-Added a third world, for our new potential update, should it come.: http://elunity.com/forums/index.php/topic,423.0.html

Talked about many things. And Focusing on new ideas and fixes for Elunity. 
Sorry for lack of updates today.


Updates:
10/25
Excuse my typing, keyboard is having water damage shortages and is acting up.
-Fixed clipping in many places (still alot more to go)
-Fixed count down timer on 120 min restart
-Added smelting for gold ore into gold bar (for future update) 115 smithing
-Added Gilded totem to abby demons. (for future update)
-Removed ice bow from armadyl Rangers.
-Removed Ring of Wealth from Armadyl Rangers.
-Lowered Ring Of wealths percentage to 1% more likely. (for future update)
-Added ring of wealth to Abby Demons.  (for future update)
-Added Gold Bar Smithing. (for future update) 115 smithing
-Added mining of gold ore. 115 mining.  (for future update) (Rocks not spawned in yet.)
-110 prayer to equip holy symbol. (for future update)
-110 prayer to equip unholy symbol. (for future update)
-Finished the effect of new Armour soon to come.
Some other minor things.

New in progress:
-New Holy symbol effect.
-New Unholy symbol effect.
-New armour for all members, with a great new ability. (start going for 115 thieveing, smithing, mining, and magic to be ready for it.)
-Another quest
-Ancient prayers
Some other still in discussion.

Thank you,
-The Elunity Team!

Edit: IceBows are still dropped in the armadyl dungeon in gwd.

Updates:
10/24:
Fixed a few problems that would null the Server.
Adding in a code when not commented out, to give free Subscription status to all. (Future Promotional Use)
Finishing the SQL integration for our 2 new quests coming soon.
Fixed an error with our 2013 Halloween event. (quest)
Fixed a Logout Rollback issue.
Fixed admin&#39;s hide button, which even when deactive was making them hidden from some players.
Setup our second account database for when the first fills.
Made some more changes to fix an eco problem that has occurred in past versions.
More progress on our CE Toolkit, to be released soon.
More to come.

Updates:
10/23
Due to the usual problem with economy in past R***S**, I have made a few changes.

PK Shop:
All gs&#39;s require 225 instead of 180 pk points.
Dragon Claws cost 500 instead of 400 pk points.
Dragon Dagger at 10 instead of 5 pk points.

Rune shop:
There are now 20k of each rune. And prices have rised.

Drop rates:
All drop rates have been substantially lowered.

Shops: 
Various items have gone up dramatically in price.
Buying items in bulk will now be more expensive.

This is my starting attempt to fix the economy problems that past times have had.
With shops higher in price, my idea is people will start making them on there on for a actual profit in skills that usually would not be profitable due to shops selling so cheap.  

To even out all the price changes for beginners, you now start with 7.5m gp.

I will see how this works and edit it as such.

Text:
&quot;Donator&quot; words have been replaced with &quot;subscriber&quot;.

Bugs: Multi drop by barrows bug has been corrected and fixed.

Thank you,
-Ruzylo.


Updates:
10/19
Forums:
-Boards have been fixed making the Forums look less scattered.
-Elunity Radio Redirect Board is now in place.
-Child boards have been put in place.
-Some boards have been split (Goals &amp; Achievements are now 2 boards)
-Report is now a general section with the child boards:
Report a Bug
Report a Staff
Report a Player
-Our home pages has had some minor link and text edits.
-The Forums has had some board name changes.
-Warning Templates are being made.

Ingame:

Done.
-H&#39;ween Event from 2009 has been turned into the 2013 event! Talk to the Witch at Hbank.
-You can now fish Sea Turtles.
You must be a donator to Fish them, cook, eat, trade, buy and pick them up.
There are two locations in the Donator zone, to fish them. Both by the Dragon ore on
each side. ::dz.
They require 105 fishing to fish, and give 2050 XP each.
They require 105 cooking to cook, and give 2550 XP each.
They heal 25hp compared to mantas 20hp.
-Elunity&#39;s Official radio has been setup and is usually always brodcasting!
Tune in here.
-All dragon items now require 60 attack to wield.
-New command ::team has been added. Shows you a list of all Ingame Staff.
-Starter has changed to as follows:
500k
Dragon Scimitar
Bronze Scimitar
Monk Robe Top
Monk Robe Bottom
Amulet of Strength
Climbing Boots
15 Noted Shrimp
5 Noted Super Attack Potions
5 Noted Super Strength Potions
Runes


Still in progress:
2 New quests.
CE Toolkit being fixed.
Attack delay. 
Tombstone on death (including item pickup on death)
Memory usage clean up.
Removing useless/unused code.
Vote4reward script.
New prayers.
Anti-bot scripts. 
Randoms.
Oak tree delay.

Stay Tuned.

Updates:
10/13-10/16
Done:
Fixed range glitch.
Run Delay.
Highscores setup again.
Auto donate setup,
ARK setup. (Email sending problem atm, working on fix)
Simple command changes and fixes.
Smtp setup for forums and ingame.
Everything starting as a service.
Some small minor bugs.
And some more.

Been working on:
2 New quests.
Attack delay. 
Tombstone on death (including item pickup on death)
Memory usage clean up.
Removing useless/unused code.
Vote4reward script.
New prayers.
Anti-bot scripts. 
Randoms.
Oak tree delay.

~Elunity Team.
[/code][size=2em]
Just posted our adv thread and will put a basic copy of what weve done and what elunity is here. Expect constant updates.:
[/size]


Elunity is not like your average servers you see around here it is very unique.  The server is 24/7, has a very experienced team and has custom which no other server has.  The server has grate load of bosses so the PvM’s are spoiled for choice and PvP’s are just as spoiled with all the spec weapons  in-game. Elunity allows players to use the yell (::yell) cannel without having to donate, all you need is over one hour online time, this is to stop any advertisers. 


Quests:
We have 7 quests already done, not including holiday quests!
We currently have our Halloween quest out!
[IMG]http://img580.imageshack.us/img580/4117/7s3p.png[/img]

Elunity Home:
Here at Elunity we decided to change thing up rather than having home/starting place at edge like every other server; we decided to have our home based in Port Phasmatys. We also based out teleports such as god wars and mini-games.

Main commands:
For all the following command you will need to write two colon’s (:: ) then followed by the name of the command without any space.

The commands are:
Dz (Donator zone)
Home (Port Phasmatys)
Hbank (homebank)
Mine (To mine rune essence)
 Pk (Mage bank)
Team (Staff team)
Yell (self-explanatory)
People (tells you how many people at pits) 
Modhelp (lets mods know you need help and they will come and see you)
Jad (fight cave)
Players (who is on, and how many)

Skills:
Once again Elunity decided they were going to do thing different from other severs rather than having levels going up to 99, we had them going up to 126 with a max xp of 250m and a max combat level of 160, but is wildness it will change to max level going up to 110 and max combat level of 140 (this changes back once you leave the wildness).

PvP:
The main place on Elunity for player killing is hill giants. The main weapons been Dragon Claws Dark bow, Night bow (costom), Seren Godsword (costom), Dragon Cross bow, Vesta long sword and also has all regular godswords, along with &quot;E&quot; Godswords  donaters.

When you have killed a player you will get 2 pk points which allows you to later spend the pk points on a certain rewards from the Pk shop. There are also recorded stats for your kills, you will have the ability to wear the Player killing skill capes. 200 kills for Un-trimmed cape, 400 kills &amp; .6 ratio for (t) cape, and 600 kills &amp; .8 ratio for (m) cape.

Pvm:
Elunity has wide range of bosses for to go PvM, some of them are; Sea Troll Queen, Jad, Dagganoth Kings, Mithril Dragon, King Black Dragon, Kalphite Queen. But the best bosses are Bandos, Armadyl, Zammy, Saradomin and Corporeal Beast.
These monsters drop the most valuable items on Elunity.

Donators:
You get a 15% increase on all experience you gain, ability to go to  donatorzone ,donator shop, spirit shields, ability to go to the corporeal beast and tormented demons, Vengance, Donator godswords, and much more! 

Pictures:

[url=http://s1180.photobucket.com/user/jimmy786/media/Bosses_zps3d2b7544.png.html][img]http://i1180.photobucket.com/albums/x405/jimmy786/Bosses_zps3d2b7544.png[/img][/url]

[url=http://s1180.photobucket.com/user/jimmy786/media/wuww_zps86786faa.png.html][img]http://i1180.photobucket.com/albums/x405/jimmy786/wuww_zps86786faa.png[/img][/url]

[url=http://s1180.photobucket.com/user/jimmy786/media/pkshop_zps608ea7be.png.html][img]http://i1180.photobucket.com/albums/x405/jimmy786/pkshop_zps608ea7be.png[/img][/url]

[url=http://s1180.photobucket.com/user/jimmy786/media/allpkcapes_zpsd4f62214.png.html][img]http://i1180.photobucket.com/albums/x405/jimmy786/allpkcapes_zpsd4f62214.png[/img][/url]

[url=http://s1180.photobucket.com/user/jimmy786/media/75379939f3b4e7d348e9aaf75ffdba89_zps68f65c1f.png.html][img]http://i1180.photobucket.com/albums/x405/jimmy786/75379939f3b4e7d348e9aaf75ffdba89_zps68f65c1f.png[/img][/url]
[COLOR=&quot;#00FF00&quot;]
Unique Highscores, and some other features. Including one price timed subscription that includes all benefits of a subscriber. Donation system automatically added status when paid, and removed when time runs out.[/COLOR]

[img]http://imageshack.us/a/img593/2827/d3mv.png[/img]
[img]http://imageshack.us/a/img268/4493/e96p.png[/img]
[img]http://imageshack.us/a/img132/9792/c4h.png[/img]

[COLOR=&quot;#00FF00&quot;]Flawless Recovery system with email notifications.[/COLOR]

[img]http://imageshack.us/a/img706/14/yy4f.png[/img]

[COLOR=&quot;#00FF00&quot;]Ce toolkit, still to come (in development still)[/COLOR]

[img]http://imageshack.us/a/img809/1287/2kxn.png[/img]
[img]http://imageshack.us/a/img837/9526/bkbg.png[/img]
[img]http://imageshack.us/a/img132/1552/jbga.png[/img]

[COLOR=&quot;#FF0000&quot;]Thank you, The Elunity Team![/COLOR][/center]</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2013 05:56:06 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/elunity-the-project-most-advanced-317/534615.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Elunity! The Project! Most advanced 317!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@ruzylo Ruzylo]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/ruzylo">@ruzylo</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“nolan2131, post:16, topic:534615”]Great, and those who know me will tell you, my skype is a bit unreliable because I keep it on my phone. Fastest contact is through here.[/quote]Pmed you.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/elunity-the-project-most-advanced-317/534615/17">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/elunity-the-project-most-advanced-317/534615/17</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2013 05:56:06 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-534615-17</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/elunity-the-project-most-advanced-317/534615.rss">Elunity! The Project! Most advanced 317!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Elunity! The Project! Most advanced 317!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@nolan2131 nolan2131]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/nolan2131">@nolan2131</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Great, and those who know me will tell you, my skype is a bit unreliable because I keep it on my phone. Fastest contact is through here.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/elunity-the-project-most-advanced-317/534615/16">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/elunity-the-project-most-advanced-317/534615/16</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2013 05:47:44 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-534615-16</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/elunity-the-project-most-advanced-317/534615.rss">Elunity! The Project! Most advanced 317!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Elunity! The Project! Most advanced 317!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@ruzylo Ruzylo]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/ruzylo">@ruzylo</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“nolan2131, post:14, topic:534615”][quote author=arham 4 link=topic=653410.msg4379020#msg4379020 date=1382933364]<br>
Most advanced 317? Hah.</p>
<p>But good luck though. Shout out to my man nolan2131.<br>
[/quote]</p>
<p>&lt;3, Sudden stop of responding though. Can’t take this project seriously unfortunately.[/quote]Gf’s sister died… Had to support her and been inactive. My appologies. I’m on skype now.</p>
<p>-Edit been waiting for you to add me on skype, which just happened 6 hours ago.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/elunity-the-project-most-advanced-317/534615/15">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/elunity-the-project-most-advanced-317/534615/15</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2013 05:35:14 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-534615-15</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/elunity-the-project-most-advanced-317/534615.rss">Elunity! The Project! Most advanced 317!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Elunity! The Project! Most advanced 317!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@nolan2131 nolan2131]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/nolan2131">@nolan2131</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“arham 4, post:13, topic:534615”]Most advanced 317? Hah.</p>
<p>But good luck though. Shout out to my man nolan2131.[/quote]</p>
<p>&lt;3, Sudden stop of responding though. Can’t take this project seriously unfortunately.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/elunity-the-project-most-advanced-317/534615/14">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/elunity-the-project-most-advanced-317/534615/14</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2013 05:02:57 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-534615-14</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/elunity-the-project-most-advanced-317/534615.rss">Elunity! The Project! Most advanced 317!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Elunity! The Project! Most advanced 317!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@arham_4 arham 4]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/arham_4">@arham_4</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Most advanced 317? Hah.</p>
<p>But good luck though. Shout out to my man nolan2131.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/elunity-the-project-most-advanced-317/534615/13">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/elunity-the-project-most-advanced-317/534615/13</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2013 04:09:24 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-534615-13</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/elunity-the-project-most-advanced-317/534615.rss">Elunity! The Project! Most advanced 317!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Elunity! The Project! Most advanced 317!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@ruzylo Ruzylo]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/ruzylo">@ruzylo</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“Loveandpower, post:10, topic:534615”]Good luck how do you plan to sort the economy?[/quote]Its ruzylo, from paladious. I’ve read your economy guide there and on other forums. I’d love some more tips from you. I made a update based mainly on Eco a few days ago as I’m attempting to make it good. Drop rates are very low along with xp rates. This was my update post:</p>
<p>"10/23 Updates. Mainly for economy.<br>
« on: October 24, 2013, 12:15:39 am »<br>
Not to many updates here.<br>
While I typed this, I decided to add some updates:</p>
<p>Due to the usual problem with economy in past R*<strong>S</strong>, I have made a few changes.</p>
<p>PK Shop:<br>
All gs’s require 225 instead of 180 pk points.<br>
Dragon Claws cost 500 instead of 400 pk points.<br>
Dragon Dagger at 10 instead of 5 pk points.</p>
<p>Rune shop:<br>
There are now 20k of each rune. And prices have rised.</p>
<p>Drop rates:<br>
All drop rates have been substantially lowered.</p>
<p>Shops:<br>
Various items have gone up dramatically in price.<br>
Buying items in bulk will now be more expensive.</p>
<p>This is my starting attempt to fix the economy problems that past times have had.<br>
With shops higher in price, my idea is people will start making them on there on for a actual profit in skills that usually would not be profitable due to shops selling so cheap.</p>
<p>To even out all the price changes for beginners, you now start with 7.5m gp.</p>
<p>I will see how this works and edit it as such.</p>
<p>Text:<br>
“Donator” words have been replaced with “subscriber”.</p>
<p>Bugs: Multi drop by barrows bug has been corrected and fixed.</p>
<p>Thank you,<br>
-Ruzylo."</p>
<p>-Note only runes are really sold in shops, along with arrows ect.<br>
Skilling is a must for the quest req’s and for some items that must be player made by gathering parts and making them you’re self. Ex: Nightbow, 110 wc, to be able to get the night seed from the tree, 110 farming to plant it, 110 wc to cut again, 110 fletch to bow and string it, 115 range to use. Most powerful bow ingame. And untradeable, making people have to get the skills. Same with Corp armour, needing dragon ore, 105 mining, 105 smithing, 105 crafting, to make corp armour, then 110 mage to enchant it with a corp charm. Corp armour makes corp hit less on you. As its nearly impossible to solo, and if soloed would require multiple inventories and take ovr 30 minutes. Making Spirit shield ect rare. Camping most monsters is impossible, and there are many other things to help keep eco going good.</p>
<p>-Posted new update log for 10/25<br>
-Posted new update log for 10/26</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/elunity-the-project-most-advanced-317/534615/12">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/elunity-the-project-most-advanced-317/534615/12</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2013 22:19:29 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-534615-12</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/elunity-the-project-most-advanced-317/534615.rss">Elunity! The Project! Most advanced 317!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Elunity! The Project! Most advanced 317!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Ambokile Ambokile]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/ambokile">@Ambokile</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I can see you’ve put a lot of effort in so far. Nice job.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/elunity-the-project-most-advanced-317/534615/11">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/elunity-the-project-most-advanced-317/534615/11</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2013 18:06:52 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-534615-11</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/elunity-the-project-most-advanced-317/534615.rss">Elunity! The Project! Most advanced 317!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Elunity! The Project! Most advanced 317!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Loveandpower Loveandpower]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/loveandpower">@Loveandpower</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Good luck how do you plan to sort the economy?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/elunity-the-project-most-advanced-317/534615/10">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/elunity-the-project-most-advanced-317/534615/10</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2013 13:36:01 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-534615-10</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/elunity-the-project-most-advanced-317/534615.rss">Elunity! The Project! Most advanced 317!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Elunity! The Project! Most advanced 317!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@ruzylo Ruzylo]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/ruzylo">@ruzylo</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“Clawz fury, post:8, topic:534615”][quote author=ruzylo link=topic=653410.msg4378144#msg4378144 date=1382668115]</p>
<aside class="quote">
<blockquote>
<p>would be better if you werent using delta</p>
<p>nice tho<br>
[/quote]Delta is very unique to me. It’s unused for the most part. To create a delta server to match the quality of newer server’s will be a challenge and a long one at that. But I am committed. Many people use Leached sources that all have the same thing, mines has a unique feel to it, being a delta that is still being advanced and going through fixes and changes. If I can say I have the best developer delta server to date, would this not be an achievement? Many people barely reach success. But to have the best of anything is an achievement in general regardless of how far it gets. However this is my views and yours may be different. Thank you.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>very mature way to look at things. the best of luck with this project, delta or not ;)[/quote]Thank you, I appreciate the luck! Haha.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/elunity-the-project-most-advanced-317/534615/9">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/elunity-the-project-most-advanced-317/534615/9</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2013 04:41:20 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-534615-9</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/elunity-the-project-most-advanced-317/534615.rss">Elunity! The Project! Most advanced 317!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Elunity! The Project! Most advanced 317!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Clawz_fury lare69]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/clawz_fury">@Clawz_fury</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“ruzylo, post:6, topic:534615”][quote author=Clawz fury link=topic=653410.msg4378140#msg4378140 date=1382667646]<br>
would be better if you werent using delta</p>
<p>nice tho<br>
[/quote]Delta is very unique to me. It’s unused for the most part. To create a delta server to match the quality of newer server’s will be a challenge and a long one at that. But I am committed. Many people use Leached sources that all have the same thing, mines has a unique feel to it, being a delta that is still being advanced and going through fixes and changes. If I can say I have the best developer delta server to date, would this not be an achievement? Many people barely reach success. But to have the best of anything is an achievement in general regardless of how far it gets. However this is my views and yours may be different. Thank you.[/quote]<br>
very mature way to look at things. the best of luck with this project, delta or not <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/wink.png?v=5" title=":wink:" class="emoji" alt=":wink:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/elunity-the-project-most-advanced-317/534615/8">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/elunity-the-project-most-advanced-317/534615/8</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2013 04:09:44 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-534615-8</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/elunity-the-project-most-advanced-317/534615.rss">Elunity! The Project! Most advanced 317!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Elunity! The Project! Most advanced 317!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@davidi2 Davidi2]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/davidi2">@davidi2</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>This is not a rule, but I also suggest fixing your BBC code in your post so people dont see random tags all over the place <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/wink.png?v=5" title=":wink:" class="emoji" alt=":wink:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/elunity-the-project-most-advanced-317/534615/7">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/elunity-the-project-most-advanced-317/534615/7</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2013 02:43:31 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-534615-7</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/elunity-the-project-most-advanced-317/534615.rss">Elunity! The Project! Most advanced 317!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Elunity! The Project! Most advanced 317!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@ruzylo Ruzylo]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/ruzylo">@ruzylo</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“Clawz fury, post:4, topic:534615”]would be better if you werent using delta</p>
<p>nice tho[/quote]Delta is very unique to me. It’s unused for the most part. To create a delta server to match the quality of newer server’s will be a challenge and a long one at that. But I am committed. Many people use Leached sources that all have the same thing, mines has a unique feel to it, being a delta that is still being advanced and going through fixes and changes. If I can say I have the best developer delta server to date, would this not be an achievement? Many people barely reach success. But to have the best of anything is an achievement in general regardless of how far it gets. However this is my views and yours may be different. Thank you.</p>
<p>[quote=“Davidi2, post:5, topic:534615”]Hey, removed your website link from your post. Please take note that posting links to a website that has a ‘play’ button/link is not allowed. You can create an advertisement thread and link to that (and in your advertisement thread you can link to this as well), just not link directly.[/quote]My appologies again, I got a link removed on my advertisement thread aswell. I have been following mopar for some time. I suppose I should brush up on the rules.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/elunity-the-project-most-advanced-317/534615/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/elunity-the-project-most-advanced-317/534615/6</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2013 02:28:35 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-534615-6</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/elunity-the-project-most-advanced-317/534615.rss">Elunity! The Project! Most advanced 317!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Elunity! The Project! Most advanced 317!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@davidi2 Davidi2]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/davidi2">@davidi2</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Hey, removed your website link from your post. Please take note that posting links to a website that has a ‘play’ button/link is not allowed. You can create an advertisement thread and link to that (and in your advertisement thread you can link to this as well), just not link directly.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/elunity-the-project-most-advanced-317/534615/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/elunity-the-project-most-advanced-317/534615/5</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2013 02:24:40 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-534615-5</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/elunity-the-project-most-advanced-317/534615.rss">Elunity! The Project! Most advanced 317!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Elunity! The Project! Most advanced 317!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Clawz_fury lare69]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/clawz_fury">@Clawz_fury</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>would be better if you werent using delta</p>
<p>nice tho</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/elunity-the-project-most-advanced-317/534615/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/elunity-the-project-most-advanced-317/534615/4</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2013 02:20:46 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-534615-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/elunity-the-project-most-advanced-317/534615.rss">Elunity! The Project! Most advanced 317!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Elunity! The Project! Most advanced 317!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@ruzylo Ruzylo]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/ruzylo">@ruzylo</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“twins, post:2, topic:534615”]looking good mate[/quote]Appreciate it, thank you.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/elunity-the-project-most-advanced-317/534615/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/elunity-the-project-most-advanced-317/534615/3</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2013 00:00:46 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-534615-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/elunity-the-project-most-advanced-317/534615.rss">Elunity! The Project! Most advanced 317!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Elunity! The Project! Most advanced 317!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@twins twins]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/twins">@twins</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>looking good mate</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/elunity-the-project-most-advanced-317/534615/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/elunity-the-project-most-advanced-317/534615/2</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2013 23:54:29 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-534615-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/elunity-the-project-most-advanced-317/534615.rss">Elunity! The Project! Most advanced 317!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Elunity! The Project! Most advanced 317!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@ruzylo Ruzylo]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/ruzylo">@ruzylo</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[center]<img src="http://elunity.com/images/elunity.png" alt width="" height=""></p>
<p>Our advertisement thread: <a href="https://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php/topic,653398.0.html" rel="nofollow noopener">https://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php/topic,653398.0.html</a><br>
[size=2em]The project! We expect elunity to become the most widly known and played 317 delta to date.<br>
Follow our progress!<br>
Updates:<br>
[/size][code]<br>
Updates:<br>
10/26<br>
-Lowered Onyx’s in store to only ten. -As suggested by U.<br>
-Added antiDos<br>
-110 magic required for master wand. (For future update)<br>
-Fixed baby d bones (useing on alter) -As suggested by Alex.<br>
-Added developers world. (Dev’s only) No more restarting to test things! Only restart with an actual update or at 120!<br>
-Added a third world, for our new potential update, should it come.: <a href="http://elunity.com/forums/index.php/topic,423.0.html" rel="nofollow noopener">http://elunity.com/forums/index.php/topic,423.0.html</a></p>
<p>Talked about many things. And Focusing on new ideas and fixes for Elunity.<br>
Sorry for lack of updates today.</p>
<p>Updates:<br>
10/25<br>
Excuse my typing, keyboard is having water damage shortages and is acting up.<br>
-Fixed clipping in many places (still alot more to go)<br>
-Fixed count down timer on 120 min restart<br>
-Added smelting for gold ore into gold bar (for future update) 115 smithing<br>
-Added Gilded totem to abby demons. (for future update)<br>
-Removed ice bow from armadyl Rangers.<br>
-Removed Ring of Wealth from Armadyl Rangers.<br>
-Lowered Ring Of wealths percentage to 1% more likely. (for future update)<br>
-Added ring of wealth to Abby Demons.  (for future update)<br>
-Added Gold Bar Smithing. (for future update) 115 smithing<br>
-Added mining of gold ore. 115 mining.  (for future update) (Rocks not spawned in yet.)<br>
-110 prayer to equip holy symbol. (for future update)<br>
-110 prayer to equip unholy symbol. (for future update)<br>
-Finished the effect of new Armour soon to come.<br>
Some other minor things.</p>
<p>New in progress:<br>
-New Holy symbol effect.<br>
-New Unholy symbol effect.<br>
-New armour for all members, with a great new ability. (start going for 115 thieveing, smithing, mining, and magic to be ready for it.)<br>
-Another quest<br>
-Ancient prayers<br>
Some other still in discussion.</p>
<p>Thank you,<br>
-The Elunity Team!</p>
<p>Edit: IceBows are still dropped in the armadyl dungeon in gwd.</p>
<p>Updates:<br>
10/24:<br>
Fixed a few problems that would null the Server.<br>
Adding in a code when not commented out, to give free Subscription status to all. (Future Promotional Use)<br>
Finishing the SQL integration for our 2 new quests coming soon.<br>
Fixed an error with our 2013 Halloween event. (quest)<br>
Fixed a Logout Rollback issue.<br>
Fixed admin’s hide button, which even when deactive was making them hidden from some players.<br>
Setup our second account database for when the first fills.<br>
Made some more changes to fix an eco problem that has occurred in past versions.<br>
More progress on our CE Toolkit, to be released soon.<br>
More to come.</p>
<p>Updates:<br>
10/23<br>
Due to the usual problem with economy in past R*<strong>S</strong>, I have made a few changes.</p>
<p>PK Shop:<br>
All gs’s require 225 instead of 180 pk points.<br>
Dragon Claws cost 500 instead of 400 pk points.<br>
Dragon Dagger at 10 instead of 5 pk points.</p>
<p>Rune shop:<br>
There are now 20k of each rune. And prices have rised.</p>
<p>Drop rates:<br>
All drop rates have been substantially lowered.</p>
<p>Shops:<br>
Various items have gone up dramatically in price.<br>
Buying items in bulk will now be more expensive.</p>
<p>This is my starting attempt to fix the economy problems that past times have had.<br>
With shops higher in price, my idea is people will start making them on there on for a actual profit in skills that usually would not be profitable due to shops selling so cheap.</p>
<p>To even out all the price changes for beginners, you now start with 7.5m gp.</p>
<p>I will see how this works and edit it as such.</p>
<p>Text:<br>
“Donator” words have been replaced with “subscriber”.</p>
<p>Bugs: Multi drop by barrows bug has been corrected and fixed.</p>
<p>Thank you,<br>
-Ruzylo.</p>
<p>Updates:<br>
10/19<br>
Forums:<br>
-Boards have been fixed making the Forums look less scattered.<br>
-Elunity Radio Redirect Board is now in place.<br>
-Child boards have been put in place.<br>
-Some boards have been split (Goals &amp; Achievements are now 2 boards)<br>
-Report is now a general section with the child boards:<br>
Report a Bug<br>
Report a Staff<br>
Report a Player<br>
-Our home pages has had some minor link and text edits.<br>
-The Forums has had some board name changes.<br>
-Warning Templates are being made.</p>
<p>Ingame:</p>
<p>Done.<br>
-H’ween Event from 2009 has been turned into the 2013 event! Talk to the Witch at Hbank.<br>
-You can now fish Sea Turtles.<br>
You must be a donator to Fish them, cook, eat, trade, buy and pick them up.<br>
There are two locations in the Donator zone, to fish them. Both by the Dragon ore on<br>
each side. ::dz.<br>
They require 105 fishing to fish, and give 2050 XP each.<br>
They require 105 cooking to cook, and give 2550 XP each.<br>
They heal 25hp compared to mantas 20hp.<br>
-Elunity’s Official radio has been setup and is usually always brodcasting!<br>
Tune in here.<br>
-All dragon items now require 60 attack to wield.<br>
-New command ::team has been added. Shows you a list of all Ingame Staff.<br>
-Starter has changed to as follows:<br>
500k<br>
Dragon Scimitar<br>
Bronze Scimitar<br>
Monk Robe Top<br>
Monk Robe Bottom<br>
Amulet of Strength<br>
Climbing Boots<br>
15 Noted Shrimp<br>
5 Noted Super Attack Potions<br>
5 Noted Super Strength Potions<br>
Runes</p>
<p>Still in progress:<br>
2 New quests.<br>
CE Toolkit being fixed.<br>
Attack delay.<br>
Tombstone on death (including item pickup on death)<br>
Memory usage clean up.<br>
Removing useless/unused code.<br>
Vote4reward script.<br>
New prayers.<br>
Anti-bot scripts.<br>
Randoms.<br>
Oak tree delay.</p>
<p>Stay Tuned.</p>
<p>Updates:<br>
10/13-10/16<br>
Done:<br>
Fixed range glitch.<br>
Run Delay.<br>
Highscores setup again.<br>
Auto donate setup,<br>
ARK setup. (Email sending problem atm, working on fix)<br>
Simple command changes and fixes.<br>
Smtp setup for forums and ingame.<br>
Everything starting as a service.<br>
Some small minor bugs.<br>
And some more.</p>
<p>Been working on:<br>
2 New quests.<br>
Attack delay.<br>
Tombstone on death (including item pickup on death)<br>
Memory usage clean up.<br>
Removing useless/unused code.<br>
Vote4reward script.<br>
New prayers.<br>
Anti-bot scripts.<br>
Randoms.<br>
Oak tree delay.</p>
<p>~Elunity Team.<br>
[/code][size=2em]<br>
Just posted our adv thread and will put a basic copy of what weve done and what elunity is here. Expect constant updates.:<br>
[/size]</p>
<p>Elunity is not like your average servers you see around here it is very unique.  The server is 24/7, has a very experienced team and has custom which no other server has.  The server has grate load of bosses so the PvM’s are spoiled for choice and PvP’s are just as spoiled with all the spec weapons  in-game. Elunity allows players to use the yell (::yell) cannel without having to donate, all you need is over one hour online time, this is to stop any advertisers.</p>
<p>Quests:<br>
We have 7 quests already done, not including holiday quests!<br>
We currently have our Halloween quest out!<br>
<img src="http://img580.imageshack.us/img580/4117/7s3p.png" alt width="" height=""></p>
<p>Elunity Home:<br>
Here at Elunity we decided to change thing up rather than having home/starting place at edge like every other server; we decided to have our home based in Port Phasmatys. We also based out teleports such as god wars and mini-games.</p>
<p>Main commands:<br>
For all the following command you will need to write two colon’s (:: ) then followed by the name of the command without any space.</p>
<p>The commands are:<br>
Dz (Donator zone)<br>
Home (Port Phasmatys)<br>
Hbank (homebank)<br>
Mine (To mine rune essence)<br>
Pk (Mage bank)<br>
Team (Staff team)<br>
Yell (self-explanatory)<br>
People (tells you how many people at pits)<br>
Modhelp (lets mods know you need help and they will come and see you)<br>
Jad (fight cave)<br>
Players (who is on, and how many)</p>
<p>Skills:<br>
Once again Elunity decided they were going to do thing different from other severs rather than having levels going up to 99, we had them going up to 126 with a max xp of 250m and a max combat level of 160, but is wildness it will change to max level going up to 110 and max combat level of 140 (this changes back once you leave the wildness).</p>
<p>PvP:<br>
The main place on Elunity for player killing is hill giants. The main weapons been Dragon Claws Dark bow, Night bow (costom), Seren Godsword (costom), Dragon Cross bow, Vesta long sword and also has all regular godswords, along with “E” Godswords  donaters.</p>
<p>When you have killed a player you will get 2 pk points which allows you to later spend the pk points on a certain rewards from the Pk shop. There are also recorded stats for your kills, you will have the ability to wear the Player killing skill capes. 200 kills for Un-trimmed cape, 400 kills &amp; .6 ratio for (t) cape, and 600 kills &amp; .8 ratio for (m) cape.</p>
<p>Pvm:<br>
Elunity has wide range of bosses for to go PvM, some of them are; Sea Troll Queen, Jad, Dagganoth Kings, Mithril Dragon, King Black Dragon, Kalphite Queen. But the best bosses are Bandos, Armadyl, Zammy, Saradomin and Corporeal Beast.<br>
These monsters drop the most valuable items on Elunity.</p>
<p>Donators:<br>
You get a 15% increase on all experience you gain, ability to go to  donatorzone ,donator shop, spirit shields, ability to go to the corporeal beast and tormented demons, Vengance, Donator godswords, and much more!</p>
<p>Pictures:</p>
<p><a href="http://s1180.photobucket.com/user/jimmy786/media/Bosses_zps3d2b7544.png.html" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener"><img src="http://i1180.photobucket.com/albums/x405/jimmy786/Bosses_zps3d2b7544.png" alt width="" height=""></a></p>
<p><a href="http://s1180.photobucket.com/user/jimmy786/media/wuww_zps86786faa.png.html" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener"><img src="http://i1180.photobucket.com/albums/x405/jimmy786/wuww_zps86786faa.png" alt width="" height=""></a></p>
<p><a href="http://s1180.photobucket.com/user/jimmy786/media/pkshop_zps608ea7be.png.html" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener"><img src="http://i1180.photobucket.com/albums/x405/jimmy786/pkshop_zps608ea7be.png" alt width="" height=""></a></p>
<p><a href="http://s1180.photobucket.com/user/jimmy786/media/allpkcapes_zpsd4f62214.png.html" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener"><img src="http://i1180.photobucket.com/albums/x405/jimmy786/allpkcapes_zpsd4f62214.png" alt width="" height=""></a></p>
<p><a href="http://s1180.photobucket.com/user/jimmy786/media/75379939f3b4e7d348e9aaf75ffdba89_zps68f65c1f.png.html" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener"><img src="http://i1180.photobucket.com/albums/x405/jimmy786/75379939f3b4e7d348e9aaf75ffdba89_zps68f65c1f.png" alt width="" height=""></a><br>
[COLOR="<span class="hashtag">#00FF00</span>"]<br>
Unique Highscores, and some other features. Including one price timed subscription that includes all benefits of a subscriber. Donation system automatically added status when paid, and removed when time runs out.[/COLOR]</p>
<p><img src="http://imageshack.us/a/img593/2827/d3mv.png" alt width="" height=""><br>
<img src="http://imageshack.us/a/img268/4493/e96p.png" alt width="" height=""><br>
<img src="http://imageshack.us/a/img132/9792/c4h.png" alt width="" height=""></p>
<p>[COLOR="<span class="hashtag">#00FF00</span>"]Flawless Recovery system with email notifications.[/COLOR]</p>
<p><img src="http://imageshack.us/a/img706/14/yy4f.png" alt width="" height=""></p>
<p>[COLOR="<span class="hashtag">#00FF00</span>"]Ce toolkit, still to come (in development still)[/COLOR]</p>
<p><img src="http://imageshack.us/a/img809/1287/2kxn.png" alt width="" height=""><br>
<img src="http://imageshack.us/a/img837/9526/bkbg.png" alt width="" height=""><br>
<img src="http://imageshack.us/a/img132/1552/jbga.png" alt width="" height=""></p>
<p>[COLOR="<span class="hashtag">#FF0000</span>"]Thank you, The Elunity Team![/COLOR][/center]</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/elunity-the-project-most-advanced-317/534615/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/elunity-the-project-most-advanced-317/534615/1</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2013 23:25:55 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-534615-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/elunity-the-project-most-advanced-317/534615.rss">Elunity! The Project! Most advanced 317!</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
