<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Let&#39;s Talk Hosting</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/lets-talk-hosting/522160</link>
    <description>So, people keep saying hosting costs like $1k+, and I just don&#39;t see how, unless you&#39;re getting 10Gbps from Staminus, which is dumb IMO.

You can get more protection, for less than half the price from Black Lotus or JavaPipe. JavaPipe is extremely cheap, and you can get the protection aspect for $100, and host wherever you want or even use their VDS service.

Also, why is everyone so hung up on getting a dedicated server? Why not just get a VPS or use a cloud based service and get DDoS protection via a reverse proxy? You can literally get a better setup than you could with Staminus for $160 (including protection).

If you need more protection, you could always just use something like AWS to absorb it, and just make your server whitelist only. Updating the security policies be automated using their APIs, then the only thing you have exposed is your website or whatever you&#39;re using for users to change their allowed IP. If you have it as a website, you can spend the $200 per month and be protected by CloudFlare, who mitigates absolutely massive attacks and offers a 100% uptime guarantee. So, for like $250 a month, you can have everything protected far beyond what anyone in the RSC scene can take down.

Using AWS and CloudFlare, you can also scale out whenever you start running out of rules for an instance(which won&#39;t happen if you make exceptions expire, base it on reserved slots or have a combination of those).

Edit:
MoparClassic should be able to run the GS and LS on a micro instance (the LS and GS take less than 200MB of RAM total). AWS offers a free usage tier, where you can have a Windows and a Linux micro instance running 24/7 for a full year. This means you can actually get the AWS aspect for free for a full year. I was profiling it for a bit, and managed to get it to a point where the GS runs on a 50MB heap w/ 20MB perm gen (with minor tweaks that took less than 5 minutes to implement); it GCs every minute or so, and you can&#39;t even notice it. Without changing anything, I was able to get the LS to run on a 7MB heap with 20MB perm gen, and it was only using like 5MB of the heap and 11MB of the perm gen. I should note, that I was logging in two accounts and doing various things like dueling (while casting spells, switching items, etc.) to make sure it didn&#39;t have bad in-game performance and things didn&#39;t run out of memory.

Anyway, that cuts costs down to $200 a month, just for CloudFlare. And if you use Lothy&#39;s suggestion and use e-mail to have users add themselves to the whitelist, you can host a DDoS protected server for free.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 08 Nov 2013 01:10:20 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/lets-talk-hosting/522160.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Let&#39;s Talk Hosting</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@cleako cleako]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/cleako">@cleako</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p><a href="http://zbode.com/gameserver-protection.php" rel="nofollow noopener">http://zbode.com/gameserver-protection.php</a> for game server, cloudflare for website + host with AWS</p>
<p>Seems like a good balance for the cost.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/lets-talk-hosting/522160/18">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/lets-talk-hosting/522160/18</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Nov 2013 01:10:20 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-522160-18</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/lets-talk-hosting/522160.rss">Let&#39;s Talk Hosting</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Let&#39;s Talk Hosting</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@CodeForFame CodeForFame]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/codeforfame">@CodeForFame</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“Lothy, post:16, topic:522160”]I’m not sure I understand the whole AWS thing. Do they provide the server that you host the game on? Because if they don’t then having your IP made public wouldn’t work at all.[/quote]It will essentially be used as a cloud based VPS that has configurable network level firewall (that can have rules added/removed programmatically). The front facing website is going to allow users to add themselves as an exception, so they can access the game server.</p>
<p>All traffic that doesn’t have an exception gets black-holed, at the network level, so it never gets to your instance.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/lets-talk-hosting/522160/17">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/lets-talk-hosting/522160/17</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2013 07:54:42 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-522160-17</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/lets-talk-hosting/522160.rss">Let&#39;s Talk Hosting</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Let&#39;s Talk Hosting</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@lothy Lothy]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/lothy">@lothy</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I’m not sure I understand the whole AWS thing. Do they provide the server that you host the game on? Because if they don’t then having your IP made public wouldn’t work at all.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/lets-talk-hosting/522160/16">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/lets-talk-hosting/522160/16</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2013 06:43:51 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-522160-16</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/lets-talk-hosting/522160.rss">Let&#39;s Talk Hosting</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Let&#39;s Talk Hosting</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@CodeForFame CodeForFame]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/codeforfame">@CodeForFame</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“xEnt, post:13, topic:522160”][quote author=CodeForFame link=topic=640666.msg4317347#msg4317347 date=1371702571]</p>
<aside class="quote">
<blockquote>
<p>Salt and hash the phone numbers. For the threat model you’ve mentioned (basically an amateur who might have access to a reasonably fast consumer CPU) this is computationally secure and more than adequate.</p>
<p>Seeing as CloudFlare wouldn’t apply to the game server, how would the game server be protected? Is there a particular affordable service that you had in mind?<br>
[/quote]What I was saying it use AWS and keep everything but the webserver private. So, you need to use the webserver to add yourself to the whitelist, and have CloudFlare protect that. When they’re not on the security policy, the traffic gets stopped before it gets to your box, so AWS will end up absorbing it rather than your box.</p>
<p>Basically, you’re forcing people to authenticate through the webserver, which is protected by CloudFlare, before their traffic is allowed to even get to the game server.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>sure you’d authenticate with the web server, but i don’t see how that’s going to stop a direct DDoS attack on your gameserver, unless your somehow talking about all packets going through cloudfare to get to your server. all they need is the server’s IP and they will spam you with junk data.[/quote]I don’t think you understand how security groups work with AWS… Things not on the whitelist get filtered before they get to your instance, so you can have your IP given out publicly, it’s just that people can’t connect. Basically, everyone is null routed unless they’re added to the security group.</p>
<p>This removes the need for any kind of proxy, or keeping your IP a secret. Also, AWS has a massive network, they power most major Facebook games, Netflix, Reddit, and many other major things.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/lets-talk-hosting/522160/15">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/lets-talk-hosting/522160/15</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2013 06:35:25 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-522160-15</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/lets-talk-hosting/522160.rss">Let&#39;s Talk Hosting</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Let&#39;s Talk Hosting</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@lothy Lothy]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/lothy">@lothy</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Yeah, that’s the idea xEnt. User -&gt; Tunnel/proxy -&gt; Game server. I don’t know anything about AWS or their capacity to deal with attacks. But if latency isn’t a problem and the service was whitelist based then yeah, it would work well enough.</p>
<p>The trick is to avoid divulging the game server’s IP address, otherwise the effort is all for nought.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/lets-talk-hosting/522160/14">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/lets-talk-hosting/522160/14</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2013 05:49:59 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-522160-14</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/lets-talk-hosting/522160.rss">Let&#39;s Talk Hosting</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Let&#39;s Talk Hosting</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@xEnt xEnt]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/xent">@xEnt</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“CodeForFame, post:12, topic:522160”][quote author=Lothy link=topic=640666.msg4317325#msg4317325 date=1371699863]<br>
Salt and hash the phone numbers. For the threat model you’ve mentioned (basically an amateur who might have access to a reasonably fast consumer CPU) this is computationally secure and more than adequate.</p>
<p>Seeing as CloudFlare wouldn’t apply to the game server, how would the game server be protected? Is there a particular affordable service that you had in mind?<br>
[/quote]What I was saying it use AWS and keep everything but the webserver private. So, you need to use the webserver to add yourself to the whitelist, and have CloudFlare protect that. When they’re not on the security policy, the traffic gets stopped before it gets to your box, so AWS will end up absorbing it rather than your box.</p>
<p>Basically, you’re forcing people to authenticate through the webserver, which is protected by CloudFlare, before their traffic is allowed to even get to the game server.[/quote]</p>
<p>sure you’d authenticate with the web server, but i don’t see how that’s going to stop a direct DDoS attack on your gameserver, unless your somehow talking about all packets going through cloudfare to get to your server. all they need is the server’s IP and they will spam you with junk data.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/lets-talk-hosting/522160/13">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/lets-talk-hosting/522160/13</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2013 05:45:02 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-522160-13</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/lets-talk-hosting/522160.rss">Let&#39;s Talk Hosting</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Let&#39;s Talk Hosting</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@CodeForFame CodeForFame]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/codeforfame">@CodeForFame</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“Lothy, post:11, topic:522160”]Salt and hash the phone numbers. For the threat model you’ve mentioned (basically an amateur who might have access to a reasonably fast consumer CPU) this is computationally secure and more than adequate.</p>
<p>Seeing as CloudFlare wouldn’t apply to the game server, how would the game server be protected? Is there a particular affordable service that you had in mind?[/quote]What I was saying it use AWS and keep everything but the webserver private. So, you need to use the webserver to add yourself to the whitelist, and have CloudFlare protect that. When they’re not on the security policy, the traffic gets stopped before it gets to your box, so AWS will end up absorbing it rather than your box.</p>
<p>Basically, you’re forcing people to authenticate through the webserver, which is protected by CloudFlare, before their traffic is allowed to even get to the game server.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/lets-talk-hosting/522160/12">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/lets-talk-hosting/522160/12</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2013 04:29:31 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-522160-12</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/lets-talk-hosting/522160.rss">Let&#39;s Talk Hosting</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Let&#39;s Talk Hosting</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@lothy Lothy]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/lothy">@lothy</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Salt and hash the phone numbers. For the threat model you’ve mentioned (basically an amateur who might have access to a reasonably fast consumer CPU) this is computationally secure and more than adequate.</p>
<p>Seeing as CloudFlare wouldn’t apply to the game server, how would the game server be protected? Is there a particular affordable service that you had in mind?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/lets-talk-hosting/522160/11">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/lets-talk-hosting/522160/11</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2013 03:44:23 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-522160-11</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/lets-talk-hosting/522160.rss">Let&#39;s Talk Hosting</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Let&#39;s Talk Hosting</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@CodeForFame CodeForFame]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/codeforfame">@CodeForFame</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“Lothy, post:7, topic:522160”]Aren’t services like CloudFlare designed for HTTP traffic? Would it even work for TCP connections that are constant rather than short-lived?<br>
The other concern is latency related.</p>
<p>In an ideal world someone could host the server from home. 20Mbps to 40Mbps up should easily cater for 100 to 200 players. Two 500GB SATA drives, one for the database log file and one for the actual database, would easily cater for this workload without any sort of thrashing. PCCaseGear (an Australian online computer parts retailer) prices WD Black 500GB drives at about $80 each.<br>
As xEnt said above, the biggest problem with shared hosting is disk thrashing.</p>
<p>Email could be used to perform tasks such as changing a user IP address. The user would send an email to a gmail account, which a software daemon would poll. New email would be received and processed, and the daemon would make the relevant API calls to update the whitelist. The benefit of this approach is that there’s no attack vector; google acts as a man in the middle.<br>
Sending a reply email would be an issue unless the headers are forged. Whatever the process though, the IP address of the server shouldn’t be divulged to anybody or anything except the proxying service that the players connect to.</p>
<p>Finally, some kind of watchdog could be set up to monitor and detect any malicious traffic from what are supposed to be good IP addresses. It could then temporarily penalise the user by removing their IP address from the proxy service whitelist AND disallowing changes to that user’s IP address for a period of time.</p>
<p>Addendum: There’s another thing that the community should consider too, and that’s the use of SMS account verification on registration. I think it would do a lot to make botting less feasible.<br>
Users register their account and then validate it using a token that is sent to them via text message. If they cheat and receive a ban then they have to go to the trouble of acquiring a new SIM card (which at the very least involves a trip to the shops and an activation process to set it up).[/quote]CloudFlare would only be used to protect your website… You’d be hosting your site on a separate VPS or a normal web host.</p>
<p>Also, I haven’t really seen anything about bad disk performance for cloud solutions, just VPS companies that oversell or follow bad practices.</p>
<p>As for SMS verification, you get get a new SIM card for a few bucks off of eBay, so it really wouldn’t be that big of an issue. Though, it would be a hassle and probably deter a lot of people. Though, I’m sure a lot of people would be hesitate to play a server with it, seeing how most servers get hacked and have databases leaked.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/lets-talk-hosting/522160/10">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/lets-talk-hosting/522160/10</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2013 03:39:01 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-522160-10</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/lets-talk-hosting/522160.rss">Let&#39;s Talk Hosting</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Let&#39;s Talk Hosting</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@lothy Lothy]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/lothy">@lothy</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Just a heads up: A $15/month service will kick you off the network the second you inconvenience them with any kind of work (such as mitigating an attack).<br>
It simply isn’t worth anybody’s time to deal with a high maintenance customer for that sort of money.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/lets-talk-hosting/522160/9">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/lets-talk-hosting/522160/9</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2013 03:27:47 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-522160-9</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/lets-talk-hosting/522160.rss">Let&#39;s Talk Hosting</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Let&#39;s Talk Hosting</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@xEnt xEnt]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/xent">@xEnt</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>VPS use software like citrix xen, hyper-v &amp; vmware for their vdi solution. the software is amazing but still not perfect with their resource allocation. RAM is not an issue, it’s mainly CPU load balancing, disk IO and ethernet IO. some of these data centers can pull down data from the internet faster than it can write to a disk, so shared resources is a little hit and miss if you want a stable server.</p>
<p>they might promise you 2 cores, 8gigs of ram and 250gb hdd space, in reality vdi software allocating virtual cores is far from perfect, and someone else thrashing out their ‘2’ cores can easily put strain on your own. and that’s just cpu talk, hdd &amp; network io will still be a problem.</p>
<p>but sure, for anything under 100 players go ahead and get a $15 vps. you get what you pay for.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/lets-talk-hosting/522160/8">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/lets-talk-hosting/522160/8</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2013 03:13:43 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-522160-8</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/lets-talk-hosting/522160.rss">Let&#39;s Talk Hosting</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Let&#39;s Talk Hosting</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@lothy Lothy]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/lothy">@lothy</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Aren’t services like CloudFlare designed for HTTP traffic? Would it even work for TCP connections that are constant rather than short-lived?<br>
The other concern is latency related.</p>
<p>In an ideal world someone could host the server from home. 20Mbps to 40Mbps up should easily cater for 100 to 200 players. Two 500GB SATA drives, one for the database log file and one for the actual database, would easily cater for this workload without any sort of thrashing. PCCaseGear (an Australian online computer parts retailer) prices WD Black 500GB drives at about $80 each.<br>
As xEnt said above, the biggest problem with shared hosting is disk thrashing.</p>
<p>Email could be used to perform tasks such as changing a user IP address. The user would send an email to a gmail account, which a software daemon would poll. New email would be received and processed, and the daemon would make the relevant API calls to update the whitelist. The benefit of this approach is that there’s no attack vector; google acts as a man in the middle.<br>
Sending a reply email would be an issue unless the headers are forged. Whatever the process though, the IP address of the server shouldn’t be divulged to anybody or anything except the proxying service that the players connect to.</p>
<p>Finally, some kind of watchdog could be set up to monitor and detect any malicious traffic from what are supposed to be good IP addresses. It could then temporarily penalise the user by removing their IP address from the proxy service whitelist AND disallowing changes to that user’s IP address for a period of time.</p>
<p>Addendum: There’s another thing that the community should consider too, and that’s the use of SMS account verification on registration. I think it would do a lot to make botting less feasible.<br>
Users register their account and then validate it using a token that is sent to them via text message. If they cheat and receive a ban then they have to go to the trouble of acquiring a new SIM card (which at the very least involves a trip to the shops and an activation process to set it up).</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/lets-talk-hosting/522160/7">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/lets-talk-hosting/522160/7</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2013 02:45:10 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-522160-7</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/lets-talk-hosting/522160.rss">Let&#39;s Talk Hosting</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Let&#39;s Talk Hosting</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@CodeForFame CodeForFame]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/codeforfame">@CodeForFame</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“Os1ris, post:5, topic:522160”]I like the <a href="http://SharkTech.net" rel="nofollow noopener">SharkTech.net</a> hosting.[/quote]What the f<span class="bbcode-b"></span>uck do you like about them?</p>
<p>Just felt like bypassing the censor…</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/lets-talk-hosting/522160/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/lets-talk-hosting/522160/6</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 19 Jun 2013 06:55:56 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-522160-6</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/lets-talk-hosting/522160.rss">Let&#39;s Talk Hosting</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Let&#39;s Talk Hosting</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Os1ris Os1ris]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/os1ris">@Os1ris</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I like the <a href="http://SharkTech.net" rel="nofollow noopener">SharkTech.net</a> hosting.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/lets-talk-hosting/522160/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/lets-talk-hosting/522160/5</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 19 Jun 2013 06:27:06 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-522160-5</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/lets-talk-hosting/522160.rss">Let&#39;s Talk Hosting</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Let&#39;s Talk Hosting</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@CodeForFame CodeForFame]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/codeforfame">@CodeForFame</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“xEnt, post:2, topic:522160”]VPS are fine for little servers, but anyone 200 players + don’t want their box shared by others constantly torrenting &amp; raping the resources.[/quote]That’s why you select a host that doesn’t oversell and uses the appropriate technology. Also, what about cloud based services?</p>
<p>BTW servers don’t really hit 200+ anymore…</p>
<p>[quote=“Rodgerwilco, post:3, topic:522160”]What happened to the times when I could run divine source off my own pc and hold 150+ without worry. Isn’t ‘cloud’ expensive?</p>
<p>[quote]$0.12/hr<br>
$87.60/mo<br>
Disk Space: 80 GB<br>
RAM: 2 GB<br>
vCPUs: 2<br>
Public Network:<br>
60 Mbps<br>
Internal Network:<br>
120 Mbps[/quote]</p>
<p>Where I can get something very similar for $40?<br>
<a href="https://manage.kickassvps.com/index.php?/cart/&amp;step=3%5B/quote%5DYou" rel="nofollow noopener">https://manage.kickassvps.com/index.php?/cart/&amp;step=3[/quote]You</a> can get an EC2 medium instance for like $49 a month, if you get a heavy utilization reserved instance. It’s like $338 upfront and knocks down the hourly to $0.028. You could even do spot instances which are generally much cheaper (at the current rate it’d be $9.36 per month (this past month it hasn’t gone over the price of a small on-demand instance at all in some regions)).</p>
<p>Also, MoparClassic should run just fine on a EC2 small instance (login server and game server).</p>
<p>BTW the link you gave won’t show us what was in your cart…</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/lets-talk-hosting/522160/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/lets-talk-hosting/522160/4</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 19 Jun 2013 04:57:43 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-522160-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/lets-talk-hosting/522160.rss">Let&#39;s Talk Hosting</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Let&#39;s Talk Hosting</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Rodgerwilco Rodgerwilco]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/rodgerwilco">@Rodgerwilco</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>What happened to the times when I could run divine source off my own pc and hold 150+ without worry. Isn’t ‘cloud’ expensive?</p>
<blockquote>$0.12/hr
$87.60/mo
Disk Space: 80 GB
RAM: 2 GB
vCPUs: 2
Public Network:
60 Mbps
Internal Network:
120 Mbps</blockquote>
<p>Where I can get something very similar for $40?<br>
<a href="https://manage.kickassvps.com/index.php?/cart/&amp;step=3" class="onebox" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">https://manage.kickassvps.com/index.php?/cart/&amp;step=3</a></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/lets-talk-hosting/522160/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/lets-talk-hosting/522160/3</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 19 Jun 2013 04:27:09 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-522160-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/lets-talk-hosting/522160.rss">Let&#39;s Talk Hosting</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Let&#39;s Talk Hosting</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@xEnt xEnt]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/xent">@xEnt</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>VPS are fine for little servers, but anyone 200 players + don’t want their box shared by others constantly torrenting &amp; raping the resources.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/lets-talk-hosting/522160/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/lets-talk-hosting/522160/2</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 19 Jun 2013 02:31:07 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-522160-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/lets-talk-hosting/522160.rss">Let&#39;s Talk Hosting</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Let&#39;s Talk Hosting</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@CodeForFame CodeForFame]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/codeforfame">@CodeForFame</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>So, people keep saying hosting costs like $1k+, and I just don’t see how, unless you’re getting 10Gbps from Staminus, which is dumb IMO.</p>
<p>You can get more protection, for less than half the price from Black Lotus or JavaPipe. JavaPipe is extremely cheap, and you can get the protection aspect for $100, and host wherever you want or even use their VDS service.</p>
<p>Also, why is everyone so hung up on getting a dedicated server? Why not just get a VPS or use a cloud based service and get DDoS protection via a reverse proxy? You can literally get a better setup than you could with Staminus for $160 (including protection).</p>
<p>If you need more protection, you could always just use something like AWS to absorb it, and just make your server whitelist only. Updating the security policies be automated using their APIs, then the only thing you have exposed is your website or whatever you’re using for users to change their allowed IP. If you have it as a website, you can spend the $200 per month and be protected by CloudFlare, who mitigates absolutely massive attacks and offers a 100% uptime guarantee. So, for like $250 a month, you can have everything protected far beyond what anyone in the RSC scene can take down.</p>
<p>Using AWS and CloudFlare, you can also scale out whenever you start running out of rules for an instance(which won’t happen if you make exceptions expire, base it on reserved slots or have a combination of those).</p>
<p>Edit:<br>
MoparClassic should be able to run the GS and LS on a micro instance (the LS and GS take less than 200MB of RAM total). AWS offers a free usage tier, where you can have a Windows and a Linux micro instance running 24/7 for a full year. This means you can actually get the AWS aspect for free for a full year. I was profiling it for a bit, and managed to get it to a point where the GS runs on a 50MB heap w/ 20MB perm gen (with minor tweaks that took less than 5 minutes to implement); it GCs every minute or so, and you can’t even notice it. Without changing anything, I was able to get the LS to run on a 7MB heap with 20MB perm gen, and it was only using like 5MB of the heap and 11MB of the perm gen. I should note, that I was logging in two accounts and doing various things like dueling (while casting spells, switching items, etc.) to make sure it didn’t have bad in-game performance and things didn’t run out of memory.</p>
<p>Anyway, that cuts costs down to $200 a month, just for CloudFlare. And if you use Lothy’s suggestion and use e-mail to have users add themselves to the whitelist, you can host a DDoS protected server for free.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/lets-talk-hosting/522160/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/lets-talk-hosting/522160/1</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 19 Jun 2013 00:21:47 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-522160-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/lets-talk-hosting/522160.rss">Let&#39;s Talk Hosting</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
