<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>[PI] A lot of questions about updates</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/pi-a-lot-of-questions-about-updates/402095</link>
    <description>PLEASE READ ALL. YOU MAY EVEN LEARN SOMETHING :) If you know any answers to any of the stuff below please answer. It would help a lot of other people too who are searching for one of these questions. I would really appreciate some help on some of these. You don&#39;t have to know them all or know exactly how just tips or some advice could help. I built up these questions after looking around on the server for stuff I need to fix or change. Thanks! By the way, I&#39;m not having you do all the stuff I don&#39;t feel like doing. That is not why there is so much questions. This is all stuff I attempted to do already and I couldn&#39;t figure it out. I also eliminated some stuff that I will ask later when it&#39;s more important. I am still looking around for answers to any of these:


[s]stop npcs from walking through walls (when i ran away from an npc inside of a castle it followed me and when i looked back it went back to its place and to get there it went through a wall???)

Can you give me some tips to keep the economy good.

Change trees (some of them look really wierd bc they are custom made by someone)[/s]

[s]I need to clean up my cache if u can get me tips or how to&#39;s that would be great and if u want i could send u the cache to do it yourself because its such a big file :( It&#39;s 205MB when it&#39;s not in a .zip file. I want it to be around 30MB inside of a .zip file.
[/s]
[s]Some roofs have weird trims around them

I need to fix some walls that are transparent on the inside of a room. on the outside wherever theres a dark area on the wall the inside of the room in that particular area is transparent

Fix grand exchange floor (its really weird its got the floor details covered up by big solid colored spacey tiles

fix run option(you get infinite energy it says 0% all the time and you can just run and run and never run out)[/s]

change pk point rewards (its not like normal shops i dont know where to edit the items in the shop)

[s]I need to know what dupes and cheats there are with PI and if you know how please tell me how to stop them otherwise just let me know of them[/s]

[s]take off doors and keep locked doors at uneeded places[/s]

speed up server as much as possible (tips please)

take off a few customs and items that dont work (how do i know which files to delete?)

add throwable food (like rotten tomatoes or something) where u click use and you click a player and it shows it being thrown at the player and tells the player that that person hit them with a tomato

make a npc that at death gives pk points

stop teleporting while in pk battle

[s]i need to fix the bug where monsters glitch when they die and some glitch when they attack they get all out of shape and bent up its weird
[/s]
[s]fix examine for items instead of examine saying
&quot;It&#39;s a -ItemNameHere-&quot; it would say the correct description[/s]

make double exp gloves for members that are very rare and valueble

make the character outfit and gender page open when the new player logs in


[s]make admin spawning more limited than normal so you can only 
spawn up to 50 items at a time example: ::item 995 50 that would be the highest you can spawn
[/s]
on the teleports take off the incorrect description for example instead of the description of the Monster Teleport says Teleports you to Varrock

some npcs open a shop if you talk to them I need to make those npcs say something like 
&quot;Hiya. It sure is a nice day in the world 1 of DestinyScape!&quot; and when you want to shop you have to right click and trade them. The problem is I don&#39;t know how to force them to have a trade option. Do I just add the text and it does it automatically?

[s]make the log out timer longer[/s]

[s]make the character appear at home each time you log in instead of the area where u logged out
[/s]
i need make a way to rotate each npc facing a 
certain way by editing the custom spawn code. instead of them all going one way

make anything you do to an object, item, or npc not work at a far distance instead send 
message: &quot;Your too far away.&quot;

I&#39;d like to again thank everyone who is going to help and has helped!!</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 03 Jul 2011 08:54:20 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/pi-a-lot-of-questions-about-updates/402095.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>[PI] A lot of questions about updates</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@_Kane † Kane †]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/_kane">@_Kane</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>No problem, always glad to help.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/pi-a-lot-of-questions-about-updates/402095/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/pi-a-lot-of-questions-about-updates/402095/5</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 03 Jul 2011 08:54:20 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-402095-5</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/pi-a-lot-of-questions-about-updates/402095.rss">[PI] A lot of questions about updates</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[PI] A lot of questions about updates</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@belhelmiel belhelmiel]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/belhelmiel">@belhelmiel</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote="† Kane †, post:2, topic:402095"]For NPCs going through walls: You need to add NPC clipping.<br>
For good economy: Don’t put EVERYTHING in shops. And make sure coins are worth something. Don’t put in a money making method that can make you max cash in an hour.<br>
Change trees: Get a different client or take out the crappy tree models.<br>
Take off custom items: Rename it in the item cfg file and remove them from class8.java in your client<br>
For the monsters ‘turning to weird shapes’ when they die: Fix their death emotes to match their proper emotes.<br>
For the spawning limit:</p>
<pre><code class="lang-auto">if (playerCommand.startsWith("item")) {
				try {
					String[] args = playerCommand.split(" ");
					if (args.length == 3) {
						int newItemID = Integer.parseInt(args[1]);
						int newItemAmount = Integer.parseInt(args[2]);
						if ((newItemID &lt;= 20000) &amp;&amp; (newItemID &gt;= 0)) {
                                                if (newItemAmount &lt;= 50) {
							c.getItems().addItem(newItemID, newItemAmount);	
	                                         }else { c.sendMessage("You can't spawn more than 50 of any item at a time.");}
						} else {
							c.sendMessage("That item ID does not exist.");
						}
					} else {
						c.sendMessage("Use as ::item ID AMOUNT");
					}
				} catch(Exception e) {
					
				} // HERE?
				}</code></pre>
<p>(I think that code will work)</p>
<aside class="quote">
<blockquote>
<p>make the character appear at home each time you log in instead of the area where u logged out</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Why would you want to do that? And uhm, just take the coord x and coord y out of the player saving and make sure their original values are the home coordinates.</p>
<p>Hope that helps with some…[/quote]</p>
<p>[size=36pt]Thanks!![/size] Your advice was sooo helpful! I’m gonna try out the code l8tr on I’m still testing my server for bugs. It looks about right. I would make you go to home at login because of cheating and if you login and your internet is slow it may take a bit and if your in PK someone could get a free kill. Usually that wouldn’t happen but it’s happened to a lot of people on websterscape. that was my first rsps. So how would I change the monsters ‘death emotes’? I’ll look up a tutorial for the NPC clip It probably won’t be hard to find. Thanks again! Keep up the good work!</p>
<p>[quote=“Dayne, post:3, topic:402095”]-Can you give me some tips to keep the economy good.<br>
Don’t load mystics, ancient staves, large amounts of foods, etc.<br>
Mystics can be obtained by killing infernal mages, no point in all the mages running around with mystics.<br>
Ancient staves are also obtained from infernal mages with the same concept.<br>
Make people work for their food/potions, so the economy is skill based rather than shop based.<br>
Take out dumb shit such as dragon armour, whips, furys, etc. from shops; they should be earned.</p>
<p>-I need to know what dupes and cheats there are with PI and if you know how please tell me how to stop them otherwise just let me know of them.<br>
I’m trying to fix this as well, but here is a major glitch. When you drop “Torag hammers” they become “Guthans chainskirt 0” which can be repaired and sold for higher price.</p>
<p>-Take off doors and keep locked doors at uneeded places.<br>
I think go to your object list and delete the object…?</p>
<p>-I need to fix the bug where monsters glitch when they die and some glitch when they attack they get all out of shape and bent up its weird.<br>
I need help with this also, but seeing as some of these are custom monsters, I don’t think this will be easily fixed.</p>
<p>-Fix examine for items instead of examine saying “It’s a -ItemNameHere-” it would say the correct description.<br>
You’re going to have to manually change all the descriptions yourself, which would take a lot of time, I suggest you keep it as is.[/quote]<br>
Those are great tips! The doors being deleted: I figured it out, your close but you have to use the object void thing inside of object manager or something like that. I dont have that major glitch with the torag hammers and guthans chainskirt 0. But you can probably find a fix somewhere on <a href="http://moparisthebest.com" rel="nofollow noopener">moparisthebest.com</a>. :3 I’m going to use all of your economy tips along with all of Kanes economy tips. I knew that about the examine so I figured I would keep most of them normal but change some. But that would just be a waste of time because it doesn’t matter if I have a good RSPS anyways. Your great keep coding and helping people on mopar youll be as good as I_Vain_I eventually [size=36pt]You too Kane!!![/size]</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/pi-a-lot-of-questions-about-updates/402095/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/pi-a-lot-of-questions-about-updates/402095/4</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 03 Jul 2011 08:17:12 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-402095-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/pi-a-lot-of-questions-about-updates/402095.rss">[PI] A lot of questions about updates</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[PI] A lot of questions about updates</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Dayne Dayne]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/dayne">@Dayne</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>-Can you give me some tips to keep the economy good.<br>
Don’t load mystics, ancient staves, large amounts of foods, etc.<br>
Mystics can be obtained by killing infernal mages, no point in all the mages running around with mystics.<br>
Ancient staves are also obtained from infernal mages with the same concept.<br>
Make people work for their food/potions, so the economy is skill based rather than shop based.<br>
Take out dumb shit such as dragon armour, whips, furys, etc. from shops; they should be earned.</p>
<p>-I need to know what dupes and cheats there are with PI and if you know how please tell me how to stop them otherwise just let me know of them.<br>
I’m trying to fix this as well, but here is a major glitch. When you drop “Torag hammers” they become “Guthans chainskirt 0” which can be repaired and sold for higher price.</p>
<p>-Take off doors and keep locked doors at uneeded places.<br>
I think go to your object list and delete the object…?</p>
<p>-I need to fix the bug where monsters glitch when they die and some glitch when they attack they get all out of shape and bent up its weird.<br>
I need help with this also, but seeing as some of these are custom monsters, I don’t think this will be easily fixed.</p>
<p>-Fix examine for items instead of examine saying “It’s a -ItemNameHere-” it would say the correct description.<br>
You’re going to have to manually change all the descriptions yourself, which would take a lot of time, I suggest you keep it as is.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/pi-a-lot-of-questions-about-updates/402095/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/pi-a-lot-of-questions-about-updates/402095/3</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 03 Jul 2011 07:52:33 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-402095-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/pi-a-lot-of-questions-about-updates/402095.rss">[PI] A lot of questions about updates</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[PI] A lot of questions about updates</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@_Kane † Kane †]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/_kane">@_Kane</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>For NPCs going through walls: You need to add NPC clipping.<br>
For good economy: Don’t put EVERYTHING in shops. And make sure coins are worth something. Don’t put in a money making method that can make you max cash in an hour.<br>
Change trees: Get a different client or take out the crappy tree models.<br>
Take off custom items: Rename it in the item cfg file and remove them from class8.java in your client<br>
For the monsters ‘turning to weird shapes’ when they die: Fix their death emotes to match their proper emotes.<br>
For the spawning limit:</p>
<pre><code class="lang-auto">if (playerCommand.startsWith("item")) {
				try {
					String[] args = playerCommand.split(" ");
					if (args.length == 3) {
						int newItemID = Integer.parseInt(args[1]);
						int newItemAmount = Integer.parseInt(args[2]);
						if ((newItemID &lt;= 20000) &amp;&amp; (newItemID &gt;= 0)) {
                                                if (newItemAmount &lt;= 50) {
							c.getItems().addItem(newItemID, newItemAmount);	
	                                         }else { c.sendMessage("You can't spawn more than 50 of any item at a time.");}
						} else {
							c.sendMessage("That item ID does not exist.");
						}
					} else {
						c.sendMessage("Use as ::item ID AMOUNT");
					}
				} catch(Exception e) {
					
				} // HERE?
				}</code></pre>
<p>(I think that code will work)</p>
<blockquote>make the character appear at home each time you log in instead of the area where u logged out</blockquote>
Why would you want to do that? And uhm, just take the coord x and coord y out of the player saving and make sure their original values are the home coordinates.
<p>Hope that helps with some…</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/pi-a-lot-of-questions-about-updates/402095/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/pi-a-lot-of-questions-about-updates/402095/2</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 03 Jul 2011 07:41:05 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-402095-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/pi-a-lot-of-questions-about-updates/402095.rss">[PI] A lot of questions about updates</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[PI] A lot of questions about updates</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@belhelmiel belhelmiel]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/belhelmiel">@belhelmiel</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>PLEASE READ ALL. YOU MAY EVEN LEARN SOMETHING <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=5" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"> If you know any answers to any of the stuff below please answer. It would help a lot of other people too who are searching for one of these questions. I would really appreciate some help on some of these. You don’t have to know them all or know exactly how just tips or some advice could help. I built up these questions after looking around on the server for stuff I need to fix or change. Thanks! By the way, I’m not having you do all the stuff I don’t feel like doing. That is not why there is so much questions. This is all stuff I attempted to do already and I couldn’t figure it out. I also eliminated some stuff that I will ask later when it’s more important. I am still looking around for answers to any of these:</p>
<p>[s]stop npcs from walking through walls (when i ran away from an npc inside of a castle it followed me and when i looked back it went back to its place and to get there it went through a wall???)</p>
<p>Can you give me some tips to keep the economy good.</p>
<p>Change trees (some of them look really wierd bc they are custom made by someone)[/s]</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-s">I need to clean up my cache if u can get me tips or how to’s that would be great and if u want i could send u the cache to do it yourself because its such a big file <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/frowning.png?v=5" title=":frowning:" class="emoji" alt=":frowning:"> It’s 205MB when it’s not in a .zip file. I want it to be around 30MB inside of a .zip file.<br>
</span><br>
[s]Some roofs have weird trims around them</p>
<p>I need to fix some walls that are transparent on the inside of a room. on the outside wherever theres a dark area on the wall the inside of the room in that particular area is transparent</p>
<p>Fix grand exchange floor (its really weird its got the floor details covered up by big solid colored spacey tiles</p>
<p>fix run option(you get infinite energy it says 0% all the time and you can just run and run and never run out)[/s]</p>
<p>change pk point rewards (its not like normal shops i dont know where to edit the items in the shop)</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-s">I need to know what dupes and cheats there are with PI and if you know how please tell me how to stop them otherwise just let me know of them</span></p>
<p><span class="bbcode-s">take off doors and keep locked doors at uneeded places</span></p>
<p>speed up server as much as possible (tips please)</p>
<p>take off a few customs and items that dont work (how do i know which files to delete?)</p>
<p>add throwable food (like rotten tomatoes or something) where u click use and you click a player and it shows it being thrown at the player and tells the player that that person hit them with a tomato</p>
<p>make a npc that at death gives pk points</p>
<p>stop teleporting while in pk battle</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-s">i need to fix the bug where monsters glitch when they die and some glitch when they attack they get all out of shape and bent up its weird<br>
</span><br>
<span class="bbcode-s">fix examine for items instead of examine saying<br>
“It’s a -ItemNameHere-” it would say the correct description</span></p>
<p>make double exp gloves for members that are very rare and valueble</p>
<p>make the character outfit and gender page open when the new player logs in</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-s">make admin spawning more limited than normal so you can only<br>
spawn up to 50 items at a time example: ::item 995 50 that would be the highest you can spawn<br>
</span><br>
on the teleports take off the incorrect description for example instead of the description of the Monster Teleport says Teleports you to Varrock</p>
<p>some npcs open a shop if you talk to them I need to make those npcs say something like<br>
“Hiya. It sure is a nice day in the world 1 of DestinyScape!” and when you want to shop you have to right click and trade them. The problem is I don’t know how to force them to have a trade option. Do I just add the text and it does it automatically?</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-s">make the log out timer longer</span></p>
<p><span class="bbcode-s">make the character appear at home each time you log in instead of the area where u logged out<br>
</span><br>
i need make a way to rotate each npc facing a<br>
certain way by editing the custom spawn code. instead of them all going one way</p>
<p>make anything you do to an object, item, or npc not work at a far distance instead send<br>
message: “Your too far away.”</p>
<p>I’d like to again thank everyone who is going to help and has helped!!</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/pi-a-lot-of-questions-about-updates/402095/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/pi-a-lot-of-questions-about-updates/402095/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 03 Jul 2011 06:42:46 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-402095-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/pi-a-lot-of-questions-about-updates/402095.rss">[PI] A lot of questions about updates</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
