<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Tutorial &quot;Weighting&quot; System</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/tutorial-weighting-system/521075</link>
    <description>What are your opinions on weighing the tutorial award selection so that those with the Tutorial Author badge are less likely to receive the award than those without it? I feel that if we are aiming to spark activity and motivate users, we should lean more towards users without the badge when awarding it because it could be offputting for users if they constantly see the Tutorial Authors being awarded (they have more experience with tutorial writing, indicated by their current badge).</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 08 Jun 2013 19:11:11 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Community Suggestions</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/tutorial-weighting-system/521075.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Tutorial &quot;Weighting&quot; System</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Ambokile Ambokile]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/ambokile">@Ambokile</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Alright, I understand your opinions on it, I just thought that may be a bit demoralising for people if they routinely see tutorials from Tutorial Authors (because their tutorials are generally going to be better than most others, or at least be good enough to qualify for the award). But I suppose that seeing as there’s no monthly limit on how many tutorials we can feature, there’ll be no need to choose which ones from the nominations “deserve” to be in the issue.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/tutorial-weighting-system/521075/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/tutorial-weighting-system/521075/3</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 08 Jun 2013 19:11:11 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-521075-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/tutorial-weighting-system/521075.rss">Tutorial &quot;Weighting&quot; System</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Tutorial &quot;Weighting&quot; System</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Flame3 John]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/flame3">@Flame3</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Rather than create a whole new reply for this, I’m going to steal snippets of responses I used in the Mopar Monthly thread.</p>
<p>The category is named ‘The Best Tutorials of the Month,’ which means that multiple tutorials will show up should there be good tutorials published. To not give others a chance to have their work shown is unfair to say the least; if many people publish noteworthy tutorials, then those tutorials will possibly appear on the next edition. Everyone has their chance, and one of the main reasons that this section exists is for attempting to spark some more activity within the areas of contributing and teaching to the community. There is no monthly quota that needs to be reached for tutorial mentions. The user’s name being mentioned is just a reward for publishing the tutorial, to have it shown is meant to spread the word of a good tutorial.<br>
Having the tutorial author award is just the icing on the cake. When you make a tutorial while holding that badge it is <span class="bbcode-i">expected</span> that your tutorials are of notable quality, thus filling the requirements for showing up in the tutorials category. Simply because they have a badge does not mean that they do not show up. Heck, if we don’t mention those with the badge, who are we to mention? The first edition only featured Arham’s tutorials simply because he was the only one to post an actual tutorial for the month.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/tutorial-weighting-system/521075/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/tutorial-weighting-system/521075/2</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 08 Jun 2013 18:30:29 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-521075-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/tutorial-weighting-system/521075.rss">Tutorial &quot;Weighting&quot; System</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Tutorial &quot;Weighting&quot; System</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Ambokile Ambokile]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/ambokile">@Ambokile</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>What are your opinions on weighing the tutorial award selection so that those with the Tutorial Author badge are less likely to receive the award than those without it? I feel that if we are aiming to spark activity and motivate users, we should lean more towards users without the badge when awarding it because it could be offputting for users if they constantly see the Tutorial Authors being awarded (they have more experience with tutorial writing, indicated by their current badge).</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/tutorial-weighting-system/521075/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/tutorial-weighting-system/521075/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 08 Jun 2013 16:02:42 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-521075-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/tutorial-weighting-system/521075.rss">Tutorial &quot;Weighting&quot; System</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
