<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Making a custom webclient FOR FREE, please help</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/making-a-custom-webclient-for-free-please-help/466594</link>
    <description>Alright so I plan on just using a weebly.com. Here&#39;s my current site, it&#39;s plain, but that&#39;s because I&#39;m waiting until I figure out how to get a webclient running on it. Alright so, I&#39;m using the source named Vistex, so credits to him, but I did change stuff around so it&#39;s not the same thing as his server. If you&#39;re needing to know whether it&#39;s a 317 or 508 and what not, I want you to go to http://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php/topic,541502.msg3966744.html#msg3966744
because I honestly can&#39;t figure out if it&#39;s 508 or not, I know it has 508 maps though. I do have the JARMaker and stuff, and I was following a tutorial on it, but he explained to find stuff in certain .java files and I couldn&#39;t find it, idk if it&#39;s because I may be on a different kind of server or what. But I just need someone to go through it with me. You can skype if you want, but I don&#39;t have a working mic. iamjmperry   Or maybe send me to a link that you know would work. thanks</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 10 Nov 2012 19:18:05 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Game Development</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/making-a-custom-webclient-for-free-please-help/466594.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Making a custom webclient FOR FREE, please help</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@justinmperry justinmperry]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/justinmperry">@justinmperry</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Alright so I plan on just using a <a href="http://weebly.com" rel="nofollow noopener">weebly.com</a>. Here’s my current site, it’s plain, but that’s because I’m waiting until I figure out how to get a webclient running on it. Alright so, I’m using the source named Vistex, so credits to him, but I did change stuff around so it’s not the same thing as his server. If you’re needing to know whether it’s a 317 or 508 and what not, I want you to go to <a href="http://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php/topic,541502.msg3966744.html#msg3966744" rel="nofollow noopener">http://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php/topic,541502.msg3966744.html#msg3966744</a><br>
because I honestly can’t figure out if it’s 508 or not, I know it has 508 maps though. I do have the JARMaker and stuff, and I was following a tutorial on it, but he explained to find stuff in certain .java files and I couldn’t find it, idk if it’s because I may be on a different kind of server or what. But I just need someone to go through it with me. You can skype if you want, but I don’t have a working mic. iamjmperry   Or maybe send me to a link that you know would work. thanks</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/making-a-custom-webclient-for-free-please-help/466594/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/making-a-custom-webclient-for-free-please-help/466594/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 10 Nov 2012 19:18:05 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-466594-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/making-a-custom-webclient-for-free-please-help/466594.rss">Making a custom webclient FOR FREE, please help</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
