<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Visix</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/visix/541416</link>
    <description>[CENTER][IMG]http://visix.org/images/logo2.png[/img][/CENTER]


[B][SIZE=2]Website[/SIZE][/B]: [url=http://Www.Visix.org]Visix[/url]
[B][SIZE=2]Webclient[/SIZE][/B]: [url=http://Www.Visix.org/webclient]Click Here[/url]
[B][SIZE=2]Downloadable[/SIZE][/B]: [url=http://Www.Visix.org/Visix.jar]Click Here[/url]
[B][SIZE=2]Vote[/SIZE][/B]: [url=http://Www.Visix.org/vote]Click here[/url]



[B][SIZE=3][COLOR=green]Visix Features:[/COLOR][/SIZE][/B]

[COLOR=green][B][SIZE=2]Overview[/SIZE][/B][/COLOR]

Visix offers a wide variety of choice and entertainment that provides a unique style of game-play for every single one of our players. We provide bug-free flawless enjoyable content that intends to provide enjoyment to several types of players. The economy around Visix is challenging enough that you need to work your way up to get what it is you desire. Just some of what we offer is 8 minigames, over 9 bosses, access to several types of dungeons such as Relekka, ancient cavern, ice dungeon - among many others. We&#39;ve taken into account the skillers community as well, and wrote nearly every skill to match the necessities of those who enjoy the latter. Nearly every skill is available including an impressive Slayer system, farming system with diseasing - among many more. We have 474 maps with 602 of everything else (items, npcs, etc). I&#39;de be able to sit and talk all day about the overview of Visix, instead let&#39;s get right into it.

[COLOR=green][B][SIZE=2]Minigames: [/SIZE][/B][/COLOR]


[ul][*][B]Barrows[/B]: A unique barrows system, complete with a custom interface and a proper addition of killcount which impacts your chance of loot from the chest. Not too mention, you have a chance at obtaining a barrows icon - an icon used to play one of our other enjoyable minigames which we&#39;ll be explained later.
[*][B]Rangers Guild Minigame[/B]: Allows you to build up a hefty amount of points which can later be spent at a shop that provides you with some goodies I&#39;m sure you&#39;ll enjoy.
[*][B]Warriors Guild[/B]: Classic warriors guild involving animating armours and killing them for tokens. These tokens are then used for the top floor for the defeat of Cyclops in hopes of gaining defenders.
[*][B]Pest Control[/B]: Nothing like going out protecting the void knight collecting points to save up for void armour. Or perhaps you want to obtain a fighter torso, barrow gloves among other things. Fully functional pest control allows you to do just that.
[*][B]Fight Caves/Fight Pits[/B]: The Tzhaar areas are all functional, including npc placement around the area. Both minigames are functional, one allowing a player to recieve a fire cape after completing all 63 waves, while the other proving who&#39;s the strongest in a fight to the death.[/ul]


[SPOILER=Minigame Media]
[IMG]http://www.pictrace.com/b/iqmD51.png[/img]
[IMG]http://www.pictrace.com/b/b0JdCe.png[/img]
[IMG]http://www.pictrace.com/b/xAEhTCN.png[/img]
[IMG]http://www.pictrace.com/b/zu3Ew.png[/img]
[IMG]http://www.pictrace.com/b/bdOOo.png[/img]
[IMG]http://www.pictrace.com/b/zhzmHWl.png[/img]
[IMG]http://www.pictrace.com/b/pqzJ.png[/img]
[IMG]http://www.pictrace.com/b/Z4GwIV.png[/img]
[IMG]http://www.pictrace.com/b/TvyW.png[/img]
[IMG]http://www.pictrace.com/b/N2wPY.png[/img]
[IMG]http://www.pictrace.com/b/PYmO.png[/img]
[/SPOILER]


[COLOR=green][B][SIZE=2]Challenge Minigame:[/SIZE][/B][/COLOR]

Take fight in 4 unique challenges allowing one to strain there skills and ability to see how far they can make it through vast waves of monsters. During your time in the game, all prayers are disabled to add a more challenging effect to the player. You can view pictures later in the thread, or continue reading how each fight works.


[ul][*][B]NPC Challenge: [/B]
[*]Take a stand against 10 tough &amp; brutal waves of NPC&#39;s that continuously get stronger and stronger each passing wave.
[*][B]Boss Challenge:[/B]
[*]Similar to the NPC challenge, it allows you to take on some of Visix&#39;s toughest bosses. 
[*][B]Barrows Challenge:[/B]
[*]Players will fight against 7 waves of brothers. They will take a stab at each brother once for 6 waves and fight all 6 at once for the final wave. As explained in the barrows minigame, entry to this is the requirement of a barrows icon which has a chance at loot from the chest doing barrows. Upon successful completion of this challenge, you receive a barrows item.
[*][B]Continual Challenge:[/B]
[*]This is by far the hardest challenge of the minigame. The amount of NPC&#39;s you fight against is equivalent to your current wave. While so, each passing wave the NPC&#39;s become increasingly more and more difficult to fight as their strength, attack, defence and hitpoints all become increased.[/ul]


[SPOILER=Challenge Minigame Media]
[IMG]http://www.pictrace.com/b/PVws.png[/img]
[IMG]http://www.pictrace.com/b/2LX3.png[/img]
[IMG]http://www.pictrace.com/b/NCLH.png[/img]
[IMG]http://www.pictrace.com/b/mhOt.png[/img]
[/SPOILER]


[B][SIZE=2][COLOR=green]Player Vs Monster[/COLOR][/SIZE][/B]

The PVM experience here at Visix provides an uncountable amount of enjoyment that can keep anyone busy. Every last one of our monsters has been designed specifically to provide a challenge unique to that monster, while at the same time allowing players to enjoy there time soloing or bashing it together with friends. Some of the bosses we offer are:


[ul][*]Tormented Demons
[*]Godwars Dungeon
[*]Corporal Beast
[*]King black Dragon
[*]Dagannoth Kings
[*]Kalphite Queen
[*]Sea Troll Queen
[*]Barrelchest
[*]Chaos Elemental[/ul]


[SPOILER=Player Vs Monster Media]
[IMG]http://www.pictrace.com/b/JG2S.png[/img]
[IMG]http://www.pictrace.com/b/cDJtQxw.png[/img]
[IMG]http://www.pictrace.com/b/3McR.png[/img]
[IMG]http://www.pictrace.com/b/yQiuA.png[/img]
[IMG]http://www.pictrace.com/b/iTkQbI.png[/img]
[IMG]http://www.pictrace.com/b/lWM2CN5.png[/img]
[IMG]http://www.pictrace.com/b/Kyph.png[/img]
[/SPOILER]


[B][SIZE=2][COLOR=green]Player Vs Player[/COLOR][/SIZE][/B]

Player Vs Player is one of the most valued things we offer here at Visix. We provide flawless hybridding, melee/range/mage combat with proper hit formulas and max hit calculations. Here at Visix we offer several different spots for players to start wars or simply go 1 on 1. We haven&#39;t given enough though that it&#39;s spread out too much. Being a new community, our intentions are to keep this part of the server more confined for now. Regardless, we have several open spots for one to slash other players:


[ul][*]Edgeville -  1 on 1.
[*]Varrock - Multi combat.
[*]Mage Bank - High level wilderness risk.
[*]Green Dragons - Higher allocation of combat levels to be attacked.
[*]Among a few more...[/ul]


[SPOILER=Player Vs Player Media]
[IMG]http://www.pictrace.com/b/dW3Hx.png[/img]
[IMG]http://www.pictrace.com/b/LNSClz4.png[/img]
[IMG]http://www.pictrace.com/b/ea1LSmd.png[/img]
[IMG]http://www.pictrace.com/b/x2dG.png[/img]
[IMG]http://www.pictrace.com/b/D1q5.png[/img]
[/SPOILER]


[B][COLOR=green][SIZE=2]Skilling[/SIZE][/COLOR][/B]

Skilling is a part in Visix we&#39;ve spent a lot of time on. Skilling in nearly every community is important and that&#39;s why we intend to provide you with the best. Without going into each skill specifically, we&#39;ve taken the time to rewrite nearly every skill to match the way it was intended to be for Visix. Every skill available works as it should and some provide even more features then you see anywhere else.

[B][U]Some[/U] skills in-depth specifically: [/B]


[ul][*][B]Slayer[/B]: Has had an impressive makeover. From an eye-catching interface to nearly every single Slayer task you can find on real Runescape. We&#39;ve done 2 different slayer masters, one providing more points per task/different slayer tasks and one also requires a high Slayer/combat level to talk to. 
[*][B]Farming[/B]: Includes trees + herb farming and diseasing working for trees. We wanted to provide better Farming then the normal herb farming you see, and because of that we provide more choice and oppurtunity for our players. 
[*][B]Smithing[/B]: Nothing has changed from the way regular Smithing works. However we have introduced a new system that involves trimming. The way it works is quite simple. Types of bars that can be earned from the challenge minigame can be used to smith trimmed or gold trimmed armour. The requirement for either varies however doing this provides a unique way of getting these items into the game.
[*][B]Woodcutting/Fishing/Mining[/B]: Skills of these natures require correct use of equipment and proper timers based on that equipment plus the resource one is trying to obtain. We&#39;ve taken account into all these factors including the players level in the skill that calculates a real, proper formula that gets timers based on what the player is trying to do. In doing so, it provides a more realistic and unique style of gameplay as it provides a more random outcome then getting a log every 4th second regardless of the tree being cut regardless of the hatchet being used. Not to mention, we also have working stumps + empty rock support which provides an even more realistic sense of gameplay. For Woodcutting you have a chance of birds nest falling out of trees which provide you with tree seeds when searched.[/ul]


[SPOILER=Skilling Media/Interfaces]
[IMG]http://www.pictrace.com/b/oi4Yi.png[/img]
[IMG]http://www.pictrace.com/b/ApCR1bd.png[/img]
[IMG]http://www.pictrace.com/b/A5AKYfb.png[/img]
[IMG]http://www.pictrace.com/b/bXOFA.png[/img]
[IMG]http://www.pictrace.com/b/WuNZ.png[/img]
[IMG]http://www.pictrace.com/b/A0bdao.png[/img]
[IMG]http://www.pictrace.com/b/iSpCFPp.png[/img]
[IMG]http://www.pictrace.com/b/ay5CzSS.png[/img]
[IMG]http://www.pictrace.com/b/Fjfg.png[/img]
[IMG]http://www.pictrace.com/b/VdFg3wx.png[/img]
[IMG]http://www.pictrace.com/b/wqLmLop.png[/img]
[IMG]http://www.pictrace.com/b/FobQ.png[/img]
[IMG]http://www.pictrace.com/b/2CeeBjQ.png[/img]
[/SPOILER]


[B][SIZE=2][COLOR=green]Questing[/COLOR][/SIZE][/B]

Quests can be an important part of any server. As of now, we currently have 1 available quest - however many more are planned. Some players do not enjoy questing, and as such it&#39;s not required you complete these quests. They are in place for those who enjoy to do a little extra on the side. Currently the quests we do have are:


[ul][*][B]A Clean Slate[/B] - Not available yet.
[*][B]Rune Discovery[/B] - A wizard has heard rumor of an ancient &#39;mysterious ruins&#39;. He wants you to investigate the matter for him. Upon completion, you&#39;ll learn that not everyone is always as first meets the eye.[/ul]


[SPOILER=Quest Media]

[img]http://www.pictrace.com/b/As1V.png[/img]
[img]http://www.pictrace.com/b/PI4vqY.png[/img]

[B][SIZE=2][COLOR=green]Only showing select scenes to avoid spoilers.[/COLOR][/SIZE][/B]
[/SPOILER]


[B][SIZE=2][COLOR=green]Teleportation System[/COLOR][/SIZE][/B]

Travelling to the many destinations of Visix is made easy with an all-in-one teleportation interface that allows users to switch between different tabs and select the destination upon they wish to go. Although this contains a lot of teleports, this is not the only way around Visix. We have most of the teleport tablets working as well, which teleport you to different destinations that provide Slayer monsters and extra training areas. You&#39;d be quite amazed what you might find lurking around the areas.

[SPOILER=Teleportation Media]
[IMG]http://www.pictrace.com/b/AnkEg.png[/img]
[IMG]http://www.pictrace.com/b/UP5NFC.png[/img]
[IMG]http://www.pictrace.com/b/GieK.png[/img]
[/SPOILER]


[B][SIZE=2][COLOR=green]Miscellaneous[/COLOR][/SIZE][/B]
We provide many features here at Visix. It&#39;s hard to categorize them all, here&#39;s some miscellaneous pictures to provide some insight into more of what we provide.

[SPOILER=Miscellaneous Pictures]
[IMG]http://www.pictrace.com/b/EP4BF.png[/img]
[IMG]http://www.pictrace.com/b/L523s.png[/img]
[IMG]http://www.pictrace.com/b/BZIp.png[/img]
[IMG]http://www.pictrace.com/b/UswoX.png[/img]
[IMG]http://www.pictrace.com/b/RwuCeH.png[/img]
[/SPOILER]</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 22 Mar 2014 01:11:17 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Uncategorized</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/visix/541416.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Visix</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@you_owns you owns]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/you_owns">@you_owns</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[CENTER]<img src="http://visix.org/images/logo2.png" alt width="" height="">[/CENTER]</p>
<p>[B][SIZE=2]Website[/SIZE][/B]: <a href="http://Www.Visix.org" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">Visix</a><br>
[B][SIZE=2]Webclient[/SIZE][/B]: <a href="http://Www.Visix.org/webclient" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">Click Here</a><br>
[B][SIZE=2]Downloadable[/SIZE][/B]: <a href="http://Www.Visix.org/Visix.jar" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">Click Here</a><br>
[B][SIZE=2]Vote[/SIZE][/B]: <a href="http://Www.Visix.org/vote" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">Click here</a></p>
<p>[B][SIZE=3][COLOR=green]Visix Features:[/COLOR][/SIZE][/B]</p>
<p>[COLOR=green][B][SIZE=2]Overview[/SIZE][/B][/COLOR]</p>
<p>Visix offers a wide variety of choice and entertainment that provides a unique style of game-play for every single one of our players. We provide bug-free flawless enjoyable content that intends to provide enjoyment to several types of players. The economy around Visix is challenging enough that you need to work your way up to get what it is you desire. Just some of what we offer is 8 minigames, over 9 bosses, access to several types of dungeons such as Relekka, ancient cavern, ice dungeon - among many others. We’ve taken into account the skillers community as well, and wrote nearly every skill to match the necessities of those who enjoy the latter. Nearly every skill is available including an impressive Slayer system, farming system with diseasing - among many more. We have 474 maps with 602 of everything else (items, npcs, etc). I’de be able to sit and talk all day about the overview of Visix, instead let’s get right into it.</p>
<p>[COLOR=green][B][SIZE=2]Minigames: [/SIZE][/B][/COLOR]</p>
<p>[ul][<em>][B]Barrows[/B]: A unique barrows system, complete with a custom interface and a proper addition of killcount which impacts your chance of loot from the chest. Not too mention, you have a chance at obtaining a barrows icon - an icon used to play one of our other enjoyable minigames which we’ll be explained later.<br>
[</em>][B]Rangers Guild Minigame[/B]: Allows you to build up a hefty amount of points which can later be spent at a shop that provides you with some goodies I’m sure you’ll enjoy.<br>
[<em>][B]Warriors Guild[/B]: Classic warriors guild involving animating armours and killing them for tokens. These tokens are then used for the top floor for the defeat of Cyclops in hopes of gaining defenders.<br>
[</em>][B]Pest Control[/B]: Nothing like going out protecting the void knight collecting points to save up for void armour. Or perhaps you want to obtain a fighter torso, barrow gloves among other things. Fully functional pest control allows you to do just that.<br>
[*][B]Fight Caves/Fight Pits[/B]: The Tzhaar areas are all functional, including npc placement around the area. Both minigames are functional, one allowing a player to recieve a fire cape after completing all 63 waves, while the other proving who’s the strongest in a fight to the death.[/ul]</p>
<p>[SPOILER=Minigame Media]<br>
<img src="http://www.pictrace.com/b/iqmD51.png" alt width="" height=""><br>
<img src="http://www.pictrace.com/b/b0JdCe.png" alt width="" height=""><br>
<img src="http://www.pictrace.com/b/xAEhTCN.png" alt width="" height=""><br>
<img src="http://www.pictrace.com/b/zu3Ew.png" alt width="" height=""><br>
<img src="http://www.pictrace.com/b/bdOOo.png" alt width="" height=""><br>
<img src="http://www.pictrace.com/b/zhzmHWl.png" alt width="" height=""><br>
<img src="http://www.pictrace.com/b/pqzJ.png" alt width="" height=""><br>
<img src="http://www.pictrace.com/b/Z4GwIV.png" alt width="" height=""><br>
<img src="http://www.pictrace.com/b/TvyW.png" alt width="" height=""><br>
<img src="http://www.pictrace.com/b/N2wPY.png" alt width="" height=""><br>
<img src="http://www.pictrace.com/b/PYmO.png" alt width="" height=""><br>
[/SPOILER]</p>
<p>[COLOR=green][B][SIZE=2]Challenge Minigame:[/SIZE][/B][/COLOR]</p>
<p>Take fight in 4 unique challenges allowing one to strain there skills and ability to see how far they can make it through vast waves of monsters. During your time in the game, all prayers are disabled to add a more challenging effect to the player. You can view pictures later in the thread, or continue reading how each fight works.</p>
<p>[ul][<em>][B]NPC Challenge: [/B]<br>
[</em>]Take a stand against 10 tough &amp; brutal waves of NPC’s that continuously get stronger and stronger each passing wave.<br>
[<em>][B]Boss Challenge:[/B]<br>
[</em>]Similar to the NPC challenge, it allows you to take on some of Visix’s toughest bosses.<br>
[<em>][B]Barrows Challenge:[/B]<br>
[</em>]Players will fight against 7 waves of brothers. They will take a stab at each brother once for 6 waves and fight all 6 at once for the final wave. As explained in the barrows minigame, entry to this is the requirement of a barrows icon which has a chance at loot from the chest doing barrows. Upon successful completion of this challenge, you receive a barrows item.<br>
[<em>][B]Continual Challenge:[/B]<br>
[</em>]This is by far the hardest challenge of the minigame. The amount of NPC’s you fight against is equivalent to your current wave. While so, each passing wave the NPC’s become increasingly more and more difficult to fight as their strength, attack, defence and hitpoints all become increased.[/ul]</p>
<p>[SPOILER=Challenge Minigame Media]<br>
<img src="http://www.pictrace.com/b/PVws.png" alt width="" height=""><br>
<img src="http://www.pictrace.com/b/2LX3.png" alt width="" height=""><br>
<img src="http://www.pictrace.com/b/NCLH.png" alt width="" height=""><br>
<img src="http://www.pictrace.com/b/mhOt.png" alt width="" height=""><br>
[/SPOILER]</p>
<p>[B][SIZE=2][COLOR=green]Player Vs Monster[/COLOR][/SIZE][/B]</p>
<p>The PVM experience here at Visix provides an uncountable amount of enjoyment that can keep anyone busy. Every last one of our monsters has been designed specifically to provide a challenge unique to that monster, while at the same time allowing players to enjoy there time soloing or bashing it together with friends. Some of the bosses we offer are:</p>
<p>[ul][<em>]Tormented Demons<br>
[</em>]Godwars Dungeon<br>
[<em>]Corporal Beast<br>
[</em>]King black Dragon<br>
[<em>]Dagannoth Kings<br>
[</em>]Kalphite Queen<br>
[<em>]Sea Troll Queen<br>
[</em>]Barrelchest<br>
[*]Chaos Elemental[/ul]</p>
<p>[SPOILER=Player Vs Monster Media]<br>
<img src="http://www.pictrace.com/b/JG2S.png" alt width="" height=""><br>
<img src="http://www.pictrace.com/b/cDJtQxw.png" alt width="" height=""><br>
<img src="http://www.pictrace.com/b/3McR.png" alt width="" height=""><br>
<img src="http://www.pictrace.com/b/yQiuA.png" alt width="" height=""><br>
<img src="http://www.pictrace.com/b/iTkQbI.png" alt width="" height=""><br>
<img src="http://www.pictrace.com/b/lWM2CN5.png" alt width="" height=""><br>
<img src="http://www.pictrace.com/b/Kyph.png" alt width="" height=""><br>
[/SPOILER]</p>
<p>[B][SIZE=2][COLOR=green]Player Vs Player[/COLOR][/SIZE][/B]</p>
<p>Player Vs Player is one of the most valued things we offer here at Visix. We provide flawless hybridding, melee/range/mage combat with proper hit formulas and max hit calculations. Here at Visix we offer several different spots for players to start wars or simply go 1 on 1. We haven’t given enough though that it’s spread out too much. Being a new community, our intentions are to keep this part of the server more confined for now. Regardless, we have several open spots for one to slash other players:</p>
<p>[ul][<em>]Edgeville -  1 on 1.<br>
[</em>]Varrock - Multi combat.<br>
[<em>]Mage Bank - High level wilderness risk.<br>
[</em>]Green Dragons - Higher allocation of combat levels to be attacked.<br>
[*]Among a few more…[/ul]</p>
<p>[SPOILER=Player Vs Player Media]<br>
<img src="http://www.pictrace.com/b/dW3Hx.png" alt width="" height=""><br>
<img src="http://www.pictrace.com/b/LNSClz4.png" alt width="" height=""><br>
<img src="http://www.pictrace.com/b/ea1LSmd.png" alt width="" height=""><br>
<img src="http://www.pictrace.com/b/x2dG.png" alt width="" height=""><br>
<img src="http://www.pictrace.com/b/D1q5.png" alt width="" height=""><br>
[/SPOILER]</p>
<p>[B][COLOR=green][SIZE=2]Skilling[/SIZE][/COLOR][/B]</p>
<p>Skilling is a part in Visix we’ve spent a lot of time on. Skilling in nearly every community is important and that’s why we intend to provide you with the best. Without going into each skill specifically, we’ve taken the time to rewrite nearly every skill to match the way it was intended to be for Visix. Every skill available works as it should and some provide even more features then you see anywhere else.</p>
<p>[B][U]Some[/U] skills in-depth specifically: [/B]</p>
<p>[ul][<em>][B]Slayer[/B]: Has had an impressive makeover. From an eye-catching interface to nearly every single Slayer task you can find on real Runescape. We’ve done 2 different slayer masters, one providing more points per task/different slayer tasks and one also requires a high Slayer/combat level to talk to.<br>
[</em>][B]Farming[/B]: Includes trees + herb farming and diseasing working for trees. We wanted to provide better Farming then the normal herb farming you see, and because of that we provide more choice and oppurtunity for our players.<br>
[<em>][B]Smithing[/B]: Nothing has changed from the way regular Smithing works. However we have introduced a new system that involves trimming. The way it works is quite simple. Types of bars that can be earned from the challenge minigame can be used to smith trimmed or gold trimmed armour. The requirement for either varies however doing this provides a unique way of getting these items into the game.<br>
[</em>][B]Woodcutting/Fishing/Mining[/B]: Skills of these natures require correct use of equipment and proper timers based on that equipment plus the resource one is trying to obtain. We’ve taken account into all these factors including the players level in the skill that calculates a real, proper formula that gets timers based on what the player is trying to do. In doing so, it provides a more realistic and unique style of gameplay as it provides a more random outcome then getting a log every 4th second regardless of the tree being cut regardless of the hatchet being used. Not to mention, we also have working stumps + empty rock support which provides an even more realistic sense of gameplay. For Woodcutting you have a chance of birds nest falling out of trees which provide you with tree seeds when searched.[/ul]</p>
<p>[SPOILER=Skilling Media/Interfaces]<br>
<img src="http://www.pictrace.com/b/oi4Yi.png" alt width="" height=""><br>
<img src="http://www.pictrace.com/b/ApCR1bd.png" alt width="" height=""><br>
<img src="http://www.pictrace.com/b/A5AKYfb.png" alt width="" height=""><br>
<img src="http://www.pictrace.com/b/bXOFA.png" alt width="" height=""><br>
<img src="http://www.pictrace.com/b/WuNZ.png" alt width="" height=""><br>
<img src="http://www.pictrace.com/b/A0bdao.png" alt width="" height=""><br>
<img src="http://www.pictrace.com/b/iSpCFPp.png" alt width="" height=""><br>
<img src="http://www.pictrace.com/b/ay5CzSS.png" alt width="" height=""><br>
<img src="http://www.pictrace.com/b/Fjfg.png" alt width="" height=""><br>
<img src="http://www.pictrace.com/b/VdFg3wx.png" alt width="" height=""><br>
<img src="http://www.pictrace.com/b/wqLmLop.png" alt width="" height=""><br>
<img src="http://www.pictrace.com/b/FobQ.png" alt width="" height=""><br>
<img src="http://www.pictrace.com/b/2CeeBjQ.png" alt width="" height=""><br>
[/SPOILER]</p>
<p>[B][SIZE=2][COLOR=green]Questing[/COLOR][/SIZE][/B]</p>
<p>Quests can be an important part of any server. As of now, we currently have 1 available quest - however many more are planned. Some players do not enjoy questing, and as such it’s not required you complete these quests. They are in place for those who enjoy to do a little extra on the side. Currently the quests we do have are:</p>
<p>[ul][<em>][B]A Clean Slate[/B] - Not available yet.<br>
[</em>][B]Rune Discovery[/B] - A wizard has heard rumor of an ancient ‘mysterious ruins’. He wants you to investigate the matter for him. Upon completion, you’ll learn that not everyone is always as first meets the eye.[/ul]</p>
<p>[SPOILER=Quest Media]</p>
<p><img src="http://www.pictrace.com/b/As1V.png" alt width="" height=""><br>
<img src="http://www.pictrace.com/b/PI4vqY.png" alt width="" height=""></p>
<p>[B][SIZE=2][COLOR=green]Only showing select scenes to avoid spoilers.[/COLOR][/SIZE][/B]<br>
[/SPOILER]</p>
<p>[B][SIZE=2][COLOR=green]Teleportation System[/COLOR][/SIZE][/B]</p>
<p>Travelling to the many destinations of Visix is made easy with an all-in-one teleportation interface that allows users to switch between different tabs and select the destination upon they wish to go. Although this contains a lot of teleports, this is not the only way around Visix. We have most of the teleport tablets working as well, which teleport you to different destinations that provide Slayer monsters and extra training areas. You’d be quite amazed what you might find lurking around the areas.</p>
<p>[SPOILER=Teleportation Media]<br>
<img src="http://www.pictrace.com/b/AnkEg.png" alt width="" height=""><br>
<img src="http://www.pictrace.com/b/UP5NFC.png" alt width="" height=""><br>
<img src="http://www.pictrace.com/b/GieK.png" alt width="" height=""><br>
[/SPOILER]</p>
<p>[B][SIZE=2][COLOR=green]Miscellaneous[/COLOR][/SIZE][/B]<br>
We provide many features here at Visix. It’s hard to categorize them all, here’s some miscellaneous pictures to provide some insight into more of what we provide.</p>
<p>[SPOILER=Miscellaneous Pictures]<br>
<img src="http://www.pictrace.com/b/EP4BF.png" alt width="" height=""><br>
<img src="http://www.pictrace.com/b/L523s.png" alt width="" height=""><br>
<img src="http://www.pictrace.com/b/BZIp.png" alt width="" height=""><br>
<img src="http://www.pictrace.com/b/UswoX.png" alt width="" height=""><br>
<img src="http://www.pictrace.com/b/RwuCeH.png" alt width="" height=""><br>
[/SPOILER]</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/visix/541416/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/visix/541416/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 22 Mar 2014 01:11:17 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-541416-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/visix/541416.rss">Visix</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
