<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Web client</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/web-client/179443</link>
    <description>     Ok, i know that im going to be flamed to all hell by posting yet ANOTHER web client or something but im tired of the &quot;look in the downloads section&quot; or &quot;use search&quot;. Those aren&#39;t answers. Seriously somebody should just write up a very noob friendly guide on how to make one, just to stop the constant bombardment of questions.

Ok enough whining.

I have a server set up and all, i&#39;ve downloaded a generic web client but it&#39;s not what i want on the internet, it has all the normal stuff of the moparscape client. How do i set it to my server Ip, port and how do i take out all the aryan and command bar, add my music and the stuff like that. Thanks in advance.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 08 Feb 2008 09:25:58 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/web-client/179443.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Web client</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@hamster40 hamster40]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/hamster40">@hamster40</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <pre><code> Ok, i know that im going to be flamed to all hell by posting yet ANOTHER web client or something but im tired of the "look in the downloads section" or "use search". Those aren't answers. Seriously somebody should just write up a very noob friendly guide on how to make one, just to stop the constant bombardment of questions.
</code></pre>
<p>Ok enough whining.</p>
<p>I have a server set up and all, i’ve downloaded a generic web client but it’s not what i want on the internet, it has all the normal stuff of the moparscape client. How do i set it to my server Ip, port and how do i take out all the aryan and command bar, add my music and the stuff like that. Thanks in advance.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/web-client/179443/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/web-client/179443/1</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Feb 2008 09:25:58 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-179443-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/web-client/179443.rss">Web client</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
