<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Is there a way to modify a string in a .txt file using Buffered Writer?</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/is-there-a-way-to-modify-a-string-in-a-txt-file-using-buffered-writer/26123</link>
    <description>Well, after a long date with Google, I&#39;ve found that it is apparently *impossible* to delete a string from a .txt file using Java. That brings me to my next question: Is there a way to *overwrite* a string of text.

So why do I need this? Well, many parts of my server use Buffered Reader to check .txt files. Things on my server that work like this include:
1. The noclip warning file, (where the player&#39;s name is appended to the list when they use ::noclip; if they&#39;re found on this list the next time they noclip, they then get automatically get banned - I find it a fair system, as it warns the user upon logging on each time that they have noclipped etc).

2. My restriction command, which relies on a .txt file. This stops players from moving permanently... I use this for idiots etc and then tele them to some remote place in the wilderness.

3. My permanent teleblock command. Serves the same purpose as the permanent restrict command - it&#39;s for annoying people that don&#39;t follow the rules, or are just idiots.

4. My mute command, which also appends a player&#39;s name to a .txt file upon me using the command.

Now, why am I asking this, and why is it so important to me? Well, my friend from school might do a bit of hosting for me, but I won&#39;t have direct access to the files... He&#39;d be doing most of that stuff. Anyway, because of this, I&#39;m still going to need a way to append and remove names from these lists. I can already add names, but the second part I&#39;m still at a loss with.

Anyone who can help, I&#39;d gladly appreciate it. Thanks if you do.
[br][size=1]Posted at: November 16, 2006, 07:22:05 PM[/size][hr]Oh, to basically highlight exactly my idea: I want to use a ::command in-game, and when I type a name after it, I want the Buffered Reader to search for that word in the .txt file, and then I want the Buffered Writer to overwrite that word with ~~~~~~~~, %%%%%%%% or something along those lines.[br][size=1]Posted at: November 16, 2006, 07:24:36 PM[/size][hr]Anyone?</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 17 Nov 2006 11:16:59 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/is-there-a-way-to-modify-a-string-in-a-txt-file-using-buffered-writer/26123.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Is there a way to modify a string in a .txt file using Buffered Writer?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Javacisnotrecognized _^_]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/javacisnotrecognized">@Javacisnotrecognized</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>If your using the BufferedWriter, an invocation of flush() will automatically replace the contents of the file being written with the contents of the buffer.</p>
<p>Your problem, however, is not with the buffer. Your problem is that the JVM will read from the buffer once, and then store the result in its memory. If the contents of the file are changed, and the file is not re-read and the variables redefined, the JVM will not make any changes.<br>
You seem to know enough Java to fix that, but since using the bufferedReader is a relatively time consuming operation, I will suggest this for you:</p>
<p>Make all the character status things (Like muted or banned or immobile any other of your punishments) part of the profile itself; so that the reader doesn’t have to go through an entire list to get to them.</p>
<p>It would almost be like storing the attack levels of your players all in one file, the names of them all in another, the passwords in another etc. Impracticle once you get a large player audience</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/is-there-a-way-to-modify-a-string-in-a-txt-file-using-buffered-writer/26123/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/is-there-a-way-to-modify-a-string-in-a-txt-file-using-buffered-writer/26123/2</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 17 Nov 2006 11:16:59 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-26123-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/is-there-a-way-to-modify-a-string-in-a-txt-file-using-buffered-writer/26123.rss">Is there a way to modify a string in a .txt file using Buffered Writer?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Is there a way to modify a string in a .txt file using Buffered Writer?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@lothy Lothy]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/lothy">@lothy</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Well, after a long date with Google, I’ve found that it is apparently <em>impossible</em> to delete a string from a .txt file using Java. That brings me to my next question: Is there a way to <em>overwrite</em> a string of text.</p>
<p>So why do I need this? Well, many parts of my server use Buffered Reader to check .txt files. Things on my server that work like this include:</p>
<ol>
<li>
<p>The noclip warning file, (where the player’s name is appended to the list when they use ::noclip; if they’re found on this list the next time they noclip, they then get automatically get banned - I find it a fair system, as it warns the user upon logging on each time that they have noclipped etc).</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>My restriction command, which relies on a .txt file. This stops players from moving permanently… I use this for idiots etc and then tele them to some remote place in the wilderness.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>My permanent teleblock command. Serves the same purpose as the permanent restrict command - it’s for annoying people that don’t follow the rules, or are just idiots.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>My mute command, which also appends a player’s name to a .txt file upon me using the command.</p>
</li>
</ol>
<p>Now, why am I asking this, and why is it so important to me? Well, my friend from school might do a bit of hosting for me, but I won’t have direct access to the files… He’d be doing most of that stuff. Anyway, because of this, I’m still going to need a way to append and remove names from these lists. I can already add names, but the second part I’m still at a loss with.</p>
<p>Anyone who can help, I’d gladly appreciate it. Thanks if you do.<br>
[br][size=1]Posted at: November 16, 2006, 07:22:05 PM[/size][hr]Oh, to basically highlight exactly my idea: I want to use a ::command in-game, and when I type a name after it, I want the Buffered Reader to search for that word in the .txt file, and then I want the Buffered Writer to overwrite that word with ~~~~~~~~, %%%%%%%% or something along those lines.[br][size=1]Posted at: November 16, 2006, 07:24:36 PM[/size][hr]Anyone?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/is-there-a-way-to-modify-a-string-in-a-txt-file-using-buffered-writer/26123/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/is-there-a-way-to-modify-a-string-in-a-txt-file-using-buffered-writer/26123/1</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 17 Nov 2006 10:58:19 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-26123-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/is-there-a-way-to-modify-a-string-in-a-txt-file-using-buffered-writer/26123.rss">Is there a way to modify a string in a .txt file using Buffered Writer?</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
