<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Tnt factions [factions] [pvp] [griefing] [friendly staff] [24/7] [economy] [mcmm</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/tnt-factions-factions-pvp-griefing-friendly-staff-24-7-economy-mcmm/439201</link>
    <description>Do you want a PvP server, where people actually want to fight you?  Want a factions server that ENCOURAGES griefing and use of TNT to raid factions? Sick of admins either not responding or using their powers to cheat? Are you tired of joining servers and then getting bored a few days later?

If you answered yes to any of these questions, then  TNT Factions is the server for you! Our server rewards people for PvP. We encourage raiding and allow TNT. Our staff are professional, responsive and are very friendly (long as you don&#39;t cheat!). Think your interested? Check out some of our features below:

PvP: At TNT factions, we LOVE PvP. Our players are rewarded for killing others with in-game money, which can be used in our admin shop. We have a leaderboard so you can see just how good you are at PvP. If you get to the top of the leaderboard, we give you a special prize........ 

Factions: Our server is factions based. You can join a faction, or make your own. Then you can partake in faction wars. These are can be either amazing battles between factions in the arena, or epic conquests to raid other faction bases, or a mix of both. We strongly recommend  joining a faction as our server is designed to be challenging, even for the best of PvPers and Raiders.

Bounty Hunters: Tired of meaninglessly slaughtering your foes? You can be a bounty hunter! Bounty Hunters are the elite PvPers in our server. They get paid huge amounts of money for killing targets. To be a bounty hunter, you have to be good at PvP, then an admin will send you an invitation to the exclusive Bounty Hunter club!

Events: Every month, we have a special event. This can be any number of things, from Capture the Admin, to Who can Survive the Zombie apocalypse? The event this month is: Refer a Friend: The person who gets the most friends to join the server and register on the forums wins a mystery prize! And for every person you refer, you get a diamond! Go to our forum for more info on events!

Anti-Cheat: While we encourage PvP and raiding, we are very against cheating. We know when someone is cheating. We know their tricks from experience :D So don&#39;t cheat. You will be banned. If you think someone is cheating, you can report them to our admins, who will carry out a thorough  investigation.

Interested? Check out our youtube video here:
[youtube]http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=PY9Hdv6DBtc&amp;context=C4192566ADvjVQa1PpcFNs2Q6k-anYfZsqri_fw_l7-Vushb0mjNg=[/youtube]

IP: tntfactions.servegame.com:25565
Visit our forum at: tntfactions.forumotion.org</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 10 Apr 2012 19:39:40 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Minecraft</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/tnt-factions-factions-pvp-griefing-friendly-staff-24-7-economy-mcmm/439201.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Tnt factions [factions] [pvp] [griefing] [friendly staff] [24/7] [economy] [mcmm</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@tntfactions tntfactions]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/tntfactions">@tntfactions</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Do you want a PvP server, where people actually want to fight you?  Want a factions server that ENCOURAGES griefing and use of TNT to raid factions? Sick of admins either not responding or using their powers to cheat? Are you tired of joining servers and then getting bored a few days later?</p>
<p>If you answered yes to any of these questions, then  TNT Factions is the server for you! Our server rewards people for PvP. We encourage raiding and allow TNT. Our staff are professional, responsive and are very friendly (long as you don’t cheat!). Think your interested? Check out some of our features below:</p>
<p>PvP: At TNT factions, we LOVE PvP. Our players are rewarded for killing others with in-game money, which can be used in our admin shop. We have a leaderboard so you can see just how good you are at PvP. If you get to the top of the leaderboard, we give you a special prize…</p>
<p>Factions: Our server is factions based. You can join a faction, or make your own. Then you can partake in faction wars. These are can be either amazing battles between factions in the arena, or epic conquests to raid other faction bases, or a mix of both. We strongly recommend  joining a faction as our server is designed to be challenging, even for the best of PvPers and Raiders.</p>
<p>Bounty Hunters: Tired of meaninglessly slaughtering your foes? You can be a bounty hunter! Bounty Hunters are the elite PvPers in our server. They get paid huge amounts of money for killing targets. To be a bounty hunter, you have to be good at PvP, then an admin will send you an invitation to the exclusive Bounty Hunter club!</p>
<p>Events: Every month, we have a special event. This can be any number of things, from Capture the Admin, to Who can Survive the Zombie apocalypse? The event this month is: Refer a Friend: The person who gets the most friends to join the server and register on the forums wins a mystery prize! And for every person you refer, you get a diamond! Go to our forum for more info on events!</p>
<p>Anti-Cheat: While we encourage PvP and raiding, we are very against cheating. We know when someone is cheating. We know their tricks from experience <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/smiley.png?v=5" title=":smiley:" class="emoji" alt=":smiley:"> So don’t cheat. You will be banned. If you think someone is cheating, you can report them to our admins, who will carry out a thorough  investigation.</p>
<p>Interested? Check out our youtube video here:<br>
[youtube]<a href="http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=PY9Hdv6DBtc&amp;context=C4192566ADvjVQa1PpcFNs2Q6k-anYfZsqri_fw_l7-Vushb0mjNg=%5B/youtube%5D" rel="nofollow noopener">http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=PY9Hdv6DBtc&amp;context=C4192566ADvjVQa1PpcFNs2Q6k-anYfZsqri_fw_l7-Vushb0mjNg=[/youtube]</a></p>
<p>IP: <a href="http://tntfactions.servegame.com:25565" rel="nofollow noopener">tntfactions.servegame.com:25565</a><br>
Visit our forum at: <a href="http://tntfactions.forumotion.org" rel="nofollow noopener">tntfactions.forumotion.org</a></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/tnt-factions-factions-pvp-griefing-friendly-staff-24-7-economy-mcmm/439201/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/tnt-factions-factions-pvp-griefing-friendly-staff-24-7-economy-mcmm/439201/1</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 10 Apr 2012 19:39:40 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-439201-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/tnt-factions-factions-pvp-griefing-friendly-staff-24-7-economy-mcmm/439201.rss">Tnt factions [factions] [pvp] [griefing] [friendly staff] [24/7] [economy] [mcmm</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
