<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>School hacking help [REQ]</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/school-hacking-help-req/157911</link>
    <description>Eh, I don&#39;t know if you&#39;d even call this hacking. I would appreciate some help.

So-basic idea, get my teacher(s) pass(es) for our school&#39;s online grading system.

Key Points:
Grading system is Aeries, you can acess it online, but you need the school code, which I can&#39;t find.
Aeries is only installed on admin accounts (teachers).
We have deepfreeze at our school, but I have an &quot;undeepfreeze&quot; program. I have yet to test it.
I have multiple accounts on our school computers.
CMD is acessible.
I won&#39;t use my home computer at all, just the library&#39;s.

So, I&#39;ve been thinking, quite a lot actually. 

#1 I was thinking of making an admin account via CMD, then I&#39;d use a cracking program with wordlists to crack one of my teachers Aeries accounts. Feasible? I would have to make a new account everyday, because you can only create, save, and edit accounts from the library computers.

#2 Get a good keylogger, (suggestions?) put keylogger on the disk/file I am to use while presenting something. That way the teacher puts it in their computer to show it on the projectors we have at school. Or I could just put the disk in when the teacher leaves the room. The thing is, our deepfreeze deletes everything except our personal H drives, so I would need it to install into there if possible...

#3 Same as #1 except I crack my teacher&#39;s school account passes, not Aeries. Then I could install a keylogger. But this is sorta impossible due to the fact that you only get 5 trys. Plus I need to get their usernames too...

Any ideas? What keylogger and cracker should I use? I was thinking of acessdriver, does that even do that shit?

Also, is there anyway they could trace it to me if I use other people&#39;s accounts at school, and I don&#39;t use my home computer. My main fear is having the system detect a keylogger on a powerpoint presentation or something.

EDIT: Thought I wouldn&#39;t have to tell people to not flame me because of morals. Wow.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 13 Nov 2007 18:03:12 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>General Discussion</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/school-hacking-help-req/157911.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>School hacking help [REQ]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@R.I.P_RSC R.I.P RSC]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/r.i.p_rsc">@R.I.P_RSC</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Try to access the system account, it’s the most powerfull account on the computer. There are some tut’s on youtube.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/school-hacking-help-req/157911/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/school-hacking-help-req/157911/6</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 13 Nov 2007 18:03:12 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-157911-6</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/school-hacking-help-req/157911.rss">School hacking help [REQ]</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>School hacking help [REQ]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@tomo6627 tomo6627]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/tomo6627">@tomo6627</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Fellix, there’s no need to attack me, give me something worthwhile ie: aspects where I’m wrong or ways to do it.</p>
<p>And thanks Eh, but I have made one, but it probably got erased after I logged off or I probably couldn’t log onto it.</p>
<p>Ugh, I feel a flame-war coming on, let’s try to mitigate it eh? Don’t insult me and think I’ll be hurt by it. If anything, I’ll only consider you more of a moron. No, I will not flame you back if you’re just looking to start something, there’s no point. And yes, I’m aware that my first post may be painfully wrong/inaccurate to some. I understand the legal side of it so no moar posts on that?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/school-hacking-help-req/157911/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/school-hacking-help-req/157911/5</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 13 Nov 2007 11:36:51 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-157911-5</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/school-hacking-help-req/157911.rss">School hacking help [REQ]</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>School hacking help [REQ]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Eh_Pretty_Easy Eh Pretty Easy]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/eh_pretty_easy">@Eh_Pretty_Easy</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“tomo6627, post:1, topic:157911”]<span class="hashtag">#1</span> I was thinking of making an admin account via CMD[/quote]Wouldn’t work, even you can access cmd there is no way for you to make new accounts on a student account.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/school-hacking-help-req/157911/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/school-hacking-help-req/157911/4</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Nov 2007 19:55:26 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-157911-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/school-hacking-help-req/157911.rss">School hacking help [REQ]</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>School hacking help [REQ]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@fellixombc fellixombc]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/fellixombc">@fellixombc</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>this is epic fail.</p>
<p>why not just study and get good grades for once and get a fricken life? and if you acsess the school system, you could go to jail for hacking moron, exspecially hacking a school system. And if you changed your grade, teachers would notice, so over all this is just gay, i just say study and your good. And btw, you won’t be able hack a school computer, because you need more than a user and pass, you need the “school system admin” to acsess anything, if you have one teachers pass and users, you can only change one class grades.<br>
overall: GAY IDEA</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/school-hacking-help-req/157911/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/school-hacking-help-req/157911/3</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Nov 2007 19:39:02 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-157911-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/school-hacking-help-req/157911.rss">School hacking help [REQ]</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>School hacking help [REQ]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@ninja_nub ninja nub]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/ninja_nub">@ninja_nub</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>You can face some hefty legal problems if you do this. Also get a mandatory 10 day suspension and/or expulsion.</p>
<p>Still want to do it?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/school-hacking-help-req/157911/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/school-hacking-help-req/157911/2</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Nov 2007 11:07:18 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-157911-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/school-hacking-help-req/157911.rss">School hacking help [REQ]</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>School hacking help [REQ]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@tomo6627 tomo6627]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/tomo6627">@tomo6627</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Eh, I don’t know if you’d even call this hacking. I would appreciate some help.</p>
<p>So-basic idea, get my teacher(s) pass(es) for our school’s online grading system.</p>
<p>Key Points:<br>
Grading system is Aeries, you can acess it online, but you need the school code, which I can’t find.<br>
Aeries is only installed on admin accounts (teachers).<br>
We have deepfreeze at our school, but I have an “undeepfreeze” program. I have yet to test it.<br>
I have multiple accounts on our school computers.<br>
CMD is acessible.<br>
I won’t use my home computer at all, just the library’s.</p>
<p>So, I’ve been thinking, quite a lot actually.</p>
<p><span class="hashtag">#1</span> I was thinking of making an admin account via CMD, then I’d use a cracking program with wordlists to crack one of my teachers Aeries accounts. Feasible? I would have to make a new account everyday, because you can only create, save, and edit accounts from the library computers.</p>
<p><span class="hashtag">#2</span> Get a good keylogger, (suggestions?) put keylogger on the disk/file I am to use while presenting something. That way the teacher puts it in their computer to show it on the projectors we have at school. Or I could just put the disk in when the teacher leaves the room. The thing is, our deepfreeze deletes everything except our personal H drives, so I would need it to install into there if possible…</p>
<p><span class="hashtag">#3</span> Same as <span class="hashtag">#1</span> except I crack my teacher’s school account passes, not Aeries. Then I could install a keylogger. But this is sorta impossible due to the fact that you only get 5 trys. Plus I need to get their usernames too…</p>
<p>Any ideas? What keylogger and cracker should I use? I was thinking of acessdriver, does that even do that shit?</p>
<p>Also, is there anyway they could trace it to me if I use other people’s accounts at school, and I don’t use my home computer. My main fear is having the system detect a keylogger on a powerpoint presentation or something.</p>
<p>EDIT: Thought I wouldn’t have to tell people to not flame me because of morals. Wow.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/school-hacking-help-req/157911/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/school-hacking-help-req/157911/1</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Nov 2007 10:40:54 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-157911-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/school-hacking-help-req/157911.rss">School hacking help [REQ]</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
