<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>~~Revolution List~~</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/revolution-list/230582</link>
    <description>[center][b]~~My revolution list~~[/b]
(This is what I&#39;m going to do to create a new revolution in Moparscape pking)
[sup]*This a very detailed list, so I&#39;m going to warn you ahead of time*[/sup] [/center]


[b][u]Table of Contents[/u]

Intro
 -Banking
 -Clans/Gangs/Teams
 -Obstacles
 -Battle-Grounds
 -Pking Minigames
 -Looting
Conclusion
[/b]

[center][b][i]Intro[/i][/b][/center]
This is my revolution list, and basically what this is, is it&#39;s just me telling you what I&#39;m going to do to &quot;revolutionize&quot; Moparscape/Private server pking... Yeah I went there, I&#39;m actually so bored that I&#39;m going to describe every last detail of what I want to do to totally own the rest of the servers (in the pking content)

[center][b][i]Banking[/i][/b][/center]
For those of you that havent seen my other post about this, I&#39;m going to limit wilderness banking to make pking more stratigic in a way that is almost cruel. So what I&#39;m planning to do is this
             -Make an item into a banking mechanism. For of those that would like further elaboration, I&#39;m going to make it to where you HAVE to have a certain item to bank in the wilderness (i.e. an amulet, chest, ring...) and this item will be non-tradeable, non-sellable, and will be somewhat hard to get, but totally worth it in the end (especially when you&#39;re the only one able to bank in the wilderness) 
             -The reason for this madness is because I really hate those people that pk in the wilderness and open up their bank and act llike pansies and get food out of their bank, and other items... So this way I made it a little more challenging but still fun

[center][b][i]Clans/Gangs/Teams[/i][/b][/center]
                If you know me (which I doubt any of you do) you would know that I am a big fan of teaming and a big fan of clan/gang/team pking. I think everyone is in a way thought. But the reason I like this form of pking the most is because I like the feeling of having power (what little of it is given to me by being a clan) over the rest of the players, and it&#39;s really fun to guide you&#39;re clan/gang/team through the wilderness and own other people. But the most epic part of this is the Clan v.s. Clan, or Gang v.s. Gang, or Team v.s. Team pking. So I added Clan Wars to my server, and this will allow you to obtain 1mil, or some other item (including the banking item). Also I want to add Clan Chat and other stuff.


[center][b][i]Obstacles[/i][/b][/center]

          What I&#39;m (mainly) trying to do, is make the wilderness more challenging and I want players to strategize more when they go pking. Now I know this is a long way away from people actually trying to strategize when pking on a simple private server, but still, it could happen... Anyway, I was thinking about adding some obstacles to the wilderness that way the archers and mages could actually have an advantage instead of fighting in that huge flat open area. Because in that huge open area, there isn&#39;t much protection for archers and mages now is there? It&#39;s basically just a huge brawl of a whole bunch of people that mass click a server until their fingers bleed. So thats why I want obstacles in my server, this way clans/gangs/teams can &quot;stratigize&quot; in positioning their players.
         Also, I&#39;m going to add the Castle Wars blockades to my server so that way clans/gangs/teams can use more strategy and totally block out everyone...

[center][b][i]Battle-Grounds[/i][/b][/center]
         I&#39;m also very tired of pking in the same old place over and over again... So I&#39;m going to add a battlegrounds arena (Castle Wars arena) this way people can fight in a huge open area, but some of you are probably thinking that my idea is kind of pointless right? Well actually I would have multiple things that you could do, and I would add in altars, and even a bank. So thing of Castle Wars, but with altars, banks, more death-like scenery, and a three headed fire breathing dragon to sum it all up...

[center][b][i]Pking Minigames[/i][/b][/center]
          I&#39;ve had this idea for a while, I even suggested it on RuneScape but it got crucified on the forums, so I&#39;m going to add it on my own private server. Yes, a Pking Minigame, but not just one, a whole fuck-load of minigames... Think of them as mini-tasks, because that&#39;s really what they are. These Minigames/tasks consist of helping out your teamates (in a certain arena) by doing things such as...
    -Capture the Flag (This is basically a neverending cycle of hell, because each team has to obtain the other team&#39;s flag, but here&#39;s the fun part... The game never resets, and neither do the tasks =Þ so people are going to be raping each other throughout the whole game, but don&#39;t think of it as a game, think of it as pking, but with friends and jobs to do)
    -Replinish Death (This task I took from my game Clan Wars, To start off I need to tell you this, When you enter the Pking task arena you get a ring for your side, so what you have to do is simply kill another player from the other side and get their ring, once you have this, you run back to your side and find your statue and pray to it, and if you have the ring from the other side you complete the tast)
    -Kill the Immortal (This is basically the same as the task mentioned before, only you have to kill a certain monster to get a certain item, and then you go to the statue and pray to it and you complete the task)
    -Water the garden (This is the most random mini-task in this mother fucker. You have to get a bucket, run to the middle of the arena, get water from a well, and then bring it back to water a patch... and you complete the task)
    
           Okay now the point of doing those mini tasks is, if you complete the first task, you get a random rare item, and +50 pk points. If you complete the second task, you get +50 pk points and 500k. If you complete the third task, you get a (random) peice of a godsword. If you complete the final task, you get 500k... Now you can re-do these tasks as many times as you want to, just remember, friendly fire is turned on!

[center][b][i]Looting[/i][/b][/center]

          This has got to be the biggest load of bullshit I&#39;ve seen in just about every single server. For some reason people have a problem with looting, however I don&#39;t give a shit about looters. When I kill someone and get their items and there&#39;s a looter running around, I think of that as bait. So there are NO anti-looting rules, so just fucking deal with it.

[center][b][i]Conclusion[/i][/b][/center]

           Well, I guess I&#39;m going to wrap this one up for now, but I would really like some feedback on these ideas and stuff, and even some things I could add to make a pking revolution. So yeah please reply to this post (or at least give me a bump ;Þ)




-Thanks for reading this heap of shit
[center]Mimz
(00ryn00)[/center]</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2008 21:53:13 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/revolution-list/230582.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>~~Revolution List~~</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@00rYn00 00rYn00]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/00ryn00">@00rYn00</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Thanks</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/revolution-list/230582/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/revolution-list/230582/3</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2008 21:53:13 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-230582-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/revolution-list/230582.rss">~~Revolution List~~</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>~~Revolution List~~</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Project_Evolution Project Evolution]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/project_evolution">@Project_Evolution</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Looks cool, I like your ideas.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/revolution-list/230582/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/revolution-list/230582/2</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2008 03:24:44 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-230582-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/revolution-list/230582.rss">~~Revolution List~~</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>~~Revolution List~~</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@00rYn00 00rYn00]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/00ryn00">@00rYn00</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[center]<span class="bbcode-b"><s>My revolution list</s></span><br>
(This is what I’m going to do to create a new revolution in Moparscape pking)<br>
[sup]<em>This a very detailed list, so I’m going to warn you ahead of time</em>[/sup] [/center]</p>
<p>[b]<span class="bbcode-u">Table of Contents</span></p>
<p>Intro<br>
-Banking<br>
-Clans/Gangs/Teams<br>
-Obstacles<br>
-Battle-Grounds<br>
-Pking Minigames<br>
-Looting<br>
Conclusion<br>
[/b]</p>
<p>[center]<span class="bbcode-b"><span class="bbcode-i">Intro</span></span>[/center]<br>
This is my revolution list, and basically what this is, is it’s just me telling you what I’m going to do to “revolutionize” Moparscape/Private server pking… Yeah I went there, I’m actually so bored that I’m going to describe every last detail of what I want to do to totally own the rest of the servers (in the pking content)</p>
<p>[center]<span class="bbcode-b"><span class="bbcode-i">Banking</span></span>[/center]<br>
For those of you that havent seen my other post about this, I’m going to limit wilderness banking to make pking more stratigic in a way that is almost cruel. So what I’m planning to do is this<br>
-Make an item into a banking mechanism. For of those that would like further elaboration, I’m going to make it to where you HAVE to have a certain item to bank in the wilderness (i.e. an amulet, chest, ring…) and this item will be non-tradeable, non-sellable, and will be somewhat hard to get, but totally worth it in the end (especially when you’re the only one able to bank in the wilderness)<br>
-The reason for this madness is because I really hate those people that pk in the wilderness and open up their bank and act llike pansies and get food out of their bank, and other items… So this way I made it a little more challenging but still fun</p>
<p>[center]<span class="bbcode-b"><span class="bbcode-i">Clans/Gangs/Teams</span></span>[/center]<br>
If you know me (which I doubt any of you do) you would know that I am a big fan of teaming and a big fan of clan/gang/team pking. I think everyone is in a way thought. But the reason I like this form of pking the most is because I like the feeling of having power (what little of it is given to me by being a clan) over the rest of the players, and it’s really fun to guide you’re clan/gang/team through the wilderness and own other people. But the most epic part of this is the Clan v.s. Clan, or Gang v.s. Gang, or Team v.s. Team pking. So I added Clan Wars to my server, and this will allow you to obtain 1mil, or some other item (including the banking item). Also I want to add Clan Chat and other stuff.</p>
<p>[center]<span class="bbcode-b"><span class="bbcode-i">Obstacles</span></span>[/center]</p>
<pre><code>      What I'm (mainly) trying to do, is make the wilderness more challenging and I want players to strategize more when they go pking. Now I know this is a long way away from people actually trying to strategize when pking on a simple private server, but still, it could happen... Anyway, I was thinking about adding some obstacles to the wilderness that way the archers and mages could actually have an advantage instead of fighting in that huge flat open area. Because in that huge open area, there isn't much protection for archers and mages now is there? It's basically just a huge brawl of a whole bunch of people that mass click a server until their fingers bleed. So thats why I want obstacles in my server, this way clans/gangs/teams can "stratigize" in positioning their players.
     Also, I'm going to add the Castle Wars blockades to my server so that way clans/gangs/teams can use more strategy and totally block out everyone...
</code></pre>
<p>[center]<span class="bbcode-b"><span class="bbcode-i">Battle-Grounds</span></span>[/center]<br>
I’m also very tired of pking in the same old place over and over again… So I’m going to add a battlegrounds arena (Castle Wars arena) this way people can fight in a huge open area, but some of you are probably thinking that my idea is kind of pointless right? Well actually I would have multiple things that you could do, and I would add in altars, and even a bank. So thing of Castle Wars, but with altars, banks, more death-like scenery, and a three headed fire breathing dragon to sum it all up…</p>
<p>[center]<span class="bbcode-b"><span class="bbcode-i">Pking Minigames</span></span>[/center]<br>
I’ve had this idea for a while, I even suggested it on RuneScape but it got crucified on the forums, so I’m going to add it on my own private server. Yes, a Pking Minigame, but not just one, a whole fuck-load of minigames… Think of them as mini-tasks, because that’s really what they are. These Minigames/tasks consist of helping out your teamates (in a certain arena) by doing things such as…<br>
-Capture the Flag (This is basically a neverending cycle of hell, because each team has to obtain the other team’s flag, but here’s the fun part… The game never resets, and neither do the tasks =Þ so people are going to be raping each other throughout the whole game, but don’t think of it as a game, think of it as pking, but with friends and jobs to do)<br>
-Replinish Death (This task I took from my game Clan Wars, To start off I need to tell you this, When you enter the Pking task arena you get a ring for your side, so what you have to do is simply kill another player from the other side and get their ring, once you have this, you run back to your side and find your statue and pray to it, and if you have the ring from the other side you complete the tast)<br>
-Kill the Immortal (This is basically the same as the task mentioned before, only you have to kill a certain monster to get a certain item, and then you go to the statue and pray to it and you complete the task)<br>
-Water the garden (This is the most random mini-task in this mother fucker. You have to get a bucket, run to the middle of the arena, get water from a well, and then bring it back to water a patch… and you complete the task)</p>
<pre><code>       Okay now the point of doing those mini tasks is, if you complete the first task, you get a random rare item, and +50 pk points. If you complete the second task, you get +50 pk points and 500k. If you complete the third task, you get a (random) peice of a godsword. If you complete the final task, you get 500k... Now you can re-do these tasks as many times as you want to, just remember, friendly fire is turned on!
</code></pre>
<p>[center]<span class="bbcode-b"><span class="bbcode-i">Looting</span></span>[/center]</p>
<pre><code>      This has got to be the biggest load of bullshit I've seen in just about every single server. For some reason people have a problem with looting, however I don't give a shit about looters. When I kill someone and get their items and there's a looter running around, I think of that as bait. So there are NO anti-looting rules, so just fucking deal with it.
</code></pre>
<p>[center]<span class="bbcode-b"><span class="bbcode-i">Conclusion</span></span>[/center]</p>
<pre><code>       Well, I guess I'm going to wrap this one up for now, but I would really like some feedback on these ideas and stuff, and even some things I could add to make a pking revolution. So yeah please reply to this post (or at least give me a bump ;Þ)
</code></pre>
<p>-Thanks for reading this heap of shit<br>
[center]Mimz<br>
(00ryn00)[/center]</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/revolution-list/230582/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/revolution-list/230582/1</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2008 01:41:42 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-230582-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/revolution-list/230582.rss">~~Revolution List~~</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
