<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>The RsPs based on teamwork and storytelling</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-rsps-based-on-teamwork-and-storytelling/548066</link>
    <description>Hello dear mopar community,

I am kinda back from a long time because I came up with some awesome ideas that will probably fuse together as one of the most unique (if not most) rsps out there. I will not post a lot of detail about my ideas for it. I can tell you that like me and strucker attempted once, it will be a private server focussed on team work with other players(although lone wolves have nothing to
Fear), on the story line ( the server will have the biggest arsenal of quests that all makes sense for the story.) now like I already said that everything people love about private servers will be in there but for people that find the servers mainstream and boring, this will be a great evolution. If/when I found a development team I will continue to post more details.

Now what do I need?
I need experienced java developers that understand the language that knows what their doing rather than just copying code and let it work in a server. I also need people with an ambition to create something new and unique for the rsps community. I want the developers to be able to explain what there doing and how they are doing it so we can all learn and benefit from them (noworries you don&#39;t need to release any code you&#39;ve written unless you desire to, but just be able to explain it in the big lines.) something that&#39;s I find very important is networking. I don&#39;t want players to experience a lot
of lag and if possible zero lag.

Myself?
I wont be developing since my skills are far from good enough for this project. So what will I do? I will carefully explain my ideas and write all of the quests and minigames. I will explain what stats I want items to be, droprates, exp rates etcc and I will focus on a stable economy that you rarely see in any private server. I also will design certain areas that are important for players. I will make a list of gfxes and animations that we&#39;ll probably are going to use.

In this server I want you to feel like you can make a difference and grow to be a legend without just having a big ass bank or a good bot to get all your skills maxed. I want to really challenge players and make them feel pleased with themself when they for example slay a king black dragon then just feel bored. Also I want almost any npc to have a backstory and I will personally write them. The server will have weekly/monthly updates that bring something new to the story and experience from the players. 

What revision/source?
Well to be honest I dont really care, I prefer 317 but all of this stuff can the developers decide.

If you are interested in this please peave a reply or pm me on forums. You can also skype me, my skypename is: stanownd
Before I let you join this project please note that I would like to see some work from you first unless I already know you and your skills ofcourse :d

Stan</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2014 12:15:14 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-rsps-based-on-teamwork-and-storytelling/548066.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>The RsPs based on teamwork and storytelling</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@luna-scape luna-scape]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/luna-scape">@luna-scape</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Hello dear mopar community,</p>
<p>I am kinda back from a long time because I came up with some awesome ideas that will probably fuse together as one of the most unique (if not most) rsps out there. I will not post a lot of detail about my ideas for it. I can tell you that like me and strucker attempted once, it will be a private server focussed on team work with other players(although lone wolves have nothing to<br>
Fear), on the story line ( the server will have the biggest arsenal of quests that all makes sense for the story.) now like I already said that everything people love about private servers will be in there but for people that find the servers mainstream and boring, this will be a great evolution. If/when I found a development team I will continue to post more details.</p>
<p>Now what do I need?<br>
I need experienced java developers that understand the language that knows what their doing rather than just copying code and let it work in a server. I also need people with an ambition to create something new and unique for the rsps community. I want the developers to be able to explain what there doing and how they are doing it so we can all learn and benefit from them (noworries you don’t need to release any code you’ve written unless you desire to, but just be able to explain it in the big lines.) something that’s I find very important is networking. I don’t want players to experience a lot<br>
of lag and if possible zero lag.</p>
<p>Myself?<br>
I wont be developing since my skills are far from good enough for this project. So what will I do? I will carefully explain my ideas and write all of the quests and minigames. I will explain what stats I want items to be, droprates, exp rates etcc and I will focus on a stable economy that you rarely see in any private server. I also will design certain areas that are important for players. I will make a list of gfxes and animations that we’ll probably are going to use.</p>
<p>In this server I want you to feel like you can make a difference and grow to be a legend without just having a big ass bank or a good bot to get all your skills maxed. I want to really challenge players and make them feel pleased with themself when they for example slay a king black dragon then just feel bored. Also I want almost any npc to have a backstory and I will personally write them. The server will have weekly/monthly updates that bring something new to the story and experience from the players.</p>
<p>What revision/source?<br>
Well to be honest I dont really care, I prefer 317 but all of this stuff can the developers decide.</p>
<p>If you are interested in this please peave a reply or pm me on forums. You can also skype me, my skypename is: stanownd<br>
Before I let you join this project please note that I would like to see some work from you first unless I already know you and your skills ofcourse :d</p>
<p>Stan</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-rsps-based-on-teamwork-and-storytelling/548066/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-rsps-based-on-teamwork-and-storytelling/548066/1</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2014 12:15:14 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-548066-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-rsps-based-on-teamwork-and-storytelling/548066.rss">The RsPs based on teamwork and storytelling</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
