<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Fairy Tale images</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/fairy-tale-images/533882</link>
    <description>Alright, so in class I have to write a fairy tale. Yeah, not fun. But luckily, my teacher is letting me do a knockoff of Little Red Riding Hood. My story is going to be a horror version of it, and it doesn&#39;t exactly follow the same plot line.

What I&#39;m looking for:
A cool cover. The title of the story is &quot;Little Red Bloody Hood&quot;. So something to do with that. Maybe like how [url=http://fc09.deviantart.net/fs70/f/2012/089/e/1/altair_ibn_la__ahad_by_thedeadbee-d4ug7te.jpg]Altaïr ibn La-Ahad[/url] from Assassin&#39;s Creed has his hood covering most of his face, but only a close up on the face. And maybe give her a evil grin?

Some images of the wolf.
Here&#39;s a snippet from my story (I&#39;m bad at writing xD) about how the wolf looks:
&lt;blockquote&gt;As she gazes at the wolfs&#39; eight foot tall shape, she can see his silver-black coat of fur, his piercing yellow eyes, his terrifyingly sharp claws on all four of his paws, and lets not forget his almost unrealistic mouth full of bleach white canine teeth that look like they could tear a human in half with a simple bite.&lt;/blockquote&gt;

Some images of little red as well.
Here&#39;s another snippet, but about her looks (before the &#39;transformation&#39;):

&lt;blockquote&gt;Her silky red hood and cape tattered with mud and torn from being drug into the cave, her soft blue eyes, and pale petrified face.&lt;/blockquote&gt;

I&#39;d also like one of after.
Basically, what she does is take her hood and cape off, and cover it in a layer of soot from charcoal. Making it a dark red almost black-like color. She also uses a piece of torn cloth as a mask, which is the same color as hood/cape. Think of it as like Hex Color: DA0000 covered by hex color: 222222

And maybe a cool &quot;The End&quot; image? Something that&#39;s written in a fairy tale like script, with the letters being black and perhaps having some blood dripping off of them?

Thank you to anyone who dares take a stab at this.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2013 04:45:01 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Graphics</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/fairy-tale-images/533882.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Fairy Tale images</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@TabbyKiller TabbyKiller]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/tabbykiller">@TabbyKiller</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I wasn’t telling you to base your story off the Grimm’s but to gather a few ideas on bad endings and maybe interpret or edit it into your story. I mean it seems easy enough to make one up but it seems even easier if you have the ideas already on paper for you.</p>
<p>Lets see, originality. Well your teachers wants a bad ending, lets give her a really bad ass ending. But first you’re going to need to layout the key points of what makes a good dark fairy tale which are; unexpected scenes, in-depth detail and an unexplained or unfinished ending. I’m thinking somewhat like the following:</p>
<blockquote>It was an ordinary weekend like usually, little red riding hood was on her skipping montage through the woods to deliver a fresh new batch of warm steaming chocolate chip cookies to her grandma. Up and down the hills, left and right through the thorn bushes her bright red hood sawed through the air and her cape following slightly behind. But as she skipped through and pass the saplings she couldn't shake the feeling that someone was watching her. Taking one quick double take around a tree to see if anything was behind her without arousing suspicion but nothing, she would not spot anything for the eye can see so off she trotted down the pathway and finally she arrived at her grandmas shack. (this is probably where you can start getting a bit dark) Standing just in front of the door with one hand about to knock on the door but she had that same feeling again, instead little red decided to press her ear against the door, but nothing. She'd double take to check behind her, and nothing, no chirps from birds, no rustle on the trees and no whistle in the air. Little red knew something was wrong, something had to be wrong. Swiftly but gently the door was open, at first to peaked in with one of her big blue eyes, then she put one foot in and shortly after another foot. Grandma, she yelled, grandma I'm here! Little red knew something was strange, she knew grandma would never leave her house without her walking stick. Little red decide to sit on grandmas bed and wait for grandma to get home. Little did she know but just under her were two red eyes glowing in the abyss in which grew under the bed by the minute and little red didn't suspect a single thing. The eyes more keen than ever awaited little red to rest and when at her weakest and most unsuspected moment. Things were about to turn dark for little red for all she didn't know was wolf right under her very bed. It was time, the big giant silver claws were the first to make their way out from under the bed, the paws bigger than little reds very own head. Next was the nose, big and black the creature sniffed the air silently. Time fell silent and the world felt cold and the wolf whispered silently, what big eyes you have. With hast little reds instinct was to make break for the exit but in which the wolf had pinned her to the wall. He sniffed the air again holding her tight, he whispered "oh what nice flesh you have." With just one claw on his paw he licked and then dragged it from shoulder to hip down little reds body. She screams but neither man or animal would here her pleas, all but one. A terrified lumberjack whom scurried off to tell his story that no-one would believe and was thrown into a mental asylum after authority had searched the woods in search for a cabin in which did not seem to exist. As for little red and her grandma, well, no-one really knew what happen to those two sweet, so sweet people. "That's a terrifying story grandma." said a small boy blankets tucked and pulled up to his cheek bones. "Well don't worry my little meaty pie, it was only just a story." Said the story teller hiding behind the moon light. "Oh wow, what big eyes you have grandma." said the boy. The black figure smiled with teeth than shined in the moonlight. "Oh what big teeth you have."</blockquote>
Half way through the story I only just clicked that it's probably going to be a story board but I decided to write the rest of it out anyway.
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/fairy-tale-images/533882/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/fairy-tale-images/533882/4</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2013 04:45:01 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-533882-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/fairy-tale-images/533882.rss">Fairy Tale images</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Fairy Tale images</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@sk8rdude461 sk8rdude461]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/sk8rdude461">@sk8rdude461</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“TabbyKiller, post:2, topic:533882”]I’ve only read the first few lines of your topic so forgive me if I’m completely wrong on what you’re looking for.</p>
<p>Fairy tales were originally horror or darker than what Disney present them as today. They were written by the Grimm Brothers, just Google Grimm Tales and you should find the real fairy tales. Just to give you an insight of how far Disney have changed them the Grimm tales contain murder, child abuse, sex, incest and rape. Might be a good thing to do a bit of research on to get some input into your own story.[/quote]<br>
My idiotic teacher (yes, I’m calling her an idiot) would not let me write this fairy tale the way I currently am without proof that fairy tales did not have a happy ending. I do know a good history behind it, but I’m writing a twist based off of Disney’s version, not Grimm’s.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/fairy-tale-images/533882/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/fairy-tale-images/533882/3</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2013 03:57:56 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-533882-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/fairy-tale-images/533882.rss">Fairy Tale images</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Fairy Tale images</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@TabbyKiller TabbyKiller]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/tabbykiller">@TabbyKiller</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I’ve only read the first few lines of your topic so forgive me if I’m completely wrong on what you’re looking for.</p>
<p>Fairy tales were originally horror or darker than what Disney present them as today. They were written by the Grimm Brothers, just Google Grimm Tales and you should find the real fairy tales. Just to give you an insight of how far Disney have changed them the Grimm tales contain murder, child abuse, sex, incest and rape. Might be a good thing to do a bit of research on to get some input into your own story.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/fairy-tale-images/533882/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/fairy-tale-images/533882/2</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2013 03:54:15 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-533882-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/fairy-tale-images/533882.rss">Fairy Tale images</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Fairy Tale images</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@sk8rdude461 sk8rdude461]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/sk8rdude461">@sk8rdude461</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Alright, so in class I have to write a fairy tale. Yeah, not fun. But luckily, my teacher is letting me do a knockoff of Little Red Riding Hood. My story is going to be a horror version of it, and it doesn’t exactly follow the same plot line.</p>
<p>What I’m looking for:<br>
A cool cover. The title of the story is “Little Red Bloody Hood”. So something to do with that. Maybe like how <a href="http://fc09.deviantart.net/fs70/f/2012/089/e/1/altair_ibn_la__ahad_by_thedeadbee-d4ug7te.jpg" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">Altaïr ibn La-Ahad</a> from Assassin’s Creed has his hood covering most of his face, but only a close up on the face. And maybe give her a evil grin?</p>
<p>Some images of the wolf.<br>
Here’s a snippet from my story (I’m bad at writing xD) about how the wolf looks:</p>
<blockquote>As she gazes at the wolfs' eight foot tall shape, she can see his silver-black coat of fur, his piercing yellow eyes, his terrifyingly sharp claws on all four of his paws, and lets not forget his almost unrealistic mouth full of bleach white canine teeth that look like they could tear a human in half with a simple bite.</blockquote>
<p>Some images of little red as well.<br>
Here’s another snippet, but about her looks (before the ‘transformation’):</p>
<blockquote>Her silky red hood and cape tattered with mud and torn from being drug into the cave, her soft blue eyes, and pale petrified face.</blockquote>
<p>I’d also like one of after.<br>
Basically, what she does is take her hood and cape off, and cover it in a layer of soot from charcoal. Making it a dark red almost black-like color. She also uses a piece of torn cloth as a mask, which is the same color as hood/cape. Think of it as like Hex Color: DA0000 covered by hex color: 222222</p>
<p>And maybe a cool “The End” image? Something that’s written in a fairy tale like script, with the letters being black and perhaps having some blood dripping off of them?</p>
<p>Thank you to anyone who dares take a stab at this.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/fairy-tale-images/533882/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/fairy-tale-images/533882/1</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2013 03:45:41 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-533882-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/fairy-tale-images/533882.rss">Fairy Tale images</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
