<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>The future?</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-future/381062</link>
    <description>i believe this is where we are heading im sure many others belive so as well. well it wont be being developed, and in movies if it wasnt. [url=http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=f8S8tbQMp2k]http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=f8S8tbQMp2k[/url] 

im sure there are ppl out there planning the samething to do with this as i am. ive been waiting for this as well: [url=http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=DJvN29076E0]http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=DJvN29076E0[/url] its a little behind oleds, but it consumes so little energy. but i believe this will only be a phase. physical displays will begone in the future, how long it will take to get rid of them idk, but just like money ppl will relise they dont need it b/c technology has made them obsolete.

i mean further in the future no one will ever have to work, and we can live the lives we want. say you would rather live in a video game well you could, and robots would take care of you body if you decided to be in some kind of comatose state so to speak.

robot will do everything for us. robot will even do research and develop new technologies, better improving themselves. will this end up like the matrix, or the terminator who knows. if we are smart it will not. 

its weird how i started on displays and when to other things? gosh my mind, does that all the time.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 05 Feb 2011 22:14:09 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>General Discussion</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-future/381062.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>The future?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Svitkona Svitkona]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/svitkona">@Svitkona</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Before we start, note that the Quran is in Arabic, and translations to English cannot convey the true meaning that is conveyed through the Arabic language. I will therefore be calling a lot on “misinterpretations”, even if they weren’t meant by the writer of that article.</p>
<p>In response to the human creation part:</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">1) Those who pursue the argument leave no room for alternative interpretations</span></p>
<p>That is not true - Islam encourages free thinking and will, and God has given us the ability to do whatever we please with the tools he gave us. The translation he provided is in fact, inaccurate, because it says “Two Seas” and not “Two Bodies Of Water”. Now that still doesn’t prove it; science says it IS two bodies of water, one a sea, and one a river. But consider this: If you get sea water and evaporate it, what are you left with? Water vapor and salt. Then what happens when the vapor cools? It will turn to fresh water. So, the saying “Two Seas” does metaphorically make sense. The Quran deals in metaphors a lot, as well; it is, after all a book, and at that time the world was famous for it’s literature and it’s writing ability. This is considered another miracle by Muslims, bat that’s beside the point.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">2) The argument as it stands makes Allah out to be weak</span><br>
That is in fact, merely an opinion. In the article, he says Allah is procuring vague details about events that require torturous examination to “unveil”, so to speak. Well…</p>
<p>“So whoever Allah wants to guide - He expands his breast to [contain] Islam; and whoever He wants to misguide - He makes his breast tight and constricted as though he were climbing into the sky. Thus does Allah place defilement upon those who do not believe.”</p>
<p>When you go up in height, it gets harder for you to breath.</p>
<p>“And the sun runs his course for a period determined for him: that is the decree of (Him), the Exalted in Might, the All-Knowing.”</p>
<p>The sun is a star, and all stars eventually run out.</p>
<p>"It is He Who stretched out the earth and placed firmly embedded mountains and rivers in it and made two types of every kind of fruit. He covers over day with night. There are Signs in that for people who reflect.  "</p>
<p>The Earth is considered to have been one mass which then split into the continents we know. Mountains are suggested to have emerged from that “stretching”.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">3) The argument is a modern polemic3) The argument is a modern polemic</span></p>
<p>That is actually considered the wisdom of Allah. He saw people would start walking away from the Quran, because the human mind is ever-developing, and always questioning, finding answers, and finding other questions. So at that time, people needed to see Literary evolution and evolution in other elements of society, such as slavery, woman rights and the rich/poor argument. Now, a lot of these elements have been addressed; woman have rights now, slavery is abolished, and people who work get rich. The Quran stops because all life will eventually end, therefore there will be no need of further scientific discovery.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">4) At the end of the day, the “modern science proves the Qur’an” polemic does not find science in  the Qur’an, rather it uses science to judge the Qur’an</span></p>
<p>He then quotes:<br>
“Until, when he reached the setting of the sun, he found it set in a spring of murky water: Near it he found a People: We said: “O Zul-qarnain! (thou hast authority,) either to punish them, or to treat them with kindness.””</p>
<p>well…</p>
<blockquote>Salam alaikum
<pre><code>    The identification of Zul-Qarnain has been a controversial matter from the earliest times. in general the commentators have been of the opinion that he was Alexander the Great but the characteristics of Zul-Qarnain described in the Qur'an are not applicable to him. However, now the commentators are inclined to believe that Zul-Qarnain was Cyrus, an ancient king of Iran. We are also of the opinion that probably Zul-Qarnain was Cyrus, but the historical facts, which have come to light up to this time, are not sufficient to make any categorical assertion.

    Now let us consider the characteristics of Zul-Qarnain in the light of his story as given in the Quran:
    (1) The title Zul-Qarnain ("The Two-Horned") should have been quite familiar to the Jews, for it was at their instigation that the disbelievers of Makkah put this question to the Holy Prophet. Therefore we must turn to the Jewish literature in order to learn who was the person known as "The Two-Horned" or which was the kingdom known as "The Two-Horned."
    (2) Zul-Qarnain must have been a great ruler and a great conqueror whose conquests might have spread from the East to the West and on the third side to the North or to the South. Before the revelation of the Qur'an there had been several persons, who were such great conquerors. So we must confine our research for the other characteristics of Zul-Qarnain to one of these persons.
    (3) This title should be applicable to such a ruler who might have constructed a strong wall across a mountain pass to protect his kingdom from the incursions of Gog and Magog. In order to investigate this thing, we will have to determine as to who were Gog and Magog. We will also have to find out when such a wall was built and by whom and to which territory it was adjacent.
    (4) Besides possessing the above-mentioned characteristics, he should also be a God-worshiper and a just ruler, for the Qur'an has brought into prominence these characteristics more than anything else.
    The first of these characteristics is easily applicable to Cyrus, for according to the Bible Prophet Daniel saw in his vision that the united kingdom of Media and Persia was like a two-horned ram before the rise of the Greeks. (Dan. 8: 3,"20). The Jews had a very high opinion of "The Two-horned" one, because it was his invasion which brought about the downfall of the kingdom of Babylon and the liberation of the Israelites (Please also refer to E.N. 8 of Chapter XVII).
    The second characteristic is applicable to him to a great extent but not completely. Though his conquests spread to Syria and Asia Minor in the West and to Bakhtar (Balkh) in the East, there is no trace of any of his great expeditions to the North or to the South, whereas the Qur'an makes an explicit mention of his third expedition. Nevertheless, this third expedition is not wholly out of question for history tells us that his kingdom extended to Caucasia in the North. As regards Gog and Magog, it has been nearly established that they were the wild tribes of Central Asia who were known by different names: Tartars, Mongols, Huns and Scythians, who 'had been making inroads on settled kingdoms and empires from very ancient times. It is also known that strong bulwarks had been built in southern regions of Caucasia, though it has not been as yet historically established that these were built by Cyrus.
    As regards the last characteristic, Cyrus is the only known conqueror among the ancient rulers, to whom this may be applicable, for even his enemies have been full of praise for him for his justice, and, Ezra, a book of the Bible, asserts that he was a God-worshiper and a God-fearing king who set free the Israelites because of his God-worship, and ordered that the Temple of Solomon should be rebuilt for the worship of Allah, Who has no partner.
    In the light of the above, we admit that of all the conquerors, who had passed away before the revelation of the Qur'an, Cyrus alone is the one to whom the characteristics of "Zul-Qarnain" are most applicable, but we need more evidence to determine specifically that Cyrus is definitely "Zul-Qarnain." Anyhow, there is no other conqueror to whom the characteristics stated in the Qur'an are as much applicable as to Cyrus.
    Historically it is enough to say that Cyrus was a Persian ruler, whose rise began about 549 B.C. In a few years, he conquered the kingdom of Media and Lydia and afterwards conquered Babylon in 539 B.C. After this no powerful kingdom was left to oppose him. His conquests extended to Sind and the territory known as Turkistan on one side, and to Egypt and Libya and to Thrace and Macedonia and to Caucasia and Khawarzam in the North. In fact, the whole civilized world was under his sway.
    "The limit where the sun set" does not mean the "place" of the setting of the sun. According to Ibn Kathir, it means that he marched to the West conquering one country after the other till he reached the last boundary of the land, beyond which there was ocean.
    "He found the sun setting in black muddy waters of the sea": if Zul Qarnain was Cyrus, then that place would be the western limit of Asia Minor and the "black waters" would be the Aegean Sea. This interpretation is supported by the use of the word "`ain"instead of "bahr" in the Qur'an.
    "We said to him" does not necessarily mean that Allah directly revealed to him these words, and that Zul-Qarnain was a Prophet or was the one who received inspiration from Allah, and the same is the reasonable conjecture. This concerns the time when Zul-Qarnain had taken possession of the land as a conqueror and the conquered people were utterly at your mercy. Then Allah posed a question before his conscience, as if to say, "Now is the time of your trial. These people are utterly at your mercy, and you have the option either to behave unjustly towards them or to treat them generously."
    That is, “When he advanced towards the East, conquering one country after the other, he reached a territory where the limits of the civilized world had come to an end and beyond which was the territory of barbaric people, who had no shelter at all of tents or buildings.”
    The "two mountains" must have been parts of that mountain range which runs between the Caspian Sea and the Black Sea (as stated in v. 96). This must be so because beyond them was the territory of Gog and Magog
</code></pre>
<p>.</p>
<p>Quoted from “Tafhim al-Quran” by al-Mawdudi</p>
</blockquote><br>
I found this on another board with someone asking about the verse in question.
<p><span class="bbcode-b">5) Selective interpretation can be used to prove anything</span></p>
<p>Well there were no examples, so I am unable to retort.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">6) Applying the argument means that the Qur’an is no longer authoritative </span></p>
<p>God orders us to seek knowledge and attempt to empower ourselves by learning about the mysteries of the world. In fact, knowledge is so high to Allah, he considered it to be as good as worshiping him. Therefore, the bare essentials are provided by God, and the rest is up to us to discover, whether or not we actually wish to discover. And think about it, if we were already given all knowledge, what would be there for us to live for? Without the unknown, the drive to learn, there would be no reason for us to live; we would be as good as mindless sheep.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Conclusion</span><br>
The writer of this article is depending on inaccurate sources which have mistranslated the Quran, therefore he has made some points based on false statements. I do not hold this against him, however; it is really sad how Islam is nowadays… a split nation unable to solidify it’s inner core, and all with different beliefs that stem from but do not purely represent the original Islam. Islam was never intended to be a terrorist cell or a 9/11 incident, Islam was meant to be fair and just, and to bring a new level of civilization into this world. Muslims nowadays are so ignorant of their religion; they think it’s all about saying “I believe in God!” when Islam is way more than that. just stating your believe in God and Muhammad is one of the 5 “tenets” if you will, that are the basis of Islam, and that’s just half of the Religion. There is also the social half, where God orders us not to sped our lives only worshiping him, but performing our duties as social individuals in a growing community as well. And the worst thing is, this ignorance is causing other people to disbelieve Islam, because If I don’t even know my own Religion, then how should I be expected to guide another live in the ways of Islam? Therefore, Islam is now split into 3 different categories:</p>
<ol>
<li>The “nun” category; also known as terrorist, mad guy, blow up, BOOM!:</li>
</ol>
<p>This is the category that is infesting Islam nowadays. They  claim being in the the high places with God, being knowledgeable in his ways when they do not truly uphold Islam’s teachings. They are usually the ones with huge beards that reach the floor 4 times over and white "galabeyya"s (the white thing we wear to Haj) and are usually the ones 24/7 at the Mosque. This image is now so incessant, I am really growing weary of it. I’m not saying all of them are like that, some of these people are really religious and do follow the true Islamic ways, but most of them are unable to participate in a discussion, let alone a debate like this. Hence, Islam is viewed by many as an uncivilized religion, and is therefore not accepted by society as a religion that they actually consider.</p>
<ol start="2">
<li>The “I’m American!” category:</li>
</ol>
<p>Muslims trying to be “badass”. They’re ignorant as well, but they don’t even pretend to follow God; they are only Muslim in name. They’re the ones going around in gangs, trying to look cool, trying to hang on to a “girlfriend”, etc. Not gonna say a lot about those because I don’t approve whatsoever.</p>
<ol start="3">
<li>The true Muslim:</li>
</ol>
<p>The ones that Follow the teachings of God as well as continue to be successful in life and always strive to be better. They do make mistakes as well, but they always try to fix them. They are able to participate in such debates, and are able to do so impressively. They do whatever they want with their lives because they know God gave them free will, but they are still careful not to break God’s will.</p>
<p>I know this seems kind of biased, but this is how I view the Islamic society around me. We need to unite, and so become the strong nation we used to be once more.</p>
<p>Anyways…<br>
I’m going to read the other article now and post my comments later.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-future/381062/33">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-future/381062/33</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 05 Feb 2011 22:14:09 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-381062-33</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-future/381062.rss">The future?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The future?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Greeny Greeny]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/greeny">@Greeny</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“ytuio9, post:31, topic:381062”][quote author=Greeny link=topic=476877.msg3490635#msg3490635 date=1296926814]<br>
You’re total fucking idiots.</p>
<p>Time travel to the past is impossible under the laws of physics, travel to the future is possible by travelling as close as possible to the speed of light.</p>
<p>I didn’t stereotype Americans, I merely said you’re the only western country that still has a lot of creationists. At no point did I say ALL.  Evolution is fact, the only reason it’s called the theory of evolution is because they have to prove it for every living species before it can be called “fact” and that is impossible. So it remains a theory despite the endless amount of proof.</p>
<p>I’m one of those atheists whose read the bible to disprove it. I’ve found most Christians haven’t even read it, if either of you are those type of Christians you better shut the fuck up right now before you completely embarrass yourselves.</p>
<p>[quote]you are aware that there are multiple head scientist that believe that there must be a greater being that created all of existence?[/quote] Irrelevant, there could be a God (by that I mean a creator) but it certainly isn’t the Christian God, nor Islamic, Jewish or any other from human history. If a god existed he wouldn’t be so vain as to require us to worship him, and if he’s so intelligent he wouldn’t be insulted by non-believers.</p>
<p>ytuio9, religion contains fuck-all science. Unless you can provide some literature that proves otherwise?</p>
<p>Oh and I didn’t say Science proves the bible wrong, it simply replaces religion by answering questions early civilisations couldn’t understand or grasp.<br>
[/quote]<br>
read the quran pl0x.[/quote]</p>
<p>Oh so we’re skipping the bible and hitting up the Quran for some scientific information?</p>
<p>Unfortunately you’ve been misinformed, the science contained in the Quran is largely inaccurate, or stolen.</p>
<p><a href="http://www.answering-islam.org/Andy/fallacies.html" class="onebox" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">http://www.answering-islam.org/Andy/fallacies.html</a></p>
<p><a href="http://www.answering-islam.org/Quran/Science/embryo.html" rel="nofollow noopener">http://www.answering-islam.org/Quran/Science/embryo.html</a> (better referenced)</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-future/381062/32">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-future/381062/32</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 05 Feb 2011 17:39:12 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-381062-32</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-future/381062.rss">The future?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The future?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Svitkona Svitkona]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/svitkona">@Svitkona</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“Greeny, post:29, topic:381062”]You’re total fucking idiots.</p>
<p>Time travel to the past is impossible under the laws of physics, travel to the future is possible by travelling as close as possible to the speed of light.</p>
<p>I didn’t stereotype Americans, I merely said you’re the only western country that still has a lot of creationists. At no point did I say ALL.  Evolution is fact, the only reason it’s called the theory of evolution is because they have to prove it for every living species before it can be called “fact” and that is impossible. So it remains a theory despite the endless amount of proof.</p>
<p>I’m one of those atheists whose read the bible to disprove it. I’ve found most Christians haven’t even read it, if either of you are those type of Christians you better shut the fuck up right now before you completely embarrass yourselves.</p>
<p>[quote]you are aware that there are multiple head scientist that believe that there must be a greater being that created all of existence?[/quote] Irrelevant, there could be a God (by that I mean a creator) but it certainly isn’t the Christian God, nor Islamic, Jewish or any other from human history. If a god existed he wouldn’t be so vain as to require us to worship him, and if he’s so intelligent he wouldn’t be insulted by non-believers.</p>
<p>ytuio9, religion contains fuck-all science. Unless you can provide some literature that proves otherwise?</p>
<p>Oh and I didn’t say Science proves the bible wrong, it simply replaces religion by answering questions early civilisations couldn’t understand or grasp.[/quote]<br>
read the quran pl0x.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-future/381062/31">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-future/381062/31</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 05 Feb 2011 17:31:57 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-381062-31</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-future/381062.rss">The future?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The future?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@n10si_t n10si t]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/n10si_t">@n10si_t</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Greeny:</p>
<p>You all are*</p>
<p>And I now feel a deep passionate love and respect for you.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-future/381062/30">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-future/381062/30</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 05 Feb 2011 17:29:34 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-381062-30</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-future/381062.rss">The future?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The future?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Greeny Greeny]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/greeny">@Greeny</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>You’re total fucking idiots.</p>
<p>Time travel to the past is impossible under the laws of physics, travel to the future is possible by travelling as close as possible to the speed of light.</p>
<p>I didn’t stereotype Americans, I merely said you’re the only western country that still has a lot of creationists. At no point did I say ALL.  Evolution is fact, the only reason it’s called the theory of evolution is because they have to prove it for every living species before it can be called “fact” and that is impossible. So it remains theory because they cannot prove the specifics, but they know evolution happened, whether by Darwin’s theory of natural selection or some others yet to be considered. (<a href="http://www.talkorigins.org/faqs/evolution-fact.html" rel="nofollow noopener">http://www.talkorigins.org/faqs/evolution-fact.html</a> - <a href="http://www.talkorigins.org/faqs/faq-misconceptions.html" rel="nofollow noopener">http://www.talkorigins.org/faqs/faq-misconceptions.html</a> - <a href="http://www.notjustatheory.com/" rel="nofollow noopener">http://www.notjustatheory.com/</a>)</p>
<p>I’m one of those atheists whose read the bible to disprove it. I’ve found most Christians haven’t even read it, if either of you are those type of Christians you better shut the fuck up right now before you completely embarrass yourselves.</p>
<blockquote>you are aware that there are multiple head scientist that believe that there must be a greater being that created all of existence?</blockquote> Irrelevant, there could be a God (by that I mean a creator) but it certainly isn't the Christian God, nor Islamic, Jewish or any other from human history. If a god existed he wouldn't be so vain as to require us to worship him, and if he's so intelligent he wouldn't be insulted by non-believers.
<p>ytuio9, religion contains fuck-all science. Unless you can provide some literature that proves otherwise?</p>
<p>Oh and I didn’t say science proves the bible wrong, it simply replaces religion by answering questions early civilisations couldn’t understand or grasp. Science doesn’t need to prove the bible wrong because the bible is so full of contradictions that it is wrong, all on it’s own.</p>
<p>EDIT: I just noticed Mr Bob went over to MITB to try and preach bible verses and got shot down with bible references to murder, rape and genocide. Clearly never read the actual bible, only some drivel put together by the modern church. How long will it take for humanity to realise you can take the teachings of morality from religion but should ignore the religion itself.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-future/381062/29">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-future/381062/29</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 05 Feb 2011 17:26:54 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-381062-29</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-future/381062.rss">The future?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The future?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Svitkona Svitkona]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/svitkona">@Svitkona</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Besides using science to disprove religion isn’t going to work because religion contains a lot of science. Evolution, now that’s an endless debate… What I believe is, God created us in some other form other than what we look like now, and we progressed to look like we are now.<br>
Makes sense?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-future/381062/28">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-future/381062/28</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 05 Feb 2011 08:53:03 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-381062-28</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-future/381062.rss">The future?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The future?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@xryz xryz]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/xryz">@xryz</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p><span class="mention">@mr</span>. bob this is off topic, but i was wondering b/c i found on wikipedia that since my mom was born in canada, and was adopted in to the us. that i can become a, or am a dual-citizen? we plan on taking a trip to canada, but right now my mom is having trouble proving her american citizenship. so right now technically she has been an illegal alien for the past 30 years? even though shes voted every year since she could, and is married to my father. its freaken messed up. we found all this out when she applied for a passport. but i am looking foward to meeting my family up there, ive only seen them by pics and video chat. my gma came down when i was young though. i thought agnostic meant you believe that a greater being is possible but you just chose not to believe in one. honestly, idky anyone would go with atheist when agnostic doesnt really make a difference.</p>
<p><a class="mention" href="/u/greeny">@greeny</a> i may read you arguments over there. b/c i need to find such arguments to make explainations why they are wrong. yes i dont believe in evolution. its totally unbelievable that we evolved from apes or w/e we supposedly eveolved from. sorry but until we have time travel and you take me back in time to witness this evolution, i will not believe. also i dont believe in traveling back in time, i think it would be interesting to hear ppls theories on traveling to the past(the only way i could see this possible, is that if every moment[the smallest divisible parcel of time] splits into multiple universes, and we find a way to travel between them.), but the traveling into the future totally makes sense. i dont think science will prove the existence of God, at least not anytime soon at all. how can you prove the existence of some being that isnt even in the same realm(one where time doesnt exist) as us? you are aware that there are multiple head scientist that believe that there must be a greater being that created all of existence?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-future/381062/27">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-future/381062/27</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 05 Feb 2011 06:25:55 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-381062-27</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-future/381062.rss">The future?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The future?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Mr_Bob3 Mr. Bob]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/mr_bob3">@Mr_Bob3</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote no-group quote-modified" data-post="22" data-topic="381062">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/greeny/40/5_1887921562df0dabfae55079ddabeb03.png" class="avatar"> Greeny:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>[quote]I dont see how DNA modifications are futher ahead in development than Nanotech</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>They’re not, I’m saying they will be. Nanobots as useful as the concept may sound would have to be extremely advanced to reside within the human body without some kind of negative reaction, synthetic DNA and DNA engineering is faster and more direct route to the same solution. (Halo Reach incidentally has Spartans which are genetically modified super soldiers. If you read the back story on Halo it is actually very interesting, the books are a sound read).</p>
<p>I’m not sure where the comments about God and the Bible came from, but I’m amidst a religious debate over on MITB: <a href="http://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php/topic,476707.0.html" rel="nofollow noopener">http://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php/topic,476707.0.html</a></p>
<p>I’m an atheist and believe I can disprove the bible through it’s endless contradictions and lack of evidence to support it. Your definition of theory is correct but if you don’t believe in evolution then you’re either stupid or American (since that’s the only western country left that still has creationists, even the Christians in the UK believe evolution) I’m not debating this here though since I’d have to repeat things between the two topics.[/quote]<span class="bbcode-i">Remember again NOT to read this like I’m angry!</span></p>
<p>The Bible states the future, what to expect at the coming of Christ, and what to expect before the coming.</p>
<p>So I was providing a backup for those (like you) who would simply post science proves the Bible wrong.</p>
<p>And it’s agnostic to say somebody is stupid for not believing in something as well as very ignorant to qualify all American citizens to be creationists.</p>
<p>I’m Canadian on a trip to the USA.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-future/381062/26">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-future/381062/26</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 04 Feb 2011 21:54:01 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-381062-26</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-future/381062.rss">The future?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The future?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@krackkid Krackkid]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/krackkid">@krackkid</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>FUTURE ISN’T REAL ITS THE PRESENT!!!</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-future/381062/25">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-future/381062/25</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 04 Feb 2011 18:35:35 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-381062-25</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-future/381062.rss">The future?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The future?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Greeny Greeny]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/greeny">@Greeny</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“TOMSCAPE BETA, post:23, topic:381062”][quote author=IlikeArrays link=topic=476877.msg3489394#msg3489394 date=1296837735]<br>
What if these nanobots get infected by a virus and they fight against your body.<br>
[/quote]</p>
<p>This thread reminds me of the Startgate Atlantis replicators for some reason…</p>
<p>Oh well.</p>
<p>But to be honest, I think some ideas on this thread are derived from modern shows/games. Though thats my take on it.[/quote]</p>
<p>I already made that point, but glad to see someone agrees.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-future/381062/24">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-future/381062/24</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 04 Feb 2011 18:34:02 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-381062-24</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-future/381062.rss">The future?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The future?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Tom Tom]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/tom">@Tom</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote no-group" data-post="20" data-topic="381062">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/ilikearrays/40/5_1887921562df0dabfae55079ddabeb03.png" class="avatar"> IlikeArrays:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>What if these nanobots get infected by a virus and they fight against your body.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>This thread reminds me of the Startgate Atlantis replicators for some reason…</p>
<p>Oh well.</p>
<p>But to be honest, I think some ideas on this thread are derived from modern shows/games. Though thats my take on it.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-future/381062/23">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-future/381062/23</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 04 Feb 2011 18:30:24 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-381062-23</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-future/381062.rss">The future?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The future?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Greeny Greeny]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/greeny">@Greeny</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <blockquote>I dont see how DNA modifications are futher ahead in development than Nanotech</blockquote>
They're not, I'm saying they will be. Nanobots as useful as the concept may sound would have to be extremely advanced to reside within the human body without some kind of negative reaction, synthetic DNA and DNA engineering is faster and more direct route to the same solution. (Halo Reach incidentally has Spartans which are genetically modified super soldiers. If you read the back story on Halo it is actually very interesting, the books are a sound read). 
<p>I’m not sure where the comments about God and the Bible came from, but I’m amidst a religious debate over on MITB: <a href="http://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php/topic,476707.0.html" rel="nofollow noopener">http://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php/topic,476707.0.html</a></p>
<p>I’m an atheist and believe I can disprove the bible through it’s endless contradictions and lack of evidence to support it. Your definition of theory is correct but if you don’t believe in evolution then you’re either stupid or American (since that’s the only western country left that still has creationists, even the Christians in the UK believe evolution) I’m not debating this here though since I’d have to repeat things between the two topics.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-future/381062/22">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-future/381062/22</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 04 Feb 2011 18:29:56 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-381062-22</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-future/381062.rss">The future?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The future?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@xryz xryz]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/xryz">@xryz</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“Greeny, post:17, topic:381062”]Synthetic DNA, and genetic modifications will give us eternal life long before nano bots, you’re just regurgitating bullshit out of a few modern games.</p>
<p>I stand by the point the human race will destroy itself long before any of this though. Although we’ll extend human life to hundreds of years in the next century (been in the news many times). Not difficult. Immortality is where the difficulty is at.[/quote]<br>
I dont see how DNA modifications are futher ahead in development than Nanotech, tbh i say they both have a ton of work b4 they are viable solutions. but yes that jellyfish(<a href="http://current.com/green/89758958_immortal-jellyfish-discovered.htm" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">http://current.com/green/89758958_immortal-jellyfish-discovered.htm</a>) that has cell rejuvenation is something that is very useful. yes theres no doubt humans well make their own downfall, you can see it all throughout history. theres only one way that humans won’t make their own doom, which is if we learned how to work together, and not fight. just to let you know the newest game ive played is halo reach.</p>
<p>@ mr.bob yes i am a believer. i havent fully read the bible. ive ben a believer since i was young. right now im lost though. idk how i did except that i didnt guard myself from satans traps. that is all seriousness im not joking. i will always believe jesus died on the cross and rose again to forgive my sins. to let you know how lost ive got, ive told myself if i had to make a choice between this girl and God i would chose this one girl. i really need to start reading my bible again but i cant be commited. thats why i dont think i should say im a christian.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-post="20" data-topic="381062">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/ilikearrays/40/5_1887921562df0dabfae55079ddabeb03.png" class="avatar"> IlikeArrays:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>What if these nanobots get infected by a virus and they fight against your body.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>like a computer virus? well if someone made a virus they would be better off making them replicate themselves until the entire earth is a giant blob of nanobots. if the bots had ROM then it may be a little difficult to infect them, right? im sure they would be extremely secure b4 they were inside humans.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-future/381062/21">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-future/381062/21</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 04 Feb 2011 16:54:01 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-381062-21</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-future/381062.rss">The future?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The future?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@IlikeArrays IlikeArrays]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/ilikearrays">@IlikeArrays</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>What if these nanobots get infected by a virus and they fight against your body.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-future/381062/20">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-future/381062/20</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 04 Feb 2011 16:42:15 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-381062-20</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-future/381062.rss">The future?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The future?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Mr_Bob3 Mr. Bob]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/mr_bob3">@Mr_Bob3</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p><span class="bbcode-i">Before you read!</span> Don’t read this like I’m angry. Read it as I’m speaking mellow to you otherwise you might become angered if you aren’t a believer - and with anger comes obnoxiousness.</p>
<hr>
<p>Try reading the <span class="bbcode-b">Bible</span> if you’re a Christian. If you aren’t, you might want to check it out, as from my experience I’ve only benefited from it, realizing that my sins destroy others and myself inclusively.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-i">Science proves it wrong.</span><br>
No and never will science “prove” the <span class="bbcode-b">Bible</span> false. Sure, there are some theories that contradict with it, but then again, here’s the definition of a theory.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-u"><span class="bbcode-b">Theory -</span></span> a well-substantiated explanation of some aspect of the natural world; an organized system of accepted knowledge that applies in a variety of circumstances to explain a specific set of phenomena.</p>
<p>If you don’t understand the definition:<br>
Theories are explanations of things that cannot be proven by human beings. No theory is proven, but an idea that attempts to solve something that happened.</p>
<p>Some examples of theories:</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">The Big Bang</span><br>
Some scientists believe in a theory called <span class="bbcode-i">The Big Bang</span> which is the cosmic explosion that is hypothesized to have marked the origin of the universe.</p>
<p>Proven? No. That would be impossible.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">What the Bible states:</span> God (the almighty ruler) created the universe in his own image.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Evolution</span><br>
Some scientists also believe in a theory called <span class="bbcode-i">evolution</span>. Human evolution, or anthropogenesis, is the origin and evolution of Homo sapiens as a distinct species from other hominids, great apes and placental mammals.</p>
<p>Sure, they have found <span class="bbcode-b">some</span> artifacts of bones, which can be similar to human bones.</p>
<p>Proven? No. That would be impossible.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">What the Bible states:</span> God created humans, we did not evolve from other creatures.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Lists go on for contradictions towards the Bible, however they are all theories (other than the miracles that were performed, and the explanation of those are the people who performed these miracles were given the power to by God)</span></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-future/381062/19">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-future/381062/19</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 04 Feb 2011 16:37:59 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-381062-19</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-future/381062.rss">The future?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The future?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Svitkona Svitkona]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/svitkona">@Svitkona</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>nanobots…? are you serious?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-future/381062/18">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-future/381062/18</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 04 Feb 2011 16:22:53 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-381062-18</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-future/381062.rss">The future?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The future?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Greeny Greeny]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/greeny">@Greeny</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Synthetic DNA, and genetic modifications will give us eternal life long before nano bots, you’re just regurgitating bullshit out of a few modern games.</p>
<p>I stand by the point the human race will destroy itself long before any of this though. Although we’ll extend human life to hundreds of years in the next century (been in the news many times). Not difficult. Immortality is where the difficulty is at.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-future/381062/17">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-future/381062/17</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 04 Feb 2011 15:59:06 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-381062-17</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-future/381062.rss">The future?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The future?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@xryz xryz]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/xryz">@xryz</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote no-group" data-post="15" data-topic="381062">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 ytuio9:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>lolwut about nanotechnology</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>its the secret to eternal youth, instant heal of wounds, and everlasting life( its not far-fetched to believe in the near future that nanobots will exist in our bloodstream just like our red and white blood cells). along with integrating electronics with organics, aka humans. there are plenty more useful things, like batteries made from carbon-nanotubes. more efficient solar panels, and solar panels can applied almost everywhere. just to let you know there are older technologies that are going to make a comeback (tesla’s ideas [wireless electricity], clockwork, the sterling engine). some of those technologies were ahead of there time.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-future/381062/16">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-future/381062/16</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 04 Feb 2011 15:35:18 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-381062-16</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-future/381062.rss">The future?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The future?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Svitkona Svitkona]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/svitkona">@Svitkona</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>lolwut about nanotechnology</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-future/381062/15">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-future/381062/15</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 04 Feb 2011 15:24:02 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-381062-15</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-future/381062.rss">The future?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The future?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@xryz xryz]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/xryz">@xryz</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote no-group" data-post="13" data-topic="381062">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 ytuio9:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Like Hao you do dat</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>thats what i plan on. and also yes others have predicted the future b4, most of them predict a time, i didnt. saying something will happen eventually and saying it will happen at a certain time is a little bit different. plus we have flying cars just not like they whated them too. 200 years ago they would of never imagined the stuff we have. the foundation of modern technology seems to have started then, but im sure they wouldnt know what cellphones, computers, satellites are. plus look how much technology has advanced in the past 2 decades. technology is growing at an alarming rate theres no reason not to believe this will happen. the question is when? all i can predict is it will happen at least by the time were about to die. the technologies neede for these ideas are currently being developed; nanotechnoogy is one tech that is going to be needed, its just a matter of when will it be a stable solution for things? b/c im not for a earth of nanobots(where the nano bots start turning everything into a nanobot).</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-future/381062/14">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-future/381062/14</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 04 Feb 2011 13:30:10 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-381062-14</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-future/381062.rss">The future?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The future?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Svitkona Svitkona]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/svitkona">@Svitkona</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“xryz, post:1, topic:381062”]i mean further in the future no one will ever have to work, and we can live the lives we want. say you would rather live in a video game well you could, and robots would take care of you body if you decided to be in some kind of comatose state so to speak.</p>
<p>robot will do everything for us. robot will even do research and develop new technologies, better improving themselves. will this end up like the matrix, or the terminator who knows. if we are smart it will not.[/quote]<br>
Like Hao you do dat</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-future/381062/13">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-future/381062/13</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 04 Feb 2011 11:39:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-381062-13</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-future/381062.rss">The future?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The future?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Cole1497 Cole1497]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/cole1497">@Cole1497</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote no-group quote-modified" data-post="11" data-topic="381062">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/user_avatar/forum.moparisthebest.com/davidi2/40/2579_1.png" class="avatar"> Davidi2:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>People have tried to predict the future before, it’s never happened. I believe people said we would have flying cars by the year 2000?</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>BTTF.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-future/381062/12">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-future/381062/12</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 04 Feb 2011 10:36:02 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-381062-12</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-future/381062.rss">The future?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The future?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@davidi2 Davidi2]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/davidi2">@davidi2</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>People have tried to predict the future before, it’s never happened. I believe people said we would have flying cars by the year 2000?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-future/381062/11">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-future/381062/11</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 04 Feb 2011 10:05:17 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-381062-11</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-future/381062.rss">The future?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The future?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Sun_Chips Sun Chips]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/sun_chips">@Sun_Chips</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>wall-E is our future</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-future/381062/10">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-future/381062/10</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 04 Feb 2011 08:44:43 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-381062-10</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-future/381062.rss">The future?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The future?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Cole1497 Cole1497]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/cole1497">@Cole1497</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>inb4flyingcars</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-future/381062/9">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-future/381062/9</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 04 Feb 2011 00:53:36 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-381062-9</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-future/381062.rss">The future?</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
