<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Something Online</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/something-online/413079</link>
    <description>In the year 2021 the world was in a very bad state, many natural resources we&#39;re getting empty and people lost hope for a future. America&#39;s economy was dieing and the dollar had been left out 3 years ago, it was replaced by the euro in an effort of Europe to save and give hope to America. That was the first big mistake of humanity. 7 years later in 2028 after Europe&#39;s attempt to save America, the euro was worth half of what the dollar was worth back in 2021. Because of America, Europe&#39;s economy went down together with America. That lead to a big vulnerability to the Eastern countries. Armenia, Russia, Ukrania, Georgia,... In an attempt to save the eastern economy, Russia rebuilt the Sovjet Union, Sovjet Union 2.0 together with Armenia, Ukrania, Georgia,...


They stopped all import and export, deported all American and European tourists and habitants and blocked all incoming Western tourism.


America and Europe were shocked of this because the whole operation took only 2 weeks to complete and happend out of nothing. A group of American USSR Nazi hackers called Anoglia hacked into all America&#39;s military mainframes. The second big mistake of humanity is the fact that they use a network for launching bombs. Anoglia took over all the control of America&#39;s nuclear bombs, and launched them on the capital city of Russia, Moscow.
11 million people were estimated to have died, Russia was furious. They started to nuke America, killing millions of civillians. A nuclear war started between the USSR and the USA.
Europe was in the middle of all of this. This is the third mistake of humanity, Europe was America&#39;s friend because they helped them with the euro back in 2021. So they decided to support them in the war. They had made a prototype bio nuke that could whipe out 10 000 000 km² in one attack. This nuke was not tested yet and was very unstable, but that was all Europe had. In the year 2028, 27 October at 17:25, Europe launched the nuke on the center of Russia. The bomb exploded and whiped Russia out, but the nuclear reaction didn&#39;t go as planned and kept going, whiping out the entire planet. Killing all that is living and exposing the ones that survived to extreme radiation.


Not everyone died, since the incident started in Moscow, a lot of people build underground shelters to provide them protection. Those people are the only survivors on the planet. Animals are all dead apart from the ones that were taken with people in the shelters, the ones that did survive are mutated. 


I&#39;m working on a project in an attempt to get rich, currently I&#39;m writing the game mechanics and other stuff required for a game to be a game.
This is the story line, it still has gotten some work on it but I&#39;d like to get opinions on it and what could be done better.


This game is going to use the unreleased Stage3D APIs from Flash, using DirectX 9 for rendering on Windows machines and OpenGL 1.3 on Mac and Linux machines. The graphics on this game won&#39;t be anything special because I want this project to be completed in a year. I have a deadline until next summer. This will be a MMORPG game possibly in first person, and I need to write some network protocols for this before I can start the actual game development.


When your first start the game, you will be able to choose from either starting in New York City, or in Moscow, both of wich are destroyed. The weather will be the only major difference between the cities, snow and rain in Moscow, sun and rain in New York. Again the game will not use very complicated graphics, but it will look good, I have an imagine in mind.


Now the game mechanics are going to be a little hard te realize though, in the fantasy world that I&#39;ll create, money will have no value, what will have value is metals, all kinds of different metals, steel, aluminium, gold, adamantine,... Everyone gets a device called the MB Compressor when they start, what it does is, for example there is this pile of steel and it&#39;s pretty much useless. With the MB Compressor, you aim at that steel, and activate it, what it does is, it breaks the steel molecules down, compresses them and puts them in it&#39;s memory. You can then edit that steel on your MB Compressor because it will be some kind of hologramish computer, and you can mix different types of steel you collected, make building shapes with them, then decompress those metal particals into the model you chose in your MB Compressor. It&#39;s hard to explain but you will be able to make all kinds of big buildings, and link buildings together and so on, of course you&#39;ll need metal for this. The goal is to get as big and as strong buildings as possible. And AI will then live in those buildings, work for you, produce money, search for metals,... You will be the boss of those people.


Here is how I&#39;m going to do this (I think), there is the main New York City, wich is totally destroyed, your goal is to rebuild the city. You can do this by buying ground and then start building on that peace of ground, you can expand your ground but all this will cost you metals, probably gold.
In the main city, noone will be able to build because that&#39;s static, but when buying ground you will have your own personal space called City Sections (for now), every account is limited to one City Section in either New York or Moscow. There you will build your part of the city. When creating a City Section, you will be asked to give it a name. When exiting the main static New York city, people can either go to their City Section or visit other City Sections, where they will only be able to look around and examine other buildings. From their own City Section, they can send attacks to other City Sections, for stealing their metals and resources. Every person who wishes to enable attacking other City Sections needs to disable their protection wich allows other people to attack that person aswell. There will be no levels, only wealth. After your city has x amount of ground, you can join in with other City Sections. For example, City Section X and City Section Y are part of City Territory X.

When one has a City Section and another person has also one and both are compatible for starting a City Territory, the person who requests to start a City Territory gets to choose the name and be the leader. After that, OTHER PEOPLE, can request to join the City Territory.
City Territories will be able to attack only other City Territories and not single City Section, all the earned goods after a succesfull attack will get shared in percentages that are based on wich individual City Section is bigger. So the goal of this game will be to be as big as possible. More content will be added after the first completed release, but this is all I&#39;m going to work on for now.


Of course there will not only be metals but also other materials such as glass,...


This is a rough sketch of what it will be like. I need to complete these game mechanics first before any development can start.


Also, this game will be completely free to play, my income will be generated with ads around the game. Not many, 3 or so. 


Another thing I forgot to mention is that the way you get metal is by collecting it in the main city from wreckage and by letting your habitants search for metal, you can &quot;buy&quot; people to come and live in your City Section with gold.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 03 Sep 2011 23:48:25 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Game Development</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/something-online/413079.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Something Online</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Frell Frell]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/frell">@Frell</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote="(Anthony), post:12, topic:413079"][quote author=Frell link=topic=514552.msg3737408#msg3737408 date=1315062351]<br>
If you’re in it for the money stop now.<br>
[/quote]<br>
you think major game devs do it for fun? no.<br>
they want money, they come up with a good idea, they put it in action.</p>
<p>p.s. have fun getting a patent or anything now that you posted it online.[/quote]<br>
Wrong. The people who overview finance just want money, the tons of people making the art and designing the game do it because its a career they enjoy.</p>
<p>Besides, those companies werent started to just ‘get rich’, they wanted to make games. Its when companies like EA and Activision get ahold of games that they become directed by greed and turn into shit.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/something-online/413079/13">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/something-online/413079/13</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 03 Sep 2011 23:48:25 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-413079-13</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/something-online/413079.rss">Something Online</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Something Online</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@_bool]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/_bool">@_bool</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote quote-modified" data-post="9" data-topic="413079">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/frell/40/5_e05bb34c421432ee4d40de30c10af3e5.png" class="avatar"> Frell:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>If you’re in it for the money stop now.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>you think major game devs do it for fun? no.<br>
they want money, they come up with a good idea, they put it in action.</p>
<p>p.s. have fun getting a patent or anything now that you posted it online.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/something-online/413079/12">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/something-online/413079/12</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 03 Sep 2011 23:41:32 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-413079-12</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/something-online/413079.rss">Something Online</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Something Online</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@MistaBigBoss MistaBigBoss]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/mistabigboss">@MistaBigBoss</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“Frell, post:9, topic:413079”]If you’re in it for the money stop now.[/quote]No, I just want to have something to be proud of, and some money coming with that would make it even better.<br>
But no, money is not my priority.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/something-online/413079/11">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/something-online/413079/11</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 03 Sep 2011 22:32:57 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-413079-11</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/something-online/413079.rss">Something Online</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Something Online</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Racist_Turtle Racist Turtle]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/racist_turtle">@Racist_Turtle</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote quote-modified" data-post="8" data-topic="413079">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 _s:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>[quote]I’m working on a project in an attempt to get rich</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>ha[/quote]</p>
<p>Exactly what it has been sounding like…</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/something-online/413079/10">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/something-online/413079/10</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 03 Sep 2011 20:11:33 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-413079-10</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/something-online/413079.rss">Something Online</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Something Online</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Frell Frell]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/frell">@Frell</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>If you’re in it for the money stop now.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/something-online/413079/9">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/something-online/413079/9</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 03 Sep 2011 15:05:51 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-413079-9</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/something-online/413079.rss">Something Online</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Something Online</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@_s11 s1gma]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/_s11">@_s11</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <blockquote>I'm working on a project in an attempt to get rich</blockquote>
ha
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/something-online/413079/8">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/something-online/413079/8</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 03 Sep 2011 12:56:44 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-413079-8</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/something-online/413079.rss">Something Online</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Something Online</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@MistaBigBoss MistaBigBoss]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/mistabigboss">@MistaBigBoss</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“Frell, post:6, topic:413079”][quote author=Charles Handson link=topic=514552.msg3736249#msg3736249 date=1314991009]<br>
This sounds… ‘Intreging’<br>
[/quote]<br>
Intriguing?[/quote]That’s great, I guess.</p>
<p>Anyway, here are some responds for this on other game development forums.</p>
<p>Ravyne:<br>
[size=8pt]<br>
I would be sure to think more deeply about the back story – as it is, it sounds like you came up with the big concept, and then tried to string it together with details that fall apart under any scrutiny at all – for example, In 2021, Europe tries to help out America by propping up the dollar with the Euro, and as a result, 7 years later the Euro is now just as worthless, the world starts getting crazy, the USSR is reborn and America, by all appearances, just decides to go kick the hornet’s nest by launching nukes at Moscow (I know the hackers did it, but what assurance does Europe have?), and Europe decides to step in and save their American friends yet again? After they were rewarded so “richly” last time? If I’m Europe in this situation, maybe I’m thinking its time to ditch my old friend and start learning to like Vodka.</p>
<p>This is all very political, but takes place in the aftermath of an earth-changing event – think really hard about people’s motives and character when they are suddenly faced with a very different world where none of yesterday’s guarantees are true any longer. My guess is that most people, faced with such a situation, would become withdrawn, suspicious of other people’s motives, prefer arrangements that provide short-term payoff, and would take advantage of a situation whenever the opportunity presented itself. In short, people will mostly be out for themselves.</p>
<p>Also, who are these “American USSR Nazi hackers” I can’t even really parse that because you’ve named 3 groups that aren’t particularly known for getting along. They’re hackers based in the USSR who are attacking America and who happen to follow Nazi ideology? I guess that’s the most sensible interpretation. Anyhow, what is their motive for hacking America’s military and launching nukes at Moscow (they have ties to the USSR, why nuke the capital?) And surely they knew that it would kick off a devastating war… why would they do that? Was it just for the Lulz?</p>
<p>You also say things like “everything dies. Except stuff that didn’t, they’re just mutants now” I think 3-4 times. Be mindful of that, but maybe its just that your command of English is lacking, as you admitted.</p>
<p>The compressor gadget is interesting, if you can set aside that it has no sound scientific basis what-so-ever. Usually the best Sci-Fi gadgets have a bit of truth to them, but the compressor is obviously a fabrication to facilitate the gameplay – that’s not necessarily wrong to do, but the story might be more believable if there were a more plausible mechanic. Maybe instead of the compressor, its a GPS-like device that tells a swarm of nano-scale robots where a deposit is, and they come break down the material and carry it back to home base? or maybe you just carry a jar of these nano-bots and pour some over whatever material you wish to gather.<br>
[/size]</p>
<p>polyfrag:<br>
[size=8pt]<br>
So if you store a certain volume of metal and then use it to build a three-level building, how will the pathfinding work? What if it has to route a way from top floor, down the stairs, to the bottom.</p>
<p>Will there be physics? Are you going to use PhysX or something?</p>
<p>If you have a lot of user-created geometry, won’t that lag up the game if you can’t use binary space partitioning (BSP) or some technique to reduce the number of drawn polygons in addition to frustum culling?</p>
<p>What if I build a physically unrealistic building, like a set of stairs that leads to a floor that just hangs in the air? Sounds like a cool game mechanic though, kind of like minecraft.<br>
[/size]</p>
<p>Me:</p>
<p>[size=8pt]Ravyne, I am truly thankful for your response as it has some very valuable information.</p>
<p>By American USSR Nazis I meant, people from America that hate the USSR so much that they can be considered USSR Nazis, I will probably have to replace that with something more like a USSR hate group called something.</p>
<p>They decided to nuke the USSR because they pretty much got abandoned by them. Europe helps America because the USSR 2.0 did the same thing to them as it did to the USA. So for their own protection aswell, they helped America to defeat the mighty USSR.</p>
<p>I should probably replace the everyone dies part with, most of the world died and those who survived and got exposed to radiation, mutated.</p>
<p>I’m going to keep the MB Compressor’s concept as I find it good as it is, altough you are completely right about the fact that I need to put some logic behind the technology.<br>
I’d say it creates a small portable and highly controlled (for putting the shapes on the right place after you decompress and assemble the particles back together) black hole that can only suck up materials such as metals, glass,… nothing organic. After sucking it up, it breaks the material down into small particles (or molecules whatever you want to call it) and sends them to the molecule compressor, wich then compresses the particles and stores them in it’s physical memory.</p>
<p>Polyfrag, since I’m only 17 and a hobby game developer I haven’t got the knowledge of BSP and other advanced techniques like that.<br>
This game will have simple physics, nothing spectacular as there is no need for them (for now). I will model efficient using as little amount of polygons as possible but with good textures and shaders to make the game look good. I also decided to use the Unity engine since it is already out in the public and is very stable compared to the unreleased Molehill APIs from Flash. Unity will give me not only the oppertunity to make the game better looking for when I am capable of doing so, but also will allow me for making it cross platform for when the time is ripe. Oh, almost forgot, the main reason for using Unity or Molehill from Flash is because of the fact that if this game works out, it will be browser based.</p>
<p>As for the building shapes, the reason why everyone gets their own City Sections is because that will allow the computer to render only one “space” at a time, for example, the main city or some City Section. But nothing merged together.</p>
<p>I originally planned to premodel all kinds of shapes for the buildings and let the player combine those shapes to make his buildings the way he or she wants. The reason I don’t want to give the player complete freedom in creating his or her city is because I will be using more complex graphics than Minecraft wich will make it harder to render and because I’m trying to recreate the effect of actually being in New York. The effect of being surrounded by big buildings, not by ugly shapes. People will be able to go on the top of buildings for example. I think you get the basic idea. But I don’t know, maybe people won’t like the game for the fact that they are restricted to premodeled shapes.</p>
<p>Also, I think I might add another 30 years to the default dates because the MB Compressor is a bit ahead of it’s time imo.[/size]</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/something-online/413079/7">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/something-online/413079/7</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 02 Sep 2011 22:43:13 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-413079-7</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/something-online/413079.rss">Something Online</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Something Online</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Frell Frell]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/frell">@Frell</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote quote-modified" data-post="4" data-topic="413079">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 Charles Handson:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>This sounds… ‘Intreging’</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Intriguing?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/something-online/413079/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/something-online/413079/6</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 02 Sep 2011 21:46:59 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-413079-6</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/something-online/413079.rss">Something Online</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Something Online</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@MistaBigBoss MistaBigBoss]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/mistabigboss">@MistaBigBoss</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“Charles Handson, post:4, topic:413079”]This sounds… ‘Intreging’[/quote]What do you mean by that,</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/something-online/413079/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/something-online/413079/5</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 02 Sep 2011 19:17:50 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-413079-5</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/something-online/413079.rss">Something Online</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Something Online</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Charles_Handson Charles Handson]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/charles_handson">@Charles_Handson</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>This sounds… ‘Intreging’</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/something-online/413079/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/something-online/413079/4</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 02 Sep 2011 19:16:49 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-413079-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/something-online/413079.rss">Something Online</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Something Online</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@MistaBigBoss MistaBigBoss]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/mistabigboss">@MistaBigBoss</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“Morx, post:2, topic:413079”]Seems very intresting…i wish you goodluck and also im not that much of a storywriter but that story was pretty good to me.[/quote]Glad you like it, but I’m going to post this on some other game development forums to see what the opinions are before starting the development of this.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/something-online/413079/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/something-online/413079/3</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 02 Sep 2011 17:49:03 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-413079-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/something-online/413079.rss">Something Online</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Something Online</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Morx Morx]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/morx">@Morx</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Seems very intresting…i wish you goodluck and also im not that much of a storywriter but that story was pretty good to me.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/something-online/413079/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/something-online/413079/2</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 02 Sep 2011 00:10:45 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-413079-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/something-online/413079.rss">Something Online</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Something Online</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@MistaBigBoss MistaBigBoss]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/mistabigboss">@MistaBigBoss</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>In the year 2021 the world was in a very bad state, many natural resources we’re getting empty and people lost hope for a future. America’s economy was dieing and the dollar had been left out 3 years ago, it was replaced by the euro in an effort of Europe to save and give hope to America. That was the first big mistake of humanity. 7 years later in 2028 after Europe’s attempt to save America, the euro was worth half of what the dollar was worth back in 2021. Because of America, Europe’s economy went down together with America. That lead to a big vulnerability to the Eastern countries. Armenia, Russia, Ukrania, Georgia,… In an attempt to save the eastern economy, Russia rebuilt the Sovjet Union, Sovjet Union 2.0 together with Armenia, Ukrania, Georgia,…</p>
<p>They stopped all import and export, deported all American and European tourists and habitants and blocked all incoming Western tourism.</p>
<p>America and Europe were shocked of this because the whole operation took only 2 weeks to complete and happend out of nothing. A group of American USSR Nazi hackers called Anoglia hacked into all America’s military mainframes. The second big mistake of humanity is the fact that they use a network for launching bombs. Anoglia took over all the control of America’s nuclear bombs, and launched them on the capital city of Russia, Moscow.<br>
11 million people were estimated to have died, Russia was furious. They started to nuke America, killing millions of civillians. A nuclear war started between the USSR and the USA.<br>
Europe was in the middle of all of this. This is the third mistake of humanity, Europe was America’s friend because they helped them with the euro back in 2021. So they decided to support them in the war. They had made a prototype bio nuke that could whipe out 10 000 000 km² in one attack. This nuke was not tested yet and was very unstable, but that was all Europe had. In the year 2028, 27 October at 17:25, Europe launched the nuke on the center of Russia. The bomb exploded and whiped Russia out, but the nuclear reaction didn’t go as planned and kept going, whiping out the entire planet. Killing all that is living and exposing the ones that survived to extreme radiation.</p>
<p>Not everyone died, since the incident started in Moscow, a lot of people build underground shelters to provide them protection. Those people are the only survivors on the planet. Animals are all dead apart from the ones that were taken with people in the shelters, the ones that did survive are mutated.</p>
<p>I’m working on a project in an attempt to get rich, currently I’m writing the game mechanics and other stuff required for a game to be a game.<br>
This is the story line, it still has gotten some work on it but I’d like to get opinions on it and what could be done better.</p>
<p>This game is going to use the unreleased Stage3D APIs from Flash, using DirectX 9 for rendering on Windows machines and OpenGL 1.3 on Mac and Linux machines. The graphics on this game won’t be anything special because I want this project to be completed in a year. I have a deadline until next summer. This will be a MMORPG game possibly in first person, and I need to write some network protocols for this before I can start the actual game development.</p>
<p>When your first start the game, you will be able to choose from either starting in New York City, or in Moscow, both of wich are destroyed. The weather will be the only major difference between the cities, snow and rain in Moscow, sun and rain in New York. Again the game will not use very complicated graphics, but it will look good, I have an imagine in mind.</p>
<p>Now the game mechanics are going to be a little hard te realize though, in the fantasy world that I’ll create, money will have no value, what will have value is metals, all kinds of different metals, steel, aluminium, gold, adamantine,… Everyone gets a device called the MB Compressor when they start, what it does is, for example there is this pile of steel and it’s pretty much useless. With the MB Compressor, you aim at that steel, and activate it, what it does is, it breaks the steel molecules down, compresses them and puts them in it’s memory. You can then edit that steel on your MB Compressor because it will be some kind of hologramish computer, and you can mix different types of steel you collected, make building shapes with them, then decompress those metal particals into the model you chose in your MB Compressor. It’s hard to explain but you will be able to make all kinds of big buildings, and link buildings together and so on, of course you’ll need metal for this. The goal is to get as big and as strong buildings as possible. And AI will then live in those buildings, work for you, produce money, search for metals,… You will be the boss of those people.</p>
<p>Here is how I’m going to do this (I think), there is the main New York City, wich is totally destroyed, your goal is to rebuild the city. You can do this by buying ground and then start building on that peace of ground, you can expand your ground but all this will cost you metals, probably gold.<br>
In the main city, noone will be able to build because that’s static, but when buying ground you will have your own personal space called City Sections (for now), every account is limited to one City Section in either New York or Moscow. There you will build your part of the city. When creating a City Section, you will be asked to give it a name. When exiting the main static New York city, people can either go to their City Section or visit other City Sections, where they will only be able to look around and examine other buildings. From their own City Section, they can send attacks to other City Sections, for stealing their metals and resources. Every person who wishes to enable attacking other City Sections needs to disable their protection wich allows other people to attack that person aswell. There will be no levels, only wealth. After your city has x amount of ground, you can join in with other City Sections. For example, City Section X and City Section Y are part of City Territory X.</p>
<p>When one has a City Section and another person has also one and both are compatible for starting a City Territory, the person who requests to start a City Territory gets to choose the name and be the leader. After that, OTHER PEOPLE, can request to join the City Territory.<br>
City Territories will be able to attack only other City Territories and not single City Section, all the earned goods after a succesfull attack will get shared in percentages that are based on wich individual City Section is bigger. So the goal of this game will be to be as big as possible. More content will be added after the first completed release, but this is all I’m going to work on for now.</p>
<p>Of course there will not only be metals but also other materials such as glass,…</p>
<p>This is a rough sketch of what it will be like. I need to complete these game mechanics first before any development can start.</p>
<p>Also, this game will be completely free to play, my income will be generated with ads around the game. Not many, 3 or so.</p>
<p>Another thing I forgot to mention is that the way you get metal is by collecting it in the main city from wreckage and by letting your habitants search for metal, you can “buy” people to come and live in your City Section with gold.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/something-online/413079/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/something-online/413079/1</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 01 Sep 2011 22:42:05 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-413079-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/something-online/413079.rss">Something Online</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
