<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Declaring animation types [SOLVED]</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/declaring-animation-types-solved/522933</link>
    <description>[u]First of all, Hello Moparscape and thank you for providing this bastion of information.[/u]

While browsing through the files for EasyRSC I noticed that the sprites for the hatchet had been changed (from the battleaxe sprite to a new one). 
I decided to mock up a quick edit on the shield sprites into a shield that looks somewhat like a kite-shield. 

I came here because I wanted to know how I can add these to my client. I have my item and itemwieldable xml files correct, however, I noticed in the animaton xml file it names each entry. For example, all the woodcutting axes have a name of &quot;hatchet&quot;, the battle axes have a name of &quot;battleaxe&quot;, the wizardhat, gnomehat, etc, have a name of &quot;wizardhat&quot;.

I&#39;m probably way off but my assumption is that these names are storing information about which sprite files to use for the item/npc/etc. I have searched through both client and server text files and I see no reference to these names anywhere, nor do I see any related references to item ID&#39;s in any of the files.

[center]Thank you in advance, 
imALLin[/center]




Update:

Figured it out, there seems to be a lack of information about this so I will post a tutorial within a day or two.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2013 09:28:21 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/declaring-animation-types-solved/522933.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Declaring animation types [SOLVED]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@imALLin imALLin]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/imallin">@imALLin</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p><span class="bbcode-u">First of all, Hello Moparscape and thank you for providing this bastion of information.</span></p>
<p>While browsing through the files for EasyRSC I noticed that the sprites for the hatchet had been changed (from the battleaxe sprite to a new one).<br>
I decided to mock up a quick edit on the shield sprites into a shield that looks somewhat like a kite-shield.</p>
<p>I came here because I wanted to know how I can add these to my client. I have my item and itemwieldable xml files correct, however, I noticed in the animaton xml file it names each entry. For example, all the woodcutting axes have a name of “hatchet”, the battle axes have a name of “battleaxe”, the wizardhat, gnomehat, etc, have a name of “wizardhat”.</p>
<p>I’m probably way off but my assumption is that these names are storing information about which sprite files to use for the item/npc/etc. I have searched through both client and server text files and I see no reference to these names anywhere, nor do I see any related references to item ID’s in any of the files.</p>
<p>[center]Thank you in advance,<br>
imALLin[/center]</p>
<p>Update:</p>
<p>Figured it out, there seems to be a lack of information about this so I will post a tutorial within a day or two.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/declaring-animation-types-solved/522933/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/declaring-animation-types-solved/522933/1</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2013 09:28:21 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-522933-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/declaring-animation-types-solved/522933.rss">Declaring animation types [SOLVED]</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
