<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Mr.Mod</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/mr-mod/446734</link>
    <description>Hmm. my post keeps being deleted?
Ill post it again so people can see what happens to the community on this server.
Thats what were trying to build right?

The Back story: players The_hybrid and thehybridx loot Tarkoffs land. Tarkoff being a moderator banned the players for the rules broken during this event.
 
In the_hybrid post he says he just took diamonds when in reality he took every item from every chest. Even zombie meat. There is a difference from looting to scorching the earth. A difference from having fun and making a statement. They might try to site the one time they were looted bt if the chat logs are checked. AGL did all the looting. I tried to give back the items that were stolen, only to be met with more hostility. 

Antagonizing a moderator. Calling me Mr.Mad or Mr.Mod. If you came on to solve an issue and were treated this way you would ban people in a second. AS Tom has proven with the AGL situation.

during our conversation The_Hybrid states &quot;read the rules, I know what allowed&quot; maybe we saw different rules. I see...

3. Animal husbandry
Do not kill someone else&#39;s animals.
Clear and plain. They say they didn’t kill them but I have the proof they entered and they are all gone. Either way we can assume they are dead as I don’t see a bunch of green sheep around my base. Im sure they have some lame excuses for this as they try to avoid a ban.

4. Player versus Player
If you break into someone&#39;s property you must repair what ever damage you do and only cause minimum damage.
After stealing all my items they did not repair any damage. They had every opportunity to but did not, no matter what they say they would have done. It wasn’t done.
Its not minimum damage when they take the pistons and Redstone that control the door.
Clear and plain.

9. Staff decisions
The staffs does not need a report to ban you for breaking the rules if we find evidence of you breaking them, appropriate actions will be taken.
I had evidence of a few rules broken. I banned them with a level head. By going around the decision you have undermined my authority as a staff member. Maybe you should change the title to this rule as Tom’s decisions as its clear as a Mod I’m just a glorified tattletale and grief-fixer. I clearly have no say in a single thing that happens.

Tom bans AGL indefinitely for no rules being broken but for a personal reasons. But in this instance when rules are clearly broken a two week ban is to much? no punishment is handed out at all? Im confused.

Here you two player sets. Me, a player who tries to build a community. I have built a city and invited people in, I have built many of this server land marks and an very active with no infractions.
Then you have these other players that you defend, trolls and greifers and ban evaders that you want to keep in your community base. This is not a server I want to be a part of any more.

I have taken the liberty while I had the power to remove all the hybrids builds form from W1 as well as my own. Hopefully this will drive them away and they will have no items anymore. And now Tom wont have ban Toms friends in the end.
I have also removed all my builds from W2 as I don’t want any of my work to be a part of this dying server for a second more. But Im sure Tom will roll it all back anyways so I encurage players please destroy all my stuff and builds, Im sure that wont be a problem for alot of the players here as this comes naturally to them.

I hereby resign as a Mod as I don’t see the point. I also will no longer be playing on this server after I demolish all my builds. Having a Rules that don’t matter will just cause for a shitty player base... Oh that’s what you’ve got. A player community that is nothing more the Trolls and children. The root to this dying server comes down to these issues, the good loyal players get fed up with all the bullshit and leave in a blaze. No amount of advertising will fix the root of the issue and I could care less.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 24 Jun 2012 20:06:58 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Minecraft</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/mr-mod/446734.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Mr.Mod</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@moparisthebest Moparisthebest]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/moparisthebest">@moparisthebest</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Look here, you may very well have been right when it comes to the hybrid incident, but no one is perfect (including me, you, and Tom), and I’m sure it could have been resolved the way issues always get resolved, through some discussion.  But you couldn’t wait and went ahead and took things into your own hands, destroying lots of things and actually breaking rules, and that can’t be looked past.  You completely lost your temper and that’s not something a staff member can do, you said you were antagonized, but that’s just what you get as a staff member.</p>
<p>The bottom line is you know what you did was wrong, and everyone reading your post knows the same.</p>
<p>edit:<br>
I also agree the rules need clarified and firmed up more, and we are currently in the process of doing that, it’s a shame you can’t take part in that decision making process anymore.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/mr-mod/446734/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/mr-mod/446734/2</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 24 Jun 2012 20:06:58 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-446734-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/mr-mod/446734.rss">Mr.Mod</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Mr.Mod</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@tarkoff100 tarkoff100]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/tarkoff100">@tarkoff100</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Hmm. my post keeps being deleted?<br>
Ill post it again so people can see what happens to the community on this server.<br>
Thats what were trying to build right?</p>
<p>The Back story: players The_hybrid and thehybridx loot Tarkoffs land. Tarkoff being a moderator banned the players for the rules broken during this event.</p>
<p>In the_hybrid post he says he just took diamonds when in reality he took every item from every chest. Even zombie meat. There is a difference from looting to scorching the earth. A difference from having fun and making a statement. They might try to site the one time they were looted bt if the chat logs are checked. AGL did all the looting. I tried to give back the items that were stolen, only to be met with more hostility.</p>
<p>Antagonizing a moderator. Calling me Mr.Mad or Mr.Mod. If you came on to solve an issue and were treated this way you would ban people in a second. AS Tom has proven with the AGL situation.</p>
<p>during our conversation The_Hybrid states “read the rules, I know what allowed” maybe we saw different rules. I see…</p>
<ol start="3">
<li>
<p>Animal husbandry<br>
Do not kill someone else’s animals.<br>
Clear and plain. They say they didn’t kill them but I have the proof they entered and they are all gone. Either way we can assume they are dead as I don’t see a bunch of green sheep around my base. Im sure they have some lame excuses for this as they try to avoid a ban.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Player versus Player<br>
If you break into someone’s property you must repair what ever damage you do and only cause minimum damage.<br>
After stealing all my items they did not repair any damage. They had every opportunity to but did not, no matter what they say they would have done. It wasn’t done.<br>
Its not minimum damage when they take the pistons and Redstone that control the door.<br>
Clear and plain.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Staff decisions<br>
The staffs does not need a report to ban you for breaking the rules if we find evidence of you breaking them, appropriate actions will be taken.<br>
I had evidence of a few rules broken. I banned them with a level head. By going around the decision you have undermined my authority as a staff member. Maybe you should change the title to this rule as Tom’s decisions as its clear as a Mod I’m just a glorified tattletale and grief-fixer. I clearly have no say in a single thing that happens.</p>
</li>
</ol>
<p>Tom bans AGL indefinitely for no rules being broken but for a personal reasons. But in this instance when rules are clearly broken a two week ban is to much? no punishment is handed out at all? Im confused.</p>
<p>Here you two player sets. Me, a player who tries to build a community. I have built a city and invited people in, I have built many of this server land marks and an very active with no infractions.<br>
Then you have these other players that you defend, trolls and greifers and ban evaders that you want to keep in your community base. This is not a server I want to be a part of any more.</p>
<p>I have taken the liberty while I had the power to remove all the hybrids builds form from W1 as well as my own. Hopefully this will drive them away and they will have no items anymore. And now Tom wont have ban Toms friends in the end.<br>
I have also removed all my builds from W2 as I don’t want any of my work to be a part of this dying server for a second more. But Im sure Tom will roll it all back anyways so I encurage players please destroy all my stuff and builds, Im sure that wont be a problem for alot of the players here as this comes naturally to them.</p>
<p>I hereby resign as a Mod as I don’t see the point. I also will no longer be playing on this server after I demolish all my builds. Having a Rules that don’t matter will just cause for a shitty player base… Oh that’s what you’ve got. A player community that is nothing more the Trolls and children. The root to this dying server comes down to these issues, the good loyal players get fed up with all the bullshit and leave in a blaze. No amount of advertising will fix the root of the issue and I could care less.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/mr-mod/446734/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/mr-mod/446734/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 24 Jun 2012 19:50:53 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-446734-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/mr-mod/446734.rss">Mr.Mod</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
