<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Need help please!</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/need-help-please/370609</link>
    <description>[s]I&#39;m new to private servers and have come across a lot of issues, but this one is the most challenging. Okay, so I add the custom models and everything looks fine, until I equip. It goes straight to the weapon slot. I have read other topics of people with the same problem and they all say to add them in Item.java and I put them in all the right spots. I compiled and restarted my server and everyone says after that point, the problem is solved. When I do that it still goes in the weapon slot, and I have tried other things myself. Sorry if this is long, I am really new. Anyways, back on topic, please help if you know the answer to my problem or think you do, (you can even tell me if you&#39;re having the same problem so I know there are other people on the same boat) all help is EXTREMELY appreciated. Thank you! :confused:[/s] I fixed it myself, I wasn&#39;t putting them in Item4.java aswell as Item.java.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 27 Nov 2010 08:14:03 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Game Development</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/need-help-please/370609.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Need help please!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@King_of_Smurfs King of Smurfs]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/king_of_smurfs">@King_of_Smurfs</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p><span class="bbcode-s">I’m new to private servers and have come across a lot of issues, but this one is the most challenging. Okay, so I add the custom models and everything looks fine, until I equip. It goes straight to the weapon slot. I have read other topics of people with the same problem and they all say to add them in Item.java and I put them in all the right spots. I compiled and restarted my server and everyone says after that point, the problem is solved. When I do that it still goes in the weapon slot, and I have tried other things myself. Sorry if this is long, I am really new. Anyways, back on topic, please help if you know the answer to my problem or think you do, (you can even tell me if you’re having the same problem so I know there are other people on the same boat) all help is EXTREMELY appreciated. Thank you! <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/confused.png?v=5" title=":confused:" class="emoji" alt=":confused:"></span> I fixed it myself, I wasn’t putting them in Item4.java aswell as Item.java.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/need-help-please/370609/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/need-help-please/370609/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 27 Nov 2010 08:14:03 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-370609-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/need-help-please/370609.rss">Need help please!</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
