<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>[HELP] Connecting my client and source to a server</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/help-connecting-my-client-and-source-to-a-server/439911</link>
    <description>I&#39;ve downloaded an OceanX Christmas Special source and client from the forums, I followed a tut on youtube and it all went well. I have all the things I believe that I need, however. My client starts up but does not connect to the server when I log in. So I tried to look on my source at the characters, there is a pre-made one. So I used the info, still won&#39;t connect.

I made a server with No-IP which is what the tut told me to do, I set it up properly by editing &quot;runserver&quot; and changing the title to my server name. Still not working! Argh!

I would like some help getting my server online so that others can play. For the time being, I don&#39;t mind it being on a free zapto.org server. In time I will buy a dedicated vps and host it on that with a decent domain etc.

Any tips would be great, never made a private server, I&#39;ve only ever made Habbo retros.

Any help would be appreciated, I&#39;m on Skype most of the time so feel free to add me: joyshh

Thanks,</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 17 Apr 2012 20:49:05 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/help-connecting-my-client-and-source-to-a-server/439911.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>[HELP] Connecting my client and source to a server</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@eJoshua eJoshua]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/ejoshua">@eJoshua</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I’ve downloaded an OceanX Christmas Special source and client from the forums, I followed a tut on youtube and it all went well. I have all the things I believe that I need, however. My client starts up but does not connect to the server when I log in. So I tried to look on my source at the characters, there is a pre-made one. So I used the info, still won’t connect.</p>
<p>I made a server with No-IP which is what the tut told me to do, I set it up properly by editing “runserver” and changing the title to my server name. Still not working! Argh!</p>
<p>I would like some help getting my server online so that others can play. For the time being, I don’t mind it being on a free <a href="http://zapto.org" rel="nofollow noopener">zapto.org</a> server. In time I will buy a dedicated vps and host it on that with a decent domain etc.</p>
<p>Any tips would be great, never made a private server, I’ve only ever made Habbo retros.</p>
<p>Any help would be appreciated, I’m on Skype most of the time so feel free to add me: joyshh</p>
<p>Thanks,</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/help-connecting-my-client-and-source-to-a-server/439911/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/help-connecting-my-client-and-source-to-a-server/439911/1</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 17 Apr 2012 20:49:05 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-439911-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/help-connecting-my-client-and-source-to-a-server/439911.rss">[HELP] Connecting my client and source to a server</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
