<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>HammareCraft [Survival] [PvP] [LWC] [World Guard] [Chest Shops] [24/7][No Lag]</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/hammarecraft-survival-pvp-lwc-world-guard-chest-shops-24-7-no-lag/445145</link>
    <description>[b][u]HammareCraft[/u][/b]
Server IP: mc.hammarecraft.com
Server Website: hammarecraft.com

Hammarcraft is a non-profit Minecraft Server. All donations go directly into the server, server website &amp; server utilities. It&#39;s popularity is spread through word of mouth rather than through pricey advertisement campaigns. Since it is a non-profit we hope to draw just enough donations to keep the server up and running and have no need for excess funds to be wasted on previously stated advertisements. The server is community run and by that we mean that it has multiple owners of interests which all work for free.

It&#39;s founding was due to a bad experience on another server where the server owner was spending the donations he received on himself rather than the server.

Hammarecraft is a cosmetic survival (normal difficulty) pvp enabled world.

About The Server
HammareCraft is a nice survival PvP server. We offer no lag, protections from people griefing your builds, chest shops to profit in the economy, great staff who is there for anything you need to ask. The server is up 24/7 so you have no doubts if its up or not. Our server focuses on the needs of the players, so we take into consideration what you guys think. More dedicated players are needed to make the server more popular and more exciting than it already is. If you have questions just let a staff member know in game.

Future Plans
1) We are currently working on a new spawn, its focused more on the needs of members than the current one.
2) Getting a new plugin named Heroes, currently we have McMMO.
3) Better Economy system coming with the new spawn along with a wide range of items in the market.

This server has been up and running for 6 months strong with no lag. We are looking for more players that are dedicated and are happy playing minecraft on survival.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 14 Jun 2012 22:22:42 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Minecraft</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/hammarecraft-survival-pvp-lwc-world-guard-chest-shops-24-7-no-lag/445145.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>HammareCraft [Survival] [PvP] [LWC] [World Guard] [Chest Shops] [24/7][No Lag]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Legend_Maker Legend_Maker]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/legend_maker">@Legend_Maker</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p><span class="bbcode-b"><span class="bbcode-u">HammareCraft</span></span><br>
Server IP: <a href="http://mc.hammarecraft.com" rel="nofollow noopener">mc.hammarecraft.com</a><br>
Server Website: <a href="http://hammarecraft.com" rel="nofollow noopener">hammarecraft.com</a></p>
<p>Hammarcraft is a non-profit Minecraft Server. All donations go directly into the server, server website &amp; server utilities. It’s popularity is spread through word of mouth rather than through pricey advertisement campaigns. Since it is a non-profit we hope to draw just enough donations to keep the server up and running and have no need for excess funds to be wasted on previously stated advertisements. The server is community run and by that we mean that it has multiple owners of interests which all work for free.</p>
<p>It’s founding was due to a bad experience on another server where the server owner was spending the donations he received on himself rather than the server.</p>
<p>Hammarecraft is a cosmetic survival (normal difficulty) pvp enabled world.</p>
<p>About The Server<br>
HammareCraft is a nice survival PvP server. We offer no lag, protections from people griefing your builds, chest shops to profit in the economy, great staff who is there for anything you need to ask. The server is up 24/7 so you have no doubts if its up or not. Our server focuses on the needs of the players, so we take into consideration what you guys think. More dedicated players are needed to make the server more popular and more exciting than it already is. If you have questions just let a staff member know in game.</p>
<p>Future Plans</p>
<ol>
<li>We are currently working on a new spawn, its focused more on the needs of members than the current one.</li>
<li>Getting a new plugin named Heroes, currently we have McMMO.</li>
<li>Better Economy system coming with the new spawn along with a wide range of items in the market.</li>
</ol>
<p>This server has been up and running for 6 months strong with no lag. We are looking for more players that are dedicated and are happy playing minecraft on survival.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/hammarecraft-survival-pvp-lwc-world-guard-chest-shops-24-7-no-lag/445145/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/hammarecraft-survival-pvp-lwc-world-guard-chest-shops-24-7-no-lag/445145/1</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 14 Jun 2012 22:22:42 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-445145-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/hammarecraft-survival-pvp-lwc-world-guard-chest-shops-24-7-no-lag/445145.rss">HammareCraft [Survival] [PvP] [LWC] [World Guard] [Chest Shops] [24/7][No Lag]</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
