<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>614 client help?</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/614-client-help/371227</link>
    <description>Hey can someone explain to me how to be able to log into my 614 source. I mean I already have it running and the client comes up perfectly normal and it says log in and i type in the user name and password, but for some reason it&#39;s not letting me in, it says error connecting to server.  Can somebody please help I am so fricken desperate and i am willing to make someone an admin can somebody please help me?? and where do i go to make the client have my connection, like i use hamachi where would i put that code??</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 01 Dec 2010 02:05:55 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/614-client-help/371227.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>614 client help?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@runyluny runyluny]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/runyluny">@runyluny</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Hey can someone explain to me how to be able to log into my 614 source. I mean I already have it running and the client comes up perfectly normal and it says log in and i type in the user name and password, but for some reason it’s not letting me in, it says error connecting to server.  Can somebody please help I am so fricken desperate and i am willing to make someone an admin can somebody please help me?? and where do i go to make the client have my connection, like i use hamachi where would i put that code??</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/614-client-help/371227/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/614-client-help/371227/1</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 01 Dec 2010 02:05:55 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-371227-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/614-client-help/371227.rss">614 client help?</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
