<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>From Dust to Dragons 2</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/from-dust-to-dragons-2/548369</link>
    <description>I&#39;ll just call this project - &quot;Dragonhide&quot;

It will be a server based on Hyperion (thanks to Scully for helping me start out :)), I will probably be the only coder of it (unless I hit a particularily tricky problem)... since I&#39;d like to learn this framework and learn the things it has and things I can manipulate to my liking.

The client will be a resize-capable 317 with 474 cache, hopefully in a webclient format (optional download). 

What will the server be about?
As was the original FDTD, it will be about slow progression, exploration, secrets, bosses, skills, combining, mysteries and of course player interaction.

I know where I want to go with this project because I had a server with this very concept before (coded on a horrific, albeit highly patched/hacked version of Delta), since then I&#39;ve learned the weaknesses of crappy programming and have (finally) decided to dedicate myself to using a new (good) base for my work.

Anyway, there&#39;s plenty of work I need to do... even just to get the basics in place.

So why the post?

Well, there will be a time where all the basics will be done... and all that I will require is populating the world with NPCs, Quests, Objects and other such funky things...
I am not sure about the reward for those who help, I guess it will depend on what the server becomes at the time.

[size=14pt][b]Current status:[/b][/size]
[size=8pt][b][content]Items - 0%[/b] - Items are obtainable, go into the right slots and are divided into types; no equipment stats exist as of yet.
[b][content]Objects - 0%[/b] - No objects have been scripted/hard-coded as of yet.
[b][system]Item On Item - 90%[/b] - Every possible outcome for a combination has been handled, mechanics simply need declaring into the statements.
[b]Item Use - 30%[/b] - Items are usable, however there&#39;s no framework in place for easy implementation of items yet.
[b]Fishing - 50%[/b] - Fishing code is there, however spots (NPC) haven&#39;t been implemented yet.
[b]Woodcutting - 70%[/b] - Trees can be cut infinitely, animation only plays once, there&#39;s no randomized delay/cutting time, objects do not get replaced yet.
[b]Combat - 0%[/b] - No work done yet.
[b]PvP - 0%[/b] - No work/planning done yet.
[b]Boss Encounters - 0%[/b] - No system in place for implementation.
[b][system]Other mechanics - 6%[/b] - Many are half-done or not done at all, there&#39;s still lots of work to do. *Update: Added healing and stat buffing[/size]

[b][size=12pt]Overall completion: 17%[/size][/b]

[b]About myself:[/b]
I will be working on this server basically on a daily basis, the workload ahead of me is huge and I do a lot of learning as I get on with things. If it comes to a point where I feel the code is just too much, I may start using git-hub for a better development process and get some extra hands on board.

[b]Who am I looking for?[/b]
I am looking for people with good imaginations, excitement for exploration (if you watch Log Horizon, think something in the direction of that) and some drive to get things done.
I am not a bad programmer, I type quickly, I create content quickly and 95% of it functions as intended (if not, I do a hotfix within milliseconds :D.). I&#39;m not the kind of guy who runs a PI with 30 people online, donations at every corner and then ask on this forum about how to fix 100 errors in a compiler. :P The server will most likely be donation-free; online 24 hours a minute (that&#39;s right, we&#39;re messing with space-time continuum here) and I will support anyone and everyone who plays on it.

I am available on skype 24 hours a day and if you&#39;d like to chitter chatter, you can comment here or just PM me or something... 

[size=8pt][i](it is at this point that I fear this post may get deleted because I may have broken a rule somewhere... Please warn me before deleting this :) I&#39;ll edit it within seconds).[/i][/size]</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2014 04:44:14 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/from-dust-to-dragons-2/548369.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>From Dust to Dragons 2</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@fuzzout fuzzout]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/fuzzout">@fuzzout</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I’ll just call this project - “Dragonhide”</p>
<p>It will be a server based on Hyperion (thanks to Scully for helping me start out :)), I will probably be the only coder of it (unless I hit a particularily tricky problem)… since I’d like to learn this framework and learn the things it has and things I can manipulate to my liking.</p>
<p>The client will be a resize-capable 317 with 474 cache, hopefully in a webclient format (optional download).</p>
<p>What will the server be about?<br>
As was the original FDTD, it will be about slow progression, exploration, secrets, bosses, skills, combining, mysteries and of course player interaction.</p>
<p>I know where I want to go with this project because I had a server with this very concept before (coded on a horrific, albeit highly patched/hacked version of Delta), since then I’ve learned the weaknesses of crappy programming and have (finally) decided to dedicate myself to using a new (good) base for my work.</p>
<p>Anyway, there’s plenty of work I need to do… even just to get the basics in place.</p>
<p>So why the post?</p>
<p>Well, there will be a time where all the basics will be done… and all that I will require is populating the world with NPCs, Quests, Objects and other such funky things…<br>
I am not sure about the reward for those who help, I guess it will depend on what the server becomes at the time.</p>
<p>[size=14pt]<span class="bbcode-b">Current status:</span>[/size]<br>
[size=8pt]<span class="bbcode-b">[content]Items - 0%</span> - Items are obtainable, go into the right slots and are divided into types; no equipment stats exist as of yet.<br>
<span class="bbcode-b">[content]Objects - 0%</span> - No objects have been scripted/hard-coded as of yet.<br>
<span class="bbcode-b">[system]Item On Item - 90%</span> - Every possible outcome for a combination has been handled, mechanics simply need declaring into the statements.<br>
<span class="bbcode-b">Item Use - 30%</span> - Items are usable, however there’s no framework in place for easy implementation of items yet.<br>
<span class="bbcode-b">Fishing - 50%</span> - Fishing code is there, however spots (NPC) haven’t been implemented yet.<br>
<span class="bbcode-b">Woodcutting - 70%</span> - Trees can be cut infinitely, animation only plays once, there’s no randomized delay/cutting time, objects do not get replaced yet.<br>
<span class="bbcode-b">Combat - 0%</span> - No work done yet.<br>
<span class="bbcode-b">PvP - 0%</span> - No work/planning done yet.<br>
<span class="bbcode-b">Boss Encounters - 0%</span> - No system in place for implementation.<br>
<span class="bbcode-b">[system]Other mechanics - 6%</span> - Many are half-done or not done at all, there’s still lots of work to do. *Update: Added healing and stat buffing[/size]</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">[size=12pt]Overall completion: 17%[/size]</span></p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">About myself:</span><br>
I will be working on this server basically on a daily basis, the workload ahead of me is huge and I do a lot of learning as I get on with things. If it comes to a point where I feel the code is just too much, I may start using git-hub for a better development process and get some extra hands on board.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Who am I looking for?</span><br>
I am looking for people with good imaginations, excitement for exploration (if you watch Log Horizon, think something in the direction of that) and some drive to get things done.<br>
I am not a bad programmer, I type quickly, I create content quickly and 95% of it functions as intended (if not, I do a hotfix within milliseconds :D.). I’m not the kind of guy who runs a PI with 30 people online, donations at every corner and then ask on this forum about how to fix 100 errors in a compiler. <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=5" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"> The server will most likely be donation-free; online 24 hours a minute (that’s right, we’re messing with space-time continuum here) and I will support anyone and everyone who plays on it.</p>
<p>I am available on skype 24 hours a day and if you’d like to chitter chatter, you can comment here or just PM me or something…</p>
<p>[size=8pt]<span class="bbcode-i">(it is at this point that I fear this post may get deleted because I may have broken a rule somewhere… Please warn me before deleting this <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=5" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"> I’ll edit it within seconds).</span>[/size]</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/from-dust-to-dragons-2/548369/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/from-dust-to-dragons-2/548369/1</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2014 04:44:14 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-548369-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/from-dust-to-dragons-2/548369.rss">From Dust to Dragons 2</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
