<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Working abilities for spirit shields?</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/working-abilities-for-spirit-shields/398488</link>
    <description>Hello(please move to models section if it goes their not sure),
I know that no RSPS I&#39;ve ever seen has had working spirit shield&#39;s I&#39;ve raped google searching for a guide or even mention of a fully working or even 10% working spirit shields.
Its clear it must be hard to make it as my analysis of making it it&#39;d require a lot of coding (professional even) a good 5-6hours of non stop work from a really good programmer.
Does anybody have any information about this? The closest idea I have is work out a ratio for bonus&#39;s on the shields to absorb 17.5% 30%(or whatever shield it is) but what would you base it on? Would you base the bonus&#39;s added on of damage ratio&#39;s made by a player(sorry if this bit doesn&#39;t make sense im not experianced).
Also even if this were to work, their would be no prayer drain and it still doesn&#39;t seperate the server that has it from the rest.

Also i&#39;d like to add in(if requested i&#39;ll remove this part of the thread) if it were possible (without like 2 weeks non stop work or something) would anyone that knows their stuff be willing to make it for me for $100 or a max of $150? As im nowhere good enough to add it in.
I know thats a small price for what i&#39;d be asking done but you could most probibly (assuming people are willing to part with donations to improve their server) get like 5-10 people that&#39;d pay like $100 each also so it could be a nice profit. Or even release it after you&#39;ve received the money, that would be ideal so everyone can benefit. I will also give you 100% credits for doing so in my server if that would make a difference.

If their is a guide which I have somehow missed can someone please give me it though? I really do think its worth the effort.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 09 Jun 2011 19:03:59 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Game Development</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/working-abilities-for-spirit-shields/398488.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Working abilities for spirit shields?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Kidpaparoach Kidpaparoach]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/kidpaparoach">@Kidpaparoach</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Hello(please move to models section if it goes their not sure),<br>
I know that no RSPS I’ve ever seen has had working spirit shield’s I’ve raped google searching for a guide or even mention of a fully working or even 10% working spirit shields.<br>
Its clear it must be hard to make it as my analysis of making it it’d require a lot of coding (professional even) a good 5-6hours of non stop work from a really good programmer.<br>
Does anybody have any information about this? The closest idea I have is work out a ratio for bonus’s on the shields to absorb 17.5% 30%(or whatever shield it is) but what would you base it on? Would you base the bonus’s added on of damage ratio’s made by a player(sorry if this bit doesn’t make sense im not experianced).<br>
Also even if this were to work, their would be no prayer drain and it still doesn’t seperate the server that has it from the rest.</p>
<p>Also i’d like to add in(if requested i’ll remove this part of the thread) if it were possible (without like 2 weeks non stop work or something) would anyone that knows their stuff be willing to make it for me for $100 or a max of $150? As im nowhere good enough to add it in.<br>
I know thats a small price for what i’d be asking done but you could most probibly (assuming people are willing to part with donations to improve their server) get like 5-10 people that’d pay like $100 each also so it could be a nice profit. Or even release it after you’ve received the money, that would be ideal so everyone can benefit. I will also give you 100% credits for doing so in my server if that would make a difference.</p>
<p>If their is a guide which I have somehow missed can someone please give me it though? I really do think its worth the effort.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/working-abilities-for-spirit-shields/398488/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/working-abilities-for-spirit-shields/398488/1</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 09 Jun 2011 19:03:59 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-398488-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/working-abilities-for-spirit-shields/398488.rss">Working abilities for spirit shields?</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
