<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>My Input</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-input/542252</link>
    <description>Reading over most of the threads in this forum has been pretty fun, and I must say that this community seems rather interesting. I don&#39;t care what you do, I&#39;ll always have the real RSC to play on. Sure, it&#39;s filled with botters and just gets more and more lonely, but it&#39;s like playing a 1 player RPG. I don&#39;t mind it, and it always has been my favorite game. I&#39;m here looking for some people to play a replica of my favorite game with, even if it&#39;s not really a replica at all. You&#39;re all just spending so much time worrying about what&#39;ll happen, when we could be playing right now. Please, rather than debating on what you want in a RSC server, release it and make changes later. Don&#39;t try to please the whole of the community, because like several people have said here, it&#39;s impossible. The idiot Jagex staff at &quot;OldSchool RuneScape&quot; did pretty much everything the community wanted them to, and now it looks worse than a 15 year old&#39;s RS2 server.

RSC was the best time of my life, and I wasn&#39;t even around for the F2P days. I&#39;d love to see what it was like, and you guys are about the only people who can show me. I played most of the RSC private servers. My favorites among them were RSCAngel and ProjectP2P, though no one played ProjectP2P really. I liked RSCE before they changed Edgeville and made it look retarded.

MoparScape has never let me down, I&#39;ve come here for EVERYTHING since I found private servers around 2007 or so. The moment I heard about this section of the forums I started reading everything. I guess I got here a little late. I wish I could&#39;ve been here to join all these lovely conversations.


Whether you want 1x XP, 3-4x XP or 30x, custom items and P2P mage arena PKing or F2P only, we can all have a final conversation regarding the future of this MoparClassic idea. I&#39;ll donate if I can, as much as I need to. Let&#39;s just not let this die, as RSC is quite lonely when you only have botters to speak to. The private servers out now are just terrible. 

I apologise if my post comes off as immature, foolish or inexperienced. I have been playing RSC for most of my 18 year old life, and I have accepted that I&#39;ll never be able to share the memories of old old RSC with you. Judging by some of your posts, some of you will obviously come right out and flame me. I don&#39;t mind. &lt;3

I&#39;m stupid when I&#39;m tired anyway, so I know it&#39;s a dumb post. Maybe I&#39;ll edit it later.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 18 Apr 2014 05:48:06 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-input/542252.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>My Input</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Brownay01 Brownay01]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/brownay01">@Brownay01</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Well, I’m glad you guys are so nice. I wish I could’ve been a little older to experience RuneScape’s birth.</p>
<p>Hopefully that replica stays around for awhile longer than the others. In the mean time, back to RuneScape and my daily RSC KBD trips.  ;D</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-input/542252/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-input/542252/5</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 18 Apr 2014 05:48:06 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-542252-5</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-input/542252.rss">My Input</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>My Input</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@xx_matty_xx Justin Bieber]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/xx_matty_xx">@xx_matty_xx</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Not at all, this was a classic piece of work written by a classic member of the RSC community.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-input/542252/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-input/542252/4</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 17 Apr 2014 22:26:01 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-542252-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-input/542252.rss">My Input</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>My Input</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@KizL KizL]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/kizl">@KizL</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>RSCE is making a replica and it should be out within 2 weeks.</p>
<p>~K!zL</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-input/542252/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-input/542252/3</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 17 Apr 2014 20:44:34 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-542252-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-input/542252.rss">My Input</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>My Input</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Nothing1 -Nothing]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/nothing1">@Nothing1</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“Brownay01, post:1, topic:542252”]Reading over most of the threads in this forum has been pretty fun, and I must say that this community seems rather interesting. I don’t care what you do, I’ll always have the real RSC to play on. Sure, it’s filled with botters and just gets more and more lonely, but it’s like playing a 1 player RPG. I don’t mind it, and it always has been my favorite game. I’m here looking for some people to play a replica of my favorite game with, even if it’s not really a replica at all. You’re all just spending so much time worrying about what’ll happen, when we could be playing right now. Please, rather than debating on what you want in a RSC server, release it and make changes later. Don’t try to please the whole of the community, because like several people have said here, it’s impossible. The idiot Jagex staff at “OldSchool RuneScape” did pretty much everything the community wanted them to, and now it looks worse than a 15 year old’s RS2 server.</p>
<p>RSC was the best time of my life, and I wasn’t even around for the F2P days. I’d love to see what it was like, and you guys are about the only people who can show me. I played most of the RSC private servers. My favorites among them were <span class="bbcode-b">RSCAngel and ProjectP2P</span>[/quote]<br>
Yo brownay, I’m really happy for u and imma let you finish but RSCR was the best server of all time. Best server of ALL time.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-input/542252/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-input/542252/2</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 17 Apr 2014 17:13:15 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-542252-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-input/542252.rss">My Input</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>My Input</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Brownay01 Brownay01]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/brownay01">@Brownay01</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Reading over most of the threads in this forum has been pretty fun, and I must say that this community seems rather interesting. I don’t care what you do, I’ll always have the real RSC to play on. Sure, it’s filled with botters and just gets more and more lonely, but it’s like playing a 1 player RPG. I don’t mind it, and it always has been my favorite game. I’m here looking for some people to play a replica of my favorite game with, even if it’s not really a replica at all. You’re all just spending so much time worrying about what’ll happen, when we could be playing right now. Please, rather than debating on what you want in a RSC server, release it and make changes later. Don’t try to please the whole of the community, because like several people have said here, it’s impossible. The idiot Jagex staff at “OldSchool RuneScape” did pretty much everything the community wanted them to, and now it looks worse than a 15 year old’s RS2 server.</p>
<p>RSC was the best time of my life, and I wasn’t even around for the F2P days. I’d love to see what it was like, and you guys are about the only people who can show me. I played most of the RSC private servers. My favorites among them were RSCAngel and ProjectP2P, though no one played ProjectP2P really. I liked RSCE before they changed Edgeville and made it look retarded.</p>
<p>MoparScape has never let me down, I’ve come here for EVERYTHING since I found private servers around 2007 or so. The moment I heard about this section of the forums I started reading everything. I guess I got here a little late. I wish I could’ve been here to join all these lovely conversations.</p>
<p>Whether you want 1x XP, 3-4x XP or 30x, custom items and P2P mage arena PKing or F2P only, we can all have a final conversation regarding the future of this MoparClassic idea. I’ll donate if I can, as much as I need to. Let’s just not let this die, as RSC is quite lonely when you only have botters to speak to. The private servers out now are just terrible.</p>
<p>I apologise if my post comes off as immature, foolish or inexperienced. I have been playing RSC for most of my 18 year old life, and I have accepted that I’ll never be able to share the memories of old old RSC with you. Judging by some of your posts, some of you will obviously come right out and flame me. I don’t mind. &lt;3</p>
<p>I’m stupid when I’m tired anyway, so I know it’s a dumb post. Maybe I’ll edit it later.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-input/542252/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-input/542252/1</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 17 Apr 2014 13:00:24 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-542252-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-input/542252.rss">My Input</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
