<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Mangocraft</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/mangocraft/515147</link>
    <description>The IP is Mangocraft.a2g.gs

We are a uniquely created server known as &quot;MangoCraft&quot;, in which we allow freedom to the Minecraft Community striving to find &quot;That Perfect Server&quot;. Globally ranked as one of the top Minecraft servers available, we offer the perfect setting to ensure the optimum experience possible on a Minecraft server anywhere. Along with having a small army of staff ready for your service, we also offer a wide array of plugins and commands to choose from! When it comes to your protection and the security of your builds, it is literally impossible the to grief and get away with it. Also, to help meet your needs, we have a moderator ticked request system if you are ever in need of a moderator&#39;s assistance. 

If this seems at all appealing, come check us out :)</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 07 Apr 2013 07:24:44 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Minecraft</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/mangocraft/515147.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Mangocraft</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@noobs_are_ftw noobs are ftw]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/noobs_are_ftw">@noobs_are_ftw</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I prefer peaches</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/mangocraft/515147/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/mangocraft/515147/2</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 07 Apr 2013 07:24:44 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-515147-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/mangocraft/515147.rss">Mangocraft</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Mangocraft</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@luckynumber56 luckynumber56]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/luckynumber56">@luckynumber56</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>The IP is Mangocraft.a2g.gs</p>
<p>We are a uniquely created server known as “MangoCraft”, in which we allow freedom to the Minecraft Community striving to find “That Perfect Server”. Globally ranked as one of the top Minecraft servers available, we offer the perfect setting to ensure the optimum experience possible on a Minecraft server anywhere. Along with having a small army of staff ready for your service, we also offer a wide array of plugins and commands to choose from! When it comes to your protection and the security of your builds, it is literally impossible the to grief and get away with it. Also, to help meet your needs, we have a moderator ticked request system if you are ever in need of a moderator’s assistance.</p>
<p>If this seems at all appealing, come check us out <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=5" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/mangocraft/515147/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/mangocraft/515147/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 07 Apr 2013 03:46:38 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-515147-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/mangocraft/515147.rss">Mangocraft</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
