<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>I&#39;ve got a few questions</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/ive-got-a-few-questions/383594</link>
    <description>I plan on re-installing Linux for the umpteenth time soon, but I&#39;ve got a few questions first so that I don&#39;t have to restore my computer 3 times to fix everything that went wrong.
1. I&#39;ve got Linux 32-bit on a LiveCD and my computer is a 64-bit. Does it matter if I install Linux 32-bit on my 64-bit computer? Also, is there such thing as a 64-bit version of Linux?
2. I plan on installing Ubuntu, and all the times I had problems with my computer were because of something called GNOME. I am not familiar with it but it was always the source of my troubles and the reason I had to restore my computer many times. I want to keep my windows boot loader instead of GNOME taking over because over time I ended up getting a GNOME error 22 when ever I would boot up and so I&#39;d have to boot up from my Windows recovery disk. Can I install Ubuntu and not have GNOME go and fuck things up again?
That&#39;s all of the questions I have for now.. Except for this: Why should I use Linux? What are the benefits of it over Windows 7? On Linux, I could never open .mp3 files so I had to go to YouTube to listen to music, and WINE was a bitch to install and really didn&#39;t work too well.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 24 Feb 2011 15:47:16 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Technology</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/ive-got-a-few-questions/383594.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>I&#39;ve got a few questions</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@z z]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/z">@z</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I learned a new word today! Umpteenth!</p>
<p>On-topic:</p>
<ol>
<li>
<p>You can’t install a 64-bit operating system on a 32-bit architecture and yes, there is a 64-bit version of Linux. Be aware that sometimes the distribution of the 64-bit is called <span class="bbcode-b">amd64</span> rather than, what I prefer, <span class="bbcode-b">x86_64</span>. amd64 releases are <span class="bbcode-b">NOT</span> specifically for AMD processors, that is simply just the release name for the 64-bit release (i.e. ubuntu-10.10-desktop-amd64.iso).</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Ubuntu has a program called <a href="http://www.ubuntu.com/desktop/get-ubuntu/windows-installer" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">Wubi</a>, which allows you to “download Ubuntu Desktop Edition and run it alongside your current Windows system.” Download and run Wubi, boot into Ubuntu and then switch to KDE through the Synaptic Package Manager.</p>
</li>
</ol>
<ul>
<li>Go to: System -&gt; Administration -&gt; Synaptic Package Manager</li>
<li>Search for Kubuntu</li>
<li>Right click “kubuntu-desktop” then highlight “mark for installation”</li>
<li>Click apply and click OK a couple of times.</li>
<li>This will download and install all the packages for you.</li>
<li>Once this is done… and it could take a while.</li>
<li>Log out of Ubuntu.</li>
<li>At the login screen, select “options” (lower left hand corner).</li>
<li>Then pick “Sessions”</li>
<li>Choose KDE.</li>
</ul>
<p>Depending on which distribution you use, Linux can bring <a href="http://linux.about.com/od/embedded/l/blnewbie_0toc.htm" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">a lot of benefits</a>. When I installed Ubuntu onto my 10-year-old laptop, it gave me a lot of new benefits that Ubuntu previously hadn’t been capable of fulfilling, such as simple WiFi connectivity, full driver support and much more.</p>
<p>Hopefully you stick with Linux – a lot of people in this community like it. <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=5" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
<p>[size=8pt]Some text used from <a href="http://fixunix.com/ubuntu/396370-install-kde-using-wubi.html" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">here</a>.[/size]</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/ive-got-a-few-questions/383594/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/ive-got-a-few-questions/383594/4</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 24 Feb 2011 15:47:16 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-383594-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/ive-got-a-few-questions/383594.rss">I&#39;ve got a few questions</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>I&#39;ve got a few questions</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@The_Un-Named The Un-Named]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/the_un-named">@The_Un-Named</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote no-group" data-post="1" data-topic="383594">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/user_avatar/forum.moparisthebest.com/r0ckstar96/40/1423_1.png" class="avatar"> r0ckstar96:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Except for this: Why should I use Linux? What are the benefits of it over Windows 7?</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>if you dont have a problem with windows dont install linux, its that simple</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-post="1" data-topic="383594">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/user_avatar/forum.moparisthebest.com/r0ckstar96/40/1423_1.png" class="avatar"> r0ckstar96:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>On Linux, I could never open .mp3</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>google: “install x on y” where x is what you want to install and y is what distro you have(read:ubuntu), I guarantee there will be a guide for absolutely fucking everything</p>
<p>ps the reason things like mp3 and the libraries needed to unscramble dvds etc aren’t usually installed by default is because there is usually legal issues with releasing them with the os, however every distro has multiple guides and ways how to get them REALLY easily, for example on fedora:</p>
<p>su<br>
yum localinstall --nogpgcheck <a href="http://download1.rpmfusion.org/free/fedora/rpmfusion-free-release-stable.noarch.rpm" rel="nofollow noopener">http://download1.rpmfusion.org/free/fedora/rpmfusion-free-release-stable.noarch.rpm</a> <a href="http://download1.rpmfusion.org/nonfree/fedora/rpmfusion-nonfree-release-stable.noarch.rpm" rel="nofollow noopener">http://download1.rpmfusion.org/nonfree/fedora/rpmfusion-nonfree-release-stable.noarch.rpm</a><br>
rpm -ivh <a href="http://rpm.livna.org/livna-release.rpm" rel="nofollow noopener">http://rpm.livna.org/livna-release.rpm</a><br>
yum install gstreamer-plugins-ugly gstreamer-plugins-bad gstreamer-ffmpeg xine-lib-extras-freeworld libdvdcss</p>
<p>seem complicated? 5 second google search and a quick skim over 2 faqs…</p>
<p>pps when something goes wrong in linux, most cases you can fix it without ever having to reinstall the OS, but when you do reinstall enjoy 10 minute installs or 20 minute installs with every coded, library and software you ever use</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/ive-got-a-few-questions/383594/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/ive-got-a-few-questions/383594/3</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 23 Feb 2011 23:14:15 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-383594-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/ive-got-a-few-questions/383594.rss">I&#39;ve got a few questions</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>I&#39;ve got a few questions</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Greeny Greeny]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/greeny">@Greeny</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Well basically I can answer your questions but you’re an ignorant douche who blatantly hasn’t even tried to answer these things for himself.</p>
<ol>
<li>
<p>Of course there’s 64 bit linux.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Gnome is a desktop environment, grub is the bootloader to which you refer. Grub is far superior to the windows bootloader and doesn’t really have any issues or problems, so the problem here is you. Chances are you turn off without shutting down, because that in my experience is the most common way to fuck up a partition and get an error such as 22 (Error 22 is easy as shit to fix without having to reinstall anything, l2google).</p>
</li>
</ol>
<p>If you truly meant gnome was the problem, then use KDE or XFCE if you’re going with a *buntu. Otherwise try crunchbang because it uses openbox and I believe it outperforms the above.</p>
<p>Why should you use Linux? <a href="http://www.whylinuxisbetter.net/" rel="nofollow noopener">http://www.whylinuxisbetter.net/</a></p>
<p>Windows 7 is the best MS OS to date (IMO), it’s pretty damn good but still you can get so much more out of a customised Linux install. I only use windows for gaming. If I could get CS:S to run as smooth in linux as in windows, I wouldn’t even use windows at all. Plus you still have to pay for Windows 7, whereas most/all linux OSes are free.</p>
<p>Listening to MP3s is as easy as on windows, seems to me you really need to lookup package managers. Wine takes a single command to install (use your package manager!) and it has enough documentation like everything on Linux to get it working in no time.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/ive-got-a-few-questions/383594/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/ive-got-a-few-questions/383594/2</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 23 Feb 2011 14:12:24 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-383594-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/ive-got-a-few-questions/383594.rss">I&#39;ve got a few questions</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>I&#39;ve got a few questions</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@r0ckstar96 r0ckstar96]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/r0ckstar96">@r0ckstar96</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I plan on re-installing Linux for the umpteenth time soon, but I’ve got a few questions first so that I don’t have to restore my computer 3 times to fix everything that went wrong.</p>
<ol>
<li>I’ve got Linux 32-bit on a LiveCD and my computer is a 64-bit. Does it matter if I install Linux 32-bit on my 64-bit computer? Also, is there such thing as a 64-bit version of Linux?</li>
<li>I plan on installing Ubuntu, and all the times I had problems with my computer were because of something called GNOME. I am not familiar with it but it was always the source of my troubles and the reason I had to restore my computer many times. I want to keep my windows boot loader instead of GNOME taking over because over time I ended up getting a GNOME error 22 when ever I would boot up and so I’d have to boot up from my Windows recovery disk. Can I install Ubuntu and not have GNOME go and fuck things up again?<br>
That’s all of the questions I have for now… Except for this: Why should I use Linux? What are the benefits of it over Windows 7? On Linux, I could never open .mp3 files so I had to go to YouTube to listen to music, and WINE was a bitch to install and really didn’t work too well.</li>
</ol>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/ive-got-a-few-questions/383594/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/ive-got-a-few-questions/383594/1</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 23 Feb 2011 04:32:17 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-383594-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/ive-got-a-few-questions/383594.rss">I&#39;ve got a few questions</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
