<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>667+ Particles?</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/667-particles/543651</link>
    <description>I&#39;d like to know more about particles. The extent of my knowledge on them is only how to add them to a model.

What I&#39;d like to know about them includes:

How are they generated? 
Where do the &quot;patterns&quot; come from? (are they cache-based, or is it some Class, or is it completely separate?)
If they&#39;re cache-based, what index are they in?
How would I go about making custom patterns? (I might need to figure this one out myself once the others are answered)
I&#39;ve seen videos where a user can change the color of the pattern. How is THAT done? 
(note: when I say &quot;pattern&quot; I mean the way it moves (gravity, length of time shown, direction, etc.))

If anyone would help me find these answers, it&#39;d be really appreciated.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2014 06:26:40 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Game Development</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/667-particles/543651.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>667+ Particles?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@MeeE59 MeeE59]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/meee59">@MeeE59</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Alright, thanks. Any idea where they may be in the client and/or cache?</p>
<p>I don’t know if they’d be in a cache index, but I mean, it’s totally possible I assume. If it’s a simple .dat file that holds color info (probably a short, maybe 3 bytes to include alpha), gravity (probably a byte, with 7f being stationary, 00 being fastest upward and ff being fastest downward), texture id (some particles have texture, I guess), particle generation rate (no clue on this one) and number of particles allowed at a time (could be a short, up to 65535 particles at a time could get really laggy), maximum deviation from main direction (could be a byte), and direction (dunno about this), then I think I might be able to figure it out. Of course, these data structures are just guesses based on prior knowledge (mostly model formats of 317s). I haven’t done any searching through anything, so I’m probably not even close. I’m also extremely tired so if this seems like total gibberish it probably is.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/667-particles/543651/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/667-particles/543651/3</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2014 06:26:40 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-543651-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/667-particles/543651.rss">667+ Particles?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>667+ Particles?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Ashi Ashi]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/ashi">@Ashi</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>The “pattern” is a bunch of complicated maths. Look at openGL on how they’re made.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/667-particles/543651/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/667-particles/543651/2</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 04 Jun 2014 08:51:12 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-543651-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/667-particles/543651.rss">667+ Particles?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>667+ Particles?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@MeeE59 MeeE59]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/meee59">@MeeE59</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I’d like to know more about particles. The extent of my knowledge on them is only how to add them to a model.</p>
<p>What I’d like to know about them includes:</p>
<p>How are they generated?<br>
Where do the “patterns” come from? (are they cache-based, or is it some Class, or is it completely separate?)<br>
If they’re cache-based, what index are they in?<br>
How would I go about making custom patterns? (I might need to figure this one out myself once the others are answered)<br>
I’ve seen videos where a user can change the color of the pattern. How is THAT done?<br>
(note: when I say “pattern” I mean the way it moves (gravity, length of time shown, direction, etc.))</p>
<p>If anyone would help me find these answers, it’d be really appreciated.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/667-particles/543651/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/667-particles/543651/1</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 04 Jun 2014 08:46:45 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-543651-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/667-particles/543651.rss">667+ Particles?</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
