<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Project Plexity ~ 474 GameFrame</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/project-plexity-474-gameframe/547923</link>
    <description>[size=36pt][left]Project Plexity[/left][/size]

Project Plexity is a new PI in developement, Probably thinking &quot;Another pi :(&quot; Well i was thinking about quiting the developement of project plexity because of all the PI&#39;s out there but then i reliased why should i quit when i may have a chance to make a good server here!

My main goal for this server is to achieve an alright player base, I don&#39;t want to become the #1 striving server, Aslong as i get dedicated members/staff i&#39;ll be willing to keep this server up and running.

Some photos:
http://imgur.com/7hY5RRx

Thats the only picture i got at the moment because i started the developement late last night and i was only changing the name of everything and redoing the quest tab, Making it cleaner.

I&#39;m currently working on refixing on a new skilling area/training area/home area/donator island... Easy shit lol.
Hopefully you&#39;ll like watching this project go further! Please tell me what you think about it!


I started development late last night, And i redid the whole quest tab and made it look 10x cleaner then the original one, I redid the mage book quest, I added a christmas tree, And this morning i added a custom welcome screen in, and i&#39;m working on adding a little tutorial island where you speak to a npc and he&#39;ll help you and stuff and i worked on adding a few interfaces.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2014 19:31:26 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/project-plexity-474-gameframe/547923.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Project Plexity ~ 474 GameFrame</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Monthly1 Monthly-]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/monthly1">@Monthly1</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[size=36pt][left]Project Plexity[/left][/size]</p>
<p>Project Plexity is a new PI in developement, Probably thinking “Another pi :(” Well i was thinking about quiting the developement of project plexity because of all the PI’s out there but then i reliased why should i quit when i may have a chance to make a good server here!</p>
<p>My main goal for this server is to achieve an alright player base, I don’t want to become the <span class="hashtag">#1</span> striving server, Aslong as i get dedicated members/staff i’ll be willing to keep this server up and running.</p>
<p>Some photos:<br>
<a href="http://imgur.com/7hY5RRx" class="onebox" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">http://imgur.com/7hY5RRx</a></p>
<p>Thats the only picture i got at the moment because i started the developement late last night and i was only changing the name of everything and redoing the quest tab, Making it cleaner.</p>
<p>I’m currently working on refixing on a new skilling area/training area/home area/donator island… Easy shit lol.<br>
Hopefully you’ll like watching this project go further! Please tell me what you think about it!</p>
<p>I started development late last night, And i redid the whole quest tab and made it look 10x cleaner then the original one, I redid the mage book quest, I added a christmas tree, And this morning i added a custom welcome screen in, and i’m working on adding a little tutorial island where you speak to a npc and he’ll help you and stuff and i worked on adding a few interfaces.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/project-plexity-474-gameframe/547923/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/project-plexity-474-gameframe/547923/1</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2014 19:31:26 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-547923-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/project-plexity-474-gameframe/547923.rss">Project Plexity ~ 474 GameFrame</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
