<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Account Problems!</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/account-problems/331419</link>
    <description>My server is so close to being done, and ready to be put online for everyone.. Except a couple problems. 1, my new capes won&#39;t show up, instead they make me invisible, but I think I know why. Then the colored Santa hats won&#39;t work. (Still appear as null.) and then there is this:

I made my owner account, Mars Tattoo.
It works for about 8 hours, then it will freeze, I will then have to exit out, reopen.. When I go to log back in, it freezes at the black screen while saying &quot;Please Wait while loading...&quot;
Why does it do that? How can I fix it? I imagine it being some bug, but what bug, and how do I get rid of it.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 02 Mar 2010 22:01:54 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/account-problems/331419.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Account Problems!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Rawrock Rawrock]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/rawrock">@Rawrock</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>My server is so close to being done, and ready to be put online for everyone… Except a couple problems. 1, my new capes won’t show up, instead they make me invisible, but I think I know why. Then the colored Santa hats won’t work. (Still appear as null.) and then there is this:</p>
<p>I made my owner account, Mars Tattoo.<br>
It works for about 8 hours, then it will freeze, I will then have to exit out, reopen… When I go to log back in, it freezes at the black screen while saying “Please Wait while loading…”<br>
Why does it do that? How can I fix it? I imagine it being some bug, but what bug, and how do I get rid of it.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/account-problems/331419/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/account-problems/331419/1</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 02 Mar 2010 22:01:54 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-331419-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/account-problems/331419.rss">Account Problems!</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
