<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>I&#39;m back!</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/im-back/524181</link>
    <description>I started coding but was getting slow since i was getting bored and started playing a private server vicious revoulution but it soon had a pop eco reset last night, I had no clue what was going on since i was on a trip, which erase all accs in game and the accs on the forums.  I decided to quit the server because after spending 20+ hrs getting 99 dung it became a load of bullshit to start over, so decided to quit and to finish coding my two projects, StormyNight and my apocalypse server, which the apocalypse server would be release to the community and StormyNight would be publish as a online private server.

My eco reset: I decided for my eco resets no stats would be reset only bank, invent, and equipment. This eco reset wouldn&#39;t piss-off the people that spent hrs like me on a skill and have be reset...because personally i know getting money is the easy part in a private server, yet depending on xp rates you might get mad if there was a stat reset.


Now time for some updates

Right now StormyNight is being nerf in some departments such as xp rates and money gain from skills, thieving and mining, plus im moving stuff around at home. I&#39;m also redoing all the slayer task and plus a new slayer tower has been added. I&#39;m not going to get it online until i go through a test zone.

On the apocalypse server I just finish the starting area and have a good looking cache. right now im working on a quest where it would you go explore a mining area where you have to do something, haven&#39;t figure out what you have to do but found a pretty good place that looks like a abandon mine area.


After all this crap i decided to quit playing other peoples ps just to see that they will just let you down. This quote summerizes my feelings about what vr just did to me...i know eco happens to all servers but if you spend hours or even days on a server they  don&#39;t refund work you spend even if you donated no refunes theres no point in playing in them  :(
[img]http://izquotes.com/quotes-pictures/quote-if-you-want-a-thing-done-well-do-it-yourself-napoleon-bonaparte-20582.jpg[/img]

[size=18pt][i][b]I&#39;m back and more motivated better then ever[/b][/i][/size]</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2013 18:45:31 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/im-back/524181.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>I&#39;m back!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Angel_Carlos Angel Carlos]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/angel_carlos">@Angel_Carlos</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Good luck on your project, sir!!!</p>
<p>All wishes and lucks are with you!</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/im-back/524181/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/im-back/524181/2</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2013 18:45:31 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-524181-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/im-back/524181.rss">I&#39;m back!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>I&#39;m back!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@MrFun MrFun]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/mrfun">@MrFun</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I started coding but was getting slow since i was getting bored and started playing a private server vicious revoulution but it soon had a pop eco reset last night, I had no clue what was going on since i was on a trip, which erase all accs in game and the accs on the forums.  I decided to quit the server because after spending 20+ hrs getting 99 dung it became a load of bullshit to start over, so decided to quit and to finish coding my two projects, StormyNight and my apocalypse server, which the apocalypse server would be release to the community and StormyNight would be publish as a online private server.</p>
<p>My eco reset: I decided for my eco resets no stats would be reset only bank, invent, and equipment. This eco reset wouldn’t piss-off the people that spent hrs like me on a skill and have be reset…because personally i know getting money is the easy part in a private server, yet depending on xp rates you might get mad if there was a stat reset.</p>
<p>Now time for some updates</p>
<p>Right now StormyNight is being nerf in some departments such as xp rates and money gain from skills, thieving and mining, plus im moving stuff around at home. I’m also redoing all the slayer task and plus a new slayer tower has been added. I’m not going to get it online until i go through a test zone.</p>
<p>On the apocalypse server I just finish the starting area and have a good looking cache. right now im working on a quest where it would you go explore a mining area where you have to do something, haven’t figure out what you have to do but found a pretty good place that looks like a abandon mine area.</p>
<p>After all this crap i decided to quit playing other peoples ps just to see that they will just let you down. This quote summerizes my feelings about what vr just did to me…i know eco happens to all servers but if you spend hours or even days on a server they  don’t refund work you spend even if you donated no refunes theres no point in playing in them  <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/frowning.png?v=5" title=":frowning:" class="emoji" alt=":frowning:"><br>
<img src="http://izquotes.com/quotes-pictures/quote-if-you-want-a-thing-done-well-do-it-yourself-napoleon-bonaparte-20582.jpg" alt width="" height=""></p>
<p>[size=18pt]<span class="bbcode-i"><span class="bbcode-b">I’m back and more motivated better then ever</span></span>[/size]</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/im-back/524181/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/im-back/524181/1</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2013 16:23:55 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-524181-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/im-back/524181.rss">I&#39;m back!</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
