<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>[PI] Need help with Pk Points Shop [PI]</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/pi-need-help-with-pk-points-shop-pi/533821</link>
    <description>[center]Hey everyone, im working on a PI source and client... theres a pk point shop in it but the items all cost 0 PKP and im not sure how to fix this... im so new to making rsps&#39;s and a big time NOOB xD. wondering if anyone could help..[/center]
[left]I also need help with a couple other things... for example.. me and my friend are doing this together.. but we have to different computers.. us there anyway possible we can link up and do stuff in game together. to test things out within the game.... if anyone could help that would be awesome.... I have a texting app just for anyone tht could help me... so heres the number. 510-340-4374.[/left]
[right]I know most people want something in return for helping... but I legit have nothing right now... and this is something im doing in my spare time but I would really like to get it fully working and have it online sometime in the future.. so... yeah loll. ALL HELP IS VERY MUCH APPRECIATED. :)[/right]</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 07 Oct 2013 23:46:44 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/pi-need-help-with-pk-points-shop-pi/533821.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>[PI] Need help with Pk Points Shop [PI]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@ohokay ohokay]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/ohokay">@ohokay</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>That layout</p>
<p>ShopAssistant.java, find out where it’s checking the item prices. You could make a new method to give the prices.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/pi-need-help-with-pk-points-shop-pi/533821/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/pi-need-help-with-pk-points-shop-pi/533821/2</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 07 Oct 2013 23:46:44 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-533821-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/pi-need-help-with-pk-points-shop-pi/533821.rss">[PI] Need help with Pk Points Shop [PI]</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[PI] Need help with Pk Points Shop [PI]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@kil0hurtz kil0hurtz]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/kil0hurtz">@kil0hurtz</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[center]Hey everyone, im working on a PI source and client… theres a pk point shop in it but the items all cost 0 PKP and im not sure how to fix this… im so new to making rsps’s and a big time NOOB xD. wondering if anyone could help…[/center]<br>
[left]I also need help with a couple other things… for example… me and my friend are doing this together… but we have to different computers… us there anyway possible we can link up and do stuff in game together. to test things out within the game… if anyone could help that would be awesome… I have a texting app just for anyone tht could help me… so heres the number. 510-340-4374.[/left]<br>
[right]I know most people want something in return for helping… but I legit have nothing right now… and this is something im doing in my spare time but I would really like to get it fully working and have it online sometime in the future… so… yeah loll. ALL HELP IS VERY MUCH APPRECIATED. :)[/right]</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/pi-need-help-with-pk-points-shop-pi/533821/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/pi-need-help-with-pk-points-shop-pi/533821/1</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 07 Oct 2013 23:31:05 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-533821-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/pi-need-help-with-pk-points-shop-pi/533821.rss">[PI] Need help with Pk Points Shop [PI]</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
