<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Server ideas</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/server-ideas/453218</link>
    <description>I&#39;m hopefully releasing BETA soon for my project, Oberon. I will most likely remove some content before then due to the opinions of others when it comes to some key content. I know there are many topics that are asking for opinions about what a server should include, but I will make sure to keep it limited.

The most important thing that a server can offer is content. I know for a fact that my server will have features around the release of Godwars; however, I&#39;m still debating bosses like the Nex, Nomad, and things around that era.

Some things that I&#39;ll most likely include that don&#39;t really involve bosses are:

[ul][li]Overloads (Fully working potion creating; will be untradeable)[/li]
	[li]Chaotics (I don&#39;t really want to add Dungeoneering, so I&#39;m up for any ideas on how they should be obtained)[/li]
	[li]Summoning (Players will love this due to the ease of bossing and this will also boost the economy if my theory is correct)[/li]
	[li]100% Fight Caves (I&#39;ve done it on real RS and on a private server with all 63 waves and it was worth it; once you complete the fight caves once to gain the fire cape, you will then be able to do it again to gain the Tokhaar-kal cape)[/li][/ul]

I might update the above list more tomorrow, but for now just let me hear your thoughts about my idea for server content.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 07 Aug 2012 17:54:36 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/server-ideas/453218.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Server ideas</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Tutorial Tutorial]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/tutorial">@Tutorial</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I understand that chaotics and overloads really did change RS; however, it wasn’t just a bad change. Most likely, I’m going to make it to where chaotic weapons can only be used for PvM.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/server-ideas/453218/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/server-ideas/453218/4</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 07 Aug 2012 17:54:36 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-453218-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/server-ideas/453218.rss">Server ideas</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Server ideas</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@runescape_sucks runescape sucks]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/runescape_sucks">@runescape_sucks</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Summoning didn’t really destroy it.<br>
It’s kinda like if you fell off a mountain, summoning would be the place where you would might land and climb back up.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/server-ideas/453218/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/server-ideas/453218/3</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 07 Aug 2012 07:20:38 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-453218-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/server-ideas/453218.rss">Server ideas</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Server ideas</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Native1 Native^]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/native1">@Native1</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Eh? The first three ones are what destroyed runescape. No offense, but…</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/server-ideas/453218/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/server-ideas/453218/2</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 07 Aug 2012 07:05:25 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-453218-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/server-ideas/453218.rss">Server ideas</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Server ideas</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Tutorial Tutorial]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/tutorial">@Tutorial</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I’m hopefully releasing BETA soon for my project, Oberon. I will most likely remove some content before then due to the opinions of others when it comes to some key content. I know there are many topics that are asking for opinions about what a server should include, but I will make sure to keep it limited.</p>
<p>The most important thing that a server can offer is content. I know for a fact that my server will have features around the release of Godwars; however, I’m still debating bosses like the Nex, Nomad, and things around that era.</p>
<p>Some things that I’ll most likely include that don’t really involve bosses are:</p>
<p>[ul][li]Overloads (Fully working potion creating; will be untradeable)[/li]<br>
[li]Chaotics (I don’t really want to add Dungeoneering, so I’m up for any ideas on how they should be obtained)[/li]<br>
[li]Summoning (Players will love this due to the ease of bossing and this will also boost the economy if my theory is correct)[/li]<br>
[li]100% Fight Caves (I’ve done it on real RS and on a private server with all 63 waves and it was worth it; once you complete the fight caves once to gain the fire cape, you will then be able to do it again to gain the Tokhaar-kal cape)[/li][/ul]</p>
<p>I might update the above list more tomorrow, but for now just let me hear your thoughts about my idea for server content.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/server-ideas/453218/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/server-ideas/453218/1</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 07 Aug 2012 06:52:33 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-453218-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/server-ideas/453218.rss">Server ideas</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
