<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>My Third Website</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-third-website/247441</link>
    <description>Sorry about the website title, I never got to changing it and im to lazy to go back now, I made this one based off a tut i found, tell me what you think.

I did the coding myself, but the tut was for photoshop.

[url=http://wiebelhaus.ultb.net/website/]http://wiebelhaus.ultb.net/website/[/url][br][br][size=1]Posted on: November 29, 2008, 09:59:12 am[/size][hr]I never got around to Lorem yadda yadda ethier, I have to go somewhere soon and I got lazy</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 30 Nov 2008 01:33:32 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>General Programming</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-third-website/247441.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>My Third Website</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@mwiebelhaus mwiebelhaus]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/mwiebelhaus">@mwiebelhaus</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“FastBawlz, post:8, topic:247441”][quote author=mwiebelhaus link=topic=326434.msg2557829#msg2557829 date=1228006944]<br>
LMAO those are sure great sites, I hate all of them except this one.</p>
<p><a href="http://andyrutledge.com/" class="onebox" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">http://andyrutledge.com/</a><br>
[/quote]</p>
<p>So then what are you laughing at?[/quote]</p>
<p>Everything[br][br][size=1]Posted on: November 29, 2008, 07:50:55 pm[/size][hr][quote=“FastBawlz, post:8, topic:247441”][quote author=mwiebelhaus link=topic=326434.msg2557829#msg2557829 date=1228006944]<br>
LMAO those are sure great sites, I hate all of them except this one.</p>
<p><a href="http://andyrutledge.com/" class="onebox" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">http://andyrutledge.com/</a><br>
[/quote]</p>
<p>I take that back, like the design but hate the content he has, this one is better.</p>
<p><a href="http://sr28.com/" class="onebox" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">http://sr28.com/</a></p>
<p>So then what are you laughing at?[/quote]</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-third-website/247441/9">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-third-website/247441/9</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 30 Nov 2008 01:33:32 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-247441-9</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-third-website/247441.rss">My Third Website</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>My Third Website</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@FastBallz FastBawlz]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/fastballz">@FastBallz</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“mwiebelhaus, post:7, topic:247441”]LMAO those are sure great sites, I hate all of them except this one.</p>
<p><a href="http://andyrutledge.com/%5B/quote%5D" class="onebox" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">http://andyrutledge.com/[/quote]</a></p>
<p>So then what are you laughing at?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-third-website/247441/8">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-third-website/247441/8</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 30 Nov 2008 01:18:07 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-247441-8</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-third-website/247441.rss">My Third Website</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>My Third Website</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@mwiebelhaus mwiebelhaus]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/mwiebelhaus">@mwiebelhaus</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>LMAO those are sure great sites, I hate all of them except this one.</p>
<p><a href="http://andyrutledge.com/" class="onebox" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">http://andyrutledge.com/</a></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-third-website/247441/7">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-third-website/247441/7</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 30 Nov 2008 01:02:24 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-247441-7</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-third-website/247441.rss">My Third Website</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>My Third Website</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@FastBallz FastBawlz]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/fastballz">@FastBallz</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“mwiebelhaus, post:5, topic:247441”]Im thinking I should go to a real place for web design, since you guys really are fucking stupid.</p>
<p>I bet you hate this site too because rounded edges are so bad</p>
<aside class="onebox whitelistedgeneric">
  <header class="source">
      <img src="https://www.divx.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/12/cropped-DivX-icon_512_v2-32x32.png" class="site-icon" width="32" height="32">
      <a href="https://www.divx.com/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">DivX Video Software</a>
  </header>
  <article class="onebox-body">
    

<h3><a href="https://www.divx.com/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Play DivX files. Free Video Software to play, convert and cast video.</a></h3>

<p>Download free DivX Software to play, convert and cast video including DivX, AVI, MKV and HEVC files -- in up to 4K quality. Play DivX files everywhere.</p>


  </article>
  <div class="onebox-metadata">
    
    
  </div>
  <div style="clear: both"></div>
</aside>

<p>and this guy right?<br>
<a href="http://moparisthebest.org/smf/index.php/topic,326317.0.html%5B/quote%5D" class="onebox" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">http://moparisthebest.org/smf/index.php/topic,326317.0.html[/quote]</a></p>
<p>Calm down on the triple post man…<br>
I guess you haven’t figured it out yet, but its not so much the fact that you have rounded edges as it is the fact that thats the only thing you have. Get a bit of   variety, will you?</p>
<p>And it’s funny how you listed 2 sites designed by amateurs. DivX’s site isn’t that great design wise and SU’s is just an image.<br>
I guess you just haven’t seen some great website designs, like oh, I don’t know:</p>
<p><a href="http://alistapart.com/" class="onebox" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">http://alistapart.com/</a><br>
<a href="http://www.processtypefoundry.com/" class="onebox" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">http://www.processtypefoundry.com/</a><br>
<a href="http://sr28.com/" class="onebox" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">http://sr28.com/</a><br>
<a href="http://www.shauninman.com/" class="onebox" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">http://www.shauninman.com/</a><br>
<a href="http://www.designingthenews.com/" class="onebox" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">http://www.designingthenews.com/</a><br>
<a href="http://andyrutledge.com/" class="onebox" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">http://andyrutledge.com/</a><br>
<a href="http://ourtype.be/" class="onebox" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">http://ourtype.be/</a><br>
<a href="http://thethingswemake.co.uk/" class="onebox" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">http://thethingswemake.co.uk/</a></p>
<p>just to list a few…</p>
<p>P.S.: Take the sand out of your vagina.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-third-website/247441/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-third-website/247441/6</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 30 Nov 2008 00:54:05 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-247441-6</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-third-website/247441.rss">My Third Website</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>My Third Website</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@mwiebelhaus mwiebelhaus]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/mwiebelhaus">@mwiebelhaus</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Im thinking I should go to a real place for web design, since you guys really are fucking stupid.[br][br][size=1]Posted on: November 29, 2008, 06:17:24 pm[/size][hr]I bet you hate this site too because rounded edges are so bad</p>
<p><a href="http://www.divx.com/%5Bbr%5D%5Bbr%5D%5Bsize=1%5DPosted" rel="nofollow noopener">http://www.divx.com/[br][br][size=1]Posted</a> on: November 29, 2008, 06:38:33 pm[/size][hr]and this guy right?<br>
<a href="http://moparisthebest.org/smf/index.php/topic,326317.0.html" rel="nofollow noopener">http://moparisthebest.org/smf/index.php/topic,326317.0.html</a></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-third-website/247441/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-third-website/247441/5</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 30 Nov 2008 00:16:44 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-247441-5</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-third-website/247441.rss">My Third Website</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>My Third Website</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@ilyaostr9 io9]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/ilyaostr9">@ilyaostr9</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges rounded edges</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-third-website/247441/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-third-website/247441/4</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 29 Nov 2008 23:42:07 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-247441-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-third-website/247441.rss">My Third Website</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>My Third Website</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@I_james_I I james I]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/i_james_i">@I_james_I</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>The colours work very well!</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-third-website/247441/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-third-website/247441/3</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 29 Nov 2008 19:03:09 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-247441-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-third-website/247441.rss">My Third Website</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>My Third Website</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Server-Unknown.Net Server-Unknown.Net]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/server-unknown.net">@Server-Unknown.Net</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>NICE! You getting better everytime, I need to get photoshop to work on my computer but its acting funny &gt;_&gt; <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/frowning.png?v=6" title=":frowning:" class="emoji" alt=":frowning:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-third-website/247441/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-third-website/247441/2</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 29 Nov 2008 16:27:35 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-247441-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-third-website/247441.rss">My Third Website</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>My Third Website</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@mwiebelhaus mwiebelhaus]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/mwiebelhaus">@mwiebelhaus</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Sorry about the website title, I never got to changing it and im to lazy to go back now, I made this one based off a tut i found, tell me what you think.</p>
<p>I did the coding myself, but the tut was for photoshop.</p>
<p><a href="http://wiebelhaus.ultb.net/website/" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">http://wiebelhaus.ultb.net/website/</a>[br][br][size=1]Posted on: November 29, 2008, 09:59:12 am[/size][hr]I never got around to Lorem yadda yadda ethier, I have to go somewhere soon and I got lazy</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-third-website/247441/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-third-website/247441/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 29 Nov 2008 15:58:27 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-247441-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-third-website/247441.rss">My Third Website</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
