<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>ShockTurf 667/711 - Need someone for webclient/auto donations</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/shockturf-667-711-need-someone-for-webclient-auto-donations/448210</link>
    <description>This is an excellent server that is quickly unfolding. I have degrees in HTML, CSS, PHP, and MySQL. The four main languages in website design, I can do pretty much anything with website design, however, when it comes to java and implementing java with the website, I have troubles doing so. I need someone that knows how to do the java part of auto donations, and someone to do the webclient. A possible in-game status will be up for offer, or I can exchange for some of my services with website design, I&#39;ve done professional website design for six years, and created hundreds of website for games, charities, blogs, unions, small businesses, and more. I&#39;ve done website for about 8-10 servers, if you need one, maybe we can work something out. I&#39;m also good with graphics as it ties into website design, (I have a worker who has done GFX for eight years). However, i&#39;d recommend the in-game status as this server is going places for sure, the first six months of the server are pure profits as the VPS, website, and other expenses are paid off already. Plus we&#39;ve received a $70 donation, and the server hasn&#39;t even been put online to the public. 

So, if you can make a webclient for 667/711 OR help with an auto-donation system, and wouldn&#39;t mind helping in exchange for something, let me know by a comment, private message, or skype (username; aj.cordio).

Thanks to anyone that is taking up my offer and I&#39;ll talk to you ASAP after you contact me. - The Web Guy / AJ</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 07 Jul 2012 13:18:58 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/shockturf-667-711-need-someone-for-webclient-auto-donations/448210.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>ShockTurf 667/711 - Need someone for webclient/auto donations</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@gears2011 gears2011]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/gears2011">@gears2011</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>i can create the webclient and the auto-donate system <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=5" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/shockturf-667-711-need-someone-for-webclient-auto-donations/448210/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/shockturf-667-711-need-someone-for-webclient-auto-donations/448210/2</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 07 Jul 2012 13:18:58 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-448210-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/shockturf-667-711-need-someone-for-webclient-auto-donations/448210.rss">ShockTurf 667/711 - Need someone for webclient/auto donations</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>ShockTurf 667/711 - Need someone for webclient/auto donations</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@The_Web_Guy The Web Guy]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/the_web_guy">@The_Web_Guy</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>This is an excellent server that is quickly unfolding. I have degrees in HTML, CSS, PHP, and MySQL. The four main languages in website design, I can do pretty much anything with website design, however, when it comes to java and implementing java with the website, I have troubles doing so. I need someone that knows how to do the java part of auto donations, and someone to do the webclient. A possible in-game status will be up for offer, or I can exchange for some of my services with website design, I’ve done professional website design for six years, and created hundreds of website for games, charities, blogs, unions, small businesses, and more. I’ve done website for about 8-10 servers, if you need one, maybe we can work something out. I’m also good with graphics as it ties into website design, (I have a worker who has done GFX for eight years). However, i’d recommend the in-game status as this server is going places for sure, the first six months of the server are pure profits as the VPS, website, and other expenses are paid off already. Plus we’ve received a $70 donation, and the server hasn’t even been put online to the public.</p>
<p>So, if you can make a webclient for 667/711 OR help with an auto-donation system, and wouldn’t mind helping in exchange for something, let me know by a comment, private message, or skype (username; aj.cordio).</p>
<p>Thanks to anyone that is taking up my offer and I’ll talk to you ASAP after you contact me. - The Web Guy / AJ</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/shockturf-667-711-need-someone-for-webclient-auto-donations/448210/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/shockturf-667-711-need-someone-for-webclient-auto-donations/448210/1</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 04 Jul 2012 15:32:06 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-448210-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/shockturf-667-711-need-someone-for-webclient-auto-donations/448210.rss">ShockTurf 667/711 - Need someone for webclient/auto donations</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
