<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>[718] Memory Error</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/718-memory-error/539643</link>
    <description>So I&#39;ve run into a couple errors with Rune-Evolution 718. The server starts up fine, although this appears in the .bat file. 

[IMG]http://i.imgur.com/DYMP2QS.png[/img]

The client loads up fine but once it finishes loading and gets to the log-in screen it gets really laggy and almost freezes. I can manage to log-in but like I said it&#39;s really laggy and almost freezes.

I ran the server in Eclipse and a few errors appeared. I was wondering if they had anything to do with this lag? This is the only server I&#39;ve experienced this much lag so it&#39;s not my computer.

These are the errors: (I&#39;m pretty sure they have something to do with it because of how much memory is being used when it shouldn&#39;t be). If someone could help me find the problem that would be awesome :). Thanks. Note, I&#39;m new to this so I&#39;m not exactly sure how I would start fixing this. I&#39;ve been at it for awhile.

[IMG]http://i.imgur.com/wGkfJzw.png[/img]
[IMG]http://i.imgur.com/BBsGqev.png[/img]
[IMG]http://i.imgur.com/MTAFiWC.png[/img]
[IMG]http://i.imgur.com/75pjH40.png[/img]</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2014 06:44:13 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/718-memory-error/539643.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>[718] Memory Error</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Crucifyyy Crucifyyy]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/crucifyyy">@Crucifyyy</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>So I’ve run into a couple errors with Rune-Evolution 718. The server starts up fine, although this appears in the .bat file.</p>
<p><img src="http://i.imgur.com/DYMP2QS.png" alt width="" height=""></p>
<p>The client loads up fine but once it finishes loading and gets to the log-in screen it gets really laggy and almost freezes. I can manage to log-in but like I said it’s really laggy and almost freezes.</p>
<p>I ran the server in Eclipse and a few errors appeared. I was wondering if they had anything to do with this lag? This is the only server I’ve experienced this much lag so it’s not my computer.</p>
<p>These are the errors: (I’m pretty sure they have something to do with it because of how much memory is being used when it shouldn’t be). If someone could help me find the problem that would be awesome :). Thanks. Note, I’m new to this so I’m not exactly sure how I would start fixing this. I’ve been at it for awhile.</p>
<p><img src="http://i.imgur.com/wGkfJzw.png" alt width="" height=""><br>
<img src="http://i.imgur.com/BBsGqev.png" alt width="" height=""><br>
<img src="http://i.imgur.com/MTAFiWC.png" alt width="" height=""><br>
<img src="http://i.imgur.com/75pjH40.png" alt width="" height=""></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/718-memory-error/539643/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/718-memory-error/539643/1</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2014 06:44:13 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-539643-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/718-memory-error/539643.rss">[718] Memory Error</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
