<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Question about Deobfuscation and BCEL</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/question-about-deobfuscation-and-bcel/510418</link>
    <description>So I&#39;ve been reading up on BCEL, and client hacking and think i have a pretty good understanding of the basics. I think I am missing something though..

Runescape code is obfuscated, but even deobfuscated versions of the code are completely a mystery to me. In the BCEL tutorials there were some lines like &quot;In the 504 version we know ca.p is for baseX&quot; and it&#39;s just glossed over. It seems to me like that is a HUGE part of using BCEL to inject. Knowing what code is what. The question is HOW do I know? Even deobfuscated the code just looks like &quot;anInt559&quot; etc etc.. which doesnt help me at all. 

How do i tell what part of the client is what since its obfuscated? Is there is version of the code from the time period that 07scape is running on which is less ambigious? If not how do i take the obfuscated(or deobfuscated) code and make sense of it. What am I missing here? I would really love some help with this.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2013 07:26:43 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/question-about-deobfuscation-and-bcel/510418.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Question about Deobfuscation and BCEL</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Ollie Ollie]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/ollie">@Ollie</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Thats the fun part - working out what bits do.</p>
<p>Look for patterns in the code which give you clues, you are then able to write programs to help in aid of searching over client revisions.</p>
<p>If you’re looking for a simple, straight answer - there isn’t one.</p>
<p>EDIT: If you are wanting some concepts which have already been implemented in the old client then maybe take a look at private servers and their respective clients, they kind of give you a insight into how things work. I know winterLove’s work on the private server and its client made runescape cheating/hacking so popular back in the day. He had a near-full refactored client (supposedly, says semaphore) which I am probably inclined to believe, so any work of his has some merit.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/question-about-deobfuscation-and-bcel/510418/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/question-about-deobfuscation-and-bcel/510418/2</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2013 07:26:43 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-510418-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/question-about-deobfuscation-and-bcel/510418.rss">Question about Deobfuscation and BCEL</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Question about Deobfuscation and BCEL</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Logistician Logistician]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/logistician">@Logistician</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>So I’ve been reading up on BCEL, and client hacking and think i have a pretty good understanding of the basics. I think I am missing something though…</p>
<p>Runescape code is obfuscated, but even deobfuscated versions of the code are completely a mystery to me. In the BCEL tutorials there were some lines like “In the 504 version we know ca.p is for baseX” and it’s just glossed over. It seems to me like that is a HUGE part of using BCEL to inject. Knowing what code is what. The question is HOW do I know? Even deobfuscated the code just looks like “anInt559” etc etc… which doesnt help me at all.</p>
<p>How do i tell what part of the client is what since its obfuscated? Is there is version of the code from the time period that 07scape is running on which is less ambigious? If not how do i take the obfuscated(or deobfuscated) code and make sense of it. What am I missing here? I would really love some help with this.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/question-about-deobfuscation-and-bcel/510418/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/question-about-deobfuscation-and-bcel/510418/1</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2013 01:34:40 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-510418-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/question-about-deobfuscation-and-bcel/510418.rss">Question about Deobfuscation and BCEL</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
