<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>I need Help Getting Unbanned(Pics)</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/i-need-help-getting-unbanned-pics/160090</link>
    <description>Okay,Jagex actually accepted my query to &quot;Recover a locked account&quot;!
But,I came to see that I&#39;m banned when I try to log in.
I need tips on what to say to them for each rule I broke-It would be terribly appreciated.

[b]Rule Numbers# Broken:[/b]
Rule 1
Rule 3
Rule 6
--------------------------------------------
I sent in an apology For the First Offence,I hope they at least accept that one.And this is the first time I commited an offence,I got them all at the same time =[

[URL=http://imageshack.us][IMG]http://img401.imageshack.us/img401/7357/awwfuckhw3.png[/img][/URL]</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2007 11:31:33 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/i-need-help-getting-unbanned-pics/160090.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>I need Help Getting Unbanned(Pics)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@bubbagump bubbagump]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/bubbagump">@bubbagump</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Erm, I think you got some of that from Zybez…btw, proper grammar means capitalization and stuff…so fix allt eh I’s and stuff…</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/i-need-help-getting-unbanned-pics/160090/12">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/i-need-help-getting-unbanned-pics/160090/12</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2007 11:31:33 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-160090-12</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/i-need-help-getting-unbanned-pics/160090.rss">I need Help Getting Unbanned(Pics)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>I need Help Getting Unbanned(Pics)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@bobby Bobby]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/bobby">@bobby</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>try <a href="http://sythe.org" rel="nofollow noopener">sythe.org</a> they deal with this stuff, i belive</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/i-need-help-getting-unbanned-pics/160090/11">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/i-need-help-getting-unbanned-pics/160090/11</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 24 Nov 2007 11:34:38 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-160090-11</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/i-need-help-getting-unbanned-pics/160090.rss">I need Help Getting Unbanned(Pics)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>I need Help Getting Unbanned(Pics)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Thebeanie TheBeanie]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/thebeanie">@Thebeanie</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>rs- no one cars your accounts got locked, the sticky means that “we dont care so dont post them”</p>
<p>Meaning, Dont post “i got banned threads”</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/i-need-help-getting-unbanned-pics/160090/10">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/i-need-help-getting-unbanned-pics/160090/10</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 24 Nov 2007 09:15:22 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-160090-10</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/i-need-help-getting-unbanned-pics/160090.rss">I need Help Getting Unbanned(Pics)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>I need Help Getting Unbanned(Pics)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@rs_w00dcut rs w00dcut]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/rs_w00dcut">@rs_w00dcut</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Thanks Kando,i’ll try it.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/i-need-help-getting-unbanned-pics/160090/9">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/i-need-help-getting-unbanned-pics/160090/9</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 24 Nov 2007 06:28:17 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-160090-9</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/i-need-help-getting-unbanned-pics/160090.rss">I need Help Getting Unbanned(Pics)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>I need Help Getting Unbanned(Pics)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@kando2 kando2]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/kando2">@kando2</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Ban Appeals - Get Your Ban Appeals Here!</p>
<p>Rule <span class="hashtag">#1</span>, Offensive Language.</p>
<p>Rule <span class="hashtag">#1</span>, Offensive Language</p>
<p>Code:<br>
Dear, Jagex</p>
<p>I’m sorry for what i’ve done. I know it was wrong and feel terrible towards the user i abused. If you decide to just give me a warning on this i would be grateful and can assure you nothing like this will occurr again. I feel it’s my duty to apologize to the user i abused as i may have hurt their feelings, and made them upset. I know i wouldn’t like to be spoken to in the way i did.Rule <span class="hashtag">#2</span>, Item Scamming.</p>
<p>Code:<br>
Dear, Jagex</p>
<p>I’m terribly sorry for trying to do this, i know it was wrong but it got the better of my everyone was doing it, so i thought i would give it ago. I’ve totally learnt my lesson and won’t even think of trying this again. Please keep in mind that i only tried to scam, i didn’t actually scam anyone but i know that doesn’t justify anything and i was in the wrong.</p>
<p>Thank You.Rule <span class="hashtag">#3</span>, Password Scamming.</p>
<p>Dear Jagex</p>
<p>Jagex i didn’t do anything wrong. Someone has been logging onto my account everyday for the last month or so. But they can’t guess my bank pin. Every time i log in my bank pin has tryed to be deleted. I keep changing my password but they keep guessing it. I’ve scanned my computer and it has no viruses please help. And please don’t add to the situation by banning me =(</p>
<p>Thank You.</p>
<p>Rule <span class="hashtag">#4</span>, Bug Abuse.</p>
<p>Code:<br>
Dear, Jagex</p>
<p>I’m sorry for doing this but i think it was a mis-understanding, i come across that bug accidently. and i was so excited of what i did i tried to do it again, but it didn’t work. I was trying to figure out how i did it exactly but i couldn’t re-do it. so i am sorry for doing it although it was an accident and i couldn’t repeat it, and i gained nothing out of it.</p>
<p>Thank You.Rule <span class="hashtag">#5</span>, Jagex Staff Imperonsation.</p>
<p>Code:<br>
Dear, Jagex</p>
<p>I’m sorry for impersonating you but it was only as a joke and i was being sarcastic i can’t express that enough. I guess ill think again before trying to express sarcasm over the internet. i hope you see that this was a mis-understanding and won’t happen again. i was also talking to my real life friend in game not anyone else, next time i guess ill use the ‘P.M’.</p>
<p>Thank you.Rule <span class="hashtag">#6</span>, Account Sharing / Trading.</p>
<p>Code:<br>
Dear, Jagex</p>
<p>I’m sorry, i didn’t know this was a bannable offence or even illegal for that matter. I’m not a rule breaker and always abide by your rules you set (well i thought i did until now). He was my best mate and wanted to have ago while he was at my house so being a good friend i let him. Now that i know that this isn’t allowed i assure you it won’t happen again.</p>
<p>Thank You.Rule <span class="hashtag">#7</span>, Macroing.</p>
<p>Code:<br>
Dear, Customer Service</p>
<p>I don’t know how I got banned for this, but please, I enjoy playing runescape and If I’ve done something wrong I’m sorry. I think you have made a slight mistake, I would never do anything wrong that stops me from enjoying an entertaining and fun online game such as this one. Please, I would very much like to play runescape again.</p>
<p>Thank You.Rule <span class="hashtag">#8</span>, Multiple Logging In.</p>
<p>Code:<br>
Dear, Jagex</p>
<p>I’m sorry, i didn’t know this was a bannable offence or even illegal for that matter. I’m not a rule breaker and always abide by your rules you set (well i thought i did until now). I have re-read your rules as you requested and now realize that it was wrong to interact in any way between my acounts. I will promise you that you will not have to deal with me again.</p>
<p>Thank You.Rule <span class="hashtag">#9</span>, Encouraging Other to Break Rules.</p>
<p>Code:<br>
Dear, Jagex</p>
<p>Jagex, im sincerely sorry for causing this trouble, i didn’t to encourage her to break the rules and i hope she didn’t. I was only joking around and when i said that it was meant to be sarcastic not meaningful. I now realize how this could be taken the wrong way and apologize for the trouble i have caused.</p>
<p>Thank You.Rule <span class="hashtag">#10</span>, Misuse of Customer Support.</p>
<p>Code:<br>
Dear Jagex</p>
<p>Sorry jagex, but i was just making sure you got the report so i sent it afew times, then my mate told me about it only takes the last 60 seconds of chat. so it wouldn’t have anything incriminating in it about the person i was reporting and you would have seen it as spam. I’m terribly sorry for causing all this extra work for you, and i was only trying to help.</p>
<p>Thank You.Rule <span class="hashtag">#11</span>, Advertising / Website.</p>
<p>Code:<br>
Dear Jagex</p>
<p>I’m sorry jagex, but she wanted to know a good runescape help site. So i was trying to help her out, its a well known fan site and isn’t a scam site i go to it myself regularly. But as the rules state it is an offence and i knew that. I’m sorry for this and hope you understand and just give me a warning. I look forward to hearing from you. <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=6" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
<p>Thank You.Rule <span class="hashtag">#12</span>, Real World Item Trading.</p>
<p>Code:<br>
Dear Jagex</p>
<p>Sorry jagex, this is just a mis-understanding. I was talking to my brother about ebay, he is buying his girlfriend a really nice 2nd hand car for her 18th birthday amd he was giving me the sellers details so i could transfer the money over to his ebay account. I know runescape isn’t the place to discuss this and it will not happen again i assure you.</p>
<p>Thank You.Rule <span class="hashtag">#13</span>, Asking for Personal Details.</p>
<p>Code:<br>
Dear Jagex</p>
<p>Jagex what did i do wrong? She asked me for my email so she could add me on msn, and in return i asked for hers. I think its a bit unfair as i was (in a way) tricked into breaking this rule. I didn’t go out of my way to ask for her details i was being polite and responding to her. I love playing runescape and wouldn’t knowingly break your rules. Sorry.</p>
<p>Thank You.Last Chance Appeal.</p>
<p>Code:<br>
Dear Jagex</p>
<p>I’m terribly sorry for the mistakes i have made on my account in the past, i love playing runescape and now that i’m at risk of losing my account i realise how i have behaved was inappropriate and irresponsible. I promise if you give me 1 last chance i will straighten up. I love runescape and won’t do anything that will put my account in jeopardy again.</p>
<p>Thanks Jagex.<br>
Global Appeal, Claiming you got hacked.</p>
<p>When you send in this appeal, go to your friends house or your local library to send it in, this appeal MUST have a different IP to what you lasted logged in with for it to work. It can be used on all offences.</p>
<p>Code:<br>
Dear, Jagex</p>
<p>I did not commit this offence, I think i was hacked last night. i think i know who did it, my friend tinanti gave me a program over msn. He told me it would give me 99 in all skills, so i tried to use it but it said i wasn’t authorized or something. I logged in this morning and i had no items worth over 10k in my bank, im really upset and thinking of quitting now.</p>
<p>Thank You.Or</p>
<p>Code:<br>
Dear Jagex<br>
I didn’t commit this offence i got an email from you about how your database was comprimised and you asked me to send you my username and password do you could secure my account. I guess you didn’t get to secure my account fast enough before the hacker got it. I apologise for not sending you the information sooner.</p>
<p>Thank You.There comes a time in some players lives, that they receive a black mark, a mute, or even a ban. While this may be the players fault, or someone else on the character, Jagex need to know. And this guide, can, and has, appeal Jagex decisions. This has helped me, and many friends out of tight spaces when something bad happened. I shall cover all cases of appealing bans, from apology, to evidence.</p>
<p>What this guide will do:<br>
:; Teach constructive argument.<br>
:; Gain an understanding of Jagex’s methods.<br>
:; Help an appeal to be successful.</p>
<p>What this guide will not do:<br>
:; Encourage you to lie.<br>
:; Trick Jagex.<br>
:; Successfully appeal bans where you are totally in the wrong.</p>
<p>:; 1: What was the reason for punishment.</p>
<p>First and foremost, there is always a reason. Even if you don’t understand how Jagex made that conclusion, it’s still important to know what you did wrong, for you to lodge an appeal. Check the evidence given, the rule you broke in the Knowledge Base (or Forum Rules). Know the rule, know what happened. If it is Autoing, payment issues, or real world trading, no evidence will be provided. If it is advertising, offensive language, or any chat based rule, you will be given evidence. Evidence is shown as your own chat, and other chat with players names censored out. This is important.</p>
<p>:; 2: Were you punished for no reason.</p>
<p>This is a common problem, and is easily fixable. What people do, is report for no reason, or report the wrong person by mistake. This is easily correctable, and asking Jagex to evaluate the chat to check reasons in it works very well. Be careful though, check the text thoroughly. If you did say something, you’ll be shown up as a liar and Jagex will, most likely, unapprove your appeal. If nothing has gone amiss, all should be OK. Explain to them carefully, and use witnesses as evidence.</p>
<p>Chance of success: 5/5.</p>
<p>:; 3: Were you punished for the wrong reason.</p>
<p>This happens, quite commonly, because the reporter, moderator, or Jagex misunderstand what has been said. This could be when naming a player with a suspect name, or a even a typo. There is two things that can be done. You can take the ‘You accused me wrongly’ stance, which is a risky prospect. Being arrogant will not be advisable. You can also apologise about the mistake and promise to be more careful. This is much better, and an understanding moderator should take this into consideration.</p>
<p>Chance of success: 4/5.</p>
<p>:; 4: Were you punished for a valid reason.</p>
<p>If this happens, the chances of being unbanned is extremely unlikely. Depending on the severity of the case. Autoing, real world trading, and advertising bad websites is an automatic denial. Offensive language or something like that, if the circumstances are odd, can get a sympathy vote, if apologising. Lying to get unbanned never works. Jagex run the game, they have access to everything. A liar will never get away with it, and if he manages to, he will always be found out. Fighting back is unadvised. Apology is the only real way to get anywhere.</p>
<p>Chance of success: 1/5.</p>
<p>:; 5: Tips and Tricks.</p>
<p>:; Jagex does read every appeal, but does give stock answers.<br>
:; Proper grammar will always get better results.<br>
:; Work with Jagex, not against them.<br>
:; Never lie. Admit mistakes.<br>
:; Having a good history helps, so report offenders wherever possible.<br>
:; Never threaten, they’ve heard it all before.<br>
:; Plan, spend at least an hour writing the appeal, you only get 400 letters to appeal a case.<br>
:; Never break the rules in the first place.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/i-need-help-getting-unbanned-pics/160090/8">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/i-need-help-getting-unbanned-pics/160090/8</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 24 Nov 2007 06:15:42 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-160090-8</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/i-need-help-getting-unbanned-pics/160090.rss">I need Help Getting Unbanned(Pics)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>I need Help Getting Unbanned(Pics)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@rs_w00dcut rs w00dcut]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/rs_w00dcut">@rs_w00dcut</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Yeah,I appealed all of the rule <span class="hashtag">#3</span>’s and <span class="hashtag">#6</span>’s.<br>
My last rules to appeal are all rule# 1’s,Any help on that?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/i-need-help-getting-unbanned-pics/160090/7">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/i-need-help-getting-unbanned-pics/160090/7</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 24 Nov 2007 06:15:25 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-160090-7</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/i-need-help-getting-unbanned-pics/160090.rss">I need Help Getting Unbanned(Pics)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>I need Help Getting Unbanned(Pics)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Sick_of_Air Sick of Air]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/sick_of_air">@Sick_of_Air</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Just come up with some excuses. It worked on me. For example, me and my cousin shared an account at one time, and Jagex, seeing two IPs from the same account, locked my account for account sharing. I just told them I used two different computers and they believed me xD</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/i-need-help-getting-unbanned-pics/160090/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/i-need-help-getting-unbanned-pics/160090/6</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 24 Nov 2007 06:11:36 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-160090-6</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/i-need-help-getting-unbanned-pics/160090.rss">I need Help Getting Unbanned(Pics)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>I need Help Getting Unbanned(Pics)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@rs_w00dcut rs w00dcut]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/rs_w00dcut">@rs_w00dcut</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“Sick of Air, post:4, topic:160090”]<a href="http://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php/topic,2997.0.html%5B/quote%5DI'm" rel="nofollow noopener">http://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php/topic,2997.0.html[/quote]I’m</a> Not complaining I’m banned,I’m clearly asking for Help or an Explanation On how to Get Unbanned and get Jagex to accept my apology</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/i-need-help-getting-unbanned-pics/160090/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/i-need-help-getting-unbanned-pics/160090/5</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 24 Nov 2007 06:09:20 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-160090-5</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/i-need-help-getting-unbanned-pics/160090.rss">I need Help Getting Unbanned(Pics)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>I need Help Getting Unbanned(Pics)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Sick_of_Air Sick of Air]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/sick_of_air">@Sick_of_Air</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p><a href="http://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php/topic,2997.0.html" class="onebox" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">http://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php/topic,2997.0.html</a></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/i-need-help-getting-unbanned-pics/160090/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/i-need-help-getting-unbanned-pics/160090/4</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 24 Nov 2007 06:06:54 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-160090-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/i-need-help-getting-unbanned-pics/160090.rss">I need Help Getting Unbanned(Pics)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>I need Help Getting Unbanned(Pics)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@rs_w00dcut rs w00dcut]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/rs_w00dcut">@rs_w00dcut</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“Casey., post:2, topic:160090”]Apology’s do nothing mate.[/quote]Yes they do,They’ve gotten about 5 of my accounts Un banned.<br>
They do something trust me</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/i-need-help-getting-unbanned-pics/160090/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/i-need-help-getting-unbanned-pics/160090/3</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 24 Nov 2007 06:05:36 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-160090-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/i-need-help-getting-unbanned-pics/160090.rss">I need Help Getting Unbanned(Pics)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>I need Help Getting Unbanned(Pics)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@gothic_queen casey.]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/gothic_queen">@gothic_queen</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Apology’s do nothing mate.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/i-need-help-getting-unbanned-pics/160090/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/i-need-help-getting-unbanned-pics/160090/2</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 24 Nov 2007 06:00:32 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-160090-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/i-need-help-getting-unbanned-pics/160090.rss">I need Help Getting Unbanned(Pics)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>I need Help Getting Unbanned(Pics)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@rs_w00dcut rs w00dcut]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/rs_w00dcut">@rs_w00dcut</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Okay,Jagex actually accepted my query to “Recover a locked account”!<br>
But,I came to see that I’m banned when I try to log in.<br>
I need tips on what to say to them for each rule I broke-It would be terribly appreciated.</p>
<h2>
<span class="bbcode-b">Rule Numbers# Broken:</span><br>
Rule 1<br>
Rule 3<br>
Rule 6</h2>
<p>I sent in an apology For the First Offence,I hope they at least accept that one.And this is the first time I commited an offence,I got them all at the same time =[</p>
<p><a href="http://imageshack.us" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener"><img src="http://img401.imageshack.us/img401/7357/awwfuckhw3.png" alt width="" height=""></a></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/i-need-help-getting-unbanned-pics/160090/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/i-need-help-getting-unbanned-pics/160090/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 24 Nov 2007 05:57:12 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-160090-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/i-need-help-getting-unbanned-pics/160090.rss">I need Help Getting Unbanned(Pics)</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
