<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Pokemon ranger walkthrough</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/pokemon-ranger-walkthrough/115823</link>
    <description>-----------------------------------------------------------
1~. Controls
    1.1~. Menus
    1.2~. Initial Notes
    1.3~. Pokemon Type
    1.4~. Mini-games
2~. Walkthrough
    2.1~. Ring Town
    2.2~. Your first mission
    2.3~. Ring Town
    2.4~. Mission 1
    2.5~. Fall City
    2.6~. Mission 2
    2.7~. Fall City
    2.8~. Mission 3
    2.9~. Fall City
    2.10~. Summer Town
    2.11~. Mission 4
    2.12~. Summer Town
    2.13~. Fall City
    2.14~. Mission 5
    2.15~. Ring Town
    2.16~. Mission 6
    2.17~. Ring Town
    2.18~. Summer Town
    2.19~. New mission
    2.20~. Yet another mission
    2.21~. Summer Town
    2.22~. Fall City
    2.23~. Mission 7
    2.24~. Fall City
    2.25~. Summer Town
    2.26~. Another mission
    2.27~. Summer Town
    2.28~. Mission 8
    2.29~. Win Town
    2.30~. Mission 9
    2.31~. Win Town
    2.32~. Mission 10
3~. What now?
    3.1~. Fall City
    3.2~. Extra Mission 1
    3.3~. Fall City
    3.4~. Ring Town
    3.5~. Summer Town
    3.6~. Extra Mission 2
    3.7~. Summer Town
    3.8~. Win Town
    3.9~. Extra Mission 3
    3.10~. Win Town
    3.11~. Special Missions
        3.11.1~. Special Mission 1 (Deoxys)
        3.11.2~. Special Mission 2 (Celebi)
        3.11.3~. Special Mission 3 (Mew)
        3.11.4~. Special Mission 4 (Manaphy&#39;s Egg)
4~. Acquirable Pokemon and their moves
5~. Frequently Asked Questions
-----------------------------------------------------------




1~. Controls

While controls for most handheld gaming systems are usually quite easy to
master, I can&#39;t say the same thing about the ones in this console. I will
try to provide as much information about them as possible, and I hope you
find it easy to comprehend.

UP       - moves the character up, moves up on menus
DOWN     - moves the character down, moves down on menus
LEFT     - moves the character left, moves to the left on menus
RIGHT    - moves the character right, moves to the right on menus
A        - interact with someone, selects YES in binary options
B        - exits in a menu, selects NO in binary options
X        - in the field, selects all your pokemon
Y        - in the field, selects all your pokemon
L        - isn&#39;t used
R        - isn&#39;t used
START    - summons (and makes it disapper) the menu, while in the field
SELECT   - isn&#39;t used

Now, the main problem (and yet, one of the most important features) in
this game turns out being the lower, tactile, screen of this game. You
will obviously need to use it several times during your adventure, and
while few of the functions are available initially, others will also be
unlocked automatically, as you advance further in the game. So, eventually
you will discover that the lower screen of the console can be used to:

- Move your character (you simply need to have your stylus pointed at the
  direction you wish to take) and talk to other characters (simply tap
  them with your stylus).

In battles, you can use it to:

- Draw closed lines around your opponent, which makes it HP go down by 1.
  Keep on doing it until the HP is below 1, in order to gain extra EXP
  points after the end of the battle. Do you see the green/red numbers?
  Those are the points you will win after the battle;

- Tap the blue area on the lower right corner, to make one of your current
  pokemons usable in the battle. Their effects largely depend on what
  pokemon you select, but such thematic will be further developed in the
  &quot;Pokemon Type&quot; section of this guide;

- By &quot;capturing&quot; a Pokemon when its HP isn&#39;t below 1, you&#39;ll see a blue
  area appearing on the lower left corner of the screen. Such option will
  only be available sometimes and it allows you to run away from your
  current battle, something that you should use if you are into trouble.

That&#39;s basically it, for this section...


1.1~. Menus

When you first start the game, you will see two options, they are:

New Game
Options

Well, all of those are quite understandable... in case you are wondering
about the &quot;Options&quot; menu, it only contain two options, the first one being
something I don&#39;t fully understand and the second one simply allowing you
to change the background image some of the menus. However, after first
saving your game, the layout will be changed to the following one:


::::::::::::::
:: Continue ::
:: New Game ::
:: Options  ::
::::::::::::::

Easy, hum?
Well, there is simply another menu requiring explanation in this game, and
that turns out being menu that will appear after pressing START. However,
don&#39;t forget that such menu will only appear after a certain part of the
game, slightly before getting your first mission. That menu will usually
ook like this (and no, this isn&#39;t an accurate translation, it&#39;s just my
interpretation of it), but in case you aren&#39;t in the middle of a mission,
its layout will slightly change:

                  Pokemon
       Mission               Tutorials
Map                                       Encyclopedia
       Options               Quick Save
                  Exit

&quot;Pokemon&quot; is the place where you can head to check information about those
pokemon that you have currently in your party.

&quot;Mission&quot; generally allows you to check the information about the mission
you are currently playing. Obviously, in case you aren&#39;t in the middle of
a mission, this option won&#39;t be seen in the menu.

&quot;Tutorials&quot; allows you to check several information about the gameplay of
this game, teaching you about something you may not know. When you haven&#39;t
read something yet, it will display a symbol stating the you haven&#39;t read
it yet. You DON&#39;T have to read them all and there&#39;s NO prize for doing so,
but it is always a good idea to check it, in case you have any questions.

&quot;Map&quot; is one of those obvious options, where you can simply check the
world MAP.

&quot;Encyclopedia&quot; can be considered as this game&#39;s Pokedex, allowing you to
check the information on all the pokemon that you&#39;ve already seen or
captured in the game.

&quot;Options&quot;, in this menu, has exactly the same layout as the other
mini-menu I&#39;ve stated before. Therefore, I don&#39;t think you will have any
trouble with it.

&quot;Quick Save&quot; is the option you should use if you are in the field and you
need to quickly leave the game, in order to do anything else. Be aware
that this only allows you to restart the game ONCE from that particular
point, and then it will erase the point where you quick saved it.

&quot;Exit&quot;, well... it exits this menu.

This is all for this section, I guess.



1.2~. Initial Notes

In this section, you will be able to read about some of the things you
should know BEFORE starting to play the game. While they may spoil a very
limited amount of the gameplay, it is in your best interest to acknowledge
them as soon as possible.

- As stated before, after dropping a pokemon&#39;s HP to below 1, you can
  usually still give it a few extra rounds, to max out the EXP you win.
  This way, you can get more EXP and still face the exact same amount of
  enemies;

- More EXP means more levels, and more levels mean more HP for you;

- Shortly after starting to play, your character will gain his first
  special bar. However, when you gain your 3rd, 5th, 7th and 9th medals,
  you will also receive a new special bar. Since more special bars mean
  that your main pokemon will be able to use a stronger paralyzing attack,
  you could consider them to be quite important;

- When acquiring your 4th, 7th and 10th medals, you will be able to
  increase the number of pokemon you can carry with you at any time, from
  the initial value of 4 up to a maximum of 7, after getting your 10th
  medal;

- Like what happens in the classical pokemon games, in here you could also
  find &quot;capturing all Pokemon&quot; to be an interesting sidequest. Therefore,
  each time you see a unique pokemon in front of you, you should give
  everything you&#39;ve got to capture it, EVEN if I have no mention to such
  pokemon in the guide;

- Save a lot and save often, as you don&#39;t want to have to replay a certain
  mission all over again, do you? Therefore, EVERY time you see a save
  point, be sure to use it, even if that isn&#39;t stated in this guide.

That&#39;s all for now, I guess...



1.3~. Pokemon Type

First, I must tell you that in this game, the Pokemon are usable inside
and outside of the battles. In the field, you can generally use them to
help you in several tasks, like removing natural barriers. While there are
more than 200 Pokemon in the game, the abilities that you can use in the
field are kinda limited, and they include:

- Break - destroys something, like a huge rock.

- Burn - burns something down, like a tree or a huge ice block.

- Charge - restores your life.

- Cross - allows your characters to be taken to another place, by using
          this ability on something they can grab.

- Cut - simply cuts something in front of you, like a fence or a bush.

- Flash - lights up an area.

- Gust - creates a windy attack that can lift stuff off the floor.

- Tackle - pushes something, as a box or a tree.

- Water - throws some water, which can be used for tasks such as
          extinguishing something that is on fire or very hot.

Besides &quot;Flash&quot; (an ability that only Staryu can use), all the other ones
come in 3 different strenghts, like the normal one, &quot;x2&quot; and &quot;x3&quot;. While
an ability of &quot;x3&quot; can remove a &quot;x2&quot; (or lower) barrier, the opposite
can&#39;t occur. Also, in the case of &quot;Charge&quot;, the normal ability restores
5 HP, the &quot;x2&quot; version restores 15 HP and finally the &quot;x3&quot; one fully
restores your HP.

This is all for the field abilities, but the game also contains battle
ones. With an higher number than the ones specified above, these can be
used by simply calling a pokemon to the battle which can use an ability of
such type, as shown in the section &quot;Acquirable Pokemon and their moves&quot; of
this guide. They include:

- Bug - entraps your opponent inside the lines you created.

- Dark - decreases your current HP BUT makes your stylus&#39; line longer.

- Electric - simply restores your HP.

- Fighting - Each time you do a full closed line, opponent&#39;s HP is halved
             by 2 points, instead of the usual 1.

- Fire - when you complete a full line around an opponent, this causes
         massive explosions in the inside of that area, usually preventing
         the opponent from attacking.

- Flying - throws gusts, which may lift opponent&#39;s from the ground for a
           while.

- Ghost - when you complete a full closed line, ghosts appear and stun the
          opponents inside the circle, making them stop whatever they were
          going to do.

- Grass - this attack allows you to create a grass barrier around your
          opponent.

- Ground - breaks the ground, stopping your enemies from crossing that
           particular place for a while.

- Ice - creates ice areas that can freeze the opponent, if he runs into
        them.

- Paralyze - this electrical attack stuns the opponent for as much time as
             the number of special bars that were currently filled.

- Poison - poisons your enemy, making it weaker.

- Psychic - stuns your opponent for a while, taking it off the floor.

- Rock - causes sandstorms.

- Water - allows you to create bubbles that can imprison your enemies
          inside, with the time being defined only by the size of the 
          bubble you created.

Some of these functions are instantly used (like the Psychic or Electric
ones), but others will last for some time, like the Fire or Grass ones,
with the time being awarded simply having the strenght of that pokemon in
mind.

And that&#39;s all for this section...



1.4~. Mini-games

While most of the events in this story are pretty linear, the game also
seems to contain some small 3 areas where you will need to play a slightly
different adventure. Those are not very hard, but turn your task of
capturing all the Pokemon into something slightly harder than what you
will usually find in the game.

The &quot;Ring Town mini-game&quot; and the &quot;Summer Town mini-game&quot; are easily
acessible by talking to the proper person, when all to the right of the
upper exit (for the Ring Town one) and to the immediate left of the Lapras
(for the Summer Town one), and you will need to hang on top of the
provided Pokemon (either a Doduo or a Lapras, depending on the game) and
try to capture as many pokemon as possible in a 3-minute time. Rarer
pokemon give you more points, and there sure are a lot of those for you to
find in each of the two areas stated above. Be aware that some of them are
really hard to find and may only be available sometimes, so it may turn
out being indeed very hard to capture a particular pokemon, even if you
know where to find them. As an added note, the biggest difference between
these 2 mini-games is that in the Summer Town one you can&#39;t see most of
your enemies, as they will be appearing below the water.

The &quot;Fall City mini-game&quot; seems to be only available after completing the
main storyline once, and available by taking the left path on the upper
area of the stated city, you will find an arena in there. Inside that one,
you should talk to the woman at the counter and she will make you enter a
tournament, where pokemon will usually be falling from the sky and you
need to capture them, in order to win points and more capture time. You
must be aware that circling them more times than required increases the
time that you have for capturing more pokemon, while capturing more than a
pokemon at the same time will greatly increase the number of points you
get from them, and that sure is important. In case you are wondering, the
main target is surpassing the 50000 points area, which turns being quite
hard.

That&#39;s all for this section, too...</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 25 Oct 2007 02:22:28 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Games</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/pokemon-ranger-walkthrough/115823.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Pokemon ranger walkthrough</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@sanga282 sanga282]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/sanga282">@sanga282</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote no-group" data-post="14" data-topic="115823">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 pk3r kyle:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>yeah i need diamond for the pc i cant find it anywhere lol</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p><a href="http://nds-roms.com" rel="nofollow noopener">nds-roms.com</a> i think</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/pokemon-ranger-walkthrough/115823/20">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/pokemon-ranger-walkthrough/115823/20</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 25 Oct 2007 02:22:28 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-115823-20</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/pokemon-ranger-walkthrough/115823.rss">Pokemon ranger walkthrough</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Pokemon ranger walkthrough</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@pk3r_kyle pk3r kyle]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/pk3r_kyle">@pk3r_kyle</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p><img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=6" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"> on saphire i have all 202 pokemon :o</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/pokemon-ranger-walkthrough/115823/19">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/pokemon-ranger-walkthrough/115823/19</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 21 Oct 2007 03:35:54 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-115823-19</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/pokemon-ranger-walkthrough/115823.rss">Pokemon ranger walkthrough</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Pokemon ranger walkthrough</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@w00tz0r_pwnz w00tz0r pwnz]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/w00tz0r_pwnz">@w00tz0r_pwnz</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Lol pokemon. I have MonsterBrain and i own at silver =)</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/pokemon-ranger-walkthrough/115823/18">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/pokemon-ranger-walkthrough/115823/18</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 07 Jul 2007 12:11:45 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-115823-18</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/pokemon-ranger-walkthrough/115823.rss">Pokemon ranger walkthrough</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Pokemon ranger walkthrough</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Heaven Heaven]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/heaven">@Heaven</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote no-group" data-post="16" data-topic="115823">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/davidude36/40/5_6259e4fa9dfe0dec282fb0955bb1974c.png" class="avatar"> davidude36:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Are the newest versions of pokemon worth playing? e.g. diamond or fire red or what ever they are called?</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Er no, i watsed $40 on it.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/pokemon-ranger-walkthrough/115823/17">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/pokemon-ranger-walkthrough/115823/17</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 03 Jul 2007 05:50:48 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-115823-17</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/pokemon-ranger-walkthrough/115823.rss">Pokemon ranger walkthrough</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Pokemon ranger walkthrough</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@davidude36 Brolapse]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/davidude36">@davidude36</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Are the newest versions of pokemon worth playing? e.g. diamond or fire red or what ever they are called?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/pokemon-ranger-walkthrough/115823/16">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/pokemon-ranger-walkthrough/115823/16</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 30 Jun 2007 17:32:11 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-115823-16</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/pokemon-ranger-walkthrough/115823.rss">Pokemon ranger walkthrough</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Pokemon ranger walkthrough</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@MybJames MybJames]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/mybjames">@MybJames</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Try to get a NDS emulator, then search for roms.<br>
As for the guide, try to state sources, including author name (if possible) and a link to where you found it from.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/pokemon-ranger-walkthrough/115823/15">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/pokemon-ranger-walkthrough/115823/15</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 30 Jun 2007 16:46:18 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-115823-15</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/pokemon-ranger-walkthrough/115823.rss">Pokemon ranger walkthrough</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Pokemon ranger walkthrough</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@pk3r_kyle pk3r kyle]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/pk3r_kyle">@pk3r_kyle</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>yeah i need diamond for the pc i cant find it anywhere lol</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/pokemon-ranger-walkthrough/115823/14">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/pokemon-ranger-walkthrough/115823/14</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 30 Jun 2007 15:26:57 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-115823-14</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/pokemon-ranger-walkthrough/115823.rss">Pokemon ranger walkthrough</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Pokemon ranger walkthrough</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@sanga282 sanga282]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/sanga282">@sanga282</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>lol pokemon games are legend</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/pokemon-ranger-walkthrough/115823/13">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/pokemon-ranger-walkthrough/115823/13</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 30 Jun 2007 15:17:47 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-115823-13</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/pokemon-ranger-walkthrough/115823.rss">Pokemon ranger walkthrough</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Pokemon ranger walkthrough</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@pk3r_kyle pk3r kyle]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/pk3r_kyle">@pk3r_kyle</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>lol i found it on google and i was lyk meh why not</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/pokemon-ranger-walkthrough/115823/12">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/pokemon-ranger-walkthrough/115823/12</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 30 Jun 2007 13:53:48 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-115823-12</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/pokemon-ranger-walkthrough/115823.rss">Pokemon ranger walkthrough</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Pokemon ranger walkthrough</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Eh_Pretty_Easy Eh Pretty Easy]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/eh_pretty_easy">@Eh_Pretty_Easy</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>LOL, all I can say is LOL. This is obviously C&amp;P, state your sources please, and I doubt anyone needs a walkthrough for a Pokemon game…</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/pokemon-ranger-walkthrough/115823/11">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/pokemon-ranger-walkthrough/115823/11</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 30 Jun 2007 13:30:25 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-115823-11</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/pokemon-ranger-walkthrough/115823.rss">Pokemon ranger walkthrough</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Pokemon ranger walkthrough</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@pk3r_kyle pk3r kyle]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/pk3r_kyle">@pk3r_kyle</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>R-150 -&gt; Primeape<br>
TYPE: Fighting<br>
FIELD MOVE: Break x2<br>
BATTLE MOVE: Fighting<br>
HOW TO GET HIM: as part of the storyline OR in the jungle (requires<br>
“Tackle x3”).</p>
<p>R-151 -&gt; Ekans<br>
TYPE: Poison<br>
FIELD MOVE: none<br>
BATTLE MOVE: Poison<br>
HOW TO GET HIM: as part of the storyline OR in the jungle, where they seem<br>
to randomly jump out of the bushes.</p>
<p>R-152 -&gt; Arbok<br>
TYPE: Poison<br>
FIELD MOVE: none<br>
BATTLE MOVE: Poison<br>
HOW TO GET HIM: in the Mountain Range.</p>
<p>R-153 -&gt; Venonat<br>
TYPE: Bug<br>
FIELD MOVE: none<br>
BATTLE MOVE: Poison<br>
HOW TO GET HIM: as part of the storyline OR in the jungle.</p>
<p>R-154 -&gt; Wurmple<br>
TYPE: Bug<br>
FIELD MOVE: none<br>
BATTLE MOVE: Bug<br>
HOW TO GET HIM: as part of the storyline OR in the jungle.</p>
<p>R-155 -&gt; Silcoon<br>
TYPE: Bug<br>
FIELD MOVE: none<br>
BATTLE MOVE: Bug<br>
HOW TO GET HIM: in the jungle.</p>
<p>R-156 -&gt; Beautifly<br>
TYPE: Bug<br>
FIELD MOVE: none<br>
BATTLE MOVE: Flying<br>
HOW TO GET HIM: as part of the storyline OR in the jungle.</p>
<p>R-157 -&gt; Spinarak<br>
TYPE: Bug<br>
FIELD MOVE: none<br>
BATTLE MOVE: Bug<br>
HOW TO GET HIM: jungle, besides some more places.</p>
<p>R-158 -&gt; Ariados<br>
TYPE: Bug<br>
FIELD MOVE: none<br>
BATTLE MOVE: Bug<br>
HOW TO GET HIM: as part of the storyline OR in the jungle OR in the<br>
temple.</p>
<p>R-159 -&gt; Flygon<br>
TYPE: Dragon<br>
FIELD MOVE: Gust x3<br>
BATTLE MOVE: Ground<br>
HOW TO GET HIM: as part of the storyline.</p>
<p>R-160 -&gt; Gligar<br>
TYPE: Ground<br>
FIELD MOVE: Cut<br>
BATTLE MOVE: Ground<br>
HOW TO GET HIM: jungle OR at the Mountain Range.</p>
<p>R-161 -&gt; Houndoom<br>
TYPE: Dark<br>
FIELD MOVE: Burn x2<br>
BATTLE MOVE: Dark<br>
HOW TO GET HIM: Pyramid, after it becomes full of fire.</p>
<p>R-162 -&gt; Slakoth<br>
TYPE: Normal<br>
FIELD MOVE: Cut<br>
BATTLE MOVE: none<br>
HOW TO GET HIM: as part of the storyline OR in the jungle.</p>
<p>R-163 -&gt; Vigoroth<br>
TYPE: Normal<br>
FIELD MOVE: Cut x2<br>
BATTLE MOVE: none<br>
HOW TO GET HIM: as part of the storyline OR in the jungle.</p>
<p>R-164 -&gt; Slaking<br>
TYPE: Normal<br>
FIELD MOVE: Break x3<br>
BATTLE MOVE: none<br>
HOW TO GET HIM: as part of the storyline OR in the jungle.</p>
<p>R-165 -&gt; Bagon<br>
TYPE: Dragon<br>
FIELD MOVE: Tackle<br>
BATTLE MOVE: none<br>
HOW TO GET HIM: as part of the storyline.</p>
<p>R-166 -&gt; Shelgon<br>
TYPE: Dragon<br>
FIELD MOVE: Tackle x2<br>
BATTLE MOVE: none<br>
HOW TO GET HIM: as part of the storyline.</p>
<p>R-167 -&gt; Salamence<br>
TYPE: Dragon<br>
FIELD MOVE: Break x3<br>
BATTLE MOVE: Flying<br>
HOW TO GET HIM: as part of the storyline.</p>
<p>R-168 -&gt; Jynx<br>
TYPE: Psychic<br>
FIELD MOVE: none<br>
BATTLE MOVE: Psychic<br>
HOW TO GET HIM: at the cave.</p>
<p>R-169 -&gt; Solrock<br>
TYPE: Rock<br>
FIELD MOVE: none<br>
BATTLE MOVE: Psychic<br>
HOW TO GET HIM: at the cave.</p>
<p>R-170 -&gt; Wobbuffet<br>
TYPE: Psychic<br>
FIELD MOVE: none<br>
BATTLE MOVE: Psychic<br>
HOW TO GET HIM: at the cave, you will need to break a big rock near the<br>
area with water, using a “Break x2” pokemon.</p>
<p>R-171 -&gt; Dusclops<br>
TYPE: Ghost<br>
FIELD MOVE: none<br>
BATTLE MOVE: Ghost<br>
HOW TO GET HIM: at the cave.</p>
<p>R-172 -&gt; Swinub<br>
TYPE: Ground<br>
FIELD MOVE: Tackle<br>
BATTLE MOVE: Ice<br>
HOW TO GET HIM: at the cave.</p>
<p>R-173 -&gt; Piloswine<br>
TYPE: Ground<br>
FIELD MOVE: Tackle x3<br>
BATTLE MOVE: Ice<br>
HOW TO GET HIM: at the cave  OR at the Mountain Range.</p>
<p>R-174 -&gt; Snorunt<br>
TYPE: Ice<br>
FIELD MOVE: Break<br>
BATTLE MOVE: Ice<br>
HOW TO GET HIM: at the cave.</p>
<p>R-175 -&gt; Glalie<br>
TYPE: Ice<br>
FIELD MOVE: none<br>
BATTLE MOVE: Ice<br>
HOW TO GET HIM: at the cave.</p>
<p>R-176 -&gt; Whismur<br>
TYPE: Normal<br>
FIELD MOVE: none<br>
BATTLE MOVE: none<br>
HOW TO GET HIM: at the cave.</p>
<p>R-177 -&gt; Loudred<br>
TYPE: Normal<br>
FIELD MOVE: none<br>
BATTLE MOVE: none<br>
HOW TO GET HIM: at the cave, by taking the rightmost exit on the water<br>
maze.</p>
<p>R-178 -&gt; Exploud<br>
TYPE: Normal<br>
FIELD MOVE: none<br>
BATTLE MOVE: none<br>
HOW TO GET HIM: at the cave.</p>
<p>R-179 -&gt; Steelix<br>
TYPE: Steel<br>
FIELD MOVE: none<br>
BATTLE MOVE: Ground<br>
HOW TO GET HIM: as part of the storyline.</p>
<p>R-180 -&gt; Seedot<br>
TYPE: Grass<br>
FIELD MOVE: Tackle<br>
BATTLE MOVE: Grass<br>
HOW TO GET HIM: as part of the storyline OR in the Mountain Range.</p>
<p>R-181 -&gt; Nuzleaf<br>
TYPE: Dark<br>
FIELD MOVE: Gust<br>
BATTLE MOVE: Grass<br>
HOW TO GET HIM: in the Mountain Range.</p>
<p>R-182 -&gt; Shiftry<br>
TYPE: Dark<br>
FIELD MOVE: Gust x2<br>
BATTLE MOVE: Grass<br>
HOW TO GET HIM: in the Mountain Range.</p>
<p>R-183 -&gt; Vaporeon<br>
TYPE: Water<br>
FIELD MOVE: Water x2<br>
BATTLE MOVE: Water<br>
HOW TO GET HIM: as part of the storyline OR at the temple.</p>
<p>R-184 -&gt; Flareon<br>
TYPE: Fire<br>
FIELD MOVE: Burn x2<br>
BATTLE MOVE: Fire<br>
HOW TO GET HIM: as part of the storyline OR at the temple.</p>
<p>R-185 -&gt; Jolteon<br>
TYPE: Electric<br>
FIELD MOVE: Charge x3<br>
BATTLE MOVE: Electric<br>
HOW TO GET HIM: as part of the storyline OR at the temple.</p>
<p>R-186 -&gt; Espeon<br>
TYPE: Psychic<br>
FIELD MOVE: none<br>
BATTLE MOVE: Psychic<br>
HOW TO GET HIM: at the temple.</p>
<p>R-187 -&gt; Umbreon<br>
TYPE: Dark<br>
FIELD MOVE: none<br>
BATTLE MOVE: Dark<br>
HOW TO GET HIM: at the temple.</p>
<p>R-188 -&gt; Electabuzz<br>
TYPE: Electric<br>
FIELD MOVE: Charge x3<br>
BATTLE MOVE: Electric<br>
HOW TO GET HIM: at Team GoGo’s base.</p>
<p>R-189 -&gt; Swalot<br>
TYPE: Poison<br>
FIELD MOVE: none<br>
BATTLE MOVE: Poison<br>
HOW TO GET HIM: at the temple.</p>
<p>R-190 -&gt; Beldum<br>
TYPE: Steel<br>
FIELD MOVE: Tackle<br>
BATTLE MOVE: Psychic<br>
HOW TO GET HIM: pyramid, after it becomes full of fire OR at Team GoGo’s<br>
base.</p>
<p>R-191 -&gt; Metang<br>
TYPE: Steel<br>
FIELD MOVE: Tackle x2<br>
BATTLE MOVE: Psychic<br>
HOW TO GET HIM: at Team GoGo’s base.</p>
<p>R-192 -&gt; Metagross<br>
TYPE: Steel<br>
FIELD MOVE: Break x3<br>
BATTLE MOVE: Psychic<br>
HOW TO GET HIM: at Team GoGo’s base, after it blows up.</p>
<p>R-193 -&gt; Larvitar<br>
TYPE: Ground<br>
FIELD MOVE: Cut<br>
BATTLE MOVE: Rock<br>
HOW TO GET HIM: as part of the storyline OR in the Mountain Range.</p>
<p>R-194 -&gt; Pupitar<br>
TYPE: Ground<br>
FIELD MOVE: none<br>
BATTLE MOVE: Rock<br>
HOW TO GET HIM: as part of the storyline OR in the Mountain Range.</p>
<p>R-195 -&gt; Tyranitar<br>
TYPE: Rock<br>
FIELD MOVE: Break x3<br>
BATTLE MOVE: Dark<br>
HOW TO GET HIM: as part of the storyline OR at Team GoGo’s base.</p>
<p>R-196 -&gt; Swablu<br>
TYPE: Flying<br>
FIELD MOVE: Gust<br>
BATTLE MOVE: Flying<br>
HOW TO GET HIM: in the Mountain Range.</p>
<p>R-197 -&gt; Altaria<br>
TYPE: Dragon<br>
FIELD MOVE: Gust x3<br>
BATTLE MOVE: Flying<br>
HOW TO GET HIM: as part of the storyline OR in the Mountain Range.</p>
<p>R-198 -&gt; Aerodactyl<br>
TYPE: Rock<br>
FIELD MOVE: none<br>
BATTLE MOVE: Flying<br>
HOW TO GET HIM: as part of the storyline OR at the temple.</p>
<p>R-199 -&gt; Sneasel<br>
TYPE: Dark<br>
FIELD MOVE: Cut x2<br>
BATTLE MOVE: Dark<br>
HOW TO GET HIM: as part of the storyline OR at the cave OR in the Mountain<br>
Range.</p>
<p>R-200 -&gt; Absol<br>
TYPE: Dark<br>
FIELD MOVE: Cut x3<br>
BATTLE MOVE: Dark<br>
HOW TO GET HIM: at the cave. Use a “Burn x3” ability to destroy the huge<br>
block of ice inside a room and then continue following the<br>
path, taking the lower exit.</p>
<p>R-201 -&gt; Kangashkan<br>
TYPE: Normal<br>
FIELD MOVE: Break x3<br>
BATTLE MOVE: none<br>
HOW TO GET HIM: on the first area, found by exiting Win Town by its upper<br>
entrance, next to the right side of the small lake. You<br>
will need a pokemon with a “Break x3” ability.</p>
<p>R-202 -&gt; Entei<br>
TYPE: Fire<br>
FIELD MOVE: Burn x3<br>
BATTLE MOVE: Fire<br>
HOW TO GET HIM: as part of the storyline.</p>
<p>R-203 -&gt; Raikou<br>
TYPE: Electic<br>
FIELD MOVE: Charge x3<br>
BATTLE MOVE: Electric<br>
HOW TO GET HIM: as part of the storyline.</p>
<p>R-204 -&gt; Suicune<br>
TYPE: Water<br>
FIELD MOVE: Water x3<br>
BATTLE MOVE: Water<br>
HOW TO GET HIM: as part of the storyline.</p>
<p>R-205 -&gt; Regirock<br>
TYPE: Rock<br>
FIELD MOVE: none<br>
BATTLE MOVE: Rock<br>
HOW TO GET HIM: Exactly before entering the temple, use “Break x3” on the<br>
rock on the right. Use “Water” on the small flower, go up<br>
and us “Break x3” on the other rock. Inside, use “Fire x3”<br>
on the ice block and continue going up and inside the huge<br>
door, where you will find this enemy.</p>
<p>R-206 -&gt; Regice<br>
TYPE: Ice<br>
FIELD MOVE: none<br>
BATTLE MOVE: Ice<br>
HOW TO GET HIM: in the cave, use a “Fire x3” pokemon to remove the lower<br>
giant ice cube. Use a “Break x2” ability to remove the<br>
huge rock in the right side and go down the hole. Use a<br>
“Cross” ability to go to the left and down the next hole.<br>
Inside the huge door, you will find this enemy.</p>
<p>R-207 -&gt; Registeel<br>
TYPE: Steel<br>
FIELD MOVE: Break x3<br>
BATTLE MOVE: none<br>
HOW TO GET HIM: tunnel, you need to use “Cross” on the lower left corner<br>
of the area filled with Zubat. Then, use “Cut x2” in the<br>
next room and continue going up. You will at least 4<br>
pokemon with a “Break x2” and yet another one with a<br>
“Cross” ability. You will find him inside a huge door.</p>
<p>R-208 -&gt; Kyogre<br>
TYPE: Water<br>
FIELD MOVE: none<br>
BATTLE MOVE: Water<br>
HOW TO GET HIM: during Extra Mission 1.</p>
<p>R-209 -&gt; Groudon<br>
TYPE: Ground<br>
FIELD MOVE: none<br>
BATTLE MOVE: Ground<br>
HOW TO GET HIM: during Extra Mission 2.</p>
<p>R-210 -&gt; Rayquaza<br>
TYPE: Dragon<br>
FIELD MOVE: none<br>
BATTLE MOVE: Flying<br>
HOW TO GET HIM: during Extra Mission 3.</p>
<p>R-211 -&gt; Deoxys<br>
TYPE: Psychic<br>
FIELD MOVE: none<br>
BATTLE MOVE: Psychic<br>
HOW TO GET HIM: in Japan, you had to pre-book tickets for the 9th pokemon<br>
movie. In the other versions, you can get it by completing<br>
Special Mission 1 in Ranger Net.</p>
<p>R-212 -&gt; Celebi<br>
TYPE: Grass<br>
FIELD MOVE: none<br>
BATTLE MOVE: Grass<br>
HOW TO GET HIM: in Japan, you could only get it in special events. In the<br>
other versions, you can get it by completing Special<br>
Mission 2 in Ranger Net.</p>
<p>R-213 -&gt; Mew<br>
TYPE: Psychic<br>
FIELD MOVE: none<br>
BATTLE MOVE: Psychic<br>
HOW TO GET HIM: in Japan, you could only get it in special events. In the<br>
other versions, you can get it by completing Special<br>
Mission 3 in Ranger Net.</p>
<p>R-??? -&gt; Manafi’s egg<br>
TYPE: probably none<br>
FIELD MOVE: probably none<br>
BATTLE MOVE: probably none<br>
HOW TO GET HIM: in Japan, you had to pre-book tickets for the 9th pokemon<br>
movie. In the other versions, you have to input a certain<br>
password, as stated in the proper section of this guide.[br][size=1]Posted on: June 24, 2007, 04:07:21 AM[/size][hr]5~. Frequently Asked Questions</p>
<p>Here, you will be able to read about some of the questions that people may<br>
be wondering about this game, at least if I consider them to be slightly<br>
important.</p>
<p>Q: What exactly is the name of this game?<br>
A: It is “Pokemon Ranger”. “Pokemon Rangers” and “The Road to Diamond and<br>
Pearl” are just slight mistranslations.</p>
<p>Q: Are pokemon an it/she/he ?<br>
A: Haven’t got a clue, and that’s probably one of the major problems in<br>
this guide, as I don’t usually</p>
<p>Q: What is the most under-rated pokemon in the game?<br>
A: I would have to say Gengar. With him, you can capture a lot of enemies<br>
easily.</p>
<p>Q: How many towns are there in this game?<br>
A: 4 different ones.</p>
<p>Q: What’s that man with 2 Drowzee, that you can see near the place where<br>
there are the 3 legendary dogs?<br>
A: By talking to that man, you will be taken back to the past and fight<br>
the 3 legendary dogs once again. WHAT? &gt;_&gt;</p>
<p>Q: What happens after you capture the Snorlax?<br>
A: After exiting its cave, you will receive a call and a cutscene will<br>
occur where all the important characters appear and you get a special<br>
badge, stating that you captured all the possible pokemon. That’s all,<br>
unfortunately.</p>
<p>Q: Besides Manaphy’s one, is there any other mission to unlock, via the<br>
password mode?<br>
A: No, I don’t think so.</p>
<p>Q: I’m trying to input a password for the Manaphy mission but I can’t get<br>
it right. What am I doing wrong?<br>
A: Probably nothing, but be aware that there are several different<br>
passwords that you need to input, depending on what region of the game<br>
you’re playing. While a single one is used for the USA, at least two<br>
different ones were found for the European version, and if none of the<br>
ones stated in this guide work for you, it’s probably because you have<br>
another version of the game.</p>
<p>You can also contribute your own questions, if I find them interesting I<br>
will add them to this section.</p>
<p>-------------------------------------------------------------------------------[br][size=1]Posted on: June 24, 2007, 04:07:54 AM[/size][hr]please post if you like!</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/pokemon-ranger-walkthrough/115823/10">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/pokemon-ranger-walkthrough/115823/10</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 30 Jun 2007 13:23:12 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-115823-10</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/pokemon-ranger-walkthrough/115823.rss">Pokemon ranger walkthrough</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Pokemon ranger walkthrough</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@pk3r_kyle pk3r kyle]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/pk3r_kyle">@pk3r_kyle</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>R-100 -&gt; Jigglypuff<br>
TYPE: Normal<br>
FIELD MOVE: none<br>
BATTLE MOVE: none<br>
HOW TO GET HIM: as part of the storyline OR on Fall City.</p>
<p>R-101 -&gt; Rattata<br>
TYPE: normal<br>
FIELD MOVE: Tackle<br>
BATTLE MOVE: none<br>
HOW TO GET HIM: as part of the storyline OR on Fall City sewers.</p>
<p>R-102 -&gt; Raticate<br>
TYPE: Normal<br>
FIELD MOVE: Cut x2<br>
BATTLE MOVE: none<br>
HOW TO GET HIM: as part of the storyline OR on Fall City sewers.</p>
<p>R-103 -&gt; Porygon<br>
TYPE: Normal<br>
FIELD MOVE: none<br>
BATTLE MOVE: none<br>
HOW TO GET HIM: at the factory, but this is one of the most difficult ones<br>
to<br>
find. He is sometimes invisible, but other times he<br>
makes himself, visible, and that’s when you can actually<br>
capture it. Look closely inside the factory and eventually<br>
you will find it.</p>
<p>R-104 -&gt; Kecleon<br>
TYPE: Normal<br>
FIELD MOVE: none<br>
BATTLE MOVE: none<br>
HOW TO GET HIM: before entering the factory, destroy the trash on the<br>
left side using a “Burn x2” ability. He will be there, but<br>
be careful as he is invisible when he isn’t attacking.<br>
Also, you may find him as part of the Ring Town mini-game.</p>
<p>R-105 -&gt; Snorlax<br>
TYPE: Normal<br>
FIELD MOVE: none<br>
BATTLE MOVE: none<br>
HOW TO GET HIM: in the Mountain Range, in a cave near where you fought the<br>
Charizard. He will only wake up (and be capturable) after<br>
capturing all other 209 pokemon.</p>
<p>R-106 -&gt; Lapras<br>
TYPE: Ice<br>
FIELD MOVE: none<br>
BATTLE MOVE: Water<br>
HOW TO GET HIM: as part of the storyline.</p>
<p>R-107 -&gt; Horsea<br>
TYPE: Water<br>
FIELD MOVE: none<br>
BATTLE MOVE: Water<br>
HOW TO GET HIM: in the Summer City mini-game.</p>
<p>R-108 -&gt; Seadra<br>
TYPE: Water<br>
FIELD MOVE: none<br>
BATTLE MOVE: Water<br>
HOW TO GET HIM: in the Summer City mini-game.</p>
<p>R-109 -&gt; Kingdra<br>
TYPE: Water<br>
FIELD MOVE: Water x3<br>
BATTLE MOVE: Water<br>
HOW TO GET HIM: as part of the storyline OR in the Summer City mini-game,<br>
after you capturing 2 Horsea.</p>
<p>R-110 -&gt; Goldeen<br>
TYPE: Water<br>
FIELD MOVE: none<br>
BATTLE MOVE: Water<br>
HOW TO GET HIM: in the Summer City mini-game.</p>
<p>R-111 -&gt; Seaking<br>
TYPE: Water<br>
FIELD MOVE: none<br>
BATTLE MOVE: Water<br>
HOW TO GET HIM: in the Summer City mini-game, appearing only after you’ve<br>
captured 2 Goldeen.</p>
<p>R-112 -&gt; Staryu<br>
TYPE: Water<br>
FIELD MOVE: Flash<br>
BATTLE MOVE: Water<br>
HOW TO GET HIM: as part of the storyline OR in the Summer City mini-game.</p>
<p>R-113 -&gt; Starmie<br>
TYPE: Water<br>
FIELD MOVE: none<br>
BATTLE MOVE: Psychic<br>
HOW TO GET HIM: in the Summer City mini-game, only after you’ve captured<br>
2 Staryu.</p>
<p>R-114 -&gt; Remoraid<br>
TYPE: Water<br>
FIELD MOVE: none<br>
BATTLE MOVE: Water<br>
HOW TO GET HIM: in the Summer City mini-game.</p>
<p>R-115 -&gt; Octillery<br>
TYPE: Water<br>
FIELD MOVE: none<br>
BATTLE MOVE: Water<br>
HOW TO GET HIM: in the Summer City mini-game.</p>
<p>R-116 -&gt; Mantine<br>
TYPE: Water<br>
FIELD MOVE: none<br>
BATTLE MOVE: Water<br>
HOW TO GET HIM: in the Summer City mini-game, but only appears after<br>
you’ve captured 2 Remoraid and 2 Octillery.</p>
<p>R-117 -&gt; Carvanha<br>
TYPE: Water<br>
FIELD MOVE: none<br>
BATTLE MOVE: Water<br>
HOW TO GET HIM: during Extra Mission 1 OR in the Summer City mini-game.</p>
<p>R-118 -&gt; Sharpedo<br>
TYPE: Water<br>
FIELD MOVE: none<br>
BATTLE MOVE: Dark<br>
HOW TO GET HIM: in the Summer City mini-game, only after you’ve captured<br>
2 Carvanha.</p>
<p>R-119 -&gt; Wailmer<br>
TYPE: Water<br>
FIELD MOVE: none<br>
BATTLE MOVE: Water<br>
HOW TO GET HIM: in the Summer City mini-game, but only after you’ve<br>
managed to capture 2 Seaking.</p>
<p>R-120 -&gt; Luvdisc<br>
TYPE: Water<br>
FIELD MOVE: none<br>
BATTLE MOVE: Water<br>
HOW TO GET HIM: in the Summer City mini-game.</p>
<p>R-121 -&gt; Psyduck<br>
TYPE: Water<br>
FIELD MOVE: none<br>
BATTLE MOVE: Water<br>
HOW TO GET HIM: in the Summer City mini-game, but only after you captured<br>
2 Starmie.</p>
<p>R-122 -&gt; Wingull<br>
TYPE: Water<br>
FIELD MOVE: none<br>
BATTLE MOVE: Water<br>
HOW TO GET HIM: on Fall City.</p>
<p>R-123 -&gt; Pelipper<br>
TYPE: Water<br>
FIELD MOVE: none<br>
BATTLE MOVE: Water<br>
HOW TO GET HIM: in the Summer City mini-game, but it will only appear<br>
after you’ve previously beaten this game’s top score of<br>
5000 points.</p>
<p>R-124 -&gt; Magikarp<br>
TYPE: Water<br>
FIELD MOVE: none<br>
BATTLE MOVE: Water<br>
HOW TO GET HIM: as part of the storyline OR in the Summer City mini-game<br>
OR in the Mountain Range.</p>
<p>R-125 -&gt; Gyarados<br>
TYPE: Water<br>
FIELD MOVE: none<br>
BATTLE MOVE: Water<br>
HOW TO GET HIM: as part of the storyline.</p>
<p>R-126 -&gt; Oddish<br>
TYPE: Grass<br>
FIELD MOVE: Cut<br>
BATTLE MOVE: Grass<br>
HOW TO GET HIM: by using a Meditite to throw a wall down, on the Fall City<br>
sewers OR in the jungle, requiring a “Gust” ability.</p>
<p>R-127 -&gt; Gloom<br>
TYPE: Grass<br>
FIELD MOVE: none<br>
BATTLE MOVE: Grass<br>
HOW TO GET HIM: in the jungle, requires someone with a “Gust x2” skill.</p>
<p>R-128 -&gt; Vileplume<br>
TYPE: Grass<br>
FIELD MOVE: none<br>
BATTLE MOVE: Grass<br>
HOW TO GET HIM: in the Mountain Range, you need someone with a “Gust x3”<br>
skill.</p>
<p>R-129 -&gt; Treecko<br>
TYPE: Grass<br>
FIELD MOVE: Cut<br>
BATTLE MOVE: Grass<br>
HOW TO GET HIM: in the jungle.</p>
<p>R-130 -&gt; Grovyle<br>
TYPE: Grass<br>
FIELD MOVE: Cut x2<br>
BATTLE MOVE: Grass<br>
HOW TO GET HIM: there are some different places to get it, but in the<br>
jungle you can do it by using “Water” on a small plant,<br>
near the place where you can throw a tree down.</p>
<p>R-131 -&gt; Sceptile<br>
TYPE: Grass<br>
FIELD MOVE: Cut x3<br>
BATTLE MOVE: Grass<br>
HOW TO GET HIM: on the Pyramid, after it becomes full of fire. You need to<br>
use a “Break x2” to remove the huge rock, exactly all to<br>
the right of your initial position.</p>
<p>R-132 -&gt; Lotad<br>
TYPE: Water<br>
FIELD MOVE: Water<br>
BATTLE MOVE: Water<br>
HOW TO GET HIM: jungle, and while you could usually need to lift him from<br>
the water, they seem to randomly get out of it</p>
<p>R-133 -&gt; Lombre<br>
TYPE: Water<br>
FIELD MOVE: Water x2<br>
BATTLE MOVE: Water<br>
HOW TO GET HIM: in the jungle, Where you can see a Grovyle, simply use<br>
someone in the bush nearby and you will be taken to a<br>
place where 2 of this pokemon can be seen.</p>
<p>R-134 -&gt; Ludicolo<br>
TYPE: Water<br>
FIELD MOVE: none<br>
BATTLE MOVE: Water<br>
HOW TO GET HIM: on Fall City OR in the jungle.</p>
<p>R-135 -&gt; Numel<br>
TYPE: Fire<br>
FIELD MOVE: Burn<br>
BATTLE MOVE: Fire<br>
HOW TO GET HIM: on the Pyramid, after it becomes full of fire.</p>
<p>R-136 -&gt; Camerupt<br>
TYPE: Fire<br>
FIELD MOVE: Burn x3<br>
BATTLE MOVE: Fire<br>
HOW TO GET HIM: as part of the storyline OR on the Pyramid, after it<br>
becomes full of fire.</p>
<p>R-137 -&gt; Magmar<br>
TYPE: Fire<br>
FIELD MOVE: Burn x2<br>
BATTLE MOVE: Fire<br>
HOW TO GET HIM: on the Pyramid, after it becomes full of fire.</p>
<p>R-138 -&gt; Slugma<br>
TYPE: Fire<br>
FIELD MOVE: Burn<br>
BATTLE MOVE: Fire<br>
HOW TO GET HIM: as part of the storyline OR on the Pyramid, after it<br>
becomes full of fire.</p>
<p>R-139 -&gt; Magcargo<br>
TYPE: Fire<br>
FIELD MOVE: Burn x2<br>
BATTLE MOVE: Fire<br>
HOW TO GET HIM: as part of the storyline OR on the Pyramid, after it<br>
becomes full of fire.</p>
<p>R-140 -&gt; Charmander<br>
TYPE: Fire<br>
FIELD MOVE: Burn<br>
BATTLE MOVE: Fire<br>
HOW TO GET HIM: on the Pyramid, after it becomes full of fire.</p>
<p>R-141 -&gt; Charmeleon<br>
TYPE: Fire<br>
FIELD MOVE: Burn x2<br>
BATTLE MOVE: Fire<br>
HOW TO GET HIM: during Extra Mission 2 OR on the Pyramid, after it<br>
becomes full of fire (which will require a “Water x3”<br>
ability).</p>
<p>R-142 -&gt; Charizard<br>
TYPE: Fire<br>
FIELD MOVE: Burn x3<br>
BATTLE MOVE: Fire<br>
HOW TO GET HIM: as part of the storyline.</p>
<p>R-143 -&gt; Torkoal<br>
TYPE: Fire<br>
FIELD MOVE: Burn x2<br>
BATTLE MOVE: Fire<br>
HOW TO GET HIM: at the cave. Use a “Burn x3” ability to destroy the huge<br>
block of ice inside a room and then continue following the<br>
path, going up the stairs.</p>
<p>R-144 -&gt; Growlithe<br>
TYPE: Fire<br>
FIELD MOVE: none<br>
BATTLE MOVE: Fire<br>
HOW TO GET HIM: at the Factory.</p>
<p>R-145 -&gt; Arcanine<br>
TYPE: Fire<br>
FIELD MOVE: Burn x3<br>
BATTLE MOVE: Fire<br>
HOW TO GET HIM: during Extra Mission 2 OR on the Pyramid, after it becomes<br>
full of fire.</p>
<p>R-146 -&gt; Electrike<br>
TYPE: Electric<br>
FIELD MOVE: Charge<br>
BATTLE MOVE: Electric<br>
HOW TO GET HIM: in the jungle, besides many other places.</p>
<p>R-147 -&gt; Manectric<br>
TYPE: Electric<br>
FIELD MOVE: Charge x2<br>
BATTLE MOVE: Electric<br>
HOW TO GET HIM: pyramid (after the fire appears), besides other places.</p>
<p>R-148 -&gt; Heracross<br>
TYPE: Bug<br>
FIELD MOVE: Tackle x3<br>
BATTLE MOVE: Fighting<br>
HOW TO GET HIM: as part of the storyline OR in the jungle.</p>
<p>R-149 -&gt; Mankey<br>
TYPE: Fighting<br>
FIELD MOVE: Break<br>
BATTLE MOVE: Fighting<br>
HOW TO GET HIM: as part of the storyline OR in the jungle (requires<br>
“Tackle x3”).</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/pokemon-ranger-walkthrough/115823/9">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/pokemon-ranger-walkthrough/115823/9</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 24 Jun 2007 15:06:16 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-115823-9</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/pokemon-ranger-walkthrough/115823.rss">Pokemon ranger walkthrough</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Pokemon ranger walkthrough</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@pk3r_kyle pk3r kyle]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/pk3r_kyle">@pk3r_kyle</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>R-001 -&gt; Bulbasaur<br>
TYPE: Grass<br>
FIELD MOVE: Cross<br>
BATTLE MOVE: Grass<br>
HOW TO GET HIM: in the forest, all down and slightly to the left before<br>
entering the tunnel, you will need to use “Cut”.</p>
<p>R-002 -&gt; Ivysaur<br>
TYPE: Grass<br>
FIELD MOVE: Cross<br>
BATTLE MOVE: Grass<br>
HOW TO GET HIM: in the forest.</p>
<p>R-003 -&gt; Venosaur<br>
TYPE: Grass<br>
FIELD MOVE: none<br>
BATTLE MOVE: Grass<br>
HOW TO GET HIM: in the forest, on mission 6 or later, you will need to use<br>
“Cut” on a bush, just before the labyrinthic area.</p>
<p>R-004 -&gt; Bellsprout<br>
TYPE: Grass<br>
FIELD MOVE: none<br>
BATTLE MOVE: Grass<br>
HOW TO GET HIM: as part of the storyline OR in the forest.</p>
<p>R-005 -&gt; Weepinbell<br>
TYPE: Grass<br>
FIELD MOVE: none<br>
BATTLE MOVE: Poison<br>
HOW TO GET HIM: in the forest, as soon as mission 6.</p>
<p>R-006 -&gt; Victreebel<br>
TYPE: Grass<br>
FIELD MOVE: none<br>
BATTLE MOVE: Poison<br>
HOW TO GET HIM: in the forest.</p>
<p>R-007 -&gt; Chikorita<br>
TYPE: Grass<br>
FIELD MOVE: none<br>
BATTLE MOVE: Grass<br>
HOW TO GET HIM: you can even easily find it in the first forest.</p>
<p>R-008 -&gt; Bayleef<br>
TYPE: Grass<br>
FIELD MOVE: Cut x2<br>
BATTLE MOVE: Grass<br>
HOW TO GET HIM: as part of the storyline.</p>
<p>R-009 -&gt; Meganium<br>
TYPE: Grass<br>
FIELD MOVE: Break x3<br>
BATTLE MOVE: Grass<br>
HOW TO GET HIM: in the jungle.</p>
<p>R-010 -&gt; Hoppip<br>
TYPE: Grass<br>
FIELD MOVE: none<br>
BATTLE MOVE: Grass<br>
HOW TO GET HIM: in the forest, as soon as mission 6.</p>
<p>R-011 -&gt; Mudkip<br>
TYPE: Water<br>
FIELD MOVE: Water<br>
BATTLE MOVE: Water<br>
HOW TO GET HIM: as part of the storyline OR in the forest.</p>
<p>R-012 -&gt; Marshtomp<br>
TYPE: Ground<br>
FIELD MOVE: Water x2<br>
BATTLE MOVE: Water<br>
HOW TO GET HIM: in the forest, on your mission number 6 or later.</p>
<p>R-013 -&gt; Swampert<br>
TYPE: Ground<br>
FIELD MOVE: Water x3<br>
BATTLE MOVE: Water<br>
HOW TO GET HIM: at Team GoGo’s base OR in the forest.</p>
<p>R-014 -&gt; Slowpoke<br>
TYPE: Water<br>
FIELD MOVE: Water<br>
BATTLE MOVE: Water<br>
HOW TO GET HIM: in the Ring Town mini-game, but he will only appear after<br>
you capturing 2 Abra.</p>
<p>R-015 -&gt; Torchic<br>
TYPE: Fire<br>
FIELD MOVE: Burn<br>
BATTLE MOVE: Fire<br>
HOW TO GET HIM: as part of the storyline OR in the forest.</p>
<p>R-016 -&gt; Combusken<br>
TYPE: Fire<br>
FIELD MOVE: Burn x2<br>
BATTLE MOVE: Fire<br>
HOW TO GET HIM: as part of the storyline.</p>
<p>R-017 -&gt; Blaziken<br>
TYPE: Fire<br>
FIELD MOVE: Burn x3<br>
BATTLE MOVE: Fire<br>
HOW TO GET HIM: at Team GoGo’s base OR in the road from the tunnel to Fall<br>
City.</p>
<p>R-018 -&gt; Rapidash<br>
TYPE: Fire<br>
FIELD MOVE: Burn x3<br>
BATTLE MOVE: Fire<br>
HOW TO GET HIM: as part of the storyline OR in the Ring Town mini-game,<br>
where he will only appear after you capturing 2 Spoink.</p>
<p>R-019 -&gt; Cyndaquil<br>
TYPE: Fire<br>
FIELD MOVE: Burn<br>
BATTLE MOVE: Fire<br>
HOW TO GET HIM: in the forest, in mission 6 or later.</p>
<p>R-020 -&gt; Quilava<br>
TYPE: Fire<br>
FIELD MOVE: Burn x2<br>
BATTLE MOVE: Fire<br>
HOW TO GET HIM: as part of the storyline OR at the Mountain Range.</p>
<p>R-021 -&gt; Typhlosion<br>
TYPE: Fire<br>
FIELD MOVE: Burn x3<br>
BATTLE MOVE: Fire<br>
HOW TO GET HIM: in the forest, you have to use “Cut” in one of the bushes,<br>
probably the one in the lower right part of that area.</p>
<p>R-022 -&gt; Pichu<br>
TYPE: Electric<br>
FIELD MOVE: Charge<br>
BATTLE MOVE: Electric<br>
HOW TO GET HIM: in several places. However, he is easily found in the<br>
forest, as soon as mission number 1.</p>
<p>R-023 -&gt; Pikachu<br>
TYPE: Electric<br>
FIELD MOVE: Charge x2<br>
BATTLE MOVE: Electric<br>
HOW TO GET HIM: in lots of places, but you can first see one in mission<br>
number 6.</p>
<p>R-024 -&gt; Raichu<br>
TYPE: Electric<br>
FIELD MOVE: Charge x3<br>
BATTLE MOVE: Electric<br>
HOW TO GET HIM: in lots of places, but you can first see one in mission<br>
number 8.</p>
<p>R-025 -&gt; Beedrill<br>
TYPE: Bug<br>
FIELD MOVE: Break<br>
BATTLE MOVE: Poison<br>
HOW TO GET HIM: in the forest, as soon as mission 6.</p>
<p>R-026 -&gt; Ralts<br>
TYPE: Psychic<br>
FIELD MOVE: none<br>
BATTLE MOVE: Psychic<br>
HOW TO GET HIM: at the Mountain Range OR at Team GoGo base.</p>
<p>R-027 -&gt; Kirlia<br>
TYPE: Psychic<br>
FIELD MOVE: none<br>
BATTLE MOVE: Psychic<br>
HOW TO GET HIM: in the tunnel (you will need to use a Graveler), OR on<br>
mission number 5 (or later) OR in the plain capture<br>
mini-game OR at the Mountain Range.</p>
<p>R-028 -&gt; Gardevoir<br>
TYPE: Psychic<br>
FIELD MOVE: none<br>
BATTLE MOVE: Psychic<br>
HOW TO GET HIM: during Extra Mission 3 OR at the Mountain Range OR in the<br>
Ring Town mini-game, where she will only appear after you<br>
capturing 2 Kirlia.</p>
<p>R-029 -&gt; Abra<br>
TYPE: Psychic<br>
FIELD MOVE: none<br>
BATTLE MOVE: Psychic<br>
HOW TO GET HIM: in the Ring Town mini-game.</p>
<p>R-030 -&gt; Spoink<br>
TYPE: Psychic<br>
FIELD MOVE: none<br>
BATTLE MOVE: Psychic<br>
HOW TO GET HIM: in the Ring Town mini-game.</p>
<p>R-031 -&gt; Nincada<br>
TYPE: Ground<br>
FIELD MOVE: Cut<br>
BATTLE MOVE: Bug<br>
HOW TO GET HIM: in the forest.</p>
<p>R-032 -&gt; Ninjask<br>
TYPE: Bug<br>
FIELD MOVE: none<br>
BATTLE MOVE: Flying<br>
HOW TO GET HIM: in the forest, use “Tackle” on certain trees.</p>
<p>R-033 -&gt; Shedinja<br>
TYPE: Bug<br>
FIELD MOVE: none<br>
BATTLE MOVE: Ghost<br>
HOW TO GET HIM: in the forest.</p>
<p>R-034 -&gt; Phanpy<br>
TYPE: Ground<br>
FIELD MOVE: Tackle<br>
BATTLE MOVE: Ground<br>
HOW TO GET HIM: in the jungle OR in the forest.</p>
<p>R-035 -&gt; Donphan<br>
TYPE: Ground<br>
FIELD MOVE: Tackle x2<br>
BATTLE MOVE: Ground<br>
HOW TO GET HIM: at the temple.</p>
<p>R-036 -&gt; Taillow<br>
TYPE: Flying<br>
FIELD MOVE: Gust<br>
BATTLE MOVE: Flying<br>
HOW TO GET HIM: as part of the storyline OR in the forest.</p>
<p>R-037 -&gt; Swellow<br>
TYPE: Flying<br>
FIELD MOVE: Gust x2<br>
BATTLE MOVE: Flying<br>
HOW TO GET HIM: in the forest, after mission 6.</p>
<p>R-038 -&gt; Dragonite<br>
TYPE: Flying<br>
FIELD MOVE: none<br>
BATTLE MOVE: Flying<br>
HOW TO GET HIM: as part of the storyline.</p>
<p>R-039 -&gt; Spearow<br>
TYPE: Flying<br>
FIELD MOVE: Gust<br>
BATTLE MOVE: Flying<br>
HOW TO GET HIM: in the Ring Town mini-game.</p>
<p>R-040 -&gt; Fearow<br>
TYPE: Flying<br>
FIELD MOVE: none<br>
BATTLE MOVE: Flying<br>
HOW TO GET HIM: in the Ring Town mini-game, but it will only appear after<br>
you getting more than 50000 points in the Fall City<br>
mini-game.</p>
<p>R-041 -&gt; Doduo<br>
TYPE: Flying<br>
FIELD MOVE: none<br>
BATTLE MOVE: Flying<br>
HOW TO GET HIM: in the Ring Town mini-game, but he will only appear after<br>
you capturing 2 Gardevoir.</p>
<p>R-042 -&gt; Dodrio<br>
TYPE: Flying<br>
FIELD MOVE: none<br>
BATTLE MOVE: Flying<br>
HOW TO GET HIM: in the Ring Town mini-game, but he will only appear if you<br>
previously scored more than 5000 points in this same<br>
mini-game.</p>
<p>R-043 -&gt; Scyther<br>
TYPE: Bug<br>
FIELD MOVE: Cut x3<br>
BATTLE MOVE: Flying<br>
HOW TO GET HIM: as part of the storyline OR in the forest.</p>
<p>R-044 -&gt; Scizor<br>
TYPE: Steel<br>
FIELD MOVE: Cut x3<br>
BATTLE MOVE: Bug<br>
HOW TO GET HIM: as part of the storyline OR in the forest.</p>
<p>R-045 -&gt; Skarmory<br>
TYPE: Steel<br>
FIELD MOVE: none<br>
BATTLE MOVE: Flying<br>
HOW TO GET HIM: in the Ring Town mini-game, but he will only appear if you<br>
previously scored more than 5000 points in the Summer Town<br>
mini-game.</p>
<p>R-046 -&gt; Murkrow<br>
TYPE: Dark<br>
FIELD MOVE: none<br>
BATTLE MOVE: Dark<br>
HOW TO GET HIM: as part of the storyline OR in the forest, by using<br>
“Tackle” in the tree where you previously saw him.</p>
<p>R-047 -&gt; Zigzagoon<br>
TYPE: Normal<br>
FIELD MOVE: none<br>
BATTLE MOVE: none<br>
HOW TO GET HIM: in several places. However, he is easily found in your<br>
first mission.</p>
<p>R-048 -&gt; Linoone<br>
TYPE: Normal<br>
FIELD MOVE: Tackle x2<br>
BATTLE MOVE: none<br>
HOW TO GET HIM: as part of the storyline OR in the forest.</p>
<p>R-049 -&gt; Tauros<br>
TYPE: Normal<br>
FIELD MOVE: Tackle x3<br>
BATTLE MOVE: none<br>
HOW TO GET HIM: in the Ring Town mini-game.</p>
<p>R-050 -&gt; Paras<br>
TYPE: Bug<br>
FIELD MOVE: Cut<br>
BATTLE MOVE: Grass<br>
HOW TO GET HIM: as part of the storyline OR in the tunnel.</p>
<p>R-051 -&gt; Parasect<br>
TYPE: Bug<br>
FIELD MOVE: Cut<br>
BATTLE MOVE: Grass<br>
HOW TO GET HIM: in the tunnel, you will need a “Gust x2” ability.</p>
<p>R-052 -&gt; Poliwag<br>
TYPE: Water<br>
FIELD MOVE: Water<br>
BATTLE MOVE: Water<br>
HOW TO GET HIM: in the tunnel.</p>
<p>R-053 -&gt; Poliwhirl<br>
TYPE: Water<br>
FIELD MOVE: Water x2<br>
BATTLE MOVE: Water<br>
HOW TO GET HIM: in the tunnel (on mission 5 or later) and in many other<br>
places.</p>
<p>R-054 -&gt; Poliwrath<br>
TYPE: Water<br>
FIELD MOVE: Water x3<br>
BATTLE MOVE: Water<br>
HOW TO GET HIM: as part of the storyline OR in the pyramid.</p>
<p>R-055 -&gt; Politoed<br>
TYPE: Water<br>
FIELD MOVE: Water x3<br>
BATTLE MOVE: Water<br>
HOW TO GET HIM: as part of the storyline.</p>
<p>R-056 -&gt; Magnemite<br>
TYPE: Electric<br>
FIELD MOVE: Charge<br>
BATTLE MOVE: Electric<br>
HOW TO GET HIM: in really lots and lots of places.</p>
<p>R-057 -&gt; Magneton<br>
TYPE: Electric<br>
FIELD MOVE: Charge x2<br>
BATTLE MOVE: Electric<br>
HOW TO GET HIM: in several places, but one of them is by using a Meditite<br>
to throw a wall down, on the Fall City sewers.</p>
<p>R-058 -&gt; Zubat<br>
TYPE: Poison<br>
FIELD MOVE: none<br>
BATTLE MOVE: Poison<br>
HOW TO GET HIM: in the tunnel, on mission 5 or later.</p>
<p>R-059 -&gt; Golbat<br>
TYPE: Poison<br>
FIELD MOVE: Gust x2<br>
BATTLE MOVE: Poison<br>
HOW TO GET HIM: at the cave.</p>
<p>R-060 -&gt; Crobat<br>
TYPE: Poison<br>
FIELD MOVE: none<br>
BATTLE MOVE: Poison<br>
HOW TO GET HIM: as part of the storyline OR in the cave.</p>
<p>R-061 -&gt; Diglett<br>
TYPE: Ground<br>
FIELD MOVE: none<br>
BATTLE MOVE: Ground<br>
HOW TO GET HIM: in the tunnel, on mission 5 or later.</p>
<p>R-062 -&gt; Dugtrio<br>
TYPE: Ground<br>
FIELD MOVE: none<br>
BATTLE MOVE: Ground<br>
HOW TO GET HIM: in the tunnel, you need to use “Cross” on the lower left<br>
corner of the area filled with Zubat. Then, use “Break x3”<br>
in the next room and you will find this pokemon in there.</p>
<p>R-063 -&gt; Rhydon<br>
TYPE: Ground<br>
FIELD MOVE: Break x3<br>
BATTLE MOVE: Ground<br>
HOW TO GET HIM: as part of the storyline OR in the pyramid.</p>
<p>R-064 -&gt; Geodude<br>
TYPE: Ground<br>
FIELD MOVE: Break<br>
BATTLE MOVE: Rock<br>
HOW TO GET HIM: as part of the storyline OR in the tunnel.</p>
<p>R-065 -&gt; Graveler<br>
TYPE: Ground<br>
FIELD MOVE: Break x2<br>
BATTLE MOVE: Rock<br>
HOW TO GET HIM: in the tunnel (on mission 5 or later) and in many other<br>
places.</p>
<p>R-066 -&gt; Golem<br>
TYPE: Ground<br>
FIELD MOVE: Break x3<br>
BATTLE MOVE: Rock<br>
HOW TO GET HIM: at the cave oR in the temple.</p>
<p>R-067 -&gt; Plusle<br>
TYPE: Electric<br>
FIELD MOVE: none<br>
BATTLE MOVE: Paralyze<br>
HOW TO GET HIM: initially select the girl as your character, or complete<br>
the game once with the boy.</p>
<p>R-068 -&gt; Minun<br>
TYPE: Electric<br>
FIELD MOVE: none<br>
BATTLE MOVE: Paralyze<br>
HOW TO GET HIM: initially select the boy as your character, or complete<br>
the game once with the girl.</p>
<p>R-069 -&gt; Tangela<br>
TYPE: Grass<br>
FIELD MOVE: Cross<br>
BATTLE MOVE: Grass<br>
HOW TO GET HIM: as part of the storyline OR in the Mountain Range.</p>
<p>R-070 -&gt; Krabby<br>
TYPE: Water<br>
FIELD MOVE: Water<br>
BATTLE MOVE: Water<br>
HOW TO GET HIM: in Fall City.</p>
<p>R-071 -&gt; Corpish<br>
TYPE: Water<br>
FIELD MOVE: Water<br>
BATTLE MOVE: Water<br>
HOW TO GET HIM: on the Fall City sewers.</p>
<p>R-072 -&gt; Crawdaunt<br>
TYPE: Dark<br>
FIELD MOVE: Cut x3<br>
BATTLE MOVE: Water<br>
HOW TO GET HIM: Fall City sewers, you will need to have a Raticate with<br>
you and simply break the fence which is placed before the<br>
tube with many different exits. You can also get it as<br>
part of the storyline.</p>
<p>R-073 -&gt; Totodile<br>
TYPE: Water<br>
FIELD MOVE: Water<br>
BATTLE MOVE: Water<br>
HOW TO GET HIM: on the Fall City sewers.</p>
<p>R-074 -&gt; Croconaw<br>
TYPE: Water<br>
FIELD MOVE: Water x2<br>
BATTLE MOVE: Water<br>
HOW TO GET HIM: on the Fall City sewers.</p>
<p>R-075 -&gt; Feraligatr<br>
TYPE: Water<br>
FIELD MOVE: Break x3<br>
BATTLE MOVE: Water<br>
HOW TO GET HIM: on the Fall City sewers, you need to use “Cross” and then<br>
“Fire x2” in the room after the one which contains<br>
Koffing.</p>
<p>R-076 -&gt; Squirtle<br>
TYPE: Water<br>
FIELD MOVE: Water<br>
BATTLE MOVE: Water<br>
HOW TO GET HIM: on the Fall City sewers, you need to use “Cross” in the<br>
room after the one which contains the Koffing.</p>
<p>R-077 -&gt; Wartortle<br>
TYPE: Water<br>
FIELD MOVE: Water x2<br>
BATTLE MOVE: Water<br>
HOW TO GET HIM: forest, on mission 6 or later, you need to use “Break” in<br>
order to remove a huge stone which is near the river.</p>
<p>R-078 -&gt; Blastoise<br>
TYPE: Water<br>
FIELD MOVE: Water x3<br>
BATTLE MOVE: Water<br>
HOW TO GET HIM: as part of the storyline OR on Fall City, where you<br>
previously a Staryu.</p>
<p>R-079 -&gt; Voltorb<br>
TYPE: Electric<br>
FIELD MOVE: Charge<br>
BATTLE MOVE: Electric<br>
HOW TO GET HIM: as part of the storyline OR near the factory.</p>
<p>R-080 -&gt; Machop<br>
TYPE: Fighting<br>
FIELD MOVE: Break<br>
BATTLE MOVE: Fighting<br>
HOW TO GET HIM: in the tunnel, on mission 5 or later.</p>
<p>R-081 -&gt; Machoke<br>
TYPE: Fighting<br>
FIELD MOVE: Break x2<br>
BATTLE MOVE: Fighting<br>
HOW TO GET HIM: as part of the storyline OR in the factory.</p>
<p>R-082 -&gt; Machamp<br>
TYPE: Fighting<br>
FIELD MOVE: Break x3<br>
BATTLE MOVE: Fighting<br>
HOW TO GET HIM: at Team GoGo’s base OR in the tunnel, after completing the<br>
game once.</p>
<p>R-083 -&gt; Makuhita<br>
TYPE: Fighting<br>
FIELD MOVE: Tackle x2<br>
BATTLE MOVE: Fighting<br>
HOW TO GET HIM: in Fall City.</p>
<p>R-084 -&gt; Hariyama<br>
TYPE: Fighting<br>
FIELD MOVE: Break x3<br>
BATTLE MOVE: Fighting<br>
HOW TO GET HIM: as part of the storyline OR in the tunnel.</p>
<p>R-085 -&gt; Meditite<br>
TYPE: Psychic<br>
FIELD MOVE: Break<br>
BATTLE MOVE: Fighting<br>
HOW TO GET HIM: in the Fall City sewers.</p>
<p>R-086 -&gt; Medicham<br>
TYPE: Psychic<br>
FIELD MOVE: Break x2<br>
BATTLE MOVE: Fighting<br>
HOW TO GET HIM: at the cave.</p>
<p>R-087 -&gt; Grimer<br>
TYPE: Poison<br>
FIELD MOVE: none<br>
BATTLE MOVE: Poison<br>
HOW TO GET HIM: as part of the storyline.</p>
<p>R-088 -&gt; Muk<br>
TYPE: Poison<br>
FIELD MOVE: none<br>
BATTLE MOVE: Poison<br>
HOW TO GET HIM: as part of the storyline.</p>
<p>R-089 -&gt; Koffing<br>
TYPE: Poison<br>
FIELD MOVE: none<br>
BATTLE MOVE: Poison<br>
HOW TO GET HIM: in the Fall City sewers.</p>
<p>R-090 -&gt; Drowzee<br>
TYPE: Psychic<br>
FIELD MOVE: none<br>
BATTLE MOVE: Psychic<br>
HOW TO GET HIM: in the Fall City sewers.</p>
<p>R-091 -&gt; Hypno<br>
TYPE: Psychic<br>
FIELD MOVE: none<br>
BATTLE MOVE: Psychic<br>
HOW TO GET HIM: at the factory.</p>
<p>R-092 -&gt; Mr. Mime<br>
TYPE: Psychic<br>
FIELD MOVE: none<br>
BATTLE MOVE: Psychic<br>
HOW TO GET HIM: as part of the storyline.</p>
<p>R-093 -&gt; Pinsir<br>
TYPE: Bug<br>
FIELD MOVE: Cut x2<br>
BATTLE MOVE: Bug<br>
HOW TO GET HIM: at the factory.</p>
<p>R-094 -&gt; Gastly<br>
TYPE: Ghost<br>
FIELD MOVE: none<br>
BATTLE MOVE: Ghost<br>
HOW TO GET HIM: at the factory.</p>
<p>R-095 -&gt; Haunter<br>
TYPE: Ghost<br>
FIELD MOVE: none<br>
BATTLE MOVE: Ghost<br>
HOW TO GET HIM: at the factory.</p>
<p>R-096 -&gt; Gengar<br>
TYPE: Ghost<br>
FIELD MOVE: none<br>
BATTLE MOVE: Ghost<br>
HOW TO GET HIM: at the temple.</p>
<p>R-097 -&gt; Snubull<br>
TYPE: Normal<br>
FIELD MOVE: Tackle<br>
BATTLE MOVE: none<br>
HOW TO GET HIM: on Fall City.</p>
<p>R-098 -&gt; Skitty<br>
TYPE: Normal<br>
FIELD MOVE: none<br>
BATTLE MOVE: none<br>
HOW TO GET HIM: as part of the storyline OR on Fall City.</p>
<p>R-099 -&gt; Meowth<br>
TYPE: Normal<br>
FIELD MOVE: Cut<br>
BATTLE MOVE: none<br>
HOW TO GET HIM: on Fall City.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/pokemon-ranger-walkthrough/115823/8">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/pokemon-ranger-walkthrough/115823/8</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 24 Jun 2007 15:05:37 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-115823-8</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/pokemon-ranger-walkthrough/115823.rss">Pokemon ranger walkthrough</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Pokemon ranger walkthrough</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@pk3r_kyle pk3r kyle]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/pk3r_kyle">@pk3r_kyle</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>3.10~. Win Town</p>
<p>A lot more conversation and then your mission will really be over. Some<br>
time later, you will finally see the (usual) screen that allows you to<br>
save the game and then it will be over.</p>
<p>I mean, the game isn’t over yet, but there aren’t any more “normal”<br>
missions for you to take. Rumor has it that in Japan you can download at<br>
least 2 extra missions, but I wasn’t able to try that, so I can’t talk<br>
much about it. Therefore, all there is to do right now is capturing all<br>
pokemon, which is actually doable in the game, without requiring you to<br>
have any other games, unlike usually happens on pokemon games.</p>
<p>But… well… that’s all for this section, I guess, unless you’re not<br>
playing the Japanese version of the game.</p>
<p>3.11~. Special Missions</p>
<p>In the American Version of the game, after beating the 3 legendary dogs<br>
you will unlock something called Ranger Net,  Basically, it is a place<br>
which grants you a couple Special Missions, which I will talk about in<br>
a minute.</p>
<p>3.11.1~. Special Mission 1 (Deoxys)</p>
<p>First, you get to battle Deoxys, which eventually runs away from battle<br>
and leading to an event where you’re informed that you can only capture<br>
such Pokemon when it is in its Normal form. Go to the place near the<br>
tunnel, you’ll fight it some more times and eventually you will reach a<br>
place where it won’t run away from you.<br>
Then, keep on attacking him and eventually it will lead to a scene where<br>
he turns into his very own Normal Form. When that happens, try to stun him<br>
using Plusle/Minun’s attack (obviously, at full power) and then circle him<br>
as quickly as possible.</p>
<p>3.11.2~. Special Mission 2 (Celebi)</p>
<p>In the forest, you’ll see this pokemon and a couple scenes. Then, try to<br>
capture it (a fire pokemon is advisable, for obvious reasons) and he won’t<br>
probably put you into much trouble, since he only requires 3 circles to<br>
capture.</p>
<p>3.11.3~. Special Mission 3 (Mew)</p>
<p>After finding him in the jungle, simply use your older strategies (mainly,<br>
the stunning one) and you can probably get it in no time.</p>
<p>3.11.4~. Special Mission 4 (Manaphy’s Egg)</p>
<p>In the Japanese version of the game, you acquired this quest by an easier<br>
task. However, in the American version, after completing the game you must<br>
go to the “Ranger Net” option, from the main menu, hold down R, X and<br>
press left (in the directional controls), which will unlock a password<br>
option. In there, enter the password for this mission, and a new mission<br>
will appear, in its proper place.<br>
In there, you’ll take a small mission, in the forest and tunnel that, when<br>
beaten, grants you the amazing Manaphy Egg, which you can later send to<br>
Pokemon Diamond/Pearl, in order to unlock that secret pokemon.<br>
In case you’re wondering on what password you need to input, it seems to<br>
change depending on your version of the game. Here are some of the<br>
possible ones:</p>
<p>P8M2-9D6F-43H7  – American version<br>
Mg35-Cpb8-4FW8  – U.K. Version<br>
C58f-t3WT-Vn79  – Overall European Version (?)</p>
<p>Be aware that these aren’t all the possible ones. There are probably many<br>
others, but since I couldn’t find all of them, I can’t add them here. If<br>
none of these work for you, try checking magazines and gaming websites<br>
from your country, as they may have the proper code.</p>
<p>4~. Acquirable Pokemon and their moves</p>
<p>Unlike what happened in most of the previous Pokemon games, in here not<br>
all of the famous monsters will be available for capturing. Actually, only<br>
around 212 of them are capturable in this game, and while some may be easy<br>
to find and capture, others aren’t. Therefore, this is the section of this<br>
guide that you should read in order to know what pokemon you can in fact<br>
capture in this game, where to capture them and their powers.<br>
Be sure to remember that each Pokemon has (usually) two powers, one that<br>
can be used in the middle of the battles and another which can be used<br>
while in the middle of the field. In order to learn more about those<br>
attacks, be sure to read the “Pokemon Type” section of this same guide.<br>
Now, on to the Pokemon themselves, their information will usually be given<br>
in the following way:</p>
<p>R-number of the pokemon in this game -&gt; name of that pokemon<br>
TYPE: the type of that particular pokemon<br>
FIELD MOVE: the field move that this pokemon can use, if any<br>
BATTLE MOVE: the battle move that this pokemon can use, if any<br>
HOW TO GET HIM: whatever you need to do in order to capture this pokemon</p>
<p>Understood? This is mostly everything you need to know in order to fully<br>
comprehend the list below. So, I hope you find it easy to do by now, as<br>
you can actually find all the important information for getting all your<br>
Pokemon in this section!</p>
<p>I have to state that when you read “as part of the storyline” in the<br>
section of “HOW TO GET HIM”, I am basically trying to tell you that you<br>
will probably find him while normally playing across the story of this<br>
game, at least I did it while writing this guide. In case you really can’t<br>
seem to find it AS PART OF THE STORY and you aren’t following my guide,<br>
contact me about such problem and I will try to fix it as soon as<br>
possible.</p>
<p>As a final note, I have to state that the best time to try capturing all<br>
these pokemon is after completing the main story. This way, you will be<br>
able to travel wherever you want and each of the areas you find will be<br>
filled with even more pokemon than before, including some new ones. Bear<br>
this in mind while reading this entire guide, meaning that if you can’t<br>
seem to find a certain pokemon in a proper location, maybe he isn’t there<br>
<em>YET</em> !</p>
<p>Now, on to what probably you wanna read…</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/pokemon-ranger-walkthrough/115823/7">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/pokemon-ranger-walkthrough/115823/7</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 24 Jun 2007 15:04:27 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-115823-7</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/pokemon-ranger-walkthrough/115823.rss">Pokemon ranger walkthrough</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Pokemon ranger walkthrough</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@pk3r_kyle pk3r kyle]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/pk3r_kyle">@pk3r_kyle</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>2.31~. Win Town</p>
<p>You’ll get your tenth (and last) medal, along with ability to finally take<br>
up to 7 pokemon with you. Eventually you will get yet another mission, so<br>
you should exit this headquarters and move out of town, by taking the<br>
upper exit. Go all the way up to the place where you had to use a Tangela<br>
to go to the other side of the cliff AND when you’re at the top of the<br>
moutain (slightly before the area I just told you about), you will notice<br>
that the huge gates from before are now open. Obviously (or we wouldn’t be<br>
be here), you should enter them and go up the stairs, which will unlock<br>
your last mission.</p>
<p>2.32~. Mission 10</p>
<p>Go slightly up, and you’ll see someone closing another of those huge<br>
gates. Interact with the gates and you’ll see a new scene, where the<br>
Charizard from before appears and opens the gates for you. Cross them and<br>
you can save your game if you like. Go up the stairs, all to the right and<br>
up the stairs, continue going up and turn left before the second stairs,<br>
falling on the hole between the 3 pillars. Follow that path to the lower<br>
left corner and then jump down, in that exact place. Proceed all to the<br>
left and when you reach the end of that platform and jump to the left,<br>
going up the stairs and all the way up and up on the next stairs, to the<br>
left and up another stairs, after which you’ll see a Raichu, which you<br>
should capture. Head all to the left and up the stairs, follow that path<br>
and eventually you will find yourself seeing another cutscene.</p>
<p>Basically, you have to put the 3 main Eevee evolutions on those stone<br>
squares, and I mean Vaporeon, Flareon and Jolteon. From here, jump down<br>
from the lower left square, then turn right and you should go down the<br>
stairs, as you will find an entrance in there. That place is full of rare<br>
pokemon, which you could try to capture, and there’s even a Flareon in the<br>
room at the lower area. Capture AT LEAST the Flareon, the 2 Gengars and<br>
the Espeon before going out, but remember that you still need to find the<br>
other 2 main Eevee evolutions.</p>
<p>From the exit of that small place, go up the stairs and all to the left,<br>
falling down the ledge from the leftmost point for the Vaporeon, who<br>
usually tries to run from the battle as soon as possible. Stun him with<br>
the electrical attack and then you should quickly capture him. Now, head<br>
back to the stone squares and interact with the ones in the left and right<br>
sides, for getting rid of 2 (out of 3) pokemon which you were required to<br>
capture.</p>
<p>From there, go all the way to the right and fall down the rightmost ledge<br>
twice, to find yourself in an area with the Jolteon, which you can capture<br>
with some help from a Gengar. Now, use the Raichu to heal you and go all<br>
the way back to the room which contained all the rare pokemon capturing a<br>
Medicham and the Gengar which you just used to capture the Jolteon.</p>
<p>Head back to the stone squares and interact with the middle one, which<br>
will cause the huge door to open. Enter it, SAVE YOUR GAME and then start<br>
climbing the huge building on front of you, facing several battles. You<br>
can (and should…) go back and save after each of them, but it’s really<br>
up to you.</p>
<p>For the first one, simply stun everyone and be sure to capture at least 2<br>
out of the 3 pokemon. As for the last one, simply capture it, as you would<br>
usually do. Proceed all to the right.</p>
<p>For the second one, use the Espeon and be sure to capture at least 2 out<br>
of the 3 pokemon. As in the battle before, you should then simply try to<br>
capture the last one as you normally would. Up the stairs…</p>
<p>For this third one, be aware that you may need to heal during the battle,<br>
and you should use your Raichu for that purpose. As soon as you have your<br>
special bar filled, stun your two enemies with the eletrical attack and<br>
the capture the Blaziken (the fire pokemon…). As for Blastoise, he isn’t<br>
much of a threat alone, but I guess you can use your Gengar to help<br>
capturing him.</p>
<p>After the battle, instead of continuing, you should go back to the<br>
previous area, fully heal yourself (and I mean it!) and then capture the<br>
following pokemon: Medicham, Gengar, Gengar (yep, 2 of them!), Espeon,<br>
Flareon, Raichu. When you have captured all of those, heal yourself, be<br>
sure to have your special bar completly filled and then head to the place<br>
inside the gates. As before, be sure to save your game and then climb to<br>
the top of the building, where you will be asked to confirm if you really<br>
wanna go (or not). Obviously, you should want to do it by now…</p>
<p>Long cutscene, and then you will have to fight a Raikou. By simply dodging<br>
his thunders (or waiting for them to go away) and then striking with one<br>
of your Gengar you will do just fine, as your enemy isn’t very strong.</p>
<p>Then, after a small cutscene, you will have to fight a Suicune. Stun him<br>
as soon as the battle begins, before he has the opportunity to create some<br>
clones, and you will then be able to easily capture him.</p>
<p>Another cutscene, and you will finally fight the most powerful of the 3<br>
beasts, an… Entei! Strangely, this time he is way stronger than the last<br>
time you saw him, and he will be covered by some small flames that grant<br>
him a certain immortality. “Capture” this pokemon normally until all the<br>
flames surrounding him disappear, and then you can use the Espeon to stun<br>
it for a while, but EXACTLY after using it, call for the Medicham and use<br>
it to have an even easier time. If you can’t do it, call for the other<br>
pokemon you currently have. There’s also an interesting technique in which<br>
you can simply held your opponent in there (by taking only 1, 2 HP at each<br>
time and then lifting your stylus) until the flames disappear, then stun<br>
him with a full powered thundershock and then use the Medicham (or simply<br>
capture him normally, like I did, but such technique is for more advanced<br>
players!). Believe me, this battle will be really hard, but eventually you<br>
will manage to beat your opponent and a cutscene will appear.</p>
<p>Strangely, the man from before will be gone, and your boss will appear,<br>
leading to this game’s final cutscene, where most of the events in this<br>
game are finally spoiled for you, and the mission will be over, as will<br>
the game. Well, or at least the main storyline will… You can see the<br>
credits and all the usual stuff, and then your game will be saved.</p>
<p>Now, you should continue reading in this next section of this guide…[br][size=1]Posted on: June 24, 2007, 04:01:56 AM[/size][hr]3~. What now?</p>
<p>As you may have read above, after the credits and all that, your game will<br>
be saved. Load it as you normally would, and then you’ll see a large<br>
cutscene, allowing you to eventually gain access to the data of your<br>
partner’s pokemon. Then, take the elevator to the second floor and talk to<br>
the man next to the Dragonite, who will allow you to choose what city you<br>
want to go to. Pick “F”, for Fall city.</p>
<p>3.1~. Fall City</p>
<p>Try to enter the headquarters and you will receive a message. Now, go to<br>
the house where you used a Staryu to light the basement, and talk to the<br>
guy who is inside, but not without first releasing the pokemon which you<br>
captured, if any. (In case you don’t know how to do it, simply access the<br>
menu by pressing START, select the upper option and then select each<br>
pokemon in there, pressing the upper button after each one)</p>
<p>You will get a new cutscene and eventually be back to the headquarters in<br>
this city and get a new mission, when you exit this headquarters.</p>
<p>3.2~. Extra Mission 1</p>
<p>After the cutscene, go down the ladder and you’ll have to fight 4 Staryu<br>
at the same time. Stun them with the electrical attack and then easily<br>
capture them. When you’re back in the outside, visit that house you’ve<br>
just seen and then you will have to beat 4 Krabby, which you can easily<br>
capture (c’mon, they are really slow!). After such battle, go to the<br>
outside and then slightly down, where you will see yet another scene. Make<br>
your way to the pokemon in the lower right corner and you will have to<br>
fight them, they are some Carvanha. Stun them all with a fully powered<br>
electrical attack and you will then be able to capture them easily.</p>
<p>Now, you’ll see some strange things in the sea, so you should board in the<br>
Lapras and you’ll (eventually) be taken into some whirlpools, where you<br>
will get to see a Kyogre. He isn’t strong, but he can summons waves that<br>
seem to cause massive damage, so you should wait until less waves are<br>
coming (that <em>eventually</em> happens, you just have to wait!) and then<br>
capture him as quickly as possible. The electrical attack may also<br>
slightly help you, but be sure to avoid the waves at all costs, as they<br>
may put you into trouble.</p>
<p>After the battle, you will be taken to the headquarters nearby and your<br>
mission will end.</p>
<p>3.3~. Fall City</p>
<p>After the long conversation, you will find yourself outside of the<br>
headquarters. Therefore, enter it once again and then take the elevator<br>
up, using the Dragonite to go to Ring Town.</p>
<p>3.4~. Ring Town</p>
<p>In here, enter the headquarters, release all the pokemon you may have (if<br>
any) and then talk to your boss. After all the conversation, you will be<br>
taken to Summer Town.</p>
<p>3.5~. Summer Town</p>
<p>Some more conversation, an eartquake will occur and you will eventually be<br>
given a new mission. Exit the headquarters and then you will find yourself<br>
instantly at the fire cave, where you found that pyramid from before and<br>
your mission will start.</p>
<p>3.6~. Extra Mission 2</p>
<p>Go to the right, up, cross the bridge to the left side, continue going and<br>
you will see that your partner is trapped inside that cave with a huge<br>
rock. Capture the Rhydon nearby and then use him to get rid of that huge<br>
rock. Small cutscene, enter the cave and be sure to capture the 2<br>
Poliwrath.</p>
<p>Back to the outside, head all to the right across the bridge and use one<br>
of the Poliwrath to get rid of the huge glowing fire stone. Capture as<br>
many pokemon as you want, but be sure to keep the other Poliwrath with you<br>
at all times. When you’re ready, go all the way up and enter the next<br>
area.</p>
<p>Continue going up and fight the guy from Team GoGo, having some help from<br>
any fire pokemon to easily capture the two enemies. After defeating them,<br>
head to the left side and capture (and use) the Manectric as many times as<br>
it takes to fully heal you. When you’re done, capture him yet again and<br>
then go up the stairs on the right.</p>
<p>On the next room, go all the way down and down the stairs. Capture the<br>
other electrical pokemon, another Manectric on the upper left corner and<br>
go up those stairs, on the upper left corner. Explore that room up to the<br>
end, as you can find some Charmeleon in there. You can also capture<br>
another Rhydon in there, if you want. After doing so, go to the outside<br>
and to the right, saving your game before going up the stairs.</p>
<p>On the next room, go all the way up until you reach a new room and you<br>
will be able to capture an Arcanine, which you can easily stun (with the<br>
eletrical attack) and capture. Now, go all the way down and back to the<br>
room with the 2 Charmeleon, where you should drop down an hole in the<br>
floor, which is placed between the 2 Charmander and the place where you<br>
could previously see 2 Charmeleon. You’ll see a new scene and you should<br>
then enter the door that just opened.</p>
<p>You’ll find a Groudon inside, which you can easily capture with the help<br>
of your Poliwrath. You kept it, didn’t you? I hope so… After the<br>
cutscene you’ll be brought back to town.</p>
<p>3.7~. Summer Town</p>
<p>The usual cutscene, and your mission will be (literally) over. When all<br>
the conversation ends, you should enter the headquarters once again, take<br>
the elevator up and talk to the guy near the Dragonite. This time, go to<br>
Win Town.</p>
<p>3.8~. Win Town</p>
<p>When you’re there, talk to the woman in the right (not before releasing<br>
your pokemon, as you did before) and a bigger cutscene will follow, where<br>
the other guy from before will join you and you will gain yet another new<br>
mission. Exit the headquarters and you will instantly find yourself in the<br>
place of the mission.</p>
<p>3.9~. Extra Mission 3</p>
<p>Start by going up and you will have to fight a guy with 3 Ekans. Easily<br>
defeat them and then search the entire area for a Ralts, a Kirlia and a<br>
Gardevoir. I can’t tell you where they are since they seem to change their<br>
location, but you can simply continue searching and eventually you will<br>
get all 3 of them.</p>
<p>After doing so, visit the place where you previously put the 3 evolutions<br>
of Eevee and you’ll see a cutscene. Interact with the 3 stone blocks and<br>
put the 3 pokemon I told you to capture in there, which will lead to yet<br>
another cutscene. Go up and fight 2 pokemon in that huge building, which<br>
you can easily defeat by using your usual thundershock. Now, go all the<br>
way down to the previous area and capture the following pokemon: Medicham,<br>
Gengar, Gengar (yes, 2 of them, once again…), Espeon, Umbreon, Raichu.<br>
Their locations are the same as before. Once you have all of them return<br>
to the huge building and fight the second group of enemies. Using a single<br>
Gengar, capture all of them and then continue going.</p>
<p>You’d better heal and save your game at this point, but it is really up to<br>
you. At the top you’ll find a Rayquaza, which you should capture with some<br>
help from a Gengar, which will make this battle really easy.</p>
<p>After the battle, some more conversation will occur and you will be back<br>
to town.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/pokemon-ranger-walkthrough/115823/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/pokemon-ranger-walkthrough/115823/6</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 24 Jun 2007 15:03:45 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-115823-6</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/pokemon-ranger-walkthrough/115823.rss">Pokemon ranger walkthrough</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Pokemon ranger walkthrough</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@pk3r_kyle pk3r kyle]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/pk3r_kyle">@pk3r_kyle</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>2.22~. Fall City</p>
<p>After the conversation, you will get a new mission, where you should go to<br>
the central part of the city and then to the exit on the right side of it.</p>
<p>2.23~. Mission 7</p>
<p>This will start with a small cutscene, you simply have to interact with<br>
the door and the guy following you will open it. The front door is (as it<br>
is usual in this kind of game) closed, so you must go all the way around<br>
the building. Simply proceed to the right, and all the way around, you can<br>
catch some Voltorb but you MUST capture a Meowth and a Makuhita.<br>
When you captured at least those 2 pokemon, head to the front of this<br>
factory and enter the silver door on the right.</p>
<p>Use the Meowth to get rid of the wooden fence on the left and then go up<br>
the stairs, where you should use the Makuhita to get rid of the box. Go<br>
down the hole and you can capture a Growlithe. After doing so, continue<br>
your way on the floor above, by taking the only possible path and<br>
defeating the 2 Voltorb. Proceed by that path for a short scene with Team<br>
GoGo, before continuing to the left.</p>
<p>There’s not much to say around here, except that you will see a Pikachu<br>
locked in a cage, but you can’t save it yet. Continue going up, for a room<br>
full of Mr. Mime, which you should exit by the left side. You’ll have to<br>
fight 2 Mr. Mime, which you should stun and capture as soon as possible.</p>
<p>Proceed to the left, then go up and to the right on the next room, going<br>
up the stairs. Be sure to capture the Pinsir in here, but you can also<br>
fight a Slakoth on the upper left corner of this room. When you’re done,<br>
go back to the room with the Pikachu and release it, which will make some<br>
Ghost pokemon appear around. Go back to the attic and capture another<br>
Pinsir before continuing.</p>
<p>Back to the room where you went up the stairs, this time you should exit<br>
the room by the lower exit, which will eventually take you to a battle<br>
against a Muk and two other strange pokemon. Capture the two of them by<br>
stunning them, and then head to capture the Muk.</p>
<p>Enter the door and capture the Houndoom, which you should then use in that<br>
big room (the one now filled with Gastly), to get rid of the thing that<br>
prevented you from going down the stairs. On that new room, beat the 3<br>
pokemon and continue going all the way down, where you will eventually<br>
need to face a whole lot of Rattata. It will be really easy to capture<br>
them all, you don’t even need to be afraid of it!</p>
<p>Down to the next room, which despite containing 3 exits, you must<br>
initially take the one in the right side. Make your way to the upper<br>
section of that room (yes, I know it is filled with eletrical floors, but<br>
I don’t think you can do it wrong, it is rather easy) and enter the new<br>
room, where you should use your Pinsir to release this Pikachu. Go back<br>
to the room you just came from, capture the Magneton and a Pinsir, then<br>
going for the room in the left, on that big room with 3 exits. Go all the<br>
way around the boxes and exit to the lower left room.</p>
<p>Here, go all the way up and you’ll see another cutscene, where you will be<br>
attacked by two pokemon, which you can easily stun and capture. When your<br>
enemy leaves, enter the room he came from and be sure to capture at least<br>
the Scyther, as you will be needing it soon.</p>
<p>Exit this room, proceed by the path in the right side of the room and<br>
enter the first door you see. Use the Scyther to release the Raichu, which<br>
will escape. Go all the way back to that room with 3 entrances, and while<br>
you are trying to do so, another member of Team GoGo will fight you. His<br>
pokemon, a Scizor, can be stunned with the electrical attack, so you can<br>
use it to easily capture it, provided you capture him quickly.</p>
<p>After the battle, your mission will be over and you will be taken back to<br>
your headquarters.</p>
<p>2.24~. Fall City</p>
<p>A small conversation, and then you will get another medal. When all the<br>
conversation ends, take the elevator to the second floor and use the<br>
Dragonite to go back to Summer Town.</p>
<p>2.25~. Summer Town</p>
<p>You’ll be seeing a slightly longer conversation, but at the end you can<br>
get a new mission. After that, exit to the jungle (as usual) and this new<br>
mission will start.</p>
<p>2.26~. Another mission</p>
<p>This one would be REALLY easy, if it wasn’t for a small detail: the guy<br>
who is following you is afraid of bugs. Interesting, hum? Every time he is<br>
touched by a bug, your position in this mission will be reset and you will<br>
have to do it all over again. A trick is to constantly check the map on<br>
the console’s upper screen, as you will normally know if anyone (either<br>
bug or simply another pokemon) are nearby.</p>
<p>You should start by exiting the first area by the upper left corner, then<br>
continue to the place where the Snorlax previously was, take the upper<br>
route in there, then the upper one and then all the way up, to reach a new<br>
area.</p>
<p>Here, go all the way up but be aware, as some bugs may cover your path. Up<br>
on the mountain parts covered with herb, and all the way up until you find<br>
a cave-like place, which contains a save point. From there, go slightly up<br>
and the guy who is following you will kick a Magikarp onto the water, an<br>
action which will awaken a powerful Gyarados, along with 4 amazing<br>
Magikarp. As soon as possible, stun everyone with an eletrical attack and<br>
then quickly capture ALL the Magikarp. As for the Gyarados, you can either<br>
restore your entire special bar and then stun (and quickly capture) him,<br>
or you can do it by skill, slowly capturing him and being specially aware<br>
of his beam, which he always uses twice in a row.</p>
<p>After the battle, another cutscene will be seen and your mission here will<br>
be over.</p>
<p>2.27~. Summer Town</p>
<p>Conversation, and eventually a new mission. Exit the headquarters and the<br>
guy you just met will talk to you, so you should visit the lower platforms<br>
in this town and another cutscene will be seen. When you are able to<br>
control your character once again, move to the submarine and your 8th<br>
mission will start.</p>
<p>2.28~. Mission 8</p>
<p>Oh, so this was the area in which the Magikarps are hanging outside of the<br>
water… I wonder how they do that, but nevermind, I am supposed to be<br>
writing about how to complete the game… Well, when the conversation<br>
ends, be sure to follow the guy into the next area.</p>
<p>When you reach it, you will notice that this room has quite a few new<br>
pokemon types, so you may want to try getting at least once of each<br>
species before heading into the next area, acessible at the top of this<br>
one. On the new one, start by going left (to capture a rare pokemon) and<br>
then go up, to yet another new room.</p>
<p>In here, instead of going up (as the man outside the cave may suggest) you<br>
should go all the way left, across the many rooms and capturing the<br>
several rare pokemon which will cross your path, but don’t forget to use<br>
that pokemon that I told you to capture in the last paragraph, as you can<br>
use it to break the huge rock and capture a Wobbuffet. When your done, go<br>
back to the place where the man was and up, to enter a not-yet-visited<br>
area.</p>
<p>In there, you will see a sleeping Steelix, which you need to awake by<br>
using the Poliwrath that you capture a few moments ago, in the area where<br>
you got the Wobbuffet. However, after making him disappear, be sure to<br>
head back and capture two water pokemon before proceeding. When you’re<br>
ready, enter the huge hole and go down the stairs, saving if you like.</p>
<p>On the next area, exit by the stairs on the left and you will see the guy<br>
from before talking to someone else. You should go right, but when you try<br>
to do it, you will see that those pokemon won’t allow you. Therefore, you<br>
need to bring them the other pokemon. In order to do it, take the upper<br>
path, go all the way up and down the hole in the floor. You will find<br>
yourself in a water area with lots of exits, but you should simply take<br>
the leftmost exit, which will take you to the pokemon you want to catch,<br>
so you should then return it to parents, so that they go away. You can<br>
proceed right away if you want, but you can also return to the water<br>
maze-like area and get the other rare pokemon in this area, which can be<br>
found by taking the rightmost exit.</p>
<p>When you’re ready, take the same path that all those pokemon and on to the<br>
next area. You can capture a Raichu and a Piloswine before going up the<br>
new stairs, something you sure should do. Next area, you can capture a<br>
Golem as a new pokemon BUT you can’t remove the huge ice blocks yet, as<br>
you will need a fire pokemon. When you’re ready, be sure to have at least<br>
a fighting pokemon (like the one you previously used to removed a rock<br>
before, a Medicham) and SAVE YOUR game in this room, then you can go all<br>
the way around the stage and up, making the Steelix attack you. He is one<br>
of the biggest pokemon you will see in the entire game, so you should be<br>
careful. Your best bet for capturing such beast is by stunning him and<br>
then QUICKLY putting the fighting pokemon into play, to cause as much<br>
damage as quickly as possible. It may take a while, but eventually you<br>
will manage to do it and a cutscene will follow.<br>
Another strategy for this battle is probably stun it at full power when he<br>
is moving in a loop and then use Medicham to quickly capture it.</p>
<p>The two people from before will appear, and so will a soldier from Team<br>
GoGo. Instead of heading to the Steelix’s cave (it doesn’t contain<br>
anything), follow those people by the only possible path and you will<br>
eventually find yourself going to another new zone, where you will be<br>
asked if you wanna drop your pokemon. Obviously, you should do it, or else<br>
you wouldn’t be able to continue. Go slightly up and your mission will be<br>
over.</p>
<p>2.29~. Win Town</p>
<p>After entering the headquarters, you will be given a new medal and you<br>
will be given another special bar, apart from a new mission. After all the<br>
conversation, leave this town by its upper exit, and your mission will<br>
start.</p>
<p>2.30~. Mission 9</p>
<p>When following the road, you will eventually see a scene with a Charizard<br>
flying around. Be sure to capture the 2 water pokemon in here, and then<br>
follow the road to the right side, fighting 6 weak enemies. When you see<br>
the sleeping Snorlax, turn left and continue following the road, fighting<br>
some more of those week enemies. Continue, and you will find yet some more<br>
enemies. Some more road, and eventually you reach the next area.</p>
<p>Some enemies will jump from tree, but you’d better run from the battle if<br>
they are too many. Up to 2 will be OK, but more of them may cause you a<br>
lot of trouble. However, they give a lot of EXP, so you could hang in here<br>
for a while, defeating them one by one. When you’re ready, go up for the<br>
next area.</p>
<p>Enter the house and you can talk to the man, who will restore your entire<br>
HP. Now, you should continue following the road BUT before crossing the<br>
bridge, go all the way up and you can capture a Raichu. Then, when<br>
crossing the bridge, you will see a rare pokemon being stalked by members<br>
of Team GoGo. It will later cause a lot of fog in this area, which you<br>
need to remove. The best way to find the pokemon causing this is by<br>
checking the map on the upper screen, you can use it to find where the<br>
pokemon are and then find the particular one. It isn’t very strong, but<br>
you will find it to be quick. After capturing such pokemon, go all the way<br>
up and continue following the road until you reach a new area.</p>
<p>You will need to knock the tree down, so you should capture a Piloswine<br>
(there’s one nearby) and use it to do the job. Go all way to the right and<br>
eventually you will see a zone with the trees burned down, you will also<br>
see the Charizard in there and you should touch him to fight him. When he<br>
is flying, start by stunning him with your thundershock and then attack<br>
your enemy with the water pokemon, but be aware to capture him QUICKLY, or<br>
else you will be in trouble. An interesting detail is that you can<br>
actually run away from this battle, so you’d better do it if you run out<br>
of water pokemon, as they are your best chance against this enemy. Even if<br>
the bubble doesn’t stand in there time enough, you can still try to<br>
capture him, but be way more careful when he is flying around, shooting<br>
flames out of his mouth.</p>
<p>After the battle you’ll see a short cutscene and you should then continue<br>
going up, obviously saving your game on the save point. Follow all the<br>
road until you find a Tangela, which you should capture. Continue going<br>
all the way up and at the top you should turn left, where you will have to<br>
face two pokemon. After defeating them, take the path in the left and<br>
follow the road, turning left on the first possible chance, but not before<br>
having 2 Tangela on your party.</p>
<p>In the next area, use those 2 Tangela to jump to the other side of the<br>
cliff and the continue following the road to the next area, where you will<br>
need to climb a huge mountain. When you’re reaching the top, an odd scene<br>
will occur and you will see a scene with a Team GoGo soldier. When you<br>
touch the switch, there will be no way back, so be sure that it is what<br>
you want to do. In case it REALLY is, continue reading.</p>
<p>Appears you’ve just entered Team GoGo’s headquarters! After the scene,<br>
enter the door and save your game, if you want. Here, there’s a single<br>
path for you to follow but there are some red floors that reset your<br>
position in this area. While you should try watch the patterns in which<br>
they lite up and turn off, I will try to provide you schematics on how to<br>
proceed in each area. You should simply follow the ordered number, but if<br>
the numbers are the same, it means that you should quickly move from one<br>
panel to the other, without waiting for the colors to change. The first<br>
two panels are easy, you just need to do:</p>
<p>X<br>
-&gt; 1</p>
<p>But continuing, you should then enter the door and you’ll see some more<br>
panels.</p>
<p>X X X X<br>
2 2 2 1 &lt;-</p>
<p>(After the first panel turns off, go there. Then, when all the other lower<br>
panels turn off, quickly move all the way, as shown above).</p>
<p>Continue advancing and the layout for the next one will be slightly<br>
harder than before:</p>
<p>X X X X<br>
-&gt; 1 2 3 4</p>
<p>(Board the first panel, and then continue heading to the right BUT only<br>
when the new panel turns off)</p>
<p>X 4 3 2 1<br>
4 4 X X X &lt;-</p>
<p>(Start slowly, but go quickly on the last 3 panels, as shown above).</p>
<p>Enter the door and continue going for more panel “fun”.</p>
<p>1 X<br>
1 X<br>
1 X<br>
1 X<br>
^<br>
|</p>
<p>(While the layout is simply, you should start moving as soon as the first<br>
panel turns off, moving in direct line AND as quickly as possible)</p>
<p>X 1<br>
X 1<br>
X 1<br>
X 1<br>
^<br>
|</p>
<p>(Once again, you should go as quickly as possible, just like in the panels<br>
you just faced)</p>
<p>Go down the stairs and this will all be finally over, no more panels for<br>
anyone. A huge door will close after you, so you’d better save your game<br>
before continuing.</p>
<p>Go left, capture the 3 pokemon in there and then exit by the upper green<br>
teleporter. Continue to the left and you will have to beat 3 pokemon at<br>
once. Here, you can get a powerful Swampert on the lower left corner, and<br>
you can then take the lower left exit. On the next room, take the only<br>
possible exit and you will find a Blaziken, which you should capture<br>
before heading to the right side. Follow all the way to the left and board<br>
the last teleporter, in the next room you should take the upper left one<br>
and you’ll have to fight against another enemy with 3 pokemon.</p>
<p>Take the only possible exit and then head to the right, going down the<br>
stairs when possible. Go down, capture all the pokemon and down once more,<br>
you’ll find your partner and you should then capture the 2 pokemon in the<br>
right, before going up two areas and using the Sneasel to remove the<br>
fence, where you will find an Electabuzz. First, use him to fully heal<br>
you, but you should then return to this same screen and capture him<br>
<em>again</em>. When you’re ready, take the red door and you will find yourself<br>
fighting against a Team GoGo member, who you should defeat with the aid of<br>
the water pokemon you captured before.</p>
<p>After the scene, heal yourself with the Electabuzz and then capture<br>
another one (and the Mankey nearby!) before heading into the blue door. In<br>
there, you’ll have to fight against 3 other enemies. Use the thundershock<br>
to easily capture the 2 weaker ones, and then go for the big one, which<br>
you should with strategy, as we did to capture it before.</p>
<p>One more scene, and you should then enter the same door which your enemies<br>
took. 3 more pokemon for you to battle, you should start by maxing out the<br>
power on your special bar and, when possible, use the thundershock to<br>
capture the 2 Scyther. Then, continue maxing out the power on the special<br>
bar, and when it is once again completly filled, you should stun the<br>
Scizor and then quickly capture it. Yet again, heal youself and capture<br>
another Electabuzz before heading down the stairs.</p>
<p>You can capture whoever you want in there, but be sure to enter the door<br>
and capture at least a single Machamp. Then, save you game and go all the<br>
way up on the room filled with Machamp, continue going up on the next room<br>
and you will need to fight the 3 forms of Larvitar. Start by easily<br>
capturing the Larvitar itself, then use a Metang to stun everyone and<br>
QUICKLY capture the Pupitar, and then finally use the Machamp to help you<br>
capturing the Tyranitar.</p>
<p>After the battle, an unusual cutscene will occur and your mission will be<br>
over. When all the conversation ends, go down the hole and exit the cave,<br>
which will take you to the outside and (eventually) back to town.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/pokemon-ranger-walkthrough/115823/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/pokemon-ranger-walkthrough/115823/5</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 24 Jun 2007 15:01:11 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-115823-5</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/pokemon-ranger-walkthrough/115823.rss">Pokemon ranger walkthrough</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Pokemon ranger walkthrough</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@pk3r_kyle pk3r kyle]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/pk3r_kyle">@pk3r_kyle</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>2.16~. Mission 6</p>
<p>While your partner is following you, there’s no way you can ask for<br>
his/her help or use his/her pokemon, in case you are wondering. So, you<br>
should simply go all the way up and talk to a man, continue going up and<br>
turn left on the second exit, head all the way down after the bridge, as<br>
you can capture a Marshtomp. As you may suppose, now you should go all the<br>
way up, until you reach a new area. A girl will start talking about her<br>
missing Jigglypuff, which you should proceed to find.</p>
<p>From here, go all the way up and you will see some rare Pokemon, go all to<br>
the left and eventually you will see her (at least a Jigglypuff is usually<br>
considered as a “she”…) jumping/floating around. When she is going to<br>
step on the floor, quickly move there and fight her. You can easily<br>
capture this pokemon, but you should then return to the little girl (who<br>
is still standing in the lower right corner of this area) and then proceed<br>
(now, without your partner) to get a Phanpy, which you should use toattack<br>
a tree, until it drops a Beedrill. Using him, get rid of the stone in the<br>
right side of scenario, next to the lower section of the river. By going<br>
down in there, you will be able to get a Wartortle.</p>
<p>Now that you’ve done it, head to the left area of this area, which will<br>
lead you to a new area, which contains a single wooden shrine. No, there<br>
isn’t any Celebi in here, so you should continue to the left and, in the<br>
next room, go all the way down to face a group of new pokemon and even to<br>
find your beloved Pikachu. From here, go back up and turn left on the<br>
first place, continue to the left and down, left on the next possible<br>
choice and continue up to the next area, where you will find a mysterious<br>
man, after jumping off a short cliff.</p>
<p>After the conversation, proceed to the left and capture a Quilava, which<br>
will lead to another short conversation. Follow the path in order to see<br>
Murkrow, which will run away. Use the Quilava to remove the tree in your<br>
path, which will lead to yet another conversation. Continue to the next<br>
area, all the way up but be careful with all the Beedrill hanging around,<br>
until you reach yet another new area.</p>
<p>The pokemon in the new are mostly peaceful, but you should capture them as<br>
usual, before heading to the area in the right. By first taking the upper<br>
path, you will understand that this area is slightly like a labyrinth, so<br>
you should take the lower path once, which will allow you to get a<br>
Nincada. Then, head back to the previous area (by taking the left path)<br>
and use this pokemon to remove the bush on the central path area. Enter<br>
the newly seen hole and you will see a Venosaur, which you can capture<br>
with some aid from a Beedrill, if you have one with you.</p>
<p>After capturing it, exit this small cave and go left, to find yourself in<br>
the labyrinthic area once again. Start by taking the lower path, then<br>
follow the upper one and finally go for the lower one, which will lead to<br>
another scene with the Murkrow. After that one, capture a Phanpy and use<br>
him on the tree, which will drop down the Murkrow, leading to another<br>
short scene.</p>
<p>When you are ready, go to the dark pokemon and be sure to capture him<br>
(however, he will have some help, if you know what I mean…), an action<br>
which may turn out easier if you use the thundershock to capture the 4<br>
Spinarak which are running around. You can then use a Phanpy (in case you<br>
have a stocked one) or even a Venosaur to help you capture the Murkrow<br>
itself, which shouldn’t pose you much of a trouble.</p>
<p>After the battle they will all run away, so you should take the lower path<br>
to exit this area and see the cutscene which ends this mission.</p>
<p>2.17~. Ring Town</p>
<p>Another medal, you will be able to carry one more pokemon with you, and<br>
you will even acquire another special bar, always nice. Your boss will<br>
take the elevator up, so you should do the same thing and you will have to<br>
fight a Dragonite. He doesn’t have much HP but he is indeed quick, so you<br>
will have to try circling him as quickly as possible (and forget about the<br>
earned EXP, in here…) and that is probably the best, and yet only, tip I<br>
can give you about it.</p>
<p>After the battle, you will be taken to Summer Town.</p>
<p>2.18~. Summer Town</p>
<p>You will eventually be taken to the inside of the headquarters, where you<br>
will once again meet your partner and all that. When possible, exit it and<br>
follow to the forest, once again making your way to the inside of the<br>
pyramid, the same one you visited in a previous mission. In your way<br>
there, you will face a funny cutscene, but when you are back inside the<br>
pyramid, your partner will touch the strange statue in front of you and a<br>
new path will be appear. Enter it, go all the way down the stairs and you<br>
will have to face a new mission.</p>
<p>2.19~. New Mission</p>
<p>While this mission doesn’t seem to have a real number, it indeed has an<br>
interesting feature, with the player being able to select which area he<br>
wants to face first. There is a cutscene with an Entei statue that you can<br>
see by crossing the upper area of main bridge, but there are 4 different<br>
areas for you to play, 2 in each side of the bridge.</p>
<p>Since the lower left area is still unable to be followed, and one of the<br>
entrances in the upper left leads nowhere, there are initially only 3<br>
areas for you to choose between, 2 on the right side of the bridge and 1<br>
on the left side of it. I suggest you start by the left side, but it is<br>
really up to you. In there, you will face:</p>
<ul>
<li>
<p>On the upper left side, you will find a windy room, where you simply<br>
need to reach the upper central area, which contains a door to a battle.<br>
In case you have been using the stylus to control the character, in here<br>
you’d better use the directional controls to do it, as it will turn your<br>
task into something easier. At the end, you should face (and obviously<br>
beat) a Flygon, which is weak but REALLY quick. Therefore, you should<br>
wait for him to be in the middle of the screen, preparing to attack, and<br>
then circle him as quickly as possible. Hopefully, you will capture it<br>
without much trouble.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>On the lower right side, you will find a room with 5 Gyarados shooting<br>
water bubbles. In case you are hit by one of those, you will fall to the<br>
floor below and you’ll have to start over. This isn’t very hard, you<br>
simply need to see where the bubbles are heading and try to walk only<br>
when you’re sure that you won’t be hit. At the end, you’ll have to face<br>
2 Kingdra, which aren’t even very hard to capture. You can simply stun<br>
(and quickly capture) one of them with your thundershock, and then you<br>
can simply normally capture the other. Be aware not to lift the stylus<br>
when they are inside the water, or your capture will fail. Apart from<br>
that, this one is probably the most easy of the 4 areas.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>On the upper right side, you will find a room where you simply need to<br>
step on the huge yellow switches to spawn some enemies, which you should<br>
capture and use to destroy the blocks nearby. It is an easy task, and<br>
you should destroy all the blocks before proceeding to the last door.<br>
There’s no way you can take more pokemon with you there, and when you<br>
destroy the last block all your pokemon will run away (well, besides the<br>
one which always follows you), as you will have to face a powerful<br>
dragon, Salamence. This will probably be your toughest battle this far,<br>
as you will need to be extremely careful with your foe. The stunning<br>
attack of your pokemon doesn’t seem to help at all, so you have to do it<br>
by skill, which turns out being really hard, as your enemy has a nice<br>
22 points of HP. Your best best is to start circling him as soon as he<br>
lands on the floor (causing a massive explosion…), be aware of his<br>
beam and when he starts flying, try to circle him as quickly as<br>
possible, always without touching it. With some tries, you will probably<br>
manage to beat him, but besides that there’s not much I can tell you,<br>
sorry about that.</p>
</li>
</ul>
<p>After beat these 3 areas, you will finally be able to enter the one in the<br>
lower left, which you should take after saving your game. In there, you<br>
will find an unimportant room (c’mon, you will only fall out of this area<br>
if you are REALLY dumb), so you should simply head to the upper section,<br>
where you will see a Charizard and Team GoGo. Another cutscene will then<br>
follow, and eventually you will see the Charizard roaming around. You must<br>
touch it when it is back in the ground, and a battle will start.</p>
<p>While he isn’t very strong, your main problem may be having enough time to<br>
capture him. Each time he starts spitting fire, his HP will reset, so your<br>
biggest problem may be the one of getting him. Well, you should bear in<br>
mind that when you’re hit with one of those small static flames, they seem<br>
to disappear, and that’s something you could try to use for your own<br>
advantage. Exactly after he stops spitting fire, you should try to circle<br>
him as many times and as quickly as possible, but don’t mind about the<br>
EXP, think simply of capturing him and completing the battle. Eventually<br>
you will be able to do it, and the game will continue.</p>
<p>Your life will (fortunately) be restored, so you should exit this area<br>
(there’s no need to check the upper room) and go the the middle of the big<br>
bridge, where the statue of an Entei was. A new scene will appear, in<br>
which the statue disappears, and then the mountain will strangely start to<br>
shake. When you proceed to check what happened, a new mission appears.</p>
<p>2.20~. Yet another mission</p>
<p>Hum, a real Entei is around… I wonder how he got here, NOT! Well, back<br>
to what matters, appears that this area was actually a volcano, which you<br>
will now need to calm down. Proceed to the right and all the way up, where<br>
you will fight two fire pokemon. From there, go up and right to get a<br>
Graveler, which you can easily capture if you wait until he rises from the<br>
floor. In this same room, use him to get rid of the huge rock on the lower<br>
right corner, above the stairs. Inside, you will capture a Tangela and a<br>
Sceptile, which you can capture with some help from a fire pokemon.</p>
<p>Getting in the outside, cross the bridge to the left side and you will<br>
fight a Rapidash. Cut the brown fence for a small cave with 2 water<br>
pokemon, all of which you should capture. Back to the outside, continue<br>
going up and you will be able to get a Manectric, but you should also<br>
enter a small cave, the same one that previously didn’t have anything in<br>
there, which now has 2 Beldum. A Magmar can sometimes also be seen in the<br>
outside, so in case you see him, be sure to capture one.</p>
<p>When you’re done, go back to the right side of the bridge and then<br>
continue all the way up, you’ll reach a new screen and eventually fight 3<br>
Slugma. Instead of following the new stairs, continue going up and you’ll<br>
have to fight a Meowth and a Sneasel, before trying to capture the Rhydon,<br>
which is hanging nearby. With his help, get into the stairs you previously<br>
unlocked (when you beat the 3 Slugma) and use him to destroy the huge<br>
rocks that fell from the top of the cave.</p>
<p>Going slightly down, you will find a Houndoom, but you should continue<br>
heading down and down in the stairs which are seen at the end. Follow the<br>
only possible path and you will see another cutscene with the woman from<br>
before. Instead of instantly going up on those stairs, take the ones in<br>
the far left and you will be able to get some Charmander. You are then<br>
free to save your game and go up the stairs.</p>
<p>In there, you will find one of those Team GoGo guys with his pokemon, a<br>
Slaking. While he can cause a lot of damage to you in case you are in<br>
front of him, you can simply circle him and stop when he is about to<br>
attack, turning this into an easy battle.</p>
<p>After the battle, you should simply go all the way up until a new room,<br>
where you will see the guy from before, along with an Entei. Such pokemon<br>
is indeed weaker than you could think, so apart from his ability to summon<br>
more fire pokemon to this battle, he isn’t strong at all. If such thing<br>
indeed happens, you can use a full power thundershock to paralyze everyone<br>
on the screen, easily capturing the weaker pokemon. As for the Entei<br>
itself, remember when I told you to stock those water pokemon? This is<br>
exactly where you should be using them, send the Entei inside one of those<br>
classic bubbles (from the water power) and then capture him as quickly as<br>
possible.</p>
<p>After getting rid (or maybe not…) of this legendary pokemon, you should<br>
head back to where the woman was, which will trigger a cutscene with the<br>
Charizard and eventually take you back to the headquarters.</p>
<p>2.21~. Summer Town</p>
<p>Some conversation, and you should exit the headquarters as soon as you are<br>
able to, which will lead you to another cutscene. After that one, take the<br>
elevator up and talk to the Dragonite, who will take you back to the<br>
second it this game’s cities.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/pokemon-ranger-walkthrough/115823/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/pokemon-ranger-walkthrough/115823/4</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 24 Jun 2007 14:59:12 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-115823-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/pokemon-ranger-walkthrough/115823.rss">Pokemon ranger walkthrough</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Pokemon ranger walkthrough</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@pk3r_kyle pk3r kyle]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/pk3r_kyle">@pk3r_kyle</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>2.8~. Mission 3</p>
<p>Start by simply following the only path available, until you find a man,<br>
where you should start going down. Eventually you will see some green ooze<br>
in the floor, head to the greatest concentration of it and you will fight<br>
a Grimer which, when defeated, will make all the green ooze disappear in<br>
that spot.</p>
<p>Another cutscene, keep on going to the right and you’ll see some more new<br>
Pokemon, continue always going down (even when you see a small bridge<br>
leading to the right) and you’ll eventually find another green ooze place,<br>
this time with 2 Grimer in it, which you should obviously defeat. Continue<br>
going and down on the ladder, when possible.</p>
<p>In that new room, you will see some Koffing and you can go all to the<br>
right, being specially careful not to fall in this room’s holes, or you<br>
will need to start this room over (and yeah, below the room you’re<br>
currently in, there’s a whole lot of Koffing). These pokemon seem to be<br>
able to poison you, but besides moving at 1 step per second, that’s not<br>
much to worry about. Well, in the right side of that room, go up the<br>
ladder and you’ll find a new area with a single Raticate.<br>
After acquiring him, go back to the place with that small bridge and go<br>
up after crossing the bridge, using the Raticate to get rid of the fence<br>
which was previously blocking your path. Continue going up and enter a new<br>
area, but be careful as some Croconaw may randomly jump out of the water<br>
in here. Having that in mind, just follow the unique path until you see<br>
another green ooze area with another 2 Grimer in there, both of which you<br>
should (as usual) defeat.</p>
<p>After doing so, continue to the right and follow that path until you get<br>
to see 2 giant water tubes. Take the one in the right and down the ladder,<br>
follow the path to the right and up the ladders, down on the water tube<br>
and you’ll see a save point. Proceed to the left and all the way up, past<br>
the bridge and on to 3 other Grimer. In case you have a Drowzee (which<br>
could be previously seen in this level), you can use it here in order to<br>
paralyze your foes for a bit and quickly capture them. Also, in case you<br>
are wondering, you can go exactly to the right after the bridge, as there<br>
is a Drowzee in there! <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/wink.png?v=6" title=":wink:" class="emoji" alt=":wink:"></p>
<p>Well, after defeating the 3 Grimer, head to the left and you’ll see a new<br>
cutscene. You need to go that way, but how? It’s rather simple, go up and<br>
be sure to capture the Tangela. Later, use his power in the pin on the<br>
other side, and you’ll be taken there. Now, you can go up and get a<br>
Meditite, go back all the way down (by taking the right side of the water<br>
path) and all to the right, where a Drowzee previously was. Use the<br>
Meditite to break the wall, and enter the newly open hole. In there, you<br>
will find both an Oddish and a Magneton. Now, make once again your way to<br>
the outside of this small cave, get the Tangela and advance to the left<br>
once again. Enter the water tube on the left and follow it to another new<br>
room. Take the tube in the left, and all the way down for another<br>
Raticate. Back to the tube, go all the way up (to the room in which you<br>
just came from) and use the Raticate to get rid of the fence exactly to<br>
your left. Check around this platform and a rare pokemon will appear in<br>
the area, which you should try to capture, a Crawdaunt.</p>
<p>Back to the tube, take the first left and head down (the upper exit is<br>
closed for good), to a place with a save point and some green ooze in the<br>
left. Defeat the 3 Grimer (once again, I used the aid of a Drowzee, you<br>
can also do it, if you like), save your game and then continue to the left<br>
side, following the path and seeing a Muk with 2 Grimer, later on. Get the<br>
Drowzee on your way there and try to defeat them. You should start by<br>
using the Drowzee’s aid to quickly get rid of the 2 Grimer, and then use<br>
your partner to stun the Muk enough time to quickly capture him.</p>
<p>After doing that, your mission will be taken to the headquarters, once<br>
again.</p>
<p>2.9~. Fall City</p>
<p>New medal, you will also earn the opportunity to take one more pokemon<br>
with you (before, you could only have 4, but now you can finally take 5)<br>
and seen more of the storyline. When it ends, exit this building and go<br>
all the way down, to the south part of the city. Search in until you see<br>
a new cutscene (with 2 Krabby attacking a Lapras), and then defeat the 2<br>
Krabby to continue.</p>
<p>You will get Lapras’ data and you should then talk to him, in order to be<br>
taken to a new city.</p>
<p>2.10~. Summer Town</p>
<p>Start by finding this city’s headquarter and enter it. After the<br>
conversation, talk to the guy who is alone and more conversation will<br>
unfold. When it ends, go to the outside and you will have a new mission to<br>
play. Follow the path to this city’s upper exit and you will face your<br>
forth mission.</p>
<p>2.11~. Mission 4</p>
<p>Go up on the green herbs stuck on the cliff and you’ll get to see you real<br>
enemies (or maybe not, it’s up to you to find out…) for your first time,<br>
in an always amusing sequence. When they leave, go to the left side and<br>
you have an easy battle against 3 Wurmple.</p>
<p>Proceed by taking the only possible path, you’ll see a short cutscene and<br>
eventually you will reach a battle against 2 Ekans. In order to have an<br>
easier time defeating them, you can try to stun them and then quickly<br>
capture one, as they usually seem to tackle you when you are least<br>
expecting it.</p>
<p>After the battle, go all the way up but be aware of the falling pokemon<br>
(usually, members of the Spinarak species) until you reach the next area,<br>
which may be considered as slightly calmer. When going to the right side<br>
of this area, you will see another cutscene, so you should go up (using<br>
the place of the mountain which you can climb) and capture the Heracross<br>
and the other pokemon which is nearby it. Now, head back to the place<br>
where the guy in the cutscene was, and use the Heracross to throw the<br>
tree down. Be sure to capture a Lotad in the water nearby, as you should<br>
use it in the upper right corner to allow an herb to grow up. Follow it<br>
up and you will fight a rare pokemon,<br>
Grovyle. You can then use it in the<br>
bush nearby, to unlock a new area where 2 Lombre will be seen. After<br>
capturing them, go back to the main area (the one where you cut the bush,<br>
in case you aren’t understanding me) and exit to the lower right corner.</p>
<p>After a small cutscene, you will have to fight against 2 Mankey and a<br>
single Primeape. You can start by stunning them all with the electrical<br>
attack and then quickly capture the Mankey. Then, in an odd move, you can<br>
even start by summoning one of them right away, in order to quickly<br>
capture the Primeape. Go back to the previous area and exit the path seen<br>
all the way up, not before seeing a cutscene. In order to get rid of the<br>
fence, get one of the pokemon nearby (I got the Grovyle for this task) and<br>
get rid of it.</p>
<p>Another battle, which you should quickly use to capture the small ones and<br>
then use the Primeape to help you capture the flying Beautifly. The enemy<br>
will run away, but you should continue going up until you reach the top of<br>
this small mountain, where another cutscene will be seen. You should then<br>
enter the top of the pyramid, where you will have to face a Politoed,<br>
which can be easily captured by using the electrical attack to stun him.</p>
<p>After this easy battle, leave the pyramid and you will see one of your<br>
enemies, who will leave without a fight. Go all the way down, a Politoed<br>
and another guy (yes, the one which you abandoned at the begining of this<br>
mission) will be back and the mission will be over.</p>
<p>2.12~. Summer Town</p>
<p>Another medal and yet another special bar will be granted to the character<br>
you are controlling. After all the chat, you will be able to move him once<br>
again, so you should go back to the Lapras, who will take you back to Fall<br>
City.</p>
<p>2.13~. Fall City</p>
<p>Move to the left, and you’ll see a new cutscene with your boss. When he<br>
finally stops talking and goes away, you should go to the headquarters,<br>
which will grant you another conversation and a new mission.</p>
<p>After that, simply leave the building and take the road to the left, which<br>
will start your fifth mission.</p>
<p>2.14~. Mission 5</p>
<p>Go the left and enter the cave. Follow the only path possible, until you<br>
see a strange pokemon taking care of one of the huge rocks, the same ones<br>
which previously blocked your path. Continue to the left and enter the<br>
first door, follow the only possible path until you find two possible<br>
ones, where you should go up for another confrontation with Team Gogo.</p>
<p>Go up, for getting a Magneton, then exit that small room and head to the<br>
left side, where you will fight 3 Geodude. You can easily defeat all of<br>
them by using the help of a water pokemon, but you should then take the<br>
lower path nearby and follow it fight against 3 Snubbull, which can be<br>
easily defeat by stunning with electrical attack and then quickly<br>
capturing them. Up on the next door, get a Poliwhirl and then head back to<br>
the room before, to use the Poliwhirl on the Graveler, which is down on<br>
the right side of the room. After capturing such pokemon, go to the room<br>
exactly up and use it on the wall, to allow the appearance of a new cave<br>
with a Kirlia inside.</p>
<p>Head back to the room where you got the Graveler, and then all the way<br>
down. Head to the right side and you will fight an enemy with 2 different<br>
pokemon and then continue to the upper door on your right side, facing 3<br>
Zubat before heading to the upper door. From there, take the lower left<br>
door, then the one which goes down, the one in the left and all the way<br>
up. Be specially aware of the Zubat, as they can confuse your character<br>
for a bit. Do you see that small cave? Enter it.</p>
<p>Here, you will have to capture one of those weird Hariyama pokemon. Then,<br>
go all the way down (where you fought 2 different pokemon) and destroy the<br>
rock blocking your path, before going down and capturing another Magneton.<br>
Go all the way back to the cave with the Hariyama to capture another one,<br>
but NEVER venture to the lower section of it, as there will be 2 Hariyama<br>
to fight at the same time, and that turns out being really hard to<br>
accomplish for most players.</p>
<p>After capturing a single one, go back to the room where you previously got<br>
a Graveler and up, up, right and down until you can use the Hariyama to<br>
get rid of one of those huge rocks. Go back to the Hariyama cave, get the<br>
one in the upper room once again, and then remove the final huge rock.</p>
<p>A small scene will occur, then you just need to leave by taking the lower<br>
left door, in the next room you simply have to head all to the left and<br>
you will see a new cutscene with Team GoGo. When you are ready to battle<br>
the powerful foe, talking to the pokemon and your battle will start. While<br>
he may seem to cause you some trouble, you can either use a water pokemon<br>
or try to circle him as quickly as possible. For newbies, I would suggest<br>
the first technique, as it requires less skill and less effort.</p>
<p>After the battle, a short scene will be seen and you will automatically<br>
exit the cave, meeting with your partner.</p>
<p>2.15~. Ring Town</p>
<p>Another medal, some conversation and you should then leave the building.<br>
Head to the upper right corner of the city and then talk to the man in<br>
there, who allows you to play a mini-game, in case you are wanting to do<br>
so. Either you do it or not, you should then head back to the headquarters<br>
and you will see your partner leaving, so you should enter that building<br>
and then watch the cutscene which follows, as you will earn a new mission.</p>
<p>Simply leave town by the upper exit and the mission will start.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/pokemon-ranger-walkthrough/115823/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/pokemon-ranger-walkthrough/115823/3</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 24 Jun 2007 14:58:22 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-115823-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/pokemon-ranger-walkthrough/115823.rss">Pokemon ranger walkthrough</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Pokemon ranger walkthrough</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@pk3r_kyle pk3r kyle]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/pk3r_kyle">@pk3r_kyle</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>2~. Walkthrough</p>
<p>I have to start by saying that while some people may have desired it, this<br>
walkthrough will simply tell you what do you need to do in each mission<br>
and how to perform it, I will not be spending my time trying to provide a<br>
lot of unuseful information or stating stuff as “give to steps to the left<br>
and then turn three steps to the right”. Therefore, I will only provide<br>
information that I think to be valuable and which can indeed matter to a<br>
random person who is playing this game.<br>
Now, on to the walkthrough itself…</p>
<p>In the first screen, you need to start by tapping the lower screen of the<br>
console with your stylus, or press any button at all. In the menu showing<br>
up next, press the first option (“New Game”), and you will be seeing the<br>
first scenes of this interesting game.<br>
When the text in the letter is simply going around the screen, you can<br>
press the lower screen with your stylus in order to make it go faster, and<br>
eventually you will reach the place where you get to pick your character,<br>
which you should do by tapping him/her with your stylus. In case you are<br>
wondering, the only difference between the two of them is the pokemon that<br>
will be following your character during the game, Minun for the guy and<br>
Plusle for the girl.</p>
<p>Pick anyone you want, and then you will see a cutscene allowing the game<br>
to finally start. (In case you are wondering, A or tapping the lower<br>
screen makes the text advance)<br>
When you finally get to control the character you picked, move it up on<br>
the stairs and you’ll see another cutscene. After its end, move up to the<br>
bridge on the upper side of this area and you’ll see a moving box,<br>
interact with it and a pokemon will jump out of it. Now, go to the<br>
building on the left and talk to the woman in the counter. You should head<br>
up the bridge once more, which will unfold a new cutscene.</p>
<p>You will see the pokemon that jumped from the box being attacked by a<br>
Houndoom, besides seeing a tutorial battle, which you don’t even have to<br>
control. The data involved in such battle is already explained in the<br>
“Controls” section of this guide, and you should fight the other Pokemon.<br>
More cutscenes, and you’ll be asked to rename your character.<br>
Eventually a Fearow will appear, and he will take you to another town.</p>
<p>2.1~. Ring Town</p>
<p>After a long cutscene, you will hear about the news and eventually you<br>
will need to press START, in order to open the menu for the first time.<br>
Some more story will be seen, you’ll hear about the save points and all<br>
that, which you should instantly use and use EVERY time you see one of<br>
them, or else you may become frustrated after losing an important battle<br>
and having to start a whole section all over again.<br>
When possible, leave this building and head to the upper part of town,<br>
leaving it in order to spot another cutscene, which will lead to the first<br>
mission you will ever face.</p>
<p>2.2~. Your first mission</p>
<p>After a long conversation, there are some pokemon to capture around here.<br>
Capture them all, and eventually you will see a Taillow hanging around,<br>
which you should capture. After doing so, go back to the main entrance and<br>
the Taillow will be given to his rightful owner.<br>
You will then see some trees one fire, which you should extinguish. In<br>
order to do so, you need to capture a water pokemon (there are some<br>
elements of the Mudkip species around) and use him to extinguish the fire,<br>
as seen in the small tutorial you get to see.<br>
After doing so, your Mudkip will run away (in this game, the pokemon<br>
always run away after completing their task) and your mission will be<br>
over.</p>
<p>2.3~. Ring Town</p>
<p>After the chat sequence, and when possible, leave that building and you<br>
will see another scene with the same man from before. Your pokemon (which<br>
one it is depends only on your initial choice for a character) will stun<br>
the Taillow and you can then easily capture it. Soon, you will get your<br>
first special bar, which allows your own pokemon (well, the only one that<br>
will always be following you) to use his electrical attack in the middle of<br>
the battles.</p>
<p>Now, you should go back to the building and you’ll see a new tutorial.<br>
Then, an older guy will appear and eventually you will be able to control<br>
your character once again. Talk to the older guy once, and then take the<br>
elevator in the left to go up. Talk to everyone in there and then head<br>
back to the floor below, and when talking to the older guy once more, a<br>
new sequence will unfold and you will (finally) be getting a new mission.<br>
Go all the way up, to exit this town, and then you will be starting that<br>
mission.</p>
<p>2.4~. Mission 1</p>
<p>A Bellsprout will jump out of the bushes, and you should obviously capture<br>
it. Another tutorial scene will appear and when you’re done, head to the<br>
upper section of this area. Yet another tutorial scene, and then you can<br>
proceed. Be sure to capture the Torchic on the left, as you will be<br>
needing him. Head to the right side, and use the Torchic on the pieces<br>
blocking your path. Later, be also sure to capture the Pichu nearby, as he<br>
can heal you. Continue following the path until you find a huge piece of<br>
wood blocking you. Go slightly back, and a Combusken will jump out of the<br>
bushes. While you can easily capture him, using a Mudkip to aid you is<br>
probably also a good idea. Use the Combusken to remove the wood and<br>
continue following that path until you can enter a cave.</p>
<p>Around here, you can find a strange area where all the Magikarps are<br>
jumping OUTSIDE OF THE WATER (cool, a water pokemon that doesn’t need<br>
water, what’s next?), but you can’t go there yet. Therefore, keep on<br>
following the only possible path and eventually some rocks will fall,<br>
blocking your path. Capture the Paras and use him to get rid of the wood<br>
fence nearby. You can’t remove the huge rocks <em>yet</em>, so… don’t worry<br>
about it, just follow the only possible path and you will eventually see<br>
some thugs from your yet-to-be enemy, Team GoGo. Proceed to the right and<br>
head to the outside of the cave and you’ll see a Rhydon, which you should<br>
also capture. He isn’t even very strong, but after the battle he will go<br>
away and you should go to the right. For the first time ever, you will be<br>
asked if you REALLY want to leave an area… in case you do, all the<br>
pokemon you captured will currently go away, except for (obviously) the<br>
main one.</p>
<p>In this new town, simply move to the new headquarters and this mission<br>
will be over.</p>
<p>2.5~. Fall City</p>
<p>A new character will appear and you will be given a new medal. You can’t<br>
exit this building yet, so be sure to talk to everyone and eventually a<br>
woman will enter, leading to a scene where you will be given a new mission<br>
for you to play.</p>
<p>2.6~. Mission 2</p>
<p>Go to the right and you’ll see a new sequence. Go all to the right and<br>
that woman will once again be seen. Enter the building and she will have a<br>
large box in front of her door, so you should go outside and capture a<br>
Makuhita. Use it to get rid of the box and defeat the Venonat inside.</p>
<p>After doing so, head to the outside of the building and to the left, where<br>
another woman will ask you to find her Skitty pokemons. You can find them<br>
in the following places:</p>
<ul>
<li>the top floor of the building you just visited.</li>
<li>behind a wooden fence, on the central area of this city. He will run<br>
away, but you can easily get him later, by checking the behind of one of<br>
the trees.</li>
<li>near the fountain, on the central area of this city.</li>
<li>on the right trash can, on the central area of this city.</li>
<li>On the upper left house, on the upper area of this city, hidden in the<br>
middle of some plushies.<br>
When you give the 5th to the woman, she will go away and take them all.<br>
Obviously, it is impossible to currently have 5 of these on your party, so<br>
whenever you feel like it, you should go back to the woman and she will<br>
take the number of Skitty pokemons you currently have. Several trips to<br>
her will do the trick, but you should now head to the right and another<br>
new woman will be seen. Follow her up to her house and you will notice her<br>
basement to be all dark and stuff like that.</li>
</ul>
<p>Now, you have to go the the south area of this city and go down, to the<br>
sewers. Yes, the place which was previously covered by a Snorlax, in case<br>
you noticed it. He won’t be there anymore, but you can go down the ladder<br>
and get a Staryu in there. Take him back to the woman’s basement and use<br>
its power to lighten everything up.</p>
<p>Exit the house, go all to the right and a woman will talk to you, but you<br>
will also see a pokemon attacking the clock tower. I advise you to save<br>
your game before confronting it, but it’s really up to you. A nice option<br>
for this battle is stunning the enemy with the usual electrical shock from<br>
your main pokemon, but it is really up to you.</p>
<p>After that, the mission will end and you will be back to the headquarters.</p>
<p>2.7~. Fall City</p>
<p>After the previous mission, you will not only get a new medal but also an<br>
upgrade to the special bar. Yeah, the one used to thundershock people! But<br>
anyway, you should continue seeing the story, and eventually you will get<br>
another new mission. Exit this building and you will instantly know where<br>
you need to go next. Head there, go down the ladder and a new mission will<br>
start.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/pokemon-ranger-walkthrough/115823/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/pokemon-ranger-walkthrough/115823/2</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 24 Jun 2007 14:57:33 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-115823-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/pokemon-ranger-walkthrough/115823.rss">Pokemon ranger walkthrough</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Pokemon ranger walkthrough</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@pk3r_kyle pk3r kyle]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/pk3r_kyle">@pk3r_kyle</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <hr>
<h2>1~. Controls<br>
1.1~. Menus<br>
1.2~. Initial Notes<br>
1.3~. Pokemon Type<br>
1.4~. Mini-games<br>
2~. Walkthrough<br>
2.1~. Ring Town<br>
2.2~. Your first mission<br>
2.3~. Ring Town<br>
2.4~. Mission 1<br>
2.5~. Fall City<br>
2.6~. Mission 2<br>
2.7~. Fall City<br>
2.8~. Mission 3<br>
2.9~. Fall City<br>
2.10~. Summer Town<br>
2.11~. Mission 4<br>
2.12~. Summer Town<br>
2.13~. Fall City<br>
2.14~. Mission 5<br>
2.15~. Ring Town<br>
2.16~. Mission 6<br>
2.17~. Ring Town<br>
2.18~. Summer Town<br>
2.19~. New mission<br>
2.20~. Yet another mission<br>
2.21~. Summer Town<br>
2.22~. Fall City<br>
2.23~. Mission 7<br>
2.24~. Fall City<br>
2.25~. Summer Town<br>
2.26~. Another mission<br>
2.27~. Summer Town<br>
2.28~. Mission 8<br>
2.29~. Win Town<br>
2.30~. Mission 9<br>
2.31~. Win Town<br>
2.32~. Mission 10<br>
3~. What now?<br>
3.1~. Fall City<br>
3.2~. Extra Mission 1<br>
3.3~. Fall City<br>
3.4~. Ring Town<br>
3.5~. Summer Town<br>
3.6~. Extra Mission 2<br>
3.7~. Summer Town<br>
3.8~. Win Town<br>
3.9~. Extra Mission 3<br>
3.10~. Win Town<br>
3.11~. Special Missions<br>
3.11.1~. Special Mission 1 (Deoxys)<br>
3.11.2~. Special Mission 2 (Celebi)<br>
3.11.3~. Special Mission 3 (Mew)<br>
3.11.4~. Special Mission 4 (Manaphy’s Egg)<br>
4~. Acquirable Pokemon and their moves<br>
5~. Frequently Asked Questions</h2>
<p>1~. Controls</p>
<p>While controls for most handheld gaming systems are usually quite easy to<br>
master, I can’t say the same thing about the ones in this console. I will<br>
try to provide as much information about them as possible, and I hope you<br>
find it easy to comprehend.</p>
<p>UP       - moves the character up, moves up on menus<br>
DOWN     - moves the character down, moves down on menus<br>
LEFT     - moves the character left, moves to the left on menus<br>
RIGHT    - moves the character right, moves to the right on menus<br>
A        - interact with someone, selects YES in binary options<br>
B        - exits in a menu, selects NO in binary options<br>
X        - in the field, selects all your pokemon<br>
Y        - in the field, selects all your pokemon<br>
L        - isn’t used<br>
R        - isn’t used<br>
START    - summons (and makes it disapper) the menu, while in the field<br>
SELECT   - isn’t used</p>
<p>Now, the main problem (and yet, one of the most important features) in<br>
this game turns out being the lower, tactile, screen of this game. You<br>
will obviously need to use it several times during your adventure, and<br>
while few of the functions are available initially, others will also be<br>
unlocked automatically, as you advance further in the game. So, eventually<br>
you will discover that the lower screen of the console can be used to:</p>
<ul>
<li>Move your character (you simply need to have your stylus pointed at the<br>
direction you wish to take) and talk to other characters (simply tap<br>
them with your stylus).</li>
</ul>
<p>In battles, you can use it to:</p>
<ul>
<li>
<p>Draw closed lines around your opponent, which makes it HP go down by 1.<br>
Keep on doing it until the HP is below 1, in order to gain extra EXP<br>
points after the end of the battle. Do you see the green/red numbers?<br>
Those are the points you will win after the battle;</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Tap the blue area on the lower right corner, to make one of your current<br>
pokemons usable in the battle. Their effects largely depend on what<br>
pokemon you select, but such thematic will be further developed in the<br>
“Pokemon Type” section of this guide;</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>By “capturing” a Pokemon when its HP isn’t below 1, you’ll see a blue<br>
area appearing on the lower left corner of the screen. Such option will<br>
only be available sometimes and it allows you to run away from your<br>
current battle, something that you should use if you are into trouble.</p>
</li>
</ul>
<p>That’s basically it, for this section…</p>
<p>1.1~. Menus</p>
<p>When you first start the game, you will see two options, they are:</p>
<p>New Game<br>
Options</p>
<p>Well, all of those are quite understandable… in case you are wondering<br>
about the “Options” menu, it only contain two options, the first one being<br>
something I don’t fully understand and the second one simply allowing you<br>
to change the background image some of the menus. However, after first<br>
saving your game, the layout will be changed to the following one:</p>
<p>::::::::::::::<br>
:: Continue ::<br>
:: New Game ::<br>
:: Options  ::<br>
::::::::::::::</p>
<p>Easy, hum?<br>
Well, there is simply another menu requiring explanation in this game, and<br>
that turns out being menu that will appear after pressing START. However,<br>
don’t forget that such menu will only appear after a certain part of the<br>
game, slightly before getting your first mission. That menu will usually<br>
ook like this (and no, this isn’t an accurate translation, it’s just my<br>
interpretation of it), but in case you aren’t in the middle of a mission,<br>
its layout will slightly change:</p>
<pre><code>              Pokemon
   Mission               Tutorials
</code></pre>
<p>Map                                       Encyclopedia<br>
Options               Quick Save<br>
Exit</p>
<p>“Pokemon” is the place where you can head to check information about those<br>
pokemon that you have currently in your party.</p>
<p>“Mission” generally allows you to check the information about the mission<br>
you are currently playing. Obviously, in case you aren’t in the middle of<br>
a mission, this option won’t be seen in the menu.</p>
<p>“Tutorials” allows you to check several information about the gameplay of<br>
this game, teaching you about something you may not know. When you haven’t<br>
read something yet, it will display a symbol stating the you haven’t read<br>
it yet. You DON’T have to read them all and there’s NO prize for doing so,<br>
but it is always a good idea to check it, in case you have any questions.</p>
<p>“Map” is one of those obvious options, where you can simply check the<br>
world MAP.</p>
<p>“Encyclopedia” can be considered as this game’s Pokedex, allowing you to<br>
check the information on all the pokemon that you’ve already seen or<br>
captured in the game.</p>
<p>“Options”, in this menu, has exactly the same layout as the other<br>
mini-menu I’ve stated before. Therefore, I don’t think you will have any<br>
trouble with it.</p>
<p>“Quick Save” is the option you should use if you are in the field and you<br>
need to quickly leave the game, in order to do anything else. Be aware<br>
that this only allows you to restart the game ONCE from that particular<br>
point, and then it will erase the point where you quick saved it.</p>
<p>“Exit”, well… it exits this menu.</p>
<p>This is all for this section, I guess.</p>
<p>1.2~. Initial Notes</p>
<p>In this section, you will be able to read about some of the things you<br>
should know BEFORE starting to play the game. While they may spoil a very<br>
limited amount of the gameplay, it is in your best interest to acknowledge<br>
them as soon as possible.</p>
<ul>
<li>
<p>As stated before, after dropping a pokemon’s HP to below 1, you can<br>
usually still give it a few extra rounds, to max out the EXP you win.<br>
This way, you can get more EXP and still face the exact same amount of<br>
enemies;</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>More EXP means more levels, and more levels mean more HP for you;</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Shortly after starting to play, your character will gain his first<br>
special bar. However, when you gain your 3rd, 5th, 7th and 9th medals,<br>
you will also receive a new special bar. Since more special bars mean<br>
that your main pokemon will be able to use a stronger paralyzing attack,<br>
you could consider them to be quite important;</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>When acquiring your 4th, 7th and 10th medals, you will be able to<br>
increase the number of pokemon you can carry with you at any time, from<br>
the initial value of 4 up to a maximum of 7, after getting your 10th<br>
medal;</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Like what happens in the classical pokemon games, in here you could also<br>
find “capturing all Pokemon” to be an interesting sidequest. Therefore,<br>
each time you see a unique pokemon in front of you, you should give<br>
everything you’ve got to capture it, EVEN if I have no mention to such<br>
pokemon in the guide;</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Save a lot and save often, as you don’t want to have to replay a certain<br>
mission all over again, do you? Therefore, EVERY time you see a save<br>
point, be sure to use it, even if that isn’t stated in this guide.</p>
</li>
</ul>
<p>That’s all for now, I guess…</p>
<p>1.3~. Pokemon Type</p>
<p>First, I must tell you that in this game, the Pokemon are usable inside<br>
and outside of the battles. In the field, you can generally use them to<br>
help you in several tasks, like removing natural barriers. While there are<br>
more than 200 Pokemon in the game, the abilities that you can use in the<br>
field are kinda limited, and they include:</p>
<ul>
<li>
<p>Break - destroys something, like a huge rock.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Burn - burns something down, like a tree or a huge ice block.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Charge - restores your life.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Cross - allows your characters to be taken to another place, by using<br>
this ability on something they can grab.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Cut - simply cuts something in front of you, like a fence or a bush.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Flash - lights up an area.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Gust - creates a windy attack that can lift stuff off the floor.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Tackle - pushes something, as a box or a tree.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Water - throws some water, which can be used for tasks such as<br>
extinguishing something that is on fire or very hot.</p>
</li>
</ul>
<p>Besides “Flash” (an ability that only Staryu can use), all the other ones<br>
come in 3 different strenghts, like the normal one, “x2” and “x3”. While<br>
an ability of “x3” can remove a “x2” (or lower) barrier, the opposite<br>
can’t occur. Also, in the case of “Charge”, the normal ability restores<br>
5 HP, the “x2” version restores 15 HP and finally the “x3” one fully<br>
restores your HP.</p>
<p>This is all for the field abilities, but the game also contains battle<br>
ones. With an higher number than the ones specified above, these can be<br>
used by simply calling a pokemon to the battle which can use an ability of<br>
such type, as shown in the section “Acquirable Pokemon and their moves” of<br>
this guide. They include:</p>
<ul>
<li>
<p>Bug - entraps your opponent inside the lines you created.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Dark - decreases your current HP BUT makes your stylus’ line longer.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Electric - simply restores your HP.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Fighting - Each time you do a full closed line, opponent’s HP is halved<br>
by 2 points, instead of the usual 1.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Fire - when you complete a full line around an opponent, this causes<br>
massive explosions in the inside of that area, usually preventing<br>
the opponent from attacking.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Flying - throws gusts, which may lift opponent’s from the ground for a<br>
while.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Ghost - when you complete a full closed line, ghosts appear and stun the<br>
opponents inside the circle, making them stop whatever they were<br>
going to do.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Grass - this attack allows you to create a grass barrier around your<br>
opponent.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Ground - breaks the ground, stopping your enemies from crossing that<br>
particular place for a while.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Ice - creates ice areas that can freeze the opponent, if he runs into<br>
them.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Paralyze - this electrical attack stuns the opponent for as much time as<br>
the number of special bars that were currently filled.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Poison - poisons your enemy, making it weaker.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Psychic - stuns your opponent for a while, taking it off the floor.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Rock - causes sandstorms.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Water - allows you to create bubbles that can imprison your enemies<br>
inside, with the time being defined only by the size of the<br>
bubble you created.</p>
</li>
</ul>
<p>Some of these functions are instantly used (like the Psychic or Electric<br>
ones), but others will last for some time, like the Fire or Grass ones,<br>
with the time being awarded simply having the strenght of that pokemon in<br>
mind.</p>
<p>And that’s all for this section…</p>
<p>1.4~. Mini-games</p>
<p>While most of the events in this story are pretty linear, the game also<br>
seems to contain some small 3 areas where you will need to play a slightly<br>
different adventure. Those are not very hard, but turn your task of<br>
capturing all the Pokemon into something slightly harder than what you<br>
will usually find in the game.</p>
<p>The “Ring Town mini-game” and the “Summer Town mini-game” are easily<br>
acessible by talking to the proper person, when all to the right of the<br>
upper exit (for the Ring Town one) and to the immediate left of the Lapras<br>
(for the Summer Town one), and you will need to hang on top of the<br>
provided Pokemon (either a Doduo or a Lapras, depending on the game) and<br>
try to capture as many pokemon as possible in a 3-minute time. Rarer<br>
pokemon give you more points, and there sure are a lot of those for you to<br>
find in each of the two areas stated above. Be aware that some of them are<br>
really hard to find and may only be available sometimes, so it may turn<br>
out being indeed very hard to capture a particular pokemon, even if you<br>
know where to find them. As an added note, the biggest difference between<br>
these 2 mini-games is that in the Summer Town one you can’t see most of<br>
your enemies, as they will be appearing below the water.</p>
<p>The “Fall City mini-game” seems to be only available after completing the<br>
main storyline once, and available by taking the left path on the upper<br>
area of the stated city, you will find an arena in there. Inside that one,<br>
you should talk to the woman at the counter and she will make you enter a<br>
tournament, where pokemon will usually be falling from the sky and you<br>
need to capture them, in order to win points and more capture time. You<br>
must be aware that circling them more times than required increases the<br>
time that you have for capturing more pokemon, while capturing more than a<br>
pokemon at the same time will greatly increase the number of points you<br>
get from them, and that sure is important. In case you are wondering, the<br>
main target is surpassing the 50000 points area, which turns being quite<br>
hard.</p>
<p>That’s all for this section, too…</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/pokemon-ranger-walkthrough/115823/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/pokemon-ranger-walkthrough/115823/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 24 Jun 2007 14:56:30 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-115823-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/pokemon-ranger-walkthrough/115823.rss">Pokemon ranger walkthrough</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
