<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Client Creativity</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/client-creativity/245191</link>
    <description>Wasn&#39;t sure what forum to post this in so here will do for now, if it&#39;s in the wrong forum please move it.

Well, lately I&#39;ve seen nothing but the same clients popping up over and over again. The typical 317 clients with 417 gameframes, the bottom sidemenu buttons etc being completely messed up in terms of clicking places and redstones not even fitting properly and the same cache-added models. What I suggest to you is before you release your client.

Think about these:

   1. Is my client the best I can make it?
   2. Is there lots of glitches in my client?
   3. Does my client differ from anybody else&#39;s?


1 - Is my client the best I can make it? If it&#39;s not then I&#39;d advise you spend a little more time on your client. Additions to your client don&#39;t have to be extremely hard to make. Nor do you have to know Java like the back of your hand. Just using what you do know about Java, come up with little modifications which can benefit other people that have never been seen before. An example of this would be Danno&#39;s Skill Calculators. The idea had been thought of before, but nobody had actually gone and integrated it with a client. You don&#39;t have to do anything this big, but the idea is right. For starters you could just make String features on the Jframe.

Note: Don&#39;t just focus on the Jframe.

2 - Is there lots of glitches in my client? Well if you are ready to release but notice there is lots of model, clicking area, sprite, redstone and other glitches in your client then just spend 10-15 minutes jotting down these glitches in notepad. Go through the glitches that you know you can fix with some time and the ones that you don&#39;t know how to fix. If the one you don&#39;t know how to fix are quite common errors, head over to the tutorial forums and see if anybody has posted fixes for them. If you try to no avail, try just asking some of your friends if they know how to counter-act the problem. Fixing the glitches makes a world of difference and lets people know your client isn&#39;t just the typical glitch-filled thing.

Note: If the clicking areas for something like side-icon buttons is completely out of place on your client. Try to make that a priority fix as it can be the difference from somebody using and not using your client.

3 - Does my client differ from anybody else&#39;s? Before releasing make sure that you have checked the download section and reviewed most of the recent clients to make sure that nobody has released a client pretty much identical to yours. If your client is unique and working perfectly with no major glitches then go for it. But if you feel that your client is just another stick in the mud then just head back to the drawing board and think to yourself, &quot;What unique thing will make my client, a great client?&quot;. Once you have gotten your ideas just add them into your client and once your ready release it.

Note: Don&#39;t go overboard with the &quot;Uniqueness&quot; as this often results in you making modifications that actually take longer then doing it the normal way.

These are just a few ways you can make your client stand out, don&#39;t be a sheep and just use the same things you find on every client. Make yours unique.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2008 22:07:24 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/client-creativity/245191.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Client Creativity</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@SilentCJ SilentCJ]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/silentcj">@SilentCJ</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Fair enough.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/client-creativity/245191/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/client-creativity/245191/5</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2008 22:07:24 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-245191-5</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/client-creativity/245191.rss">Client Creativity</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Client Creativity</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@i_nelson_i i nelson i]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/i_nelson_i">@i_nelson_i</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>you meen all jagex items added…silab didnt make them so they aint hers[quote=“SilentCJ, post:2, topic:245191”]Nice one, i hope some of the noobs take a look at this before releasing their clients.</p>
<p>I know that when i release my client eventually, it will be unique, all silabs added :P[/quote]</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/client-creativity/245191/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/client-creativity/245191/4</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2008 19:53:14 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-245191-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/client-creativity/245191.rss">Client Creativity</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Client Creativity</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@sanga282 sanga282]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/sanga282">@sanga282</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“SilentCJ, post:2, topic:245191”]Nice one, i hope some of the noobs take a look at this before releasing their clients.</p>
<p>I know that when i release my client eventually, it will be unique, <span class="bbcode-b">all silabs added</span> :P[/quote]<br>
thats so ragetastic i daren’t even think about it</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/client-creativity/245191/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/client-creativity/245191/3</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2008 14:31:09 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-245191-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/client-creativity/245191.rss">Client Creativity</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Client Creativity</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@SilentCJ SilentCJ]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/silentcj">@SilentCJ</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Nice one, i hope some of the noobs take a look at this before releasing their clients.</p>
<p>I know that when i release my client eventually, it will be unique, all silabs added <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=6" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/client-creativity/245191/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/client-creativity/245191/2</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2008 19:58:21 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-245191-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/client-creativity/245191.rss">Client Creativity</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Client Creativity</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@webber webber]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/webber">@webber</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Wasn’t sure what forum to post this in so here will do for now, if it’s in the wrong forum please move it.</p>
<p>Well, lately I’ve seen nothing but the same clients popping up over and over again. The typical 317 clients with 417 gameframes, the bottom sidemenu buttons etc being completely messed up in terms of clicking places and redstones not even fitting properly and the same cache-added models. What I suggest to you is before you release your client.</p>
<p>Think about these:</p>
<ol>
<li>Is my client the best I can make it?</li>
<li>Is there lots of glitches in my client?</li>
<li>Does my client differ from anybody else’s?</li>
</ol>
<p>1 - Is my client the best I can make it? If it’s not then I’d advise you spend a little more time on your client. Additions to your client don’t have to be extremely hard to make. Nor do you have to know Java like the back of your hand. Just using what you do know about Java, come up with little modifications which can benefit other people that have never been seen before. An example of this would be Danno’s Skill Calculators. The idea had been thought of before, but nobody had actually gone and integrated it with a client. You don’t have to do anything this big, but the idea is right. For starters you could just make String features on the Jframe.</p>
<p>Note: Don’t just focus on the Jframe.</p>
<p>2 - Is there lots of glitches in my client? Well if you are ready to release but notice there is lots of model, clicking area, sprite, redstone and other glitches in your client then just spend 10-15 minutes jotting down these glitches in notepad. Go through the glitches that you know you can fix with some time and the ones that you don’t know how to fix. If the one you don’t know how to fix are quite common errors, head over to the tutorial forums and see if anybody has posted fixes for them. If you try to no avail, try just asking some of your friends if they know how to counter-act the problem. Fixing the glitches makes a world of difference and lets people know your client isn’t just the typical glitch-filled thing.</p>
<p>Note: If the clicking areas for something like side-icon buttons is completely out of place on your client. Try to make that a priority fix as it can be the difference from somebody using and not using your client.</p>
<p>3 - Does my client differ from anybody else’s? Before releasing make sure that you have checked the download section and reviewed most of the recent clients to make sure that nobody has released a client pretty much identical to yours. If your client is unique and working perfectly with no major glitches then go for it. But if you feel that your client is just another stick in the mud then just head back to the drawing board and think to yourself, “What unique thing will make my client, a great client?”. Once you have gotten your ideas just add them into your client and once your ready release it.</p>
<p>Note: Don’t go overboard with the “Uniqueness” as this often results in you making modifications that actually take longer then doing it the normal way.</p>
<p>These are just a few ways you can make your client stand out, don’t be a sheep and just use the same things you find on every client. Make yours unique.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/client-creativity/245191/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/client-creativity/245191/1</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2008 19:14:53 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-245191-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/client-creativity/245191.rss">Client Creativity</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
