<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Need a cool coder, read for more. :)</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/need-a-cool-coder-read-for-more/342370</link>
    <description>I am looking for somebody to help code a runescape private server.
I know a little bit of how to code it, but some things, I just need somebody else to code because I just can&#39;t get it figured out.
E-mail me, and let me know what you would want in return. Maybe just Ownership? You can be Co-Owner or just Admin..?
You will most definately get credit in coding it.
Below is a description of what I&#39;m wanting. If you can get me that, I will be satisfyed.

Just so everybody knows, I&#39;m not wanting a server to make money, I want a server so people can play without having to pay.

-----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------
Updated sprites.
Colored whips, Party Hats, Santa Hats &amp; Dragonfire Shields.
A few customs need to be added. (I can code hats, weapons &amp; shields.)
I want the GE area to be opened. GE doesn&#39;t NEED to work, it would be cool if it did, but I&#39;ll be fine if it doesn&#39;t.
When first logged in, I want the welcome screen to be there, doesn&#39;t have to be linked to website, but would be cool if it was.
(Click to play needs to be clickable.)
Summoning, Hunter, &amp; Construction all need to work. I don&#39;t really want the newest runescape skill... Once again, it would
be cool if it was there, but doesn&#39;t have to be..
All the monsters need to drop SOMETHING... Even if it&#39;s just bones &amp; some cash.
I don&#39;t want items to be to cheap, but not to expensive. Maybe something like, Bandos Chestplate is 1000mil.. Starter amount
being about 25mil-50mil... Monster maybe drop about 300k-500k.
I don&#39;t want really fast xp, but not really slow either. It should take about a day to get to level 99 in 2 skills, or something like that.
It shouldn&#39;t take a week-5 years to get 99 in 1 skill, but not 1 day and your 99 in all the skills.. you know?
I want HD to be available.
It would be very awesome if CC worked, as alot of you reading this may know, there are maybe 10-20 prs&#39;s out there that have
that working, but even then, it doesn&#39;t run the same as regular Runescape.
Friends &amp; Ignore lists MUST work.
The server needs Bandos, Dragonfire Shield, Dragon Platebody, Dragon Full Helm, Dragon Claws, etc..
All Specials need to work.
The quest tab I want to have teles added:
king black dragon
grand exchange
shops
pest control
castlewars
barrows
assult
godwars
fightpits

then quests.
Monkey Madness
Reciepe for Distaster....

They need to tele to the area.
Quests don&#39;t have to work, but once again.. Would be super intense if they did.
Pest Control needs to work 100% not 75%, not 90%, but 100%!
All the monsters need to attack, but a little easier to kill. (not too easy)
Castle wars needs to work.
I want the shops to be at ge...
Here is a little of different shops that I want there:
Dragon Market - All dragon armour, then all dragon weapons.
Trainee Market - Bronze, Iron, Steel, Mithril, Adamant Platebody, Platelegs, Kiteshield, Scimitar &amp; Full Helm. Dragon fireshield
Pro Market - Bandos Chestplate, Bandos legs, Dragonfire Shield, BGS, SGS, ZGS, AGS, Spirit shields, Helm on Neitiznot
&amp; Abysal Whip.
Skill Cape Market - All TRIMMED skillcapes, then non trimmed skillcapes, then end with the Quest cape. (Must be Bob)
Barrows Market - (Needs to be at barrows) Veracs, Dharoks, Guthans, Torags, Arhims then Karil&#39;s.
-In this order: head, top, bottom, weapon-
Pest Control items don&#39;t really matter. Just want something cool.
Assult items need to be: Rune Defender, Fighter Torso &amp; 
Colored Market - Colored Whips, Colored Dragonfire Shields, Colored Party Hats &amp; Colored Santa Hats. 
Trick Market - All infinity, Wizard, Mystic, Zamorak, Guthix &amp; Saradomin Magic items.
Rune Market - Air, Fire, Water, Earth, Mind, Body, Chaos, Nature, Cozmic, Death, Blood, Law, Soul, and so on. 
(Magic skill needs to work 100%)
Archery Market - Shortbow, Oak Shortbow, Maple Shortbow, willow shortbow, Magic Shortbow, Magic Longbow, Dark Bow, 
Crystal Bow, Bronze, Iron, Steel, Mithril, Adamant, Rune, Dragon arrows.. Adamant, Rune Crossbow.. Bronze, Steel, Opal,
Rune, Dragon bolts. Archer&#39;s Ring.
(If enough room) Green d&#39;hide armour, then blue, red, black. (coif, top, bottom, vambraces) Robinhood Hat, then boots.
Toktz Market - All the different obby armour (prefer the order that it&#39;s in on Runescape. but doesn&#39;t matter.)
Granite Market - Granite helm, Granite Platebody, Granite Platelegs, Granite Maul, Berserker ring, Warrior ring, Seers ring.
Robe Market - All the colored robes. Hat, top, bottom, Gloves, then boots. Order of color doesn&#39;t matter.
General Market - Needs to have Tinderbox, Hammer, knife, Net, Big Net, Cage, Harpoon, rune essence, pure essence,
Bronze, Iron, Steel, Mithril, Adamant &amp; Rune Arrow heads, Feathers, Arrow Shafts.
Skiller Market - Bronze, Iron, Black, Steel, Mithril, Adamant, Rune, Dragon Pickaxe, then in that order with Hatchets.

There needs to be a shop with items for Hunting, Summoning, Construction, Herblore, Slayer, Crafting.
All shops need to have all the item amounts be atleast 100, but if it&#39;s stuff like, Tinderbox, runes, arrows, etc. make 10,000+
Hunter shop needs to have all the hunters equipment. Summoning needs to have pouches to summon, Herblore need vails of
water, abunch of unclean herbs, and things to mix with the herbs. Construction needs all the planks, nails, Cloths, Clay,
hammer, limstone, etc... Slayer needs all the slayer stuff. Crafting needs all uncut gems, a chisel, needle, thread, already
tanned leather.. both hard &amp; soft. then all the d&#39;hides (ready to craft)
The names can just be like, Hunting Market, Summoning Market, Construction Market, Herblore Market, Slayer Market, &amp;
Crafting Market.

I don&#39;t want all the shops to be in the same area, try to break them up a little bit. There needs to be 1 Custom Market.. I can
add the items to that, or give you the items when they are done to add.
Some of the shops, obviously need to be in a specific area, like Barrows. Needs to be in the Barrows area.
(I would like Barrows to be in the oringal spot.)

A couple of my idea&#39;s to completely add to it are:
When you click the skill icon, a thing will appear in the chatbox asking, &quot;What would you like to do?&quot; :Teleport :View Stats
If you cick Teleport, it tele&#39;s you to one of the best spots to train in that skill, if you click view stats, the menu thing appears,
telling you what level you need for each different thing.
That&#39;s just an idea there, but can  be added.

I have a runescape website like the oringal one (not the updated one.) I just don&#39;t know how to get it on webs.com
If you know how to do that, I would appreicate that too. :)

I want the name to ofcourse be changed to &quot;Eternal Scape&quot;
I&#39;ve seen some servers have it to where, whenever the owners log in, it informs everbody online. Regardless of if friends or not.
I want that! So whenever &quot;Mars Tattoo&quot; &quot;Pluto View&quot; or &quot;DevinHeaven&quot; sign on, that everybody knows.

Price Checker needs to work, &amp; Be located inbetween the teleports &amp; Quests.

All skills must work 100%!!!!
Items kept on Death, and Show Equipment Stats buttons must work.


If you have any questions, or if you are wanting to help.. E-mail me Marstattoo@aol.com
Either leave the subject blank, or title it &quot;Eternal Scape&quot;
-----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------






Don&#39;t leave comments if your going to say something negative... You&#39;ll just be wasting your time because I don&#39;t care what you have to say.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 08 Jun 2010 15:15:38 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/need-a-cool-coder-read-for-more/342370.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Need a cool coder, read for more. :)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@si_force Si Force]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/si_force">@si_force</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Requests are not allowed, sorry.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/need-a-cool-coder-read-for-more/342370/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/need-a-cool-coder-read-for-more/342370/6</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 08 Jun 2010 15:15:38 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-342370-6</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/need-a-cool-coder-read-for-more/342370.rss">Need a cool coder, read for more. :)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Need a cool coder, read for more. :)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@skillerzgod skillerzgod]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/skillerzgod">@skillerzgod</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>how do you actually code?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/need-a-cool-coder-read-for-more/342370/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/need-a-cool-coder-read-for-more/342370/5</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 08 Jun 2010 08:11:25 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-342370-5</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/need-a-cool-coder-read-for-more/342370.rss">Need a cool coder, read for more. :)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Need a cool coder, read for more. :)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@the_gril the gril]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/the_gril">@the_gril</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>i cnt code for u add me on  msn <a href="mailto:benscott4119@hotmail.com">benscott4119@hotmail.com</a></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/need-a-cool-coder-read-for-more/342370/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/need-a-cool-coder-read-for-more/342370/4</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 08 Jun 2010 08:09:09 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-342370-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/need-a-cool-coder-read-for-more/342370.rss">Need a cool coder, read for more. :)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Need a cool coder, read for more. :)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Rawrock Rawrock]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/rawrock">@Rawrock</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote no-group" data-post="2" data-topic="342370">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/shorty626/40/5_513041d5f7104045db30895d3b90af16.png" class="avatar"> Shorty626:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>I suggest you just buy a webhost rather than use <a href="http://webs.com" rel="nofollow noopener">webs.com</a></p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I plan on it, but before I do, I want to make sure that I have a good server for it.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/need-a-cool-coder-read-for-more/342370/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/need-a-cool-coder-read-for-more/342370/3</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 08 Jun 2010 03:19:41 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-342370-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/need-a-cool-coder-read-for-more/342370.rss">Need a cool coder, read for more. :)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Need a cool coder, read for more. :)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Shorty626 Shorty626]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/shorty626">@Shorty626</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I suggest you just buy a webhost rather than use <a href="http://webs.com" rel="nofollow noopener">webs.com</a></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/need-a-cool-coder-read-for-more/342370/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/need-a-cool-coder-read-for-more/342370/2</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 02 Jun 2010 05:32:06 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-342370-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/need-a-cool-coder-read-for-more/342370.rss">Need a cool coder, read for more. :)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Need a cool coder, read for more. :)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Rawrock Rawrock]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/rawrock">@Rawrock</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I am looking for somebody to help code a runescape private server.<br>
I know a little bit of how to code it, but some things, I just need somebody else to code because I just can’t get it figured out.<br>
E-mail me, and let me know what you would want in return. Maybe just Ownership? You can be Co-Owner or just Admin…?<br>
You will most definately get credit in coding it.<br>
Below is a description of what I’m wanting. If you can get me that, I will be satisfyed.</p>
<p>Just so everybody knows, I’m not wanting a server to make money, I want a server so people can play without having to pay.</p>
<hr>
<p>Updated sprites.<br>
Colored whips, Party Hats, Santa Hats &amp; Dragonfire Shields.<br>
A few customs need to be added. (I can code hats, weapons &amp; shields.)<br>
I want the GE area to be opened. GE doesn’t NEED to work, it would be cool if it did, but I’ll be fine if it doesn’t.<br>
When first logged in, I want the welcome screen to be there, doesn’t have to be linked to website, but would be cool if it was.<br>
(Click to play needs to be clickable.)<br>
Summoning, Hunter, &amp; Construction all need to work. I don’t really want the newest runescape skill… Once again, it would<br>
be cool if it was there, but doesn’t have to be…<br>
All the monsters need to drop SOMETHING… Even if it’s just bones &amp; some cash.<br>
I don’t want items to be to cheap, but not to expensive. Maybe something like, Bandos Chestplate is 1000mil… Starter amount<br>
being about 25mil-50mil… Monster maybe drop about 300k-500k.<br>
I don’t want really fast xp, but not really slow either. It should take about a day to get to level 99 in 2 skills, or something like that.<br>
It shouldn’t take a week-5 years to get 99 in 1 skill, but not 1 day and your 99 in all the skills… you know?<br>
I want HD to be available.<br>
It would be very awesome if CC worked, as alot of you reading this may know, there are maybe 10-20 prs’s out there that have<br>
that working, but even then, it doesn’t run the same as regular Runescape.<br>
Friends &amp; Ignore lists MUST work.<br>
The server needs Bandos, Dragonfire Shield, Dragon Platebody, Dragon Full Helm, Dragon Claws, etc…<br>
All Specials need to work.<br>
The quest tab I want to have teles added:<br>
king black dragon<br>
grand exchange<br>
shops<br>
pest control<br>
castlewars<br>
barrows<br>
assult<br>
godwars<br>
fightpits</p>
<p>then quests.<br>
Monkey Madness<br>
Reciepe for Distaster…</p>
<p>They need to tele to the area.<br>
Quests don’t have to work, but once again… Would be super intense if they did.<br>
Pest Control needs to work 100% not 75%, not 90%, but 100%!<br>
All the monsters need to attack, but a little easier to kill. (not too easy)<br>
Castle wars needs to work.<br>
I want the shops to be at ge…<br>
Here is a little of different shops that I want there:<br>
Dragon Market - All dragon armour, then all dragon weapons.<br>
Trainee Market - Bronze, Iron, Steel, Mithril, Adamant Platebody, Platelegs, Kiteshield, Scimitar &amp; Full Helm. Dragon fireshield<br>
Pro Market - Bandos Chestplate, Bandos legs, Dragonfire Shield, BGS, SGS, ZGS, AGS, Spirit shields, Helm on Neitiznot<br>
&amp; Abysal Whip.<br>
Skill Cape Market - All TRIMMED skillcapes, then non trimmed skillcapes, then end with the Quest cape. (Must be Bob)<br>
Barrows Market - (Needs to be at barrows) Veracs, Dharoks, Guthans, Torags, Arhims then Karil’s.<br>
-In this order: head, top, bottom, weapon-<br>
Pest Control items don’t really matter. Just want something cool.<br>
Assult items need to be: Rune Defender, Fighter Torso &amp;<br>
Colored Market - Colored Whips, Colored Dragonfire Shields, Colored Party Hats &amp; Colored Santa Hats.<br>
Trick Market - All infinity, Wizard, Mystic, Zamorak, Guthix &amp; Saradomin Magic items.<br>
Rune Market - Air, Fire, Water, Earth, Mind, Body, Chaos, Nature, Cozmic, Death, Blood, Law, Soul, and so on.<br>
(Magic skill needs to work 100%)<br>
Archery Market - Shortbow, Oak Shortbow, Maple Shortbow, willow shortbow, Magic Shortbow, Magic Longbow, Dark Bow,<br>
Crystal Bow, Bronze, Iron, Steel, Mithril, Adamant, Rune, Dragon arrows… Adamant, Rune Crossbow… Bronze, Steel, Opal,<br>
Rune, Dragon bolts. Archer’s Ring.<br>
(If enough room) Green d’hide armour, then blue, red, black. (coif, top, bottom, vambraces) Robinhood Hat, then boots.<br>
Toktz Market - All the different obby armour (prefer the order that it’s in on Runescape. but doesn’t matter.)<br>
Granite Market - Granite helm, Granite Platebody, Granite Platelegs, Granite Maul, Berserker ring, Warrior ring, Seers ring.<br>
Robe Market - All the colored robes. Hat, top, bottom, Gloves, then boots. Order of color doesn’t matter.<br>
General Market - Needs to have Tinderbox, Hammer, knife, Net, Big Net, Cage, Harpoon, rune essence, pure essence,<br>
Bronze, Iron, Steel, Mithril, Adamant &amp; Rune Arrow heads, Feathers, Arrow Shafts.<br>
Skiller Market - Bronze, Iron, Black, Steel, Mithril, Adamant, Rune, Dragon Pickaxe, then in that order with Hatchets.</p>
<p>There needs to be a shop with items for Hunting, Summoning, Construction, Herblore, Slayer, Crafting.<br>
All shops need to have all the item amounts be atleast 100, but if it’s stuff like, Tinderbox, runes, arrows, etc. make 10,000+<br>
Hunter shop needs to have all the hunters equipment. Summoning needs to have pouches to summon, Herblore need vails of<br>
water, abunch of unclean herbs, and things to mix with the herbs. Construction needs all the planks, nails, Cloths, Clay,<br>
hammer, limstone, etc… Slayer needs all the slayer stuff. Crafting needs all uncut gems, a chisel, needle, thread, already<br>
tanned leather… both hard &amp; soft. then all the d’hides (ready to craft)<br>
The names can just be like, Hunting Market, Summoning Market, Construction Market, Herblore Market, Slayer Market, &amp;<br>
Crafting Market.</p>
<p>I don’t want all the shops to be in the same area, try to break them up a little bit. There needs to be 1 Custom Market… I can<br>
add the items to that, or give you the items when they are done to add.<br>
Some of the shops, obviously need to be in a specific area, like Barrows. Needs to be in the Barrows area.<br>
(I would like Barrows to be in the oringal spot.)</p>
<p>A couple of my idea’s to completely add to it are:<br>
When you click the skill icon, a thing will appear in the chatbox asking, “What would you like to do?” :Teleport :View Stats<br>
If you cick Teleport, it tele’s you to one of the best spots to train in that skill, if you click view stats, the menu thing appears,<br>
telling you what level you need for each different thing.<br>
That’s just an idea there, but can  be added.</p>
<p>I have a runescape website like the oringal one (not the updated one.) I just don’t know how to get it on <a href="http://webs.com" rel="nofollow noopener">webs.com</a><br>
If you know how to do that, I would appreicate that too. <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=5" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
<p>I want the name to ofcourse be changed to “Eternal Scape”<br>
I’ve seen some servers have it to where, whenever the owners log in, it informs everbody online. Regardless of if friends or not.<br>
I want that! So whenever “Mars Tattoo” “Pluto View” or “DevinHeaven” sign on, that everybody knows.</p>
<p>Price Checker needs to work, &amp; Be located inbetween the teleports &amp; Quests.</p>
<p>All skills must work 100%!!!<br>
Items kept on Death, and Show Equipment Stats buttons must work.</p>
<h2>If you have any questions, or if you are wanting to help… E-mail me <a href="mailto:Marstattoo@aol.com">Marstattoo@aol.com</a><br>
Either leave the subject blank, or title it “Eternal Scape”</h2>
<p>Don’t leave comments if your going to say something negative… You’ll just be wasting your time because I don’t care what you have to say.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/need-a-cool-coder-read-for-more/342370/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/need-a-cool-coder-read-for-more/342370/1</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 02 Jun 2010 04:56:14 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-342370-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/need-a-cool-coder-read-for-more/342370.rss">Need a cool coder, read for more. :)</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
