<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>The Hunter [2012]</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-hunter-2012/526624</link>
    <description>[center]*disclaimer, most people here probably wont end up watching but I thought I&#39;d give my opinion just in case*
http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=fhDwv8PBGAk

[size=14pt][b]Everything you need to know:[/b][/size]
First of the first the movie is about a mercenary sent by some unknown company to somewhere in Australia where he is on the hunt for a soul surviving Tasmanian Tiger, priceless as mentioned in the movie. Uncovering as a scientist from a university to hide from rivalry.

[size=14pt][b]No spoiler review:[/b][/size]
Okay so watching half of the trailer I expected to see a nice simmering horror or at the very least action but it turned out to be a drama and I&#39;m not big on that but I did watch it all, though it is a movie you probably wouldn&#39;t want to schedule to watch. It was one of those movies where things happen when you don&#39;t want them do, you expect one thing and they give you dog shit and it makes you literally feel like shit or at least make the main character feel like he is feeling shit. There isn&#39;t much I can say without spoiling the whole thing but I can say I wouldn&#39;t watch again, first time is enough and I would definitely watch it with a emotional girl by my side.

[center][b]After Movie Review:[/b][/center]
[size=5pt]I felt the ending was perfect for the film even though I literally felt like dog shit for the main character. I literally wanted to jump into the movie and give him a nice hug and pat on the back, I really felt for him. He played that character where you really want him to be happy, you see what he goes through and when the mother and daughter die you just want him to turn Darth Vader and seek revenge on everyone. Him killing the Tiger was also a good move and the director interpreting the fact that the Tiger knew its time was up is perfect, even though I felt sorry as shit for the thing. I mean Martin was only just a replacement for the father which he figured out after finding the documents on the fathers remains and realizing so ending up in killing the Tiger for the sake of no more deaths, it is all just perfect though I wouldn&#39;t think it&#39;ll be original but more cliche. You also feel for that kid man, his sister and himself were really close and thinking back when they were plying together, its sad man but not enough to blabber about.[/size]

I would rate this movie a solid 6.5 out of 10 tabbies.[/center]</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 19 Aug 2013 08:25:13 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>General Discussion</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-hunter-2012/526624.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>The Hunter [2012]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@TabbyKiller TabbyKiller]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/tabbykiller">@TabbyKiller</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Sure AmazingFilms247, you can have a Tabby.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-hunter-2012/526624/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-hunter-2012/526624/3</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 19 Aug 2013 08:25:13 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-526624-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-hunter-2012/526624.rss">The Hunter [2012]</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The Hunter [2012]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@jc22493 Jc22493]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/jc22493">@jc22493</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Can I have a tabby?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-hunter-2012/526624/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-hunter-2012/526624/2</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 11 Aug 2013 21:25:43 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-526624-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-hunter-2012/526624.rss">The Hunter [2012]</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The Hunter [2012]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@TabbyKiller TabbyKiller]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/tabbykiller">@TabbyKiller</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[center]<em>disclaimer, most people here probably wont end up watching but I thought I’d give my opinion just in case</em><br>
<div class="lazyYT" data-youtube-id="fhDwv8PBGAk" data-youtube-title="The Hunter MOVIE Trailer (Willem Dafoe, Sam Neil - 2012)" data-width="480" data-height="270" data-parameters="feature=oembed&amp;wmode=opaque"></div></p>
<p>[size=14pt]<span class="bbcode-b">Everything you need to know:</span>[/size]<br>
First of the first the movie is about a mercenary sent by some unknown company to somewhere in Australia where he is on the hunt for a soul surviving Tasmanian Tiger, priceless as mentioned in the movie. Uncovering as a scientist from a university to hide from rivalry.</p>
<p>[size=14pt]<span class="bbcode-b">No spoiler review:</span>[/size]<br>
Okay so watching half of the trailer I expected to see a nice simmering horror or at the very least action but it turned out to be a drama and I’m not big on that but I did watch it all, though it is a movie you probably wouldn’t want to schedule to watch. It was one of those movies where things happen when you don’t want them do, you expect one thing and they give you dog shit and it makes you literally feel like shit or at least make the main character feel like he is feeling shit. There isn’t much I can say without spoiling the whole thing but I can say I wouldn’t watch again, first time is enough and I would definitely watch it with a emotional girl by my side.</p>
<p>[center]<span class="bbcode-b">After Movie Review:</span>[/center]<br>
[size=5pt]I felt the ending was perfect for the film even though I literally felt like dog shit for the main character. I literally wanted to jump into the movie and give him a nice hug and pat on the back, I really felt for him. He played that character where you really want him to be happy, you see what he goes through and when the mother and daughter die you just want him to turn Darth Vader and seek revenge on everyone. Him killing the Tiger was also a good move and the director interpreting the fact that the Tiger knew its time was up is perfect, even though I felt sorry as shit for the thing. I mean Martin was only just a replacement for the father which he figured out after finding the documents on the fathers remains and realizing so ending up in killing the Tiger for the sake of no more deaths, it is all just perfect though I wouldn’t think it’ll be original but more cliche. You also feel for that kid man, his sister and himself were really close and thinking back when they were plying together, its sad man but not enough to blabber about.[/size]</p>
<p>I would rate this movie a solid 6.5 out of 10 tabbies.[/center]</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-hunter-2012/526624/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-hunter-2012/526624/1</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2013 11:09:16 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-526624-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-hunter-2012/526624.rss">The Hunter [2012]</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
