<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Just A Personal Suggestion</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/just-a-personal-suggestion/130743</link>
    <description>[b]Presentation[/b]
During my first 3 days (going on 4) I have quickly gain reputation from people, however. I wish for you to know this that:

I am No java expert, I only know about strings, constructers etc - things for beginners. Though I am currently learning each night I take out my java book to read. My goals are programming for the fun, helping anyone I can &amp; being a no argumenter on this board; for that is a violation of rule 3 &amp; 10 on this forum. I may speak of a intelligent person, yet I am really not - Just a calm person who is 14 years old trying to enjoy life &amp; train on java source codes for there future education. I write a lot, do not talk to much as I like to concentrate on my objective ideas first - then comes conversation. I will become a treaty of your life if you let me into your life, if not then let it be, though I will always have space for you when you need that special moment. How I was introduced was from a great angelling friend called Dan, #1 friend in my life &amp; will most likely always be with a 92.7 adverage reputation in it with another angel that came picking me up with greatful suggestions for programming called Chris who has excellence in website designing &amp; developing.

[b]Amazed At All The Troubling MPU&#39;ers (Mopar Users)[/b]
I have over 30 messages about this &amp; that on where should I put this &amp; that. Take my suggestion - If you can&#39;t learn java then play other people servers so you want have to waste your life on pointless server projects of yours. If you do want to learn &amp; really, really will do somethen for it then learn java &amp; instead of learning from websites, buy a book. The book is better because it explains various methods of how java cycles in use of its language. Back on to my topic with my 30 messages statement now. I can not keep track of who though I can give you lessons if you need. I could always respond to your messages as well, but there is a contract between us, you stay strict of disobeying the rules of this board &amp; I can help you; this board is already under spam if you haven&#39;t notice. Many of you who&#39;ve taking the test with &quot;always search for tutors of what your looking for before attempting a question for help.&quot; have not been paying attention &amp; for this I litterally suggest for the admins to set out new questions a month or your account gets locked up until the survey quiz is complete &amp; that the admins should have a time out ban for people who repeat a certain word all day in each post that could possibly have you timed out off of the board for an hour. I just want people to understand that I will try my best at helping you with all of my abilitys at its limit &amp; for those project developement thread I hope you didnt find me as a permanant volunteer for I am working on a different generation of coding &amp; thats to make a 3D Online game (Currently working on a 2D game called Tex which will advance to a 3D game once its set up). 

[b]Some Thoughts I Could Never Get Rid off[/b]
Many people say C+ &amp; C++ is better then java but what the results are is something like a cousin next to it:

C+ was the first language that was developed for game programming
Then
C+ got upgraded to C++ which made it 1x time better then C++
And
Then C++ got upgraded to java by James Gosling - Thanks to this man we would not be using his wonderful language.

Now Java was made in 1991 by Jame Gosling, he stabled himself in his office just to fix a program that was not functioning right on a project called star7; that he &amp; his group mates were working on since C++ had not been working well on the program. After 4 years later the language had finally been release &amp; at that time was called oak. The language was called OAK, but later only they notice that it had already been in use by another company so they had to think of a name for the language, but only that time it was to be a special name called Java. So now you know the truth about java &amp; nothing but the truth about its past. Java is the same as C+ &amp; C++ is the same as C+ only C++ is better then C+ because C++ is a updated version of the C+ language &amp; Java is a version of C++ only writen down to a good quality where you do not have to learn that much about C++ &amp; C+ anymore. People still use C++ &amp; C+ today because they know that in C++ &amp; C+ you dont have to compile everytime you remodifie a .Java file extention for update.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 06 Aug 2007 15:33:16 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/just-a-personal-suggestion/130743.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Just A Personal Suggestion</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Jay_Laze .Jay Laze]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/jay_laze">@Jay_Laze</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p><span class="bbcode-b">Presentation</span><br>
During my first 3 days (going on 4) I have quickly gain reputation from people, however. I wish for you to know this that:</p>
<p>I am No java expert, I only know about strings, constructers etc - things for beginners. Though I am currently learning each night I take out my java book to read. My goals are programming for the fun, helping anyone I can &amp; being a no argumenter on this board; for that is a violation of rule 3 &amp; 10 on this forum. I may speak of a intelligent person, yet I am really not - Just a calm person who is 14 years old trying to enjoy life &amp; train on java source codes for there future education. I write a lot, do not talk to much as I like to concentrate on my objective ideas first - then comes conversation. I will become a treaty of your life if you let me into your life, if not then let it be, though I will always have space for you when you need that special moment. How I was introduced was from a great angelling friend called Dan, <span class="hashtag">#1</span> friend in my life &amp; will most likely always be with a 92.7 adverage reputation in it with another angel that came picking me up with greatful suggestions for programming called Chris who has excellence in website designing &amp; developing.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Amazed At All The Troubling MPU’ers (Mopar Users)</span><br>
I have over 30 messages about this &amp; that on where should I put this &amp; that. Take my suggestion - If you can’t learn java then play other people servers so you want have to waste your life on pointless server projects of yours. If you do want to learn &amp; really, really will do somethen for it then learn java &amp; instead of learning from websites, buy a book. The book is better because it explains various methods of how java cycles in use of its language. Back on to my topic with my 30 messages statement now. I can not keep track of who though I can give you lessons if you need. I could always respond to your messages as well, but there is a contract between us, you stay strict of disobeying the rules of this board &amp; I can help you; this board is already under spam if you haven’t notice. Many of you who’ve taking the test with “always search for tutors of what your looking for before attempting a question for help.” have not been paying attention &amp; for this I litterally suggest for the admins to set out new questions a month or your account gets locked up until the survey quiz is complete &amp; that the admins should have a time out ban for people who repeat a certain word all day in each post that could possibly have you timed out off of the board for an hour. I just want people to understand that I will try my best at helping you with all of my abilitys at its limit &amp; for those project developement thread I hope you didnt find me as a permanant volunteer for I am working on a different generation of coding &amp; thats to make a 3D Online game (Currently working on a 2D game called Tex which will advance to a 3D game once its set up).</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Some Thoughts I Could Never Get Rid off</span><br>
Many people say C+ &amp; C++ is better then java but what the results are is something like a cousin next to it:</p>
<p>C+ was the first language that was developed for game programming<br>
Then<br>
C+ got upgraded to C++ which made it 1x time better then C++<br>
And<br>
Then C++ got upgraded to java by James Gosling - Thanks to this man we would not be using his wonderful language.</p>
<p>Now Java was made in 1991 by Jame Gosling, he stabled himself in his office just to fix a program that was not functioning right on a project called star7; that he &amp; his group mates were working on since C++ had not been working well on the program. After 4 years later the language had finally been release &amp; at that time was called oak. The language was called OAK, but later only they notice that it had already been in use by another company so they had to think of a name for the language, but only that time it was to be a special name called Java. So now you know the truth about java &amp; nothing but the truth about its past. Java is the same as C+ &amp; C++ is the same as C+ only C++ is better then C+ because C++ is a updated version of the C+ language &amp; Java is a version of C++ only writen down to a good quality where you do not have to learn that much about C++ &amp; C+ anymore. People still use C++ &amp; C+ today because they know that in C++ &amp; C+ you dont have to compile everytime you remodifie a .Java file extention for update.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/just-a-personal-suggestion/130743/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/just-a-personal-suggestion/130743/1</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 06 Aug 2007 15:33:16 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-130743-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/just-a-personal-suggestion/130743.rss">Just A Personal Suggestion</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
