<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Throw Some Cheese</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/throw-some-cheese/75393</link>
    <description>[flash=200,200]http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=iRwz65vKHiU[/flash]

http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=iRwz65vKHiU

By Po` Boy


Lyrics:

THROW SOME CHEESE LYRICS

WhiteWood. Get hungry?! Who hungry?! Heeeey!

Chorus x2:
Po&#39; boy smelling dat, dope niggas wanna snack, I&#39;m like no snacks, Just bought a Big Mac. THROW SOME CHEESE ON DAT BITCH! Just bought a Big Mac. THROW SOME CHEESE ON DAT BITCH! Just bought a Big Mac.

1st Verse:
Po&#39; boy smelling dat, dope niggas wanna snack, I&#39;m like no snack, Just bought a Big Mac. Passed by the grocery shop, turned down the lollipop, I was ridin&#39; non-stop, reached for my coin slot. It&#39;s hoes in the parking lot! So I got a parking spot. Who hungry muthafucka bout to cop a big Sprite. Standin&#39; in this big line, bout to cop a big meal. Wonder who they waiting on lately, baby, this here. Caint wait, man, I&#39;m &#39;bout to eat, call me hungry. Get it understood, #1 and a #3. Haters wish they could steal the goods out my #3. Slam my arch card so them muthafuckas know it&#39;s me!

Chorusx2

2nd Verse:
I never slip, I never fall. A large drink with my #1 because it&#39;s never small. I&#39;m real huungry, look in the lobby and see a nigga ball. And after we smash them nuggets with sweet and sour sauce, yeah I&#39;mma break em off. (And that&#39;s all!) Every freak should have a dollar menu list (On they wall!). Ronald be the shit, milkshakes be thick, nuggets (For my dogs!). Yeah, dranks and custards, lace me with mustard. (Wait a minute muthafucka!)

Chorus x2

3rd Verse
Hit McDonalds, pocket full of 10 one-dollar-bills, cain&#39;t explain how it feel, two pies it&#39;s unreal. Got fudge sunday ice cream wasting on my seats. Just got a fresh buck and we looking for McKey D&#39;s, baby. I&#39;ll cop a dollar pop, never drop my straw. Imma show you how to ball, middle finger to all of ya&#39;ll. So fuck them niggas, what they wanna do? Hatin&#39; &#39;cause they food sorry on they dollar menu. When I pull up, Imma park right at the front, Hi-C in my cup, might see me with a buck. I&#39;m a real pimp, cashiers swear that I be rich, &#39;cause I copped a Big Mac and Parfait with that bitch!</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 07 Apr 2007 08:18:47 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>General Discussion</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/throw-some-cheese/75393.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Throw Some Cheese</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@YourDistracted YourDistracted]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/yourdistracted">@YourDistracted</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Wtf. This is the most random thing I have ever seen lol.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/throw-some-cheese/75393/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/throw-some-cheese/75393/2</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 07 Apr 2007 08:18:47 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-75393-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/throw-some-cheese/75393.rss">Throw Some Cheese</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Throw Some Cheese</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@0uch_a_arr0w 0uch a arr0w]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/0uch_a_arr0w">@0uch_a_arr0w</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[flash=200,200]<a href="http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=iRwz65vKHiU%5B/flash%5D" rel="nofollow noopener">http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=iRwz65vKHiU[/flash]</a></p>
<div class="lazyYT" data-youtube-id="iRwz65vKHiU" data-youtube-title="PO' BOY - THROW SOME CHEESE" data-width="480" data-height="270" data-parameters="feature=oembed&amp;wmode=opaque"></div>
<p>By Po` Boy</p>
<p>Lyrics:</p>
<p>THROW SOME CHEESE LYRICS</p>
<p>WhiteWood. Get hungry?! Who hungry?! Heeeey!</p>
<p>Chorus x2:<br>
Po’ boy smelling dat, dope niggas wanna snack, I’m like no snacks, Just bought a Big Mac. THROW SOME CHEESE ON DAT BITCH! Just bought a Big Mac. THROW SOME CHEESE ON DAT BITCH! Just bought a Big Mac.</p>
<p>1st Verse:<br>
Po’ boy smelling dat, dope niggas wanna snack, I’m like no snack, Just bought a Big Mac. Passed by the grocery shop, turned down the lollipop, I was ridin’ non-stop, reached for my coin slot. It’s hoes in the parking lot! So I got a parking spot. Who hungry muthafucka bout to cop a big Sprite. Standin’ in this big line, bout to cop a big meal. Wonder who they waiting on lately, baby, this here. Caint wait, man, I’m 'bout to eat, call me hungry. Get it understood, <span class="hashtag">#1</span> and a <span class="hashtag">#3</span>. Haters wish they could steal the goods out my <span class="hashtag">#3</span>. Slam my arch card so them muthafuckas know it’s me!</p>
<p>Chorusx2</p>
<p>2nd Verse:<br>
I never slip, I never fall. A large drink with my <span class="hashtag">#1</span> because it’s never small. I’m real huungry, look in the lobby and see a nigga ball. And after we smash them nuggets with sweet and sour sauce, yeah I’mma break em off. (And that’s all!) Every freak should have a dollar menu list (On they wall!). Ronald be the shit, milkshakes be thick, nuggets (For my dogs!). Yeah, dranks and custards, lace me with mustard. (Wait a minute muthafucka!)</p>
<p>Chorus x2</p>
<p>3rd Verse<br>
Hit McDonalds, pocket full of 10 one-dollar-bills, cain’t explain how it feel, two pies it’s unreal. Got fudge sunday ice cream wasting on my seats. Just got a fresh buck and we looking for McKey D’s, baby. I’ll cop a dollar pop, never drop my straw. Imma show you how to ball, middle finger to all of ya’ll. So fuck them niggas, what they wanna do? Hatin’ 'cause they food sorry on they dollar menu. When I pull up, Imma park right at the front, Hi-C in my cup, might see me with a buck. I’m a real pimp, cashiers swear that I be rich, 'cause I copped a Big Mac and Parfait with that bitch!</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/throw-some-cheese/75393/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/throw-some-cheese/75393/1</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 06 Apr 2007 23:42:07 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-75393-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/throw-some-cheese/75393.rss">Throw Some Cheese</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
