<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Help with my custom command. &quot;punish&quot; 317</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/help-with-my-custom-command-punish-317/326842</link>
    <description>I have created a custom command called &quot;punish&quot; within my combattscape based private server. and  basically what its supposed to do is send another player to the coordinates i set it to. and where the person is teleported is where he dies by tons of monsters in a box. and it yells over the chatbox to type ::watch or ::watch2 (which are easy commands i fulfilled) . and the people can go there and watch the person die and lose his items. The purpose is to punish. Now, after studying all the commands, it has made this command considerably hard to create because i had to choose the structure of the &quot;jail command&quot; i copied jails command exactly, changed the coordinates and name of command, and the messages is sends to players, but it still wont teleport them. the jail command is right because ive tested it. it just wont find players with my other command. all help is appreciated, and i will rep the person who helps me make this work. thanks :D this is the command it didnt work correctly----it never finds the players name to teleport them------ i apologize for not knowing how to condense the code into those little boxes.


} 
            if(command.startsWith(&quot;punish&quot;) &amp;&amp; playerRights &gt;= 1) {
                try {
                    String otherPName = command.substring(5);
                    int otherPIndex = PlayerHandler.getPlayerID(otherPName);

                    if (otherPIndex != -1) {
                        client p = (client) server.playerHandler.players[otherPIndex];
                        p.toX = 2893;
			p.toY = 3535;
                        p.sM(
                                &quot;You have been PUNISHED by &quot; + playerName);
			sM(&quot;You have punished &quot;+p.playerName+&quot;.&quot;);
                    } else { 
                       sM(&quot;The name doesnt exist, or the player is offline.&quot;); 
                    }
                } catch (Exception e) { 
                    sM(&quot;Try entering a name you want to punish..&quot;);
                }</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 23 Jan 2010 22:08:22 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/help-with-my-custom-command-punish-317/326842.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Help with my custom command. &quot;punish&quot; 317</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@delmarvascape delmarvascape]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/delmarvascape">@delmarvascape</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I have created a custom command called “punish” within my combattscape based private server. and  basically what its supposed to do is send another player to the coordinates i set it to. and where the person is teleported is where he dies by tons of monsters in a box. and it yells over the chatbox to type ::watch or ::watch2 (which are easy commands i fulfilled) . and the people can go there and watch the person die and lose his items. The purpose is to punish. Now, after studying all the commands, it has made this command considerably hard to create because i had to choose the structure of the “jail command” i copied jails command exactly, changed the coordinates and name of command, and the messages is sends to players, but it still wont teleport them. the jail command is right because ive tested it. it just wont find players with my other command. all help is appreciated, and i will rep the person who helps me make this work. thanks <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/smiley.png?v=5" title=":smiley:" class="emoji" alt=":smiley:"> this is the command it didnt work correctly----it never finds the players name to teleport them------ i apologize for not knowing how to condense the code into those little boxes.</p>
<p>}<br>
if(command.startsWith(“punish”) &amp;&amp; playerRights &gt;= 1) {<br>
try {<br>
String otherPName = command.substring(5);<br>
int otherPIndex = PlayerHandler.getPlayerID(otherPName);</p>
<pre><code>                if (otherPIndex != -1) {
                    client p = (client) server.playerHandler.players[otherPIndex];
                    p.toX = 2893;
		p.toY = 3535;
                    p.sM(
                            "You have been PUNISHED by " + playerName);
		sM("You have punished "+p.playerName+".");
                } else { 
                   sM("The name doesnt exist, or the player is offline."); 
                }
            } catch (Exception e) { 
                sM("Try entering a name you want to punish..");
            }</code></pre>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/help-with-my-custom-command-punish-317/326842/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/help-with-my-custom-command-punish-317/326842/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 23 Jan 2010 22:08:22 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-326842-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/help-with-my-custom-command-punish-317/326842.rss">Help with my custom command. &quot;punish&quot; 317</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
