<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Applying RuneScape Website Template to a Website?</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/applying-runescape-website-template-to-a-website/433631</link>
    <description>I&#39;m really good with Java, but I&#39;m clueless with all this website stuff. I just got the RuneScape 2007 Website Template (174 mB), but I have no idea what to do with it, or how to apply it to my website. So I went to 000webhost.com and signed up, then I went to &quot;1 Click Website Restore!&quot; because their Support Noobs told me to do that to apply my website template, so that little loading bar that looks like a grey candy cane kept on rolling, and rolling, and loading, but it didn&#39;t finish. I let it run all night, until I saw the text below it:

50mb MAX is what you can upload here, if it&#39;s bigger, use the FTP Uploader.

*megaexetremefacepalm*
I could have been watching porn or something on that instead of waiting for this crap to load, and it didn&#39;t even load!

So then I tried the FTP Uploader, and it didn&#39;t work.

Anyway, now I&#39;m asking you. How do I apply this template to a website?</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 20 Feb 2012 17:01:07 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/applying-runescape-website-template-to-a-website/433631.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Applying RuneScape Website Template to a Website?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@TiVo TiVo]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/tivo">@TiVo</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I’m really good with Java, but I’m clueless with all this website stuff. I just got the RuneScape 2007 Website Template (174 mB), but I have no idea what to do with it, or how to apply it to my website. So I went to <a href="http://000webhost.com" rel="nofollow noopener">000webhost.com</a> and signed up, then I went to “1 Click Website Restore!” because their Support Noobs told me to do that to apply my website template, so that little loading bar that looks like a grey candy cane kept on rolling, and rolling, and loading, but it didn’t finish. I let it run all night, until I saw the text below it:</p>
<p>50mb MAX is what you can upload here, if it’s bigger, use the FTP Uploader.</p>
<p><em>megaexetremefacepalm</em><br>
I could have been watching porn or something on that instead of waiting for this crap to load, and it didn’t even load!</p>
<p>So then I tried the FTP Uploader, and it didn’t work.</p>
<p>Anyway, now I’m asking you. How do I apply this template to a website?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/applying-runescape-website-template-to-a-website/433631/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/applying-runescape-website-template-to-a-website/433631/1</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 20 Feb 2012 17:01:07 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-433631-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/applying-runescape-website-template-to-a-website/433631.rss">Applying RuneScape Website Template to a Website?</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
