<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Server idea</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/server-idea/432167</link>
    <description>So basically I&#39;m working on a server in which you&#39;re in a town ravaged by chaos that&#39;s always in turmoil. Your goal will to either rule those lands or break out. Anyway the place has to look rather apocalyptic, so here&#39;s what I&#39;ve got so far.

As I work I&#39;m going to mess up the landscape more, add a number of tall, ruined buildings, place some fire here and there, a few water\lava streams, and of course, some challenging ways out in which you still might be caught. The only thing I don&#39;t have an idea for is how people could obtain resources within the area without breaking out or completely demolishing the landscape, so suggestions would be nice.

The server will be set up where you spawn within the borders. They&#39;re going to be extended to roughly 100x400. I like to keep the area skinny so that you&#39;re forced to interact with people. These poor souls will do anything to survive, as food will be scarce and materials scarcer. Some people might want to become powerful, so with some form of connection to the outside there will be a way in which resources could be obtained. A person with a diamond sword could be the biggest threat to all. There will be no &#39;surveillance&#39; of this area, however if someone attempts to escape, there will always be guards on the lookout. I&#39;ll probably set up some &#39;black market&#39; system in which you could get a fake ID and become a civilian of the outside. 

I noticed when prison servers came out their popularity skyrocketed, and so I took a similar approach here. I keep people in a small area, and they can interact how they choose. There is an option of &#39;freedom&#39;, and a chance to start your own life if you just want to obtain materials on the outside. It&#39;s a flat world, so I might have to take the entire area and paste it into a normal world for those who escape, but I&#39;m not sure. Anyway just hit me with some suggestions, I want this to actually go pretty big, and hopefully start a new wave of ideas.

Here&#39;s my progress of about 2 hours.
[IMG]http://i39.tinypic.com/8yc1le.png[/img]</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 08 Feb 2012 02:09:27 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Minecraft</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/server-idea/432167.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Server idea</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@reyx7 reyx7]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/reyx7">@reyx7</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>So basically I’m working on a server in which you’re in a town ravaged by chaos that’s always in turmoil. Your goal will to either rule those lands or break out. Anyway the place has to look rather apocalyptic, so here’s what I’ve got so far.</p>
<p>As I work I’m going to mess up the landscape more, add a number of tall, ruined buildings, place some fire here and there, a few water\lava streams, and of course, some challenging ways out in which you still might be caught. The only thing I don’t have an idea for is how people could obtain resources within the area without breaking out or completely demolishing the landscape, so suggestions would be nice.</p>
<p>The server will be set up where you spawn within the borders. They’re going to be extended to roughly 100x400. I like to keep the area skinny so that you’re forced to interact with people. These poor souls will do anything to survive, as food will be scarce and materials scarcer. Some people might want to become powerful, so with some form of connection to the outside there will be a way in which resources could be obtained. A person with a diamond sword could be the biggest threat to all. There will be no ‘surveillance’ of this area, however if someone attempts to escape, there will always be guards on the lookout. I’ll probably set up some ‘black market’ system in which you could get a fake ID and become a civilian of the outside.</p>
<p>I noticed when prison servers came out their popularity skyrocketed, and so I took a similar approach here. I keep people in a small area, and they can interact how they choose. There is an option of ‘freedom’, and a chance to start your own life if you just want to obtain materials on the outside. It’s a flat world, so I might have to take the entire area and paste it into a normal world for those who escape, but I’m not sure. Anyway just hit me with some suggestions, I want this to actually go pretty big, and hopefully start a new wave of ideas.</p>
<p>Here’s my progress of about 2 hours.<br>
<div class="lightbox-wrapper"><a class="lightbox" href="http://i39.tinypic.com/8yc1le.png" title="8yc1le.png" rel="nofollow noopener"><img src="http://i39.tinypic.com/8yc1le.png" alt width="690" height="361"><div class="meta">
<svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-far-image svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#far-image"></use></svg><span class="filename">8yc1le.png</span><span class="informations">1599×838</span><svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-discourse-expand svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#discourse-expand"></use></svg>
</div></a></div></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/server-idea/432167/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/server-idea/432167/1</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 08 Feb 2012 02:09:27 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-432167-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/server-idea/432167.rss">Server idea</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
