<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>We need to change</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/we-need-to-change/470706</link>
    <description>Hey guys.

Now, before I start I want to state that yes; I am the first to oppose change. If something works, don&#39;t change it. If it isn&#39;t broken, why fix it? I know, I know. However, I believe it&#39;s time MoparScape had a change. We really, really need it. For years upon years there&#39;s always been the three main RSPS communities. Ourselves, Rune-Server and Rune Locus. That won&#39;t change for a good while and I know that. However, I feel we&#39;re lagging behind. Rune-Server and Rune Locus are gaining users while we&#39;re just staying right where we are with the same users as we&#39;ve had for a while don&#39;t get me wrong, we are growing, but we&#39;re not growing at the speed of those two. Even smaller communities such as RSPSCoding are moving up and we&#39;re still here.

I&#39;ll start first with Rune Locus. Now, I know myself and Ikliki (doug) whatever you call him don&#39;t get along but I have to admit he&#39;s doing wonders and going to great lengths to gain users. The revamp he&#39;s just done (not without help from members of course) seems very, very good to me. The templates and forums themes are looking attractive, with the launch of MineLocus that&#39;ll be bound to bring in new users. We always had our minecraft community on top of the other two and now we&#39;re down without that. They offer a wide array of tools for anyone to use and start up their RSPS. The new starter pack option is great, once the  tutorials option is complete I&#39;m sure that&#39;ll be very useful, they offer a whole load of ID lists and databases, the status pages and I&#39;m sure they&#39;ll start to bring more and more areas into it. They&#39;re also involved more with social networks than we are, I mean, I think we&#39;re about the only organization in the planet to not use some form of social networking site. I could go on all day regarding them.

Rune-Server aren&#39;t as good as Rune Locus are in my opinion, while they have more users than the two of us put together I still don&#39;t believe that they&#39;re the superior community. As it is right now, they offer more than us but I don&#39;t think they deserve to have that user count. Rune-Server offer 4 ID databases, while once again we don&#39;t offer any. I mean, there&#39;s dumps for these databases all over the place. It&#39;d take a case of two hours to add them. It&#39;s as simple as writing a converter to convert them into SQL format, importing that file to a database and writing a simple search program in PHP. It&#39;s not hard at all yet we still don&#39;t offer it. However, Rune-Server is very, very hideously laid out. The boards are a mind fuck, with the exception of a few staff members they&#39;re corrupt in some ways (so I&#39;ve heard from several trusted sources) the list goes on. I don&#39;t understand why they have the higher user count, the people with the programmer badge don&#39;t deserve it, well, the majority of them don&#39;t. The donator ranks are just silly. They offer an affiliates option along with the toplist sponsor and more or less seem highly motivated by money, they don&#39;t deserve their users yet somehow they have them. We need to change.

I realise we still offer the MoparScape webclient but a lot of people aren&#39;t interested in that anymore. We must change. It ranges from where we don&#39;t even offer a callback system for our toplist to some simple, well explained tutorials laid out for beginners. I&#39;m not aiming this at anyone in particular, I realise Taharok is busy with school, moparisthebest is busy with his kid and what not but surely we can come together as a community and become the community we deserve to be. I realise we&#39;re trying to hand out badges and reduce elitism etc etc and that&#39;s all fine and well but that doesn&#39;t take a whole team of people to do. I don&#39;t know what goes on behind the scenes in the staff section and what the staff are talking about doing, there&#39;s been a few slips of the tongue but nothing actually confirmed. 

I believe a re-vamp is in order. As much as having the webclient on the homepage is useful for people visiting us we need to get rid of it. I mean, come on, we need to be more visually appealing and have some things that we can just refer people  who are wishing to be spoonfed to (like a featured tutorials section). I realise we have the featured tutorials board but we could be doing with some tutorials in it. Davidi2; you have the java guru award, couldn&#39;t you whip up a few tutorials to get people started?

The last thing I want us to do is be mimicking the other communities but we need to offer tools like theirs. ID databases, a source library, archived development tools (zodiac, mendorphins dev tool, arhams thing) a status and port checker, a revamp on the styling of the server status page, add an attractive homepage we can do things like that as a community, provide MITB with the files and he could put them to work. I hate to see where we&#39;ll be in two years time if we don&#39;t do something about it. If we remove the hourly vote limit on our toplist then that&#39;d make it easier for servers with vote for items, cash, tickets easier to incorporate. They would actually use us then.

It&#39;s time we come together as one and work together in getting us back in contention. If our staff are too busy to do it themselves then lets help them. The whole point of us being here is to help others with servers and be a general chat community. If we want to help people and still keep a fairly large amount of users coming back then something must be done or we won&#39;t have a place to come back to in the next few years. I&#39;d hate to have us go down as a dying community, lets make ourselves known again.

I hope you guys can come up with some form of ideas and keep this thread alive. It needed to be said in my opinion, I hope some people share my views. If you&#39;d like to help us come back to where we should be post under here or PM me. We can then set up some form of chat room/IRC channel/Skype chat or some form of contact other than the forums. [b]Everyone is welcome no matter who you are.[/b]

Thanks.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 09 Sep 2015 15:17:37 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>General Discussion</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/we-need-to-change/470706.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>We need to change</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Tutorial Tutorial]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/tutorial">@Tutorial</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>The only way you can change this community is get rid of the nostalgic ways things are done, and simply open your eyes to growth and expansion. We need more involvement with more modern ideas, whether it be games or maybe even new emulations.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/we-need-to-change/470706/217">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/we-need-to-change/470706/217</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 09 Sep 2015 15:17:37 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-470706-217</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/we-need-to-change/470706.rss">We need to change</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>We need to change</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Ruby_Forums_Coder Ruby]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/ruby_forums_coder">@Ruby_Forums_Coder</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“the elve age, post:214, topic:470706”][quote author=Ruby link=topic=588187.msg4494884#msg4494884 date=1441207042]<br>
I actually remember posting this, hard to believe it’s been 3 years since then.<br>
[/quote]I can’t believe how immature I was even 3 years ago. It’s really crazy to see the time fly. I was a freshmen in high school when I joined here… O.o[/quote]<br>
I know dude it’s crazy looking back. Everything changes and yet we still visit here.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/we-need-to-change/470706/216">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/we-need-to-change/470706/216</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 05 Sep 2015 12:47:40 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-470706-216</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/we-need-to-change/470706.rss">We need to change</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>We need to change</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@arham_4 arham 4]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/arham_4">@arham_4</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“the elve age, post:214, topic:470706”][quote author=Ruby link=topic=588187.msg4494884#msg4494884 date=1441207042]<br>
I actually remember posting this, hard to believe it’s been 3 years since then.<br>
[/quote]I can’t believe how immature I was even 3 years ago. It’s really crazy to see the time fly. I was a freshmen in high school when I joined here… O.o[/quote]<br>
3 years ago I was starting middle school.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/we-need-to-change/470706/215">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/we-need-to-change/470706/215</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 05 Sep 2015 12:37:52 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-470706-215</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/we-need-to-change/470706.rss">We need to change</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>We need to change</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@the_elve_age the elve age]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/the_elve_age">@the_elve_age</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“Ruby, post:213, topic:470706”]I actually remember posting this, hard to believe it’s been 3 years since then.[/quote]I can’t believe how immature I was even 3 years ago. It’s really crazy to see the time fly. I was a freshmen in high school when I joined here… O.o</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/we-need-to-change/470706/214">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/we-need-to-change/470706/214</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 05 Sep 2015 07:10:29 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-470706-214</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/we-need-to-change/470706.rss">We need to change</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>We need to change</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Ruby_Forums_Coder Ruby]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/ruby_forums_coder">@Ruby_Forums_Coder</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I actually remember posting this, hard to believe it’s been 3 years since then.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/we-need-to-change/470706/213">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/we-need-to-change/470706/213</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 02 Sep 2015 15:17:22 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-470706-213</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/we-need-to-change/470706.rss">We need to change</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>We need to change</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@drubrkletern drubrkletern]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/drubrkletern">@drubrkletern</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>rest in pistachios moparscape</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/we-need-to-change/470706/212">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/we-need-to-change/470706/212</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2015 21:59:33 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-470706-212</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/we-need-to-change/470706.rss">We need to change</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>We need to change</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@gothic_queen casey.]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/gothic_queen">@gothic_queen</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Tom has started changing somethings now after years of the community desperately pleading and crying to make a change. However, a 14 year old is incapable of administrating a site of this size and sadly it is appearing to be too late…</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/we-need-to-change/470706/211">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/we-need-to-change/470706/211</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2015 16:04:57 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-470706-211</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/we-need-to-change/470706.rss">We need to change</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>We need to change</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Mezzyscape562 Mezzyscape562]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/mezzyscape562">@Mezzyscape562</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Yet here we are, 3 years later and nothing has changed… I do agree with everything you’ve stated, and I may be a bit late to this.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/we-need-to-change/470706/210">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/we-need-to-change/470706/210</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2015 15:34:49 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-470706-210</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/we-need-to-change/470706.rss">We need to change</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>We need to change</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@drubrkletern drubrkletern]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/drubrkletern">@drubrkletern</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“Team_Rocket, post:208, topic:470706”][quote author=drubrkletern link=topic=588187.msg4194882#msg4194882 date=1357370137]</p>
<aside class="quote">
<blockquote>
<aside class="quote">
<blockquote>
<p>being racist because that is certainly frowned upon here.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Yeah, right. I’ve had many people from this community speak with me, and they ask, “T_R, are you black?”. I  respond with, “No, what makes you ask such a thing?”. Their response is usually proceeded by the most foul racist ‘jokes’ I’ve ever read. This can probably be accredited to the immature community though.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Someone failed to detect the sarcasm in that  <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/expressionless.png?v=5" title=":expressionless:" class="emoji" alt=":expressionless:"><br>
We are probably one of the most racist communities I know of, behind the KKK at least<br>
[/quote]</p>
<p>I didn’t fail to detect anything. You [b]African.[/quote]<br>
ho ho i see what you did there</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/we-need-to-change/470706/209">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/we-need-to-change/470706/209</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 05 Jan 2013 20:56:10 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-470706-209</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/we-need-to-change/470706.rss">We need to change</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>We need to change</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Team_Rocket Team_Rocket]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/team_rocket">@Team_Rocket</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“drubrkletern, post:205, topic:470706”][quote author=Team_Rocket link=topic=588187.msg4194729#msg4194729 date=1357351950]</p>
<aside class="quote">
<blockquote>
<p>being racist because that is certainly frowned upon here.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Yeah, right. I’ve had many people from this community speak with me, and they ask, “T_R, are you black?”. I  respond with, “No, what makes you ask such a thing?”. Their response is usually proceeded by the most foul racist ‘jokes’ I’ve ever read. This can probably be accredited to the immature community though.<br>
[/quote]<br>
Someone failed to detect the sarcasm in that  <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/expressionless.png?v=5" title=":expressionless:" class="emoji" alt=":expressionless:"><br>
We are probably one of the most racist communities I know of, behind the KKK at least[/quote]</p>
<p>I didn’t fail to detect anything. You [b]NIGGER.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/we-need-to-change/470706/208">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/we-need-to-change/470706/208</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 05 Jan 2013 20:48:48 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-470706-208</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/we-need-to-change/470706.rss">We need to change</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>We need to change</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Tree Tree]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/tree">@Tree</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>11 pages in and nothing has changed. This is just like any other threads on this topic that have been posted in the past.</p>
<p>I hope you’ve all learnt just to go with the flow and to never clutter my screen with threads like this again.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/we-need-to-change/470706/207">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/we-need-to-change/470706/207</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 05 Jan 2013 16:00:23 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-470706-207</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/we-need-to-change/470706.rss">We need to change</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>We need to change</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@runescape_sucks runescape sucks]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/runescape_sucks">@runescape_sucks</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote" data-post="205" data-topic="470706">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/drubrkletern/40/5_e05bb34c421432ee4d40de30c10af3e5.png" class="avatar"> drubrkletern:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>We are probably one of the most racist communities I know of, behind the KKK at least</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I almost died of laughing.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/we-need-to-change/470706/206">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/we-need-to-change/470706/206</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 05 Jan 2013 08:15:38 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-470706-206</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/we-need-to-change/470706.rss">We need to change</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>We need to change</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@drubrkletern drubrkletern]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/drubrkletern">@drubrkletern</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“Team_Rocket, post:203, topic:470706”][quote author=drubrkletern link=topic=588187.msg4194367#msg4194367 date=1357290505]<br>
being racist because that is certainly frowned upon here.<br>
[/quote]</p>
<p>Yeah, right. I’ve had many people from this community speak with me, and they ask, “T_R, are you black?”. I  respond with, “No, what makes you ask such a thing?”. Their response is usually proceeded by the most foul racist ‘jokes’ I’ve ever read. This can probably be accredited to the immature community though.[/quote]<br>
Someone failed to detect the sarcasm in that  <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/expressionless.png?v=5" title=":expressionless:" class="emoji" alt=":expressionless:"><br>
We are probably one of the most racist communities I know of, behind the KKK at least</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/we-need-to-change/470706/205">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/we-need-to-change/470706/205</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 05 Jan 2013 07:15:37 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-470706-205</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/we-need-to-change/470706.rss">We need to change</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>We need to change</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@vManlyMan vManlyMan]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/vmanlyman">@vManlyMan</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“Team_Rocket, post:203, topic:470706”][quote author=drubrkletern link=topic=588187.msg4194367#msg4194367 date=1357290505]<br>
being racist because that is certainly frowned upon here.<br>
[/quote]</p>
<p>Yeah, right. I’ve had many people from this community speak with me, and they ask, “T_R, are you black?”. I  respond with, “No, what makes you ask such a thing?”. Their response is usually proceeded by the most foul racist ‘jokes’ I’ve ever read. This can probably be accredited to the immature community though.[/quote]</p>
<p>When I lived in Detroit and people found out, so many people were asking if I was black.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/we-need-to-change/470706/204">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/we-need-to-change/470706/204</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 05 Jan 2013 02:23:25 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-470706-204</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/we-need-to-change/470706.rss">We need to change</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>We need to change</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Team_Rocket Team_Rocket]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/team_rocket">@Team_Rocket</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote" data-post="201" data-topic="470706">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/drubrkletern/40/5_e05bb34c421432ee4d40de30c10af3e5.png" class="avatar"> drubrkletern:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>being racist because that is certainly frowned upon here.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Yeah, right. I’ve had many people from this community speak with me, and they ask, “T_R, are you black?”. I  respond with, “No, what makes you ask such a thing?”. Their response is usually proceeded by the most foul racist ‘jokes’ I’ve ever read. This can probably be accredited to the immature community though.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/we-need-to-change/470706/203">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/we-need-to-change/470706/203</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 05 Jan 2013 02:12:30 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-470706-203</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/we-need-to-change/470706.rss">We need to change</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>We need to change</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Cole1497 Cole1497]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/cole1497">@Cole1497</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>vb is garbage</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/we-need-to-change/470706/202">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/we-need-to-change/470706/202</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 04 Jan 2013 14:56:58 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-470706-202</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/we-need-to-change/470706.rss">We need to change</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>We need to change</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@drubrkletern drubrkletern]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/drubrkletern">@drubrkletern</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“tomato721, post:200, topic:470706”][quote author=Si Force link=topic=588187.msg4193920#msg4193920 date=1357233170]</p>
<aside class="quote">
<blockquote>
<aside class="quote">
<blockquote>
<p>Donations/RWT is too easy to get MITB in trouble, and too easy for people to get scammed.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>rune-server seems to deal with it easily, another thing is we should upgrade to vbulletin 5-connect, it  makes us look more proffesional</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>What’s wrong with SMF?<br>
[/quote]<br>
looks cheaper with this white stuff (not being racist) lol[/quote]<br>
For a moment I thought you were being racist because that is certainly frowned upon here.</p>
<p>For some reason people think because you pay for Vb, makes it superior, not sure why though, when I look at vb I really don’t see much in it, and it seems less convenient to use/more annoying imo</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/we-need-to-change/470706/201">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/we-need-to-change/470706/201</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 04 Jan 2013 09:08:25 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-470706-201</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/we-need-to-change/470706.rss">We need to change</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>We need to change</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@tomato721 tomato721]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/tomato721">@tomato721</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“Si Force, post:194, topic:470706”][quote author=tomato721 link=topic=588187.msg4193914#msg4193914 date=1357232674]</p>
<aside class="quote">
<blockquote>
<p>Donations/RWT is too easy to get MITB in trouble, and too easy for people to get scammed.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>rune-server seems to deal with it easily, another thing is we should upgrade to vbulletin 5-connect, it  makes us look more proffesional<br>
[/quote]</p>
<p>What’s wrong with SMF?[/quote]<br>
looks cheaper with this white stuff (not being racist) lol</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/we-need-to-change/470706/200">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/we-need-to-change/470706/200</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 04 Jan 2013 05:45:39 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-470706-200</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/we-need-to-change/470706.rss">We need to change</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>We need to change</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@drubrkletern drubrkletern]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/drubrkletern">@drubrkletern</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Getting fifth too</p>
<p>And considering the way this community is, its probably never going to change due to:</p>
<ol>
<li>Idiots like me</li>
<li>People who don’t believe in any change</li>
<li>People who think its never going to change</li>
</ol>
<p>Especially the third considering if they don’t try, even if they did in the past, it won’t happen now</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/we-need-to-change/470706/199">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/we-need-to-change/470706/199</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 03 Jan 2013 23:43:22 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-470706-199</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/we-need-to-change/470706.rss">We need to change</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>We need to change</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Cole1497 Cole1497]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/cole1497">@Cole1497</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“Dokan42, post:197, topic:470706”][quote author=marcbob link=topic=588187.msg4194014#msg4194014 date=1357244241]<br>
“runescape private server creation”<br>
-For me MoparScape is 5th on the 1st page. Only one other popular community, rL, is before us. Otherwise it’s like random forums with someone who posted a guide.<br>
[/quote]<br>
I’m getting 5th aswell.[/quote]<br>
Ditto. I think Google bases your searches based on previous searches and visits to sites with Google’s adsense or whatever if you have cookies enabled, so thinks more relevant to your interests appear first.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/we-need-to-change/470706/198">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/we-need-to-change/470706/198</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 03 Jan 2013 22:09:05 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-470706-198</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/we-need-to-change/470706.rss">We need to change</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>We need to change</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Dokan42 Dokan42]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/dokan42">@Dokan42</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“marcbob, post:196, topic:470706”]“runescape private server creation”<br>
-For me MoparScape is 5th on the 1st page. Only one other popular community, rL, is before us. Otherwise it’s like random forums with someone who posted a guide.[/quote]<br>
I’m getting 5th aswell.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/we-need-to-change/470706/197">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/we-need-to-change/470706/197</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 03 Jan 2013 20:20:19 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-470706-197</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/we-need-to-change/470706.rss">We need to change</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>We need to change</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@marcbob marcbob]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/marcbob">@marcbob</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>“runescape private server creation”<br>
-For me MoparScape is 5th on the 1st page. Only one other popular community, rL, is before us. Otherwise it’s like random forums with someone who posted a guide.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/we-need-to-change/470706/196">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/we-need-to-change/470706/196</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 03 Jan 2013 20:17:21 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-470706-196</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/we-need-to-change/470706.rss">We need to change</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>We need to change</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Kidpaparoach Kidpaparoach]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/kidpaparoach">@Kidpaparoach</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“Ambokile, post:189, topic:470706”][quote author=XxJtxX link=topic=588187.msg4193538#msg4193538 date=1357173756]<br>
I came here in 08 because this was the first link on Google when I typed in “How to make a RuneScape Private Server”. Now MoparScape is pretty much the last thing on the first page of Google when you type that in - right after RL and even Near-Reality (for some reason). I remember coming here and asking for help - people were nice and I learned things. Nowadays, if a newbie wants help, I’d immediately tell them to try RL because IMO that’s where all the friendly newbies are/go. I admit, MoparScape has the most brilliant people compared to R-S and RL but that doesn’t mean anything if they don’t get off their damn pedestal and only flame the newbies that want nothing more but to learn.</p>
<p>I don’t believe the staff need to change anything, I believe the actual community needs to change.<br>
[/quote]</p>
<p>Type in “runescape private server creation”, MoparScape isn’t even on the first page. It’s the fourth listing on the second page.[/quote]<br>
I believe its area dependant for me its first page, second link.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/we-need-to-change/470706/195">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/we-need-to-change/470706/195</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 03 Jan 2013 20:12:27 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-470706-195</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/we-need-to-change/470706.rss">We need to change</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>We need to change</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@si_force Si Force]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/si_force">@si_force</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“tomato721, post:193, topic:470706”][quote author=Cole1497 link=topic=588187.msg4193862#msg4193862 date=1357221249]<br>
Donations/RWT is too easy to get MITB in trouble, and too easy for people to get scammed.<br>
[/quote]<br>
rune-server seems to deal with it easily, another thing is we should upgrade to vbulletin 5-connect, it  makes us look more proffesional[/quote]</p>
<p>What’s wrong with SMF?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/we-need-to-change/470706/194">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/we-need-to-change/470706/194</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 03 Jan 2013 17:12:50 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-470706-194</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/we-need-to-change/470706.rss">We need to change</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>We need to change</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@tomato721 tomato721]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/tomato721">@tomato721</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote" data-post="192" data-topic="470706">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/user_avatar/forum.moparisthebest.com/cole1497/40/10925_1.png" class="avatar"> Cole1497:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Donations/RWT is too easy to get MITB in trouble, and too easy for people to get scammed.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>rune-server seems to deal with it easily, another thing is we should upgrade to vbulletin 5-connect, it  makes us look more proffesional</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/we-need-to-change/470706/193">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/we-need-to-change/470706/193</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 03 Jan 2013 17:04:34 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-470706-193</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/we-need-to-change/470706.rss">We need to change</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
