<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>SethScape 508</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/sethscape-508/363467</link>
    <description>SethScape 508: This server is my own base (reconfirgured the whole coding implements), this server is for all players, skills, quests, and more...

This server is set to Runescape - like preference.

I will be adding pictures shortly but im here to give a short description of the features up to date.

FEATURES:

All 24 skills trainable.

3 Quests: Dragon Slayer, Vampire Slayer, and Imp Catcher.

DESCRIPTION: The Dragon Slayer Quest is like Runescape&#39;s but slightly easier, The Vampire Slayer is like Runescape&#39;s but slightly easier with a SethScape twist, as for Imp Catcher which is the most recent one i developed is somewhat like Runescape&#39;s you must collect the 4 bead&#39;s from the thief&#39;s of SethScape , this quest requires alot of walking around and good map location information. Plus 10,000,000 coins.

Good Economy.

DESCRIPTION: The Economy is based on a standard runescape private server, meaning it is somewhat easy and somewhat hard to earn money... it has its pros and cons.

Random Event.

DESCRIPTION: The Random Event is based of Runescape&#39;s Damien workout random event, but with SethScape&#39;s twist... the prize is decent

HOW IT WORKS: I&#39;ve created a bunch of random timer&#39;s subsiquental to the random event, it is not as hard to get as Runescape&#39;s but decent...

Smithing:

DESCRIPTION: I&#39;ve added a full smithing supplement only for rune smithing (dragon smithing) it requires 99 smithing in order to smith, the rune bar requirements are between 3 - 26.

Censored Words:

DESCRIPTION: I&#39;ve added a censoreship system which blocks out all bad words.

Summoning Combat:

DESCRIPTION: Well it&#39;s not much to discuss but the  max combat is 138 with summoning combat...

Sets:

DESCRIPTION: There is a set&#39;s shop located at ::shops which allows you to use a hammer to get a full set subsequental to the set you have bought.


MORE TO COME... let me know what you think about this project, i regularily update it, there is obviously more to this server... but there minor updates and what not... COMMENT!</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 09 Oct 2010 05:56:03 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/sethscape-508/363467.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>SethScape 508</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@sethscape508 sethscape508]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/sethscape508">@sethscape508</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>SethScape 508: This server is my own base (reconfirgured the whole coding implements), this server is for all players, skills, quests, and more…</p>
<p>This server is set to Runescape - like preference.</p>
<p>I will be adding pictures shortly but im here to give a short description of the features up to date.</p>
<p>FEATURES:</p>
<p>All 24 skills trainable.</p>
<p>3 Quests: Dragon Slayer, Vampire Slayer, and Imp Catcher.</p>
<p>DESCRIPTION: The Dragon Slayer Quest is like Runescape’s but slightly easier, The Vampire Slayer is like Runescape’s but slightly easier with a SethScape twist, as for Imp Catcher which is the most recent one i developed is somewhat like Runescape’s you must collect the 4 bead’s from the thief’s of SethScape , this quest requires alot of walking around and good map location information. Plus 10,000,000 coins.</p>
<p>Good Economy.</p>
<p>DESCRIPTION: The Economy is based on a standard runescape private server, meaning it is somewhat easy and somewhat hard to earn money… it has its pros and cons.</p>
<p>Random Event.</p>
<p>DESCRIPTION: The Random Event is based of Runescape’s Damien workout random event, but with SethScape’s twist… the prize is decent</p>
<p>HOW IT WORKS: I’ve created a bunch of random timer’s subsiquental to the random event, it is not as hard to get as Runescape’s but decent…</p>
<p>Smithing:</p>
<p>DESCRIPTION: I’ve added a full smithing supplement only for rune smithing (dragon smithing) it requires 99 smithing in order to smith, the rune bar requirements are between 3 - 26.</p>
<p>Censored Words:</p>
<p>DESCRIPTION: I’ve added a censoreship system which blocks out all bad words.</p>
<p>Summoning Combat:</p>
<p>DESCRIPTION: Well it’s not much to discuss but the  max combat is 138 with summoning combat…</p>
<p>Sets:</p>
<p>DESCRIPTION: There is a set’s shop located at ::shops which allows you to use a hammer to get a full set subsequental to the set you have bought.</p>
<p>MORE TO COME… let me know what you think about this project, i regularily update it, there is obviously more to this server… but there minor updates and what not… COMMENT!</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/sethscape-508/363467/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/sethscape-508/363467/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 09 Oct 2010 05:56:03 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-363467-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/sethscape-508/363467.rss">SethScape 508</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
