<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>[Competitive Fighter] RemiX SF</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/competitive-fighter-remix-sf/412483</link>
    <description>Project: RemiX SF
That&#39;s the file name on a little notepad I have. I&#39;ve yet to come up with an official name for it, but I&#39;ve been thinking about something like this for quite a while.

[b]Brief Overview[/b]
What I&#39;m trying to do here is create a Street Fighter game with ALL the Street Fighter Characters in one game. Retaining its hardcore fighting mechanics, and minor casual friendly mechanics into one game. Having tons of gamemodes and online play. Basically a 2D Street Fighter Mega Game in general.

I&#39;ll be borrowing a lot of mechanics from

[b]Game List[/b]
Street Fighter Alpha Series
- Guard System
- Air Tech System

Street Fighter III Series
- Defensive Parry System
- Forward Dash System
- Tech Throw System
- EX Special Move Properties

Street Fighter IV Series
- Focus Attack (Huge difference though)

[b]Combo System[/b]
I&#39;m thinking of using the Chain Combo system (Similar to Dial-a-Combo) rather than a hardcore Link System (Like SF4). The reason for this is because it&#39;s harder to do Link Combos rather than Chain Combos when playing online, due to lag.

[b]Graphics[/b]
The Graphics would be a mixture of many games thorough the series.
List:
- Street Fighter II Series (Certain Stages Only)

Street Fighter Alpha Series (Stages/Characters)

- Street Fighter III Series (Certain Characters Only, with major resize to fit Alpha/CvS style characters size. Also taking out a few sprites in animations to make their movement feel more fluent when standing next to Alpha or CvS animated sprites.)

- Capcom vs SNK Series (Ryu, Ken, Akuma, Dan, Maki, and Eagle. The Shotos (Ryu, Ken, etc) were given new sprites and is far superior to their Alpha counter-parts. Maki and Eagle are new sprites as well.)

[b]Extras[/b]
Other Capcom characters may be present. Pretty much any Capcom styled fighter is fair game. This includes the Marvel characters, Darkstalkers characters, SNK characters, etc. I&#39;m not limiting the roster to SF characters entirely.

Well nothing is set in stone, so this a scratch of what I&#39;ve been planning. Hell I don&#39;t even know what engine is going to be used. Since I&#39;m learning programming, I thought I&#39;d just create the engine, but everything is still up for grabs. Thought I&#39;d post it up here and see what you guys think about it. I&#39;ll be posting a few pictures and such to actually paint a picture.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 01 Sep 2011 13:55:43 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Game Development</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/competitive-fighter-remix-sf/412483.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>[Competitive Fighter] RemiX SF</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@mod_taharok Taharok]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/mod_taharok">@mod_taharok</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>This sounds like a pretty good idea. I’m not familiar with most of the games you mentioned. <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=5" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"> I do wish you luck though, it sounds like it would be a lot of work doing all this if you haven’t built a game before. I recommend posting in the game mechanics section for acquiring feedback on doing the combat, etc for this game.</p>
<p>As for a library, why not use Slick2D? <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=5" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/competitive-fighter-remix-sf/412483/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/competitive-fighter-remix-sf/412483/2</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 01 Sep 2011 13:55:43 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-412483-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/competitive-fighter-remix-sf/412483.rss">[Competitive Fighter] RemiX SF</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Competitive Fighter] RemiX SF</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Erj Erj]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/erj">@Erj</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Project: RemiX SF<br>
That’s the file name on a little notepad I have. I’ve yet to come up with an official name for it, but I’ve been thinking about something like this for quite a while.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Brief Overview</span><br>
What I’m trying to do here is create a Street Fighter game with ALL the Street Fighter Characters in one game. Retaining its hardcore fighting mechanics, and minor casual friendly mechanics into one game. Having tons of gamemodes and online play. Basically a 2D Street Fighter Mega Game in general.</p>
<p>I’ll be borrowing a lot of mechanics from</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Game List</span><br>
Street Fighter Alpha Series</p>
<ul>
<li>Guard System</li>
<li>Air Tech System</li>
</ul>
<p>Street Fighter III Series</p>
<ul>
<li>Defensive Parry System</li>
<li>Forward Dash System</li>
<li>Tech Throw System</li>
<li>EX Special Move Properties</li>
</ul>
<p>Street Fighter IV Series</p>
<ul>
<li>Focus Attack (Huge difference though)</li>
</ul>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Combo System</span><br>
I’m thinking of using the Chain Combo system (Similar to Dial-a-Combo) rather than a hardcore Link System (Like SF4). The reason for this is because it’s harder to do Link Combos rather than Chain Combos when playing online, due to lag.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Graphics</span><br>
The Graphics would be a mixture of many games thorough the series.<br>
List:</p>
<ul>
<li>Street Fighter II Series (Certain Stages Only)</li>
</ul>
<p>Street Fighter Alpha Series (Stages/Characters)</p>
<ul>
<li>
<p>Street Fighter III Series (Certain Characters Only, with major resize to fit Alpha/CvS style characters size. Also taking out a few sprites in animations to make their movement feel more fluent when standing next to Alpha or CvS animated sprites.)</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Capcom vs SNK Series (Ryu, Ken, Akuma, Dan, Maki, and Eagle. The Shotos (Ryu, Ken, etc) were given new sprites and is far superior to their Alpha counter-parts. Maki and Eagle are new sprites as well.)</p>
</li>
</ul>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Extras</span><br>
Other Capcom characters may be present. Pretty much any Capcom styled fighter is fair game. This includes the Marvel characters, Darkstalkers characters, SNK characters, etc. I’m not limiting the roster to SF characters entirely.</p>
<p>Well nothing is set in stone, so this a scratch of what I’ve been planning. Hell I don’t even know what engine is going to be used. Since I’m learning programming, I thought I’d just create the engine, but everything is still up for grabs. Thought I’d post it up here and see what you guys think about it. I’ll be posting a few pictures and such to actually paint a picture.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/competitive-fighter-remix-sf/412483/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/competitive-fighter-remix-sf/412483/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 28 Aug 2011 19:06:13 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-412483-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/competitive-fighter-remix-sf/412483.rss">[Competitive Fighter] RemiX SF</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
