<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>You&#39;re Mopar T.O.S. is total bull shit</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/youre-mopar-t-o-s-is-total-bull-shit/333116</link>
    <description>A good friend of mine pointed this out for a laugh. You guys truly are total morons when it comes to that law aren&#39;t you? Because let me point out a few things to you people;

Here&#39;s your current T.O.S.:
[code]By clicking &#39;I Agree&#39; you agree to everything stated below:
1. You are not an employee of Jagex LTD, or runescape, and are not a family member or acquaintance of the aforementioned.
2. You are not an employee of any law firm contracted with Jagex LTD, and are not a family member or acquaintance of said firm.
3. You do not currently play runescape, or any other Jagex game, and are therefore not subject to their TOS or any other agreement with them.
4. All of the information on this site is solely for learning purposes, as the main purpose of this site is to instruct people in the art of programming. All programs provided for download from this site are entirely coded by the members of this community and are not the intellectual property of any business or organization.
Click &#39;I Agree&#39; if, and only if, you agree to ALL of the above terms.
You must have cookies enabled for this to work.[/code]

This entire thing is void, and here&#39;s why:

1. This term is void, because staff members of Jagex made the client and had a lot to do with the creation of their games created by JaGex games studio, obviously needless to say. So why shouldn&#39;t they be allowed to visit what is the property of JaGex? That is like me telling my mom that she is not allowed inside my house (which is hers.. durr). Please give me a damn break, for real.

2. JaGex reserves the right to permit any law office or firm they want when it comes to the fight against non-distributable property, by which is clearly the case here, since all of what this place consumes is stolen property.

3. Like I&#39;ve told my friend that pointed this ridiculous crap out to me, you putting this as your 3rd term is like me opening a burger business and stealing McDonald&#39;s Big Mac, same everything, just free from my burger joint, and that is like me putting a damn copyright on the box that says anyone who has bitten off of McDonald&#39;s big mac previously, is not allowed to take even a bite off of our Big Mac. Really childish ToS you should really just stop now while you&#39;re a head because with these Jagex is going to tear you a new ass hole.

4. This one really made me laugh. Because first of all if people really want to learn Java or whatever else goes down into being &quot;added&quot; onto JaGex&#39;s property, then they should go to college and get proper training, and not waste time working with such shitty servers and shitty code. 

Also with the 4th term, you claim that everything downloaded from this website is 100% created from its members. Well that&#39;s also total horse shit, because you people are all using Deob Clients that have been also again.. stolen, from JaGex LTD, and if it were not stolen then this place would never be here, because Jagex made RuneScape, you people are just these so called &#39;hackers&#39; that stole the property and used everything as a base and all of your shitty java programmers compiled their knowledge all into one of few decent communities and as a result, you get a decent non-legitimate private server industry, illegally.

That&#39;s all and I hope you all enjoy your time here.

(Rofl).

~Singod</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 17 Mar 2010 12:11:32 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/youre-mopar-t-o-s-is-total-bull-shit/333116.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>You&#39;re Mopar T.O.S. is total bull shit</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@chassy13 Chassy13]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/chassy13">@chassy13</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>And u’r an idiot because you don’t know how to use apostrophe’s.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/youre-mopar-t-o-s-is-total-bull-shit/333116/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/youre-mopar-t-o-s-is-total-bull-shit/333116/4</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 17 Mar 2010 12:11:32 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-333116-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/youre-mopar-t-o-s-is-total-bull-shit/333116.rss">You&#39;re Mopar T.O.S. is total bull shit</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>You&#39;re Mopar T.O.S. is total bull shit</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Singod09 Singod09]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/singod09">@Singod09</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Well none of it is personally yours because you’re a monkey.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/youre-mopar-t-o-s-is-total-bull-shit/333116/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/youre-mopar-t-o-s-is-total-bull-shit/333116/3</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 17 Mar 2010 03:08:10 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-333116-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/youre-mopar-t-o-s-is-total-bull-shit/333116.rss">You&#39;re Mopar T.O.S. is total bull shit</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>You&#39;re Mopar T.O.S. is total bull shit</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@John459 John459]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/john459">@John459</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>You are retarded. I know not ALL of it is ours, but if everything you say is true, this website would have been shutdown by now.</p>
<p>Read this - <a href="http://www.moparisthebest.com/lawstuff" rel="nofollow noopener">http://www.moparisthebest.com/lawstuff</a></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/youre-mopar-t-o-s-is-total-bull-shit/333116/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/youre-mopar-t-o-s-is-total-bull-shit/333116/2</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 17 Mar 2010 03:04:50 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-333116-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/youre-mopar-t-o-s-is-total-bull-shit/333116.rss">You&#39;re Mopar T.O.S. is total bull shit</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>You&#39;re Mopar T.O.S. is total bull shit</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Singod09 Singod09]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/singod09">@Singod09</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>A good friend of mine pointed this out for a laugh. You guys truly are total morons when it comes to that law aren’t you? Because let me point out a few things to you people;</p>
<p>Here’s your current T.O.S.:</p>
<p>[code]By clicking ‘I Agree’ you agree to everything stated below:</p>
<ol>
<li>You are not an employee of Jagex LTD, or runescape, and are not a family member or acquaintance of the aforementioned.</li>
<li>You are not an employee of any law firm contracted with Jagex LTD, and are not a family member or acquaintance of said firm.</li>
<li>You do not currently play runescape, or any other Jagex game, and are therefore not subject to their TOS or any other agreement with them.</li>
<li>All of the information on this site is solely for learning purposes, as the main purpose of this site is to instruct people in the art of programming. All programs provided for download from this site are entirely coded by the members of this community and are not the intellectual property of any business or organization.<br>
Click ‘I Agree’ if, and only if, you agree to ALL of the above terms.<br>
You must have cookies enabled for this to work.[/code]</li>
</ol>
<p>This entire thing is void, and here’s why:</p>
<ol>
<li>
<p>This term is void, because staff members of Jagex made the client and had a lot to do with the creation of their games created by JaGex games studio, obviously needless to say. So why shouldn’t they be allowed to visit what is the property of JaGex? That is like me telling my mom that she is not allowed inside my house (which is hers… durr). Please give me a damn break, for real.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>JaGex reserves the right to permit any law office or firm they want when it comes to the fight against non-distributable property, by which is clearly the case here, since all of what this place consumes is stolen property.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Like I’ve told my friend that pointed this ridiculous crap out to me, you putting this as your 3rd term is like me opening a burger business and stealing McDonald’s Big Mac, same everything, just free from my burger joint, and that is like me putting a damn copyright on the box that says anyone who has bitten off of McDonald’s big mac previously, is not allowed to take even a bite off of our Big Mac. Really childish ToS you should really just stop now while you’re a head because with these Jagex is going to tear you a new ass hole.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>This one really made me laugh. Because first of all if people really want to learn Java or whatever else goes down into being “added” onto JaGex’s property, then they should go to college and get proper training, and not waste time working with such shitty servers and shitty code.</p>
</li>
</ol>
<p>Also with the 4th term, you claim that everything downloaded from this website is 100% created from its members. Well that’s also total horse shit, because you people are all using Deob Clients that have been also again… stolen, from JaGex LTD, and if it were not stolen then this place would never be here, because Jagex made RuneScape, you people are just these so called ‘hackers’ that stole the property and used everything as a base and all of your shitty java programmers compiled their knowledge all into one of few decent communities and as a result, you get a decent non-legitimate private server industry, illegally.</p>
<p>That’s all and I hope you all enjoy your time here.</p>
<p>(Rofl).</p>
<p>~Singod</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/youre-mopar-t-o-s-is-total-bull-shit/333116/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/youre-mopar-t-o-s-is-total-bull-shit/333116/1</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 17 Mar 2010 02:56:09 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-333116-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/youre-mopar-t-o-s-is-total-bull-shit/333116.rss">You&#39;re Mopar T.O.S. is total bull shit</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
