<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>NPC and monster help</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/npc-and-monster-help/202377</link>
    <description>I just got the MoparScape client running and walked around noticed that there weren&#39;t really any enemies around. In Varrock all I saw were a few Guards and some rats but that was all. I went to the Wilderness and saw no monsters there. And around towns there we&#39;re no NPC&#39;s selling items. Is there something I have to download or something I have to run to see/put/add them in?</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2009 18:27:56 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/npc-and-monster-help/202377.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>NPC and monster help</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@sneakyscape sneakyscape]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/sneakyscape">@sneakyscape</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>hey  <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=6" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"><br>
im a pretty new moparscape user and need alot of help myself, but i know about this so i thought id help out.</p>
<p>to get monster where you want, you can stand where you want the monster to be and use the command</p>
<p>::npc “monster id”          this is a cool command, but the monster you spawn will have 0 hp and wont stay there forever.   if your wanting monsters to spawn perminantly, go to the hybridscape folder, open “autospawn”  (it will have a funny symbol) with notepad, and do the following.</p>
<p>heres the code you will paste in there to make a monster autospawn where you want (i dont know the code on here to put the text in a code box, so if anyone could tell me it would be appriciated.)</p>
<p>anyways, say you want a chaos dwarf in varrock, so youll put this in the “autospawn” file.</p>
<pre><code>         (npcid      coordx    coordy   walkpatrn -- leave the rest of it how it is.                  description)
</code></pre>
<p>spawn = 0000	xxxx	xxxx	0	3347	3396	3243	3393	1	Chaos Dwarf</p>
<p>(note, all the stuff in parenthises is written by me just to tell you what the numbers are, its NOT in the autospawn file, in this form at least.)</p>
<p>this will make a chaos dwarf automatically spawn right outside the varrock shop.<br>
to figure out coordinates, type ::coordson   and just walk around. as you walk the coordinates of where you are will change.</p>
<p>walk pattern = will the monster walk around or not.    if you leave it at 0, the monster will stand still. i reccomend 1 or 0.  1 will make it just walk around a lil bit  <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/wink.png?v=6" title=":wink:" class="emoji" alt=":wink:"></p>
<p>now,   part 2 of this.<br>
only simple monsters like cows and men come with hitpoints, so if you want to have a KBD, then you must open the file called “npc” in the hybirdscape folder (open it with notepad).<br>
now.   you find the monster that you put in autospawn, so in our case, we did chaos dwarf so well look for the monster id “119” in the npc file.</p>
<p>this is what it will look like un-edited.</p>
<p>(monster id               name                                      CBlevel       hp)</p>
<p>npc = 119	Chaos_dwarf			48	0</p>
<p>ok so it has 0 hp.  you must change the 0 to how much hitpoints you want the monster to have.<br>
ive learned that the higher the monsters hp is, the higher it can hit.    you can change the combat level in the “npc” file, but it wont change in game, so i recomend just not touching it.</p>
<p>i hope this really helped you  <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/smiley.png?v=6" title=":smiley:" class="emoji" alt=":smiley:"><br>
anyway, good luck <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/smiley.png?v=6" title=":smiley:" class="emoji" alt=":smiley:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/npc-and-monster-help/202377/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/npc-and-monster-help/202377/2</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2009 18:27:56 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-202377-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/npc-and-monster-help/202377.rss">NPC and monster help</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>NPC and monster help</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@firefoxyoshi firefoxyoshi]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/firefoxyoshi">@firefoxyoshi</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I just got the MoparScape client running and walked around noticed that there weren’t really any enemies around. In Varrock all I saw were a few Guards and some rats but that was all. I went to the Wilderness and saw no monsters there. And around towns there we’re no NPC’s selling items. Is there something I have to download or something I have to run to see/put/add them in?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/npc-and-monster-help/202377/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/npc-and-monster-help/202377/1</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 28 Apr 2008 04:48:35 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-202377-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/npc-and-monster-help/202377.rss">NPC and monster help</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
