<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Hydrascape is not welcome here</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/hydrascape-is-not-welcome-here/231379</link>
    <description>Quick warning about &quot;Hydrascape&quot; - [b]it is being run by known scammers[/b], probably with the intention of stealing any passwords they can get from you after they&#39;ve whored everyone for their money through donations and adverts.

Talking about Hydrascape anywhere outside questions in this thread = ban.
Advertising Hydrascape = ban.

[b]If you have run anything from them already, I strongly suggest taking measures to get rid of the ddosers/password stealers that are probably running on your pc.[/b]

Thanks and good day :)[br][br][size=1]Posted on: September 18, 2008, 12:07:04 am[/size][hr]An amendment to the original post:

I have spoken with the owner of Hydrascape, and he is understandably pretty pissed that we&#39;ve felt the need to do this. I realise that in my original post I was pretty aggresive, so I should probably point out that I have no proof that there is anything going on at Hydrascape other than a group of people trying to make a successful server, and it is possible that they are 100% legit. However, given the reputation of the staff, it&#39;s equally possible that its not.

So for now I&#39;m going to say that the above post still applies, but if it is shown that I am wrong and the Hydrascape crew really have given up all the shit, then of course it will be lifted. I never said it was permanent.[br][br][size=1]Posted on: September 18, 2008, 12:48:41 am[/size][hr]Another amendment, wow I&#39;m on a roll.

Please read http://moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php/topic,305182.0.html</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2008 23:54:05 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Community Suggestions</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/hydrascape-is-not-welcome-here/231379.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Hydrascape is not welcome here</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Mopman Mopman]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/mopman">@Mopman</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Quick warning about “Hydrascape” - <span class="bbcode-b">it is being run by known scammers</span>, probably with the intention of stealing any passwords they can get from you after they’ve whored everyone for their money through donations and adverts.</p>
<p>Talking about Hydrascape anywhere outside questions in this thread = ban.<br>
Advertising Hydrascape = ban.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">If you have run anything from them already, I strongly suggest taking measures to get rid of the ddosers/password stealers that are probably running on your pc.</span></p>
<p>Thanks and good day :)[br][br][size=1]Posted on: September 18, 2008, 12:07:04 am[/size][hr]An amendment to the original post:</p>
<p>I have spoken with the owner of Hydrascape, and he is understandably pretty pissed that we’ve felt the need to do this. I realise that in my original post I was pretty aggresive, so I should probably point out that I have no proof that there is anything going on at Hydrascape other than a group of people trying to make a successful server, and it is possible that they are 100% legit. However, given the reputation of the staff, it’s equally possible that its not.</p>
<p>So for now I’m going to say that the above post still applies, but if it is shown that I am wrong and the Hydrascape crew really have given up all the shit, then of course it will be lifted. I never said it was permanent.[br][br][size=1]Posted on: September 18, 2008, 12:48:41 am[/size][hr]Another amendment, wow I’m on a roll.</p>
<p>Please read <a href="http://moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php/topic,305182.0.html" rel="nofollow noopener">http://moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php/topic,305182.0.html</a></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/hydrascape-is-not-welcome-here/231379/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/hydrascape-is-not-welcome-here/231379/1</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2008 23:54:05 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-231379-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/hydrascape-is-not-welcome-here/231379.rss">Hydrascape is not welcome here</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
