<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Web Advertising; Pros &amp; Cons?</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/web-advertising-pros-cons/169621</link>
    <description>[center][img]http://i17.tinypic.com/8e0t8i8.png[/img]
[/center]

[center][b]Introduction;[/b][/center]
Well, just about everybody knows that in just about any business, if you want to make money, you&#39;re either going to have to provide a service, or advertise. The easier by far, being the latter. 

[center][b]Explaination;[/b][/center]
Web advertising (PPC in particular) is very popular amonsgt almost every site nowadays, mainly because it&#39;s a free, easy way, of making money. The way PPC works [i](very basically)[/i] is;

[size=8pt]       You put an advertiser&#39;s advert on your site.
       People click on the advert.
       You get money. Usually around 10c[i](USD)[/i] or 5p[i](GBP)[/i] per click.[/size]

[center][b]Providers;[/b][/center]
Almost every major Search Engine provides a PPC service, the most popular being [url=http://adsense.google.com][b]Google Adwords[/b][/url].

[center][b]Setting them up;[/b][/center]
Setting up PPC adverts on your website couldn&#39;t be easier. Just fill in your details, set up an ad, and implement the the code into your page. You&#39;re probably thinking that this system is quite vunerable. Many people try and cheat the system. Asking people to click ads etc. Your provider will more often than not find this out, and cancel your account. It&#39;s not worth trying. 

Another problem with PPC is the amount. There isn&#39;t really a limit to how many ad&#39;s you can implement on a single page. But if you&#39;re not plannin on ruining the aesthetics or the traffic of your site, I wouldn&#39;t put too many in. Pages that are crowded with adverts don&#39;t usually get as many visitors, simply because people can&#39;t be bothered scrolling through adverts. My website [b]www.lolism.org[/b] is probably a prime example of PPC crowding, but tbh, I need the money! :)

[center][b][size=11pt]to be continued..[/size][/b][/center]</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 01 Jan 2008 02:11:26 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>General Programming</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/web-advertising-pros-cons/169621.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Web Advertising; Pros &amp; Cons?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@JV1 JV]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/jv1">@JV1</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[center]<img src="http://i17.tinypic.com/8e0t8i8.png" alt width="140" height="120"><br>
[/center]</p>
<p>[center]<span class="bbcode-b">Introduction;</span>[/center]<br>
Well, just about everybody knows that in just about any business, if you want to make money, you’re either going to have to provide a service, or advertise. The easier by far, being the latter.</p>
<p>[center]<span class="bbcode-b">Explaination;</span>[/center]<br>
Web advertising (PPC in particular) is very popular amonsgt almost every site nowadays, mainly because it’s a free, easy way, of making money. The way PPC works <span class="bbcode-i">(very basically)</span> is;</p>
<p>[size=8pt]       You put an advertiser’s advert on your site.<br>
People click on the advert.<br>
You get money. Usually around 10c<a>i</a>[/i] or 5p<a>i</a>[/i] per click.[/size]</p>
<p>[center]<span class="bbcode-b">Providers;</span>[/center]<br>
Almost every major Search Engine provides a PPC service, the most popular being <a href="http://adsense.google.com" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener"><span class="bbcode-b">Google Adwords</span></a>.</p>
<p>[center]<span class="bbcode-b">Setting them up;</span>[/center]<br>
Setting up PPC adverts on your website couldn’t be easier. Just fill in your details, set up an ad, and implement the the code into your page. You’re probably thinking that this system is quite vunerable. Many people try and cheat the system. Asking people to click ads etc. Your provider will more often than not find this out, and cancel your account. It’s not worth trying.</p>
<p>Another problem with PPC is the amount. There isn’t really a limit to how many ad’s you can implement on a single page. But if you’re not plannin on ruining the aesthetics or the traffic of your site, I wouldn’t put too many in. Pages that are crowded with adverts don’t usually get as many visitors, simply because people can’t be bothered scrolling through adverts. My website <span class="bbcode-b"><a href="http://www.lolism.org" rel="nofollow noopener">www.lolism.org</a></span> is probably a prime example of PPC crowding, but tbh, I need the money! <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=6" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
<p>[center]<span class="bbcode-b">[size=11pt]to be continued…[/size]</span>[/center]</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/web-advertising-pros-cons/169621/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/web-advertising-pros-cons/169621/1</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jan 2008 02:11:26 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-169621-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/web-advertising-pros-cons/169621.rss">Web Advertising; Pros &amp; Cons?</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
