<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>C# Questions(2)</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/c-questions-2/397008</link>
    <description>Hello all,

I am starting a project in C# and I&#39;m brainstorming ideas and things that I can include in the game, and I&#39;m stuck on a few things. It&#39;s going to be a console application that has arrow key controls, text based commands, and reflex commands. And my questions are:

How do I create and get/give information to a database?
I want to create a large database filled with text commands and such(Commands, items, locations, etc...). How would I create a database to access these files and be able to change properties and such within the database?
[code]
Location   HasBeenTo
Room5      true[/code]
Kind of like that. Get variables for a room, like if you have been there. If there are items there, and so on.
I was thinking that it would be best for me to learn XML for that? But I&#39;m not totally sure if XML can do what I want. Such as change and write to the XML file. Can that be done?

And my second question is this:

What is the default value for Char?
For my reflex controls I&#39;m going to be running multiple threads at a time. So I want to declare a character variable and then have the user press any key before a timer of say 1 second runs out. And I wanted to have the checking system as easy as
[code]if (charval != null)
break;[/code].
Is there any way to check for a default character value like this?

All help is appreciated.
(And links for any tutorials)</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 29 May 2011 23:56:57 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>General Programming</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/c-questions-2/397008.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>C# Questions(2)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Kirai Kirai]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/kirai">@Kirai</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Hello all,</p>
<p>I am starting a project in C# and I’m brainstorming ideas and things that I can include in the game, and I’m stuck on a few things. It’s going to be a console application that has arrow key controls, text based commands, and reflex commands. And my questions are:</p>
<p>How do I create and get/give information to a database?<br>
I want to create a large database filled with text commands and such(Commands, items, locations, etc…). How would I create a database to access these files and be able to change properties and such within the database?</p>
<p><code>
Location   HasBeenTo
Room5      true</code><br>
Kind of like that. Get variables for a room, like if you have been there. If there are items there, and so on.<br>
I was thinking that it would be best for me to learn XML for that? But I’m not totally sure if XML can do what I want. Such as change and write to the XML file. Can that be done?</p>
<p>And my second question is this:</p>
<p>What is the default value for Char?<br>
For my reflex controls I’m going to be running multiple threads at a time. So I want to declare a character variable and then have the user press any key before a timer of say 1 second runs out. And I wanted to have the checking system as easy as</p>
<p><code>if (charval != null)
break;</code>.<br>
Is there any way to check for a default character value like this?</p>
<p>All help is appreciated.<br>
(And links for any tutorials)</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/c-questions-2/397008/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/c-questions-2/397008/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 29 May 2011 23:56:57 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-397008-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/c-questions-2/397008.rss">C# Questions(2)</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
