<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Just some more News</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/just-some-more-news/18745</link>
    <description>[center]Just some more News.[/center]

[url=http://www.canada.com/topics/news/world/story.html?id=c06e5fae-8ae5-4c09-b9d5-49a9a0b11685&amp;k=56264]Bush signs bill to interrogate and prosecute suspected terrorists[/url] - The CIA was interrogating suspected terrorists overseas and Bush just realized, and decided to sign a bill so those people will be arrested. Sounds like a good thing he did. 

[url=http://news.yahoo.com/s/ap/20061017/ap_en_mo/wesley_snipes_indicted]Actor Wesley Snipes accused of tax fraud[/url] - Wesley Snipes has been indicted on Tax Fraud! [i]&quot;..Snipes, who had a home in Windermere, Fla., has not been arrested because authorities don&#39;t know where he is, the IRS said...&quot;[/i] Wow he is a very good actor, I wonder why he would do this? I hope it&#39;s not like the Redd Foxx case in 1989 where the IRS litterally hounded the actor and falsified evidence.

[url=http://news.yahoo.com/s/ap/20061017/ap_on_he_me/diabetes_drug]Merck diabetes drug wins federal OK[/url] - [i]&quot;Diabetics gained a new way of controlling their blood sugar levels Tuesday with federal approval of a novel pill for Type 2 diabetes, which affects about 20 million Americans.&quot;[/i] Yay! I know a ton of diabetic people and this will definitely help them. This new way of getting the blood sugar levels has fewer side effects and with NO weight gain! Woo! Less fat people. [i]&quot;...Merck is expected to charge $4.86 for the once-daily tablet, a price tag that may limit its use. Older diabetes drugs can cost 50 cents a day...More than 230 million people worldwide have diabetes, up from just 30 million in 1985, according to the International Diabetes Federation. Diabetes is expected to affect 350 million people by 2025.&quot;[/i]

[url=http://news.yahoo.com/s/ap/20061017/ap_on_fe_st/pet_fire]Dog saves owner, dies trying to save cat[/url] - [i]&quot;After a disabled woman&#39;s cat started a house fire, her specially trained dog came to the rescue, then died trying to help the cat still in the house. Jamie Hanson said the 13-year-old dog named Jesse brought the phone so she could call 911 and also brought her artificial leg.&quot;[/i]

[url=http://news.yahoo.com/s/ap/20061012/ap_on_he_me/fitness_creative_gyms]Gyms push the creative envelope[/url] - [i]&quot;Get off that boring old treadmill and belt out a cheesy Elvis song on the exercise bike, instead. Strut around in 3-inch heels or work up a sweat on the pogo stick. As gyms compete with dance studios and adult sports leagues to hold on to members with ever-shorter attention spans, run-of-the-mill aerobics and other classes are getting an injection of creativity.&quot;[/i]

[url=http://news.yahoo.com/s/ap/20061017/ap_on_sp_bo_ne/box_tyson_tour]Mike Tyson says he may fight against woman[/url] - [i]&quot;STRONGSVILLE, Ohio - Mike Tyson says he may include bouts with women on his next tour, and mentioned professional boxer Ann Wolfe, who is 21-1 with 15 knockouts. &#39;She&#39;s such a prominent, dominant woman in the boxing field,&#39; Tyson said. When asked if he was joking about fighting women, Tyson said, &#39;I&#39;m very serious.&#39;&quot;[/i]

[url=http://news.yahoo.com/s/ap/20061017/ap_on_re_as/koreas_nuclear]N. Korea: Sanctions are war declaration[/url] - [i]&quot;SEOUL, South Korea - North Korea said Tuesday it considered U.N. sanctions aimed at punishing the country for its nuclear test &quot;a declaration of war,&quot; as Japan and South Korea reported the communist nation might be preparing a second explosion. The North broke two days of silence about the U.N. resolution adopted after its Oct. 9 nuclear test with a statement on the official state news agency, as China warned Pyongyang against stoking tensions.&quot;[/i]

[url=http://news.yahoo.com/s/ap/google_solar]Google to convert HQ to solar power[/url] - [i]&quot;SAN FRANCISCO - Google Inc. is converting its renowned headquarters to run partly on solar power, hoping to set an example for corporate America. The Internet search leader announced what is believed to be the largest solar project undertaken by a U.S. company during a solar energy conference in Silicon Valley on Monday. Google believes the sun eventually can deliver as much as 30 percent of the power at its 1-million-square-foot campus in Mountain View — a suburb about 35 miles south of San Francisco.&quot;[/i]

[url=http://www.chron.com/disp/story.mpl/ap/health/4263881.html]Study links hair to eating disorders[/url] - [i]&quot; SALT LAKE CITY — Hair strands reveal evidence of a person&#39;s diet and can help doctors diagnose eating disorders, researchers at Brigham Young University reported. Researchers found differences in nitrogen and carbon when samples from females at an eating-disorder clinic were compared with hair from females who didn&#39;t have a problem. They said they were able to accurately determine the source 80 percent of the time.&quot;[/i]

[url=http://abcnews.go.com/International/story?id=2576474&amp;page=1]Deadly Subway Crash in Rome[/url] - [i]&quot;ROME, Oct. 17, 2006 — A subway crash in the heart of Rome&#39;s underground has left at least one person dead and has injured about 60 people, five seriously. Authorities say two subway trains crashed Tuesday, just as the peak rush hour was ending. The crash took place at the Piazza Vittorio underground, not far from the city&#39;s main train station.&quot;[/i]

[url=http://www.tvguide.com/News-Views/Interviews-Features/Article/default.aspx?posting=%7B2FC4FFA6-E813-483A-BC00-89250281FB73%7D]Inside Scoop: The Stars Come Out for Bruce Willis![/url] - Burce Willis got his own STAR on the Hollywood Walk of Fame! Bruce Willis is awesome. The guy in Die Hard! So awesome!</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 18 Oct 2006 02:56:16 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>General Discussion</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/just-some-more-news/18745.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Just some more News</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Itachi_Uchiha Itachi Uchiha]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/itachi_uchiha">@Itachi_Uchiha</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>yay first post <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=9" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"><br>
<img src="http://img124.imageshack.us/img124/3531/omgbush1vy3.jpg" alt width="" height=""></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/just-some-more-news/18745/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/just-some-more-news/18745/2</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 18 Oct 2006 02:56:16 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-18745-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/just-some-more-news/18745.rss">Just some more News</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Just some more News</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Ron Ron]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/ron">@Ron</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[center]Just some more News.[/center]</p>
<p><a href="http://www.canada.com/topics/news/world/story.html?id=c06e5fae-8ae5-4c09-b9d5-49a9a0b11685&amp;k=56264" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">Bush signs bill to interrogate and prosecute suspected terrorists</a> - The CIA was interrogating suspected terrorists overseas and Bush just realized, and decided to sign a bill so those people will be arrested. Sounds like a good thing he did.</p>
<p><a href="http://news.yahoo.com/s/ap/20061017/ap_en_mo/wesley_snipes_indicted" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">Actor Wesley Snipes accused of tax fraud</a> - Wesley Snipes has been indicted on Tax Fraud! <span class="bbcode-i">“…Snipes, who had a home in Windermere, Fla., has not been arrested because authorities don’t know where he is, the IRS said…”</span> Wow he is a very good actor, I wonder why he would do this? I hope it’s not like the Redd Foxx case in 1989 where the IRS litterally hounded the actor and falsified evidence.</p>
<p><a href="http://news.yahoo.com/s/ap/20061017/ap_on_he_me/diabetes_drug" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">Merck diabetes drug wins federal OK</a> - <span class="bbcode-i">“Diabetics gained a new way of controlling their blood sugar levels Tuesday with federal approval of a novel pill for Type 2 diabetes, which affects about 20 million Americans.”</span> Yay! I know a ton of diabetic people and this will definitely help them. This new way of getting the blood sugar levels has fewer side effects and with NO weight gain! Woo! Less fat people. <span class="bbcode-i">“…Merck is expected to charge $4.86 for the once-daily tablet, a price tag that may limit its use. Older diabetes drugs can cost 50 cents a day…More than 230 million people worldwide have diabetes, up from just 30 million in 1985, according to the International Diabetes Federation. Diabetes is expected to affect 350 million people by 2025.”</span></p>
<p><a href="http://news.yahoo.com/s/ap/20061017/ap_on_fe_st/pet_fire" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">Dog saves owner, dies trying to save cat</a> - <span class="bbcode-i">“After a disabled woman’s cat started a house fire, her specially trained dog came to the rescue, then died trying to help the cat still in the house. Jamie Hanson said the 13-year-old dog named Jesse brought the phone so she could call 911 and also brought her artificial leg.”</span></p>
<p><a href="http://news.yahoo.com/s/ap/20061012/ap_on_he_me/fitness_creative_gyms" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">Gyms push the creative envelope</a> - <span class="bbcode-i">“Get off that boring old treadmill and belt out a cheesy Elvis song on the exercise bike, instead. Strut around in 3-inch heels or work up a sweat on the pogo stick. As gyms compete with dance studios and adult sports leagues to hold on to members with ever-shorter attention spans, run-of-the-mill aerobics and other classes are getting an injection of creativity.”</span></p>
<p><a href="http://news.yahoo.com/s/ap/20061017/ap_on_sp_bo_ne/box_tyson_tour" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">Mike Tyson says he may fight against woman</a> - <span class="bbcode-i">“STRONGSVILLE, Ohio - Mike Tyson says he may include bouts with women on his next tour, and mentioned professional boxer Ann Wolfe, who is 21-1 with 15 knockouts. ‘She’s such a prominent, dominant woman in the boxing field,’ Tyson said. When asked if he was joking about fighting women, Tyson said, ‘I’m very serious.’”</span></p>
<p><a href="http://news.yahoo.com/s/ap/20061017/ap_on_re_as/koreas_nuclear" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">N. Korea: Sanctions are war declaration</a> - <span class="bbcode-i">“SEOUL, South Korea - North Korea said Tuesday it considered U.N. sanctions aimed at punishing the country for its nuclear test “a declaration of war,” as Japan and South Korea reported the communist nation might be preparing a second explosion. The North broke two days of silence about the U.N. resolution adopted after its Oct. 9 nuclear test with a statement on the official state news agency, as China warned Pyongyang against stoking tensions.”</span></p>
<p><a href="http://news.yahoo.com/s/ap/google_solar" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">Google to convert HQ to solar power</a> - <span class="bbcode-i">“SAN FRANCISCO - Google Inc. is converting its renowned headquarters to run partly on solar power, hoping to set an example for corporate America. The Internet search leader announced what is believed to be the largest solar project undertaken by a U.S. company during a solar energy conference in Silicon Valley on Monday. Google believes the sun eventually can deliver as much as 30 percent of the power at its 1-million-square-foot campus in Mountain View — a suburb about 35 miles south of San Francisco.”</span></p>
<p><a href="http://www.chron.com/disp/story.mpl/ap/health/4263881.html" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">Study links hair to eating disorders</a> - <span class="bbcode-i">" SALT LAKE CITY — Hair strands reveal evidence of a person’s diet and can help doctors diagnose eating disorders, researchers at Brigham Young University reported. Researchers found differences in nitrogen and carbon when samples from females at an eating-disorder clinic were compared with hair from females who didn’t have a problem. They said they were able to accurately determine the source 80 percent of the time."</span></p>
<p><a href="http://abcnews.go.com/International/story?id=2576474&amp;page=1" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">Deadly Subway Crash in Rome</a> - <span class="bbcode-i">“ROME, Oct. 17, 2006 — A subway crash in the heart of Rome’s underground has left at least one person dead and has injured about 60 people, five seriously. Authorities say two subway trains crashed Tuesday, just as the peak rush hour was ending. The crash took place at the Piazza Vittorio underground, not far from the city’s main train station.”</span></p>
<p><a href="http://www.tvguide.com/News-Views/Interviews-Features/Article/default.aspx?posting=%7B2FC4FFA6-E813-483A-BC00-89250281FB73%7D" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">Inside Scoop: The Stars Come Out for Bruce Willis!</a> - Burce Willis got his own STAR on the Hollywood Walk of Fame! Bruce Willis is awesome. The guy in Die Hard! So awesome!</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/just-some-more-news/18745/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/just-some-more-news/18745/1</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 18 Oct 2006 02:45:33 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-18745-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/just-some-more-news/18745.rss">Just some more News</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
