<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>[422]How Strings Work</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/422-how-strings-work/9008</link>
    <description>I guess this could of been posted in NOURLOL&#39;s post but I am using the deob to explain how they work so I didn&#39;t think it would be fitting.

I also do know that there is no foreseen future in deob bots but this just explains the concept and could be applied to any method of botmaking.

Read the recap first and if you understand it don&#39;t bother reading the rest.

You can look in just about any class in Deob 422 and notice that strings are being stored in a class40 object. 
class48.method500 would seem to convert the string into a byte array then assigned to the class40&#39;s aByteArray1568.

If the string is in English then right after it is assigned to the first class40 you&#39;ll see it be reassigned to another class40.
I&#39;ll refer to this as the universal class40.

So open up class52 and I&#39;ll give you an example of how this works.
The class40 is already declared at the beginning of the class.

So at the bottom of the class you&#39;ll see this along with some other German strings.
[code]	aClass40_1217 = Class48.method500(-5, &quot;Take&quot;);
	aBoolean1214 = false;
	anInt1218 = 0;
	aClass40_1210 = aClass40_1217;[/code]
See that aclass40_1217 now stores the string &quot;Take&quot;.
But if you try to find usages of aClass40_1217 in the rest of the client you will only find it once. 
Right below it is the only use in the client at all.

This is because right after it is assigned the string &quot;Take&quot;, aClass40_1210 is assigned a reference to it.
Look in class15 and you&#39;ll find method192 that when called will take aClass40_1210 and other references to strings and reassign them to all new German translated strings.

[b]Recap[/b]:
All strings are stored in a String Wrapper which in deob422 is class40.
Each English class40 has a universal counterpart which is defaultly referenced to the English class40.
If method192 is called then the universal class40s are rereferenced to thier German counterparts.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2006 01:15:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/422-how-strings-work/9008.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>[422]How Strings Work</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Pwnd Pwnd]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/pwnd">@Pwnd</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Thank you.  ‘Props’ to you.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/422-how-strings-work/9008/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/422-how-strings-work/9008/2</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2006 01:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-9008-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/422-how-strings-work/9008.rss">[422]How Strings Work</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[422]How Strings Work</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Fishygame Fishygame]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/fishygame">@Fishygame</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I guess this could of been posted in NOURLOL’s post but I am using the deob to explain how they work so I didn’t think it would be fitting.</p>
<p>I also do know that there is no foreseen future in deob bots but this just explains the concept and could be applied to any method of botmaking.</p>
<p>Read the recap first and if you understand it don’t bother reading the rest.</p>
<p>You can look in just about any class in Deob 422 and notice that strings are being stored in a class40 object.<br>
class48.method500 would seem to convert the string into a byte array then assigned to the class40’s aByteArray1568.</p>
<p>If the string is in English then right after it is assigned to the first class40 you’ll see it be reassigned to another class40.<br>
I’ll refer to this as the universal class40.</p>
<p>So open up class52 and I’ll give you an example of how this works.<br>
The class40 is already declared at the beginning of the class.</p>
<p>So at the bottom of the class you’ll see this along with some other German strings.</p>
<p><code>	aClass40_1217 = Class48.method500(-5, "Take");
	aBoolean1214 = false;
	anInt1218 = 0;
	aClass40_1210 = aClass40_1217;</code><br>
See that aclass40_1217 now stores the string “Take”.<br>
But if you try to find usages of aClass40_1217 in the rest of the client you will only find it once.<br>
Right below it is the only use in the client at all.</p>
<p>This is because right after it is assigned the string “Take”, aClass40_1210 is assigned a reference to it.<br>
Look in class15 and you’ll find method192 that when called will take aClass40_1210 and other references to strings and reassign them to all new German translated strings.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Recap</span>:<br>
All strings are stored in a String Wrapper which in deob422 is class40.<br>
Each English class40 has a universal counterpart which is defaultly referenced to the English class40.<br>
If method192 is called then the universal class40s are rereferenced to thier German counterparts.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/422-how-strings-work/9008/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/422-how-strings-work/9008/1</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 11 Aug 2006 17:29:24 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-9008-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/422-how-strings-work/9008.rss">[422]How Strings Work</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
