<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Question</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/question/360980</link>
    <description>Does anyone have any srcs that having working doorframes, (gamewallobjects), not trees ect. doorframes.

The only one i&#39;ve seen is Geminus,
And im guessing rscd and easyrsc&#39;s work aswell,
but there all xml based, which isn&#39;t really a problem, but it&#39;s far too much to rip out, you end up taking 3/4 of the server and it&#39;s coded completely different.

I understand theres an older rscd, one that doesn&#39;t use the .rscd extention, was there a server for this?

Im looking for anything that has working doorframes, xml, prefrably .cfg type. but yeah, it&#39;s fucking me off it&#39;s the only thing holding me back on my development and im not going to continue till i resolve this.

thanks</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 19 Sep 2010 09:34:34 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/question/360980.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Question</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@dimebagx dimebagx]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/dimebagx">@dimebagx</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Does anyone have any srcs that having working doorframes, (gamewallobjects), not trees ect. doorframes.</p>
<p>The only one i’ve seen is Geminus,<br>
And im guessing rscd and easyrsc’s work aswell,<br>
but there all xml based, which isn’t really a problem, but it’s far too much to rip out, you end up taking 3/4 of the server and it’s coded completely different.</p>
<p>I understand theres an older rscd, one that doesn’t use the .rscd extention, was there a server for this?</p>
<p>Im looking for anything that has working doorframes, xml, prefrably .cfg type. but yeah, it’s fucking me off it’s the only thing holding me back on my development and im not going to continue till i resolve this.</p>
<p>thanks</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/question/360980/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/question/360980/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 19 Sep 2010 09:34:34 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-360980-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/question/360980.rss">Question</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
