<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Redstone competition</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/redstone-competition/454029</link>
    <description>Well, in order to get the ball rolling once again and hand out the redstone award, I want to organize a redstone competition. All members will be eligible to compete in this competition (staff members too, although if you compete you&#39;ll be discluded from the judging panel!) but there must be certain criteria for this. For starters, Tom and I were just discussing this on the IRC and we came to this conclusion so far:


[ul][li]Entries must be moparcraft-specific[/li][li]All competitors must post a text-description or a video tutorial of how they designed their contraption.[/li][/ul]

These tie in with the current criteria required for the redstone award. First of all though, we need to discuss what contraptions the members will be designing. I&#39;d like to mention that this competition will be occurring after the 1.3 update comes out due to the usual increase of activity on the server and server updates.

So, what do you guys think the redstone contraption should be? Also we need to discuss how long they will have to build this contraption, and whether we should cap the amount of redstone used (for more of a challenge and hopefulyl increased efficiency).</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 13 Aug 2012 00:39:31 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Games</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/redstone-competition/454029.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Redstone competition</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@si_force Si Force]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/si_force">@si_force</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Well, in order to get the ball rolling once again and hand out the redstone award, I want to organize a redstone competition. All members will be eligible to compete in this competition (staff members too, although if you compete you’ll be discluded from the judging panel!) but there must be certain criteria for this. For starters, Tom and I were just discussing this on the IRC and we came to this conclusion so far:</p>
<p>[ul][li]Entries must be moparcraft-specific[/li][li]All competitors must post a text-description or a video tutorial of how they designed their contraption.[/li][/ul]</p>
<p>These tie in with the current criteria required for the redstone award. First of all though, we need to discuss what contraptions the members will be designing. I’d like to mention that this competition will be occurring after the 1.3 update comes out due to the usual increase of activity on the server and server updates.</p>
<p>So, what do you guys think the redstone contraption should be? Also we need to discuss how long they will have to build this contraption, and whether we should cap the amount of redstone used (for more of a challenge and hopefulyl increased efficiency).</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/redstone-competition/454029/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/redstone-competition/454029/1</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 13 Aug 2012 00:39:31 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-454029-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/redstone-competition/454029.rss">Redstone competition</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
