<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Offering Marketing Services - Get Lots Of Players On Your Server!</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/offering-marketing-services-get-lots-of-players-on-your-server/449514</link>
    <description>Hello, I&#39;m MrDuck. Let me start of by thanking you for clicking my topic!

[u][b]So, you have a server and/or are working on one? [/b][/u]
You put a development team together, worked on some good idea&#39;s, and you made an original, great server people are definitely going to enjoy playing. You put it online, buy hosting or host it yourself, register it on the regular websites, and wait for people to come. But, you only get 20 people online and it seems like all your work was for nothing.

This happends [u]alot[/u] to new private servers. Thats why I&#39;m here: I will [u]guarantee[/u] you alot of active players and a great community. 

[u][b]So, who am I?[/b][/u]
I&#39;m active in private servers for years now. I had a few myself, I was admin / mod on a couple, I made alot of website&#39;s and forums for them, I&#39;ve seen many come and go. 
I also just finished my Marketing study in Holland, I can do all your GFX needs, I can do some server-sided coding and I can manage your community. With all of those things, I have alot of experience. I have never, [u]ever[/u], failed making a server popular.

[u][b]Why am I doing this?[/b][/u]
Well, I have some spare time on my hands and had a good time working with private servers. So I thought I should open a topic, just give it a try. I hope you can use me in your team, I&#39;m looking for a serious team which is working on an original server. 

[u][b]How do you contact me?[/b][/u]
Its very easy; I&#39;ll check for replies daily, but you can also PM me. 

Do you have any questions? Feel free to ask them! 


Thank you for reading, have a great day!

Hope to hear from you!</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 13 Jul 2012 15:43:38 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/offering-marketing-services-get-lots-of-players-on-your-server/449514.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Offering Marketing Services - Get Lots Of Players On Your Server!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@mrduck mrduck]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/mrduck">@mrduck</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Hello, I’m MrDuck. Let me start of by thanking you for clicking my topic!</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-u"><span class="bbcode-b">So, you have a server and/or are working on one? </span></span><br>
You put a development team together, worked on some good idea’s, and you made an original, great server people are definitely going to enjoy playing. You put it online, buy hosting or host it yourself, register it on the regular websites, and wait for people to come. But, you only get 20 people online and it seems like all your work was for nothing.</p>
<p>This happends <span class="bbcode-u">alot</span> to new private servers. Thats why I’m here: I will <span class="bbcode-u">guarantee</span> you alot of active players and a great community.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-u"><span class="bbcode-b">So, who am I?</span></span><br>
I’m active in private servers for years now. I had a few myself, I was admin / mod on a couple, I made alot of website’s and forums for them, I’ve seen many come and go.<br>
I also just finished my Marketing study in Holland, I can do all your GFX needs, I can do some server-sided coding and I can manage your community. With all of those things, I have alot of experience. I have never, <span class="bbcode-u">ever</span>, failed making a server popular.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-u"><span class="bbcode-b">Why am I doing this?</span></span><br>
Well, I have some spare time on my hands and had a good time working with private servers. So I thought I should open a topic, just give it a try. I hope you can use me in your team, I’m looking for a serious team which is working on an original server.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-u"><span class="bbcode-b">How do you contact me?</span></span><br>
Its very easy; I’ll check for replies daily, but you can also PM me.</p>
<p>Do you have any questions? Feel free to ask them!</p>
<p>Thank you for reading, have a great day!</p>
<p>Hope to hear from you!</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/offering-marketing-services-get-lots-of-players-on-your-server/449514/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/offering-marketing-services-get-lots-of-players-on-your-server/449514/1</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 13 Jul 2012 15:43:38 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-449514-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/offering-marketing-services-get-lots-of-players-on-your-server/449514.rss">Offering Marketing Services - Get Lots Of Players On Your Server!</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
