<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Clicking on an NPC OR bringing up the &quot;option box&quot; thing or NPC tele you places</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/clicking-on-an-npc-or-bringing-up-the-option-box-thing-or-npc-tele-you-places/187862</link>
    <description>I&#39;m busy with like... 4 things right now lol and I can&#39;t get something to work, actually either two things

1.) You know when you click on a NPC and it brings up the option box replacing the chat box at the bottom of the screen, left of your inventory? [I&#39;d sound a lot more professional if  I knew what it was called lol, but it&#39;s basically what comes up if you click on a banker in RS2, except when you click the first option, it teles you somewhere instead of opening your bank.] Well, I can&#39;t get that to work... I tried a lot of things, and even tried [this was originally Dodian, but is NOTHING like it now] switching the thing Vannaka brings up when you talk to him to tele you to Mage Arena, and I switched the NPC ID, what he says and all that, but it still comes up on Vannaka even though when I changed what it says worked and where it teles you, just not the right NPC... So I need where to change the NPC or even a brand new code please  :D

either I need that... OR something easier for me and you...

2.) Just clicking on an NPC, the NPC says something, animation, then it teles you somewhere. Kinda like Aubury in RS2.

THANKS!</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 10 Mar 2008 01:52:39 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/clicking-on-an-npc-or-bringing-up-the-option-box-thing-or-npc-tele-you-places/187862.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Clicking on an NPC OR bringing up the &quot;option box&quot; thing or NPC tele you places</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Lucas_Shocked Lucas[Shocked]]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/lucas_shocked">@Lucas_Shocked</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I’m busy with like… 4 things right now lol and I can’t get something to work, actually either two things</p>
<p>1.) You know when you click on a NPC and it brings up the option box replacing the chat box at the bottom of the screen, left of your inventory? [I’d sound a lot more professional if  I knew what it was called lol, but it’s basically what comes up if you click on a banker in RS2, except when you click the first option, it teles you somewhere instead of opening your bank.] Well, I can’t get that to work… I tried a lot of things, and even tried [this was originally Dodian, but is NOTHING like it now] switching the thing Vannaka brings up when you talk to him to tele you to Mage Arena, and I switched the NPC ID, what he says and all that, but it still comes up on Vannaka even though when I changed what it says worked and where it teles you, just not the right NPC… So I need where to change the NPC or even a brand new code please  <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/smiley.png?v=6" title=":smiley:" class="emoji" alt=":smiley:"></p>
<p>either I need that… OR something easier for me and you…</p>
<p>2.) Just clicking on an NPC, the NPC says something, animation, then it teles you somewhere. Kinda like Aubury in RS2.</p>
<p>THANKS!</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/clicking-on-an-npc-or-bringing-up-the-option-box-thing-or-npc-tele-you-places/187862/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/clicking-on-an-npc-or-bringing-up-the-option-box-thing-or-npc-tele-you-places/187862/1</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 10 Mar 2008 01:52:39 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-187862-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/clicking-on-an-npc-or-bringing-up-the-option-box-thing-or-npc-tele-you-places/187862.rss">Clicking on an NPC OR bringing up the &quot;option box&quot; thing or NPC tele you places</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
