<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Loads of BCEL questions</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/loads-of-bcel-questions/145905</link>
    <description>Before I begin, I&#39;d like to say that it&#39;s not so much a matter of programming as it is knowing current logic for making Runescape BCEL bots. I just need some guidance as to what to do. My purpose in the beginning is to reinvent the wheel so that I can get up to date on the current world of Runescape Bot making. I really want to start from the ground up. Also, please realize that I can only work on projects like these in my spare time. If you&#39;re interested in creating 3D games, I would invite you to join project SkyCastle, located at skycastle.org. Skycastle is a project that utilizes jME (Java Monkey Engine) to develop a realistic 3D game in Java, the possibilities are endless :)

This is a living post meaning that it will be updated regularly as needed.

&lt;Current_Questions&gt;
Hmm, I&#39;m kind of fuzzy when it comes to creating an interface and then using bytecode instrumentation to make a class (inside runescape.jar) implement that interface to rename methods. [s]For instance, when Yakman&#39;s tutorial says anEntity.getCurrentHP(); how do I create/find an object of type Entity? In other words where does anEntity come from? Is it an object generated by runescape.jar at run-time?[/s] [Answered by Silver Lining - Post 2]  Also, how do current bytecode bots work? I&#39;m guessing that they modify the client at run-time to implement hooks (which are really just interfaces defining what methods a class must have in order to function), and when you need information about the surrounding area, such as if and where an NPC is standing you use the hooks that will in turn call methods in the runescape client itself. [s]Why do you need to use an interface, why can&#39;t you just modify the class to contain a method to return the data of an obfuscated field? Is that just good Object Oriented Programming style, or is there something that I&#39;m missing?[/s][Answered by Silver Lining - Post 2] What about when they come to a &quot;loading please wait&quot; does the bot have to retrieve information from the surrounding area again?[s] If it does, how does it detect the &quot;loading please wait.&quot;[/s][Answered by Silver Lining - Post 2]  What about things like HP announcers, how do they work? My guess is that the Runescape client is edited at run-time to rename the field that contains the current hp of your character, but AGAIN, how do you know that it&#39;s your character and not someone elses? Are the objects going to be named directly after the character on the field? If my characters name is &quot;unlimitedorb&quot; would &quot;unlimitedorb&quot; be an actual object that I can call getCurrentHP() on? What about importing? Do I have to import classes from runescape.jar into my bot.class to use them. What about if I didn&#39;t want to use BCEL at all, in fact, if you knew what you were doing would there be any reason for BCEL at all? Couldn&#39;t you just create some documentation detailing what is what and what it does despite it being obfuscated (Not that I&#39;m going to do that, but I need the true purpose of BCEL cleared up.)
&lt;/Current_Questions&gt;

After writing all these questions here&#39;s what a project for an HP announcer would look like according to my knowledge (It&#39;s going to be my first project and it will be written from scratch without references to any other source code except for BCEL documentation. Who knows? Maybe I&#39;ll come up with a method that someone hasn&#39;t used before.) At this point I&#39;m disregarding Object Oriented Style and taking a monolithic approach so I can better understand the concept, and then I&#39;ll make it &quot;beautiful&quot; later.

&lt;project&gt;
(Please give me thoughtful edits to my first project as this is by no means the final revision...I don&#39;t understand everything fully!)

Create bot.java and place it inside the folder runescape.jar is located in (probably in the cache somewhere.) bot.java will contain an interface to return getCurrentHP(), I&#39;ll then insert a hook into the client using BCEL in bot.java that will make the obfuscated field that returns the current hp of the character that is yours ([s]how do you know the object is your character???[/s] [Answered by Silver Lining - Post 2] ) implement the interface inside bot.java to make it easier to read. Once this is done, I&#39;ll have the runescape, BCEL modified, class that contains the obfuscated name of getCurrentHP imported so that I can use the method that it specifies. I&#39;ll then return this value to the standard output stream.
&lt;/project&gt;

&lt;Long_Term_Questions&gt;
(The following are questions that don&#39;t apply to what I am currently working on, but rather they are problems that I see will arise in the future of my bot-making journey)

One thing that I forsee is being able to communicate with the client itself. Would I use the Robot class coupled with random mouse movements to generate clicks, or is it possible to send clicks silently without the need for a client? That&#39;s another question, if there are methods within the runescape client to generate mouse clicks, is there a need for a graphical client at all? Couldn&#39;t I just have a plain old terminal running my Bot? (I&#39;m using linux by the way) By invoking methods, would I make myself vulnerable to detection somehow, if so, how is it possible for them to detect that?
&lt;/Long_Term_Questions&gt;
//This will be updated as my knowledge of BCEL increases (or, worst case scenario, decreases)</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 24 Sep 2007 08:01:09 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>General Programming</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/loads-of-bcel-questions/145905.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Loads of BCEL questions</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@unlimitedorb unlimitedorb]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/unlimitedorb">@unlimitedorb</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Thank you Silver Lining and Yakman, it’s extremely helpful to have an abstract idea come to concrete conclusions. The above two posts cleared up a ton of core ideas that I didn’t have down. Thank you once again.</p>
<p>I’ll try to strike out questions that have been answered as I go along and make references to who answered them and in what post (In case there are other aspiring RS client tweakers following along.)</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/loads-of-bcel-questions/145905/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/loads-of-bcel-questions/145905/4</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 24 Sep 2007 08:01:09 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-145905-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/loads-of-bcel-questions/145905.rss">Loads of BCEL questions</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Loads of BCEL questions</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@yakman yakman]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/yakman">@yakman</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote no-group" data-post="1" data-topic="145905">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/unlimitedorb/40/5_6259e4fa9dfe0dec282fb0955bb1974c.png" class="avatar"> unlimitedorb:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Hmm, I’m kind of fuzzy when it comes to creating an interface and then using bytecode instrumentation to make a class (inside runescape.jar) implement that interface to rename methods. For instance, when Yakman’s tutorial says anEntity.getCurrentHP(); how do I create/find an object of type Entity? In other words where does anEntity come from? Is it an object generated by runescape.jar at run-time?</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>im just going to add something here,<br>
you get instances of interfaces by getting the static fields in the client, like theres a static field called myPlayer<br>
you get these with getXXX(), the same as other methods, except you put them in the Client interface (you could put them in another interface, but client makes more sence)</p>
<p>so lets say you make your applet loader</p>
<pre><code class="lang-auto">Applet clientApplet = new client();
clientApplet.init();
clientApplet.start();

Client client = (Client)clientApplet;
int playerCount = client.getPlayerCount();
Entity myPlayer = client.getMyPlayer();
int myPlayersHp = myPlayer.getCurrentHp();</code></pre>
<p>with bytecode, you change the client class so it looks like this…</p>
<pre><code class="lang-auto">public class client extends Applet implements Client {


     public int getPlayerCount() {
             return someClass.someInt;
     }

     public Player getMyPlayer() {
             return someOtherClass.someField;
     }
}</code></pre>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-post="2" data-topic="145905">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 Silver Lining:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>I love to see someone that seems interested in the client, asks questions on how things work, and especially when I’m in a great mood.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I like it also <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/smiley.png?v=6" title=":smiley:" class="emoji" alt=":smiley:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/loads-of-bcel-questions/145905/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/loads-of-bcel-questions/145905/3</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 24 Sep 2007 02:34:04 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-145905-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/loads-of-bcel-questions/145905.rss">Loads of BCEL questions</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Loads of BCEL questions</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Silver_Lining Silver Lining]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/silver_lining">@Silver_Lining</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“unlimitedorb, post:1, topic:145905”]Hmm, I’m kind of fuzzy when it comes to creating an interface and then using bytecode instrumentation to make a class (inside runescape.jar) implement that interface to rename methods. For instance, when Yakman’s tutorial says anEntity.getCurrentHP(); how do I create/find an object of type Entity? In other words where does anEntity come from? Is it an object generated by runescape.jar at run-time?[/quote]There are three sources of “Entity” objects: the array of players, the array of NPCs/Monsters, depending on what you name it. And lastly, the field “myPlayer”, which is the player you have logged into Runescape as. </p><blockquote>Also, how do current bytecode bots work? I’m guessing that they modify the client at run-time to implement hooks (which are really just interfaces defining what methods a class must have in order to function), and when you need information about the surrounding area, such as if and where an NPC is standing you use the hooks that will in turn call methods in the runescape client itself.</blockquote>Bingo! It’s really just author’s preference whether the client is modified on runtime or modified beforehand and the modified classes substituted for the originals.<blockquote>Why do you need to use an interface, why can’t you just modify the class to contain a method to return the data of an obfuscated field? Is that just good Object Oriented Programming style, or is there something that I’m missing?</blockquote>In method injection, implementing interfaces in the classes is almost vital. With an interface, it’s just ((Interface)object).method(). Without injecting interfaces, one way (praps there are more? I don’t feel like thinking on it) would be object.getClass().getMethod(“methodName”,new Class[]{}).invoke(object). See how much easier the implementing is?<blockquote>What about when they come to a “loading please wait” does the bot have to retrieve information from the surrounding area again? If it does, how does it detect the "loading please wait."</blockquote>The “loading please wait” stage is detected using the “login index”, which is a horribly name for what is really a symbol of the game state. The “login index” is an integer used to represent the client’s current state, e.g. loading, at the welcome screen, logging in, logged in. I’ll answer a few of your questions later if I get around to it. I love to see someone that seems interested in the client, asks questions on how things work, and especially when I’m in a great mood.
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/loads-of-bcel-questions/145905/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/loads-of-bcel-questions/145905/2</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 24 Sep 2007 02:24:34 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-145905-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/loads-of-bcel-questions/145905.rss">Loads of BCEL questions</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Loads of BCEL questions</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@unlimitedorb unlimitedorb]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/unlimitedorb">@unlimitedorb</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Before I begin, I’d like to say that it’s not so much a matter of programming as it is knowing current logic for making Runescape BCEL bots. I just need some guidance as to what to do. My purpose in the beginning is to reinvent the wheel so that I can get up to date on the current world of Runescape Bot making. I really want to start from the ground up. Also, please realize that I can only work on projects like these in my spare time. If you’re interested in creating 3D games, I would invite you to join project SkyCastle, located at <a href="http://skycastle.org" rel="nofollow noopener">skycastle.org</a>. Skycastle is a project that utilizes jME (Java Monkey Engine) to develop a realistic 3D game in Java, the possibilities are endless <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=6" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
<p>This is a living post meaning that it will be updated regularly as needed.</p>
<p>&lt;Current_Questions&gt;<br>
Hmm, I’m kind of fuzzy when it comes to creating an interface and then using bytecode instrumentation to make a class (inside runescape.jar) implement that interface to rename methods. <span class="bbcode-s">For instance, when Yakman’s tutorial says anEntity.getCurrentHP(); how do I create/find an object of type Entity? In other words where does anEntity come from? Is it an object generated by runescape.jar at run-time?</span> [Answered by Silver Lining - Post 2]  Also, how do current bytecode bots work? I’m guessing that they modify the client at run-time to implement hooks (which are really just interfaces defining what methods a class must have in order to function), and when you need information about the surrounding area, such as if and where an NPC is standing you use the hooks that will in turn call methods in the runescape client itself. <span class="bbcode-s">Why do you need to use an interface, why can’t you just modify the class to contain a method to return the data of an obfuscated field? Is that just good Object Oriented Programming style, or is there something that I’m missing?</span>[Answered by Silver Lining - Post 2] What about when they come to a “loading please wait” does the bot have to retrieve information from the surrounding area again?<span class="bbcode-s"> If it does, how does it detect the “loading please wait.”</span>[Answered by Silver Lining - Post 2]  What about things like HP announcers, how do they work? My guess is that the Runescape client is edited at run-time to rename the field that contains the current hp of your character, but AGAIN, how do you know that it’s your character and not someone elses? Are the objects going to be named directly after the character on the field? If my characters name is “unlimitedorb” would “unlimitedorb” be an actual object that I can call getCurrentHP() on? What about importing? Do I have to import classes from runescape.jar into my bot.class to use them. What about if I didn’t want to use BCEL at all, in fact, if you knew what you were doing would there be any reason for BCEL at all? Couldn’t you just create some documentation detailing what is what and what it does despite it being obfuscated (Not that I’m going to do that, but I need the true purpose of BCEL cleared up.)<br>
&lt;/Current_Questions&gt;</p>
<p>After writing all these questions here’s what a project for an HP announcer would look like according to my knowledge (It’s going to be my first project and it will be written from scratch without references to any other source code except for BCEL documentation. Who knows? Maybe I’ll come up with a method that someone hasn’t used before.) At this point I’m disregarding Object Oriented Style and taking a monolithic approach so I can better understand the concept, and then I’ll make it “beautiful” later.</p>

(Please give me thoughtful edits to my first project as this is by no means the final revision...I don't understand everything fully!)
<p>Create bot.java and place it inside the folder runescape.jar is located in (probably in the cache somewhere.) bot.java will contain an interface to return getCurrentHP(), I’ll then insert a hook into the client using BCEL in bot.java that will make the obfuscated field that returns the current hp of the character that is yours (<span class="bbcode-s">how do you know the object is your character???</span> [Answered by Silver Lining - Post 2] ) implement the interface inside bot.java to make it easier to read. Once this is done, I’ll have the runescape, BCEL modified, class that contains the obfuscated name of getCurrentHP imported so that I can use the method that it specifies. I’ll then return this value to the standard output stream.<br>
</p>
<p>&lt;Long_Term_Questions&gt;<br>
(The following are questions that don’t apply to what I am currently working on, but rather they are problems that I see will arise in the future of my bot-making journey)</p>
<p>One thing that I forsee is being able to communicate with the client itself. Would I use the Robot class coupled with random mouse movements to generate clicks, or is it possible to send clicks silently without the need for a client? That’s another question, if there are methods within the runescape client to generate mouse clicks, is there a need for a graphical client at all? Couldn’t I just have a plain old terminal running my Bot? (I’m using linux by the way) By invoking methods, would I make myself vulnerable to detection somehow, if so, how is it possible for them to detect that?<br>
&lt;/Long_Term_Questions&gt;<br>
//This will be updated as my knowledge of BCEL increases (or, worst case scenario, decreases)</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/loads-of-bcel-questions/145905/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/loads-of-bcel-questions/145905/1</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 24 Sep 2007 00:50:20 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-145905-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/loads-of-bcel-questions/145905.rss">Loads of BCEL questions</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
