<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Beginner GIMP Tutorial [ DESCRIPTIVE BASICS]</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/beginner-gimp-tutorial-descriptive-basics/314729</link>
    <description>[IMG]http://img12.imageshack.us/img12/5642/yoshibitch2.png[/img]


[THIS IS 100% BASIC, USING NOTHING BUT THE ORIGANAL STARTER BRUSHES ETC]

Ok, you clicked this to learn how to use a program Called GIMP, i will briefly explain the concept of what GIMP is, and how it can be used, in my own words.

- GIMP, is a basic, FREE art software, that allows users to create a large amount of images, basic 2d animations, and MANY more types of art. Most of the features that are in Photoshop, are basically in GIMP, except, GIMP doesn&#39;t cost $100, it&#39;s 100% FREE. With GIMP, you will be able to create, banners, signatures, avatars, by following this simple Tutorial on how to get started. I will provide you with MANY links on where to get GOOD images, brushes, the Download Link for GIMP, and i will provide images later.

[b]
Lesson ONE - Getting your files.
Difficulty -As easy as pie! (0/10).

Here is the link for GIMP - http://www.gimp.org/

A place to get your new Brushes - http://www.deviantart.com/
For the brushes, simply search &quot;Gimp Brushes&quot;.

A place to get your Renders (ready to crop pictures) - http://planetrenders.net/


Simply, download GIMP, install it, and Open it. The other links, save for later.
 
Lesson one, COMPLETE!
[/b]

[b]Lesson TWO - The basics!
Difficulty - 1/10
Understanding - 3/10[/b]

Ok, so you have GIMP opened, what do you see other than a bunch of buttons and pictures? NOTHING! That&#39;s all gimp is, buttons and pictures, that allow you to create AMAZING images.

To Start off a picture, click File &gt; New, you now have a dialog box displayed infront of you, I want you to set the Width, to 350, and the height, to 125. Click OK.

A new window is opened, it&#39;s a big box, with a smaller box in it. That smaller box, is the box you created, with the width of 350, and a height of 125.

THIS STEP VARIES - If you have a toolbar on the left side of your screen, it should probably go from the top to the bottom of your screen, if you do, read the next step and continue, if not i&#39;ll write a sentence at the bottom with a &quot;*&quot; to resemble it.

As you can see, there are many buttons, and below that, you will see options.
In those options, click the &quot;Brush:&quot; that shows a picture with a black circle in it.
As you can see, there is not that many creative brushes, i&#39;ll explain how to add them later.
For now, click the biggest  brush that looks like a circle, but semi faded, sort of like a shadow.
This means you selected your Brush to use this new paintbrush style.
[b]
Lesson TWO Complete![/b]


[b]
Lesson THREE - Beginning your first picture.[/b]

Now that you have your brush, click the four corners on the small square (i will refer to this as the &quot;work area&quot;), you now have 4 circles on your work area.

Now click on your toolbar, Colours &gt; Colourize
A box is displayed.
It is very self explanitory, and is very hands on.
as you clicked Colourize, you should notice, your circles are a dark blue. to change the colour, move the HUE left and right,  the SATURATION, means the intesity of the colour, the more right, the brighter and more intense it is, and BRIGHTNESS, adjusts the brightness of the circles.

You may mess around with it, but for now, i want you to set the HUE To,  125, the SATURATION to, 100, and the BRIGHTNESS, to -25. Your white screen should now have a pale green, and the circles will now be dark.
[b]
LESSON 3 1/4 COMPLETE![/b]

Now your going to learn how to use distortion to make cool edits to the picture.

I want you to click Filters&gt;Distorts&gt;Emboss
A box is displayed, this basically deeply BOLDS a brush, i want you to set the Function to BumpMap
then change the AZIMUTH to 190, the ELEVATION to 70 and the DEPTH to 30, click ok.

Your circles are now more larger, deeper, and bolder.

Now click Filters &gt; Lights and Shadows&gt; Super Nova.

A new box is displayed, it shows a bright blue light on your picture, on the example box, you may click with your mouse to change the position of the Lighting.

You may mess around with it, but for now i want you to change the settings to:

X: 175
Y: 120
Click Colour, a new box is displayed
You may mess around with the colour, but for now, where you see: &quot;HTML notation&quot; paste this into it.
4eff00
It should be a greenish yellow, select ok, then ok again to close the Lighting box.

Your image now has a Super Nova lighting in it.

Now i want you to click Filters &gt; Distorts &gt; Lens Distortion.

A box is displayed.

You may mess around to see what the functions are, but for now, set yours to mine, the only ones i list are the only ones that need changing:
Main: -1.500
Edge: -7.000
Brighten: -100.000

Click ok to close the box and change your picture.
The picture now has a faint darkness enclosing the picture, the Super Nova and colouring makes it harder to notice. You may also notice, the image is a bit more stretched.

[b]STEP THREE 2/4 COMPLETE!![/b]

Finding Your render -
Difficulty - 5/10
Understanding - 5/10

In this half way point, you are going to learn how to get an image off PlanetRenders, and place it on your image.

First, go to http://planetrenders.net/ Search for Yoshi.

You should hopefully generate results with many Yoshies, with black backrounds.

We are going to use this one for today: http://planetrenders.net/renders/displayimage.php?album=search&amp;cat=0&amp;pos=18

Simply save the picture to your documents, or where ever you find necessary. 


Now that the easy part is done, click &quot;File&gt;OPEN&quot; Then open your image.

Now, your probably wondering, how do i get rid of that black stuff, well the answer is : Magic Wand.

On your toolbox on the left hand side where you found your brush options, select the button that looks like a Magic Wand it should be on the top row, fourth one going right.

Now on your right side tool bar, right click the box that shows a small image of the picture, and click &quot;add to alpha channel&quot; in the right click option.

Now i want you to select the black part with your mouse above his tail, IN THE BLACK SPOT, and click and hold your mouse, now, this is a hard render to do, because once you figure out how this works, it&#39;ll be stuck in your head, as you click, you&#39;ll notice that Yoshi becomes Outline with a dotted line, if you move your mouse around it moves. i want you to click above the tail, and slowly move your mouse left, if you see that the outlined becomes boxes, you went to far left, move it until the outline is on the outside of his eyes, so that his black eyes don&#39;t get deleted with the black backround. when you have it selected, click CTRL+X on your keyboard to delete it. If that key doesn&#39;t work, i believe right clicking the screen, then clicking file&gt;Cut, works as well.
You&#39;ll notice the backround is white with a whole bunch of black stuff around yoshi.
[b]
STEP THREE 3/4 COMPLETE, LAST STEP!!!![/b]

You finished the hard part, congratz, now you have to fix it up!

Beside the brush button on the toolbar to the left, select, the eraser, a pink rectangle.
Now click, Brush: and change the brush style to the largest sized circle, now you can erase instead of brushing on yoshi to remove the BLACK fuzzy stuff outside of his body. if you find the brush is too big,  select a smaller one. a GOOD way to get exact details, is to hold the CTRL key on your keyboard, and with your mouse, Scroll up to increase the zoom. Remove all the black stuff.

When your done, simply save the picture and then go back to your old picture. 
NOTE: If you had trouble with that render, feel free to try this one! http://planetrenders.net/renders/displayimage.php?album=search&amp;cat=0&amp;pos=26

You can do the steps with this render as well, although it might be a tad more confusing when i refer to &quot;white blocks&quot; etc.

Open your orignal picture, File&gt;OPEN AS LAYERS, open the new yoshi picture.
You&#39;ll notice that yoshi is EXTREMLY Big, and there is a white backround, simply repeat what you did last time, right click the little box in the right hand toolbar, add alpha channel, but this time, when you magic wand just click anywhere on the white, and delete, this will delete all the white, although there is some small rough white outline left.

Now when your done with that, on your left toolbar click the &quot;rotate 90 degrees button&quot; its a blue window showing it being rotated. Now click his big white cheek, then rotate his head upwards so that he&#39;s looking in the top left corner. Click Rotate, your yoshi is now rotated.

Now to make him smaller, go Layer&gt;Scale Layer&gt; change the width to 300 and the height will automatically adjust, click ok. Your yoshi is now fit to the screen.
Remove the rest of those white boxes now.

Now click the yoshi render in the right side toolbar so it goes blue, now above that, change the Opacity to 75.

[b]
STEP THREE 4/4 DONE!![/b]

[b]Step FOUR 1/2 - Making small adjustments, and adding text.
Difficulty - 0/10
Understanding - 1/10
Your almost done![/b]

Click Colours&gt;Brightness-Contrast&gt;Change the contrast to -20. Click ok.

Now change the opacity up to 85.


Now click the backround part on the right hand toolbar to select it, click Colours&gt;Colourize&gt;change the settings from top to bottom to
115
70
-25

Click ok, you&#39;ll notice the colour looks a tad bit similar to yoshi&#39;s now.

Now select the yoshi render again, Select Filter&gt;Enhance&gt;Sharpen&gt; set it to 35, ok.
Yoshi now looks bolder.
[b]
STEP FOUR 2/2 TEXT[/b]

Now on the left hand side toolbar, click the big A, that represents Text.

Now click to the right of yoshi&#39;s head, a text box will display, type your name in. before you do anything after that, click the top of the browser, the bar where the &quot;x&quot; etc is, so you can display your options again, now where your brush options were, you&#39;ll notice that they changed to text font etc.
Change the text font to Segoe UI Bold Italic, change the colour to a dark green, and the font size to fit. Now on the left hand toolbar, click the button that has 4 arrows pointing out from eachother like
so kinda -|-. This is the button that moves layers. now click DIRECTLY ON ANY LETTER, and move the text to fit. 

Reclick the add text, but this time add it to say &quot;Yoshi&quot;. same font, but make it 2 sizes smaller, and make the green a tad lighter. Place it below your name.
Now select your name box on the right hand side, set it&#39;s opacity to 85 and change yoshi&#39;s text to 70.

Now select Yoshi text box, select Layer&gt;Merge Down. ONCE. Now the boxes are combined.

Now click the box you made, click Filters&gt;Lights and Shadows, select Gradient Flare.
Now in the example box place your mouse below the picture, in the grey area so that the flare top just sets in on the bottom of your name, and set the star picture to &quot;Default&quot;. make sure that the star goes in the bottom right corner as well. Select ok, you&#39;ll notice there is a box around your text that has a brighter green shade. 

Now select Layer&gt;Merge down Do that as many times as you can until the option isn&#39;t availible.

[b]
STEP FIVE - THE END!![/b]

Save your image as Yoshi.png, a box will pop up, do nothing but click &quot;export&quot;, another box pops up, do nothing but click save.

[b]YOUR FINISHED!
WOOT!![/b]


Now, upload your picture to a website and post your website to flaunt your skill about how well you did.


[b]BONUS!

Finding the right brushes.
Difficulty 2/10
Understanding 4/10[/b]

First go to the website i supplied at the top about brushes. Search for Gimp Brushes in the search box.

Find the one you want, download it, and go to the file where you downloaded it. Copy it and then go to Program Files, or where ever you installed gimp, oh, and be sure to extract the brushes using winRar if they are in that format.
then open the folder go to Share&gt;Gimp&gt;2.0&gt;Brushes, and place the extracted brushes in there.

[b]Reload gimp, and Voila.[/b]

I hope you enjoyed this tutorial, i realized i rushed the ends, but i have to go, i promise i&#39;ll be back to fix this up. If you read this, and liked it, please write a small Revision, if there are any errors, and give me a rating out of 10 :D.


[b]Here is what i made by my tutorial:[/b][IMG]http://img199.imageshack.us/img199/1483/yoshiz.png[/img]</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 27 Feb 2010 03:49:08 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Graphics</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/beginner-gimp-tutorial-descriptive-basics/314729.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Beginner GIMP Tutorial [ DESCRIPTIVE BASICS]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@moparisthebest Moparisthebest]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/moparisthebest">@moparisthebest</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I love gimp!  I can’t use it for anything else but some simple resizing, cropping, or making backgrounds transparent, but it’s great to see a tutorial on it.  Good job! <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=5" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/beginner-gimp-tutorial-descriptive-basics/314729/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/beginner-gimp-tutorial-descriptive-basics/314729/6</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 27 Feb 2010 03:49:08 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-314729-6</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/beginner-gimp-tutorial-descriptive-basics/314729.rss">Beginner GIMP Tutorial [ DESCRIPTIVE BASICS]</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Beginner GIMP Tutorial [ DESCRIPTIVE BASICS]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@the1337legend the1337legend]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/the1337legend">@the1337legend</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>blah, now mitb has to read this :l</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/beginner-gimp-tutorial-descriptive-basics/314729/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/beginner-gimp-tutorial-descriptive-basics/314729/5</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 18 Nov 2009 02:20:02 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-314729-5</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/beginner-gimp-tutorial-descriptive-basics/314729.rss">Beginner GIMP Tutorial [ DESCRIPTIVE BASICS]</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Beginner GIMP Tutorial [ DESCRIPTIVE BASICS]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@P_I_M_P_3_D_Tut `Lewk_]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/p_i_m_p_3_d_tut">@P_I_M_P_3_D_Tut</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Hey. Good work, may not be the best, but it’s decent.</p>
<p>Thank you for sharing.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/beginner-gimp-tutorial-descriptive-basics/314729/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/beginner-gimp-tutorial-descriptive-basics/314729/4</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 18 Nov 2009 01:29:46 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-314729-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/beginner-gimp-tutorial-descriptive-basics/314729.rss">Beginner GIMP Tutorial [ DESCRIPTIVE BASICS]</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Beginner GIMP Tutorial [ DESCRIPTIVE BASICS]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@the1337legend the1337legend]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/the1337legend">@the1337legend</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>sorry, i have to go in 5 min, i did it very quickly, and i was just trying to get the point of the main uses of gimp, and what it can do, and as it says, i will post more pictures of the steps and progress, just when i get back.</p>
<p>EDIT: and that’s w.o downloaded brushes, theres obviously nothing to work with, with the default brush set, i used what i said i’d use.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/beginner-gimp-tutorial-descriptive-basics/314729/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/beginner-gimp-tutorial-descriptive-basics/314729/3</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 18 Nov 2009 01:24:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-314729-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/beginner-gimp-tutorial-descriptive-basics/314729.rss">Beginner GIMP Tutorial [ DESCRIPTIVE BASICS]</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Beginner GIMP Tutorial [ DESCRIPTIVE BASICS]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Lin Lin]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/lin">@Lin</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Honestly, if what your tutorial makes what you made, it’s… not very good… Very plain and the render doesn’t look too good.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/beginner-gimp-tutorial-descriptive-basics/314729/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/beginner-gimp-tutorial-descriptive-basics/314729/2</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 18 Nov 2009 01:22:46 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-314729-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/beginner-gimp-tutorial-descriptive-basics/314729.rss">Beginner GIMP Tutorial [ DESCRIPTIVE BASICS]</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Beginner GIMP Tutorial [ DESCRIPTIVE BASICS]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@the1337legend the1337legend]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/the1337legend">@the1337legend</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p><img src="http://img12.imageshack.us/img12/5642/yoshibitch2.png" alt width="" height=""></p>
<p>[THIS IS 100% BASIC, USING NOTHING BUT THE ORIGANAL STARTER BRUSHES ETC]</p>
<p>Ok, you clicked this to learn how to use a program Called GIMP, i will briefly explain the concept of what GIMP is, and how it can be used, in my own words.</p>
<ul>
<li>GIMP, is a basic, FREE art software, that allows users to create a large amount of images, basic 2d animations, and MANY more types of art. Most of the features that are in Photoshop, are basically in GIMP, except, GIMP doesn’t cost $100, it’s 100% FREE. With GIMP, you will be able to create, banners, signatures, avatars, by following this simple Tutorial on how to get started. I will provide you with MANY links on where to get GOOD images, brushes, the Download Link for GIMP, and i will provide images later.</li>
</ul>
<p>[b]<br>
Lesson ONE - Getting your files.<br>
Difficulty -As easy as pie! (0/10).</p>
<p>Here is the link for GIMP - <a href="http://www.gimp.org/" rel="nofollow noopener">http://www.gimp.org/</a></p>
<p>A place to get your new Brushes - <a href="http://www.deviantart.com/" rel="nofollow noopener">http://www.deviantart.com/</a><br>
For the brushes, simply search “Gimp Brushes”.</p>
<p>A place to get your Renders (ready to crop pictures) - <a href="http://planetrenders.net/" rel="nofollow noopener">http://planetrenders.net/</a></p>
<p>Simply, download GIMP, install it, and Open it. The other links, save for later.</p>
<p>Lesson one, COMPLETE!<br>
[/b]</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Lesson TWO - The basics!<br>
Difficulty - 1/10<br>
Understanding - 3/10</span></p>
<p>Ok, so you have GIMP opened, what do you see other than a bunch of buttons and pictures? NOTHING! That’s all gimp is, buttons and pictures, that allow you to create AMAZING images.</p>
<p>To Start off a picture, click File &gt; New, you now have a dialog box displayed infront of you, I want you to set the Width, to 350, and the height, to 125. Click OK.</p>
<p>A new window is opened, it’s a big box, with a smaller box in it. That smaller box, is the box you created, with the width of 350, and a height of 125.</p>
<p>THIS STEP VARIES - If you have a toolbar on the left side of your screen, it should probably go from the top to the bottom of your screen, if you do, read the next step and continue, if not i’ll write a sentence at the bottom with a “*” to resemble it.</p>
<p>As you can see, there are many buttons, and below that, you will see options.<br>
In those options, click the “Brush:” that shows a picture with a black circle in it.<br>
As you can see, there is not that many creative brushes, i’ll explain how to add them later.<br>
For now, click the biggest  brush that looks like a circle, but semi faded, sort of like a shadow.<br>
This means you selected your Brush to use this new paintbrush style.<br>
<span class="bbcode-b"><br>
Lesson TWO Complete!</span></p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b"><br>
Lesson THREE - Beginning your first picture.</span></p>
<p>Now that you have your brush, click the four corners on the small square (i will refer to this as the “work area”), you now have 4 circles on your work area.</p>
<p>Now click on your toolbar, Colours &gt; Colourize<br>
A box is displayed.<br>
It is very self explanitory, and is very hands on.<br>
as you clicked Colourize, you should notice, your circles are a dark blue. to change the colour, move the HUE left and right,  the SATURATION, means the intesity of the colour, the more right, the brighter and more intense it is, and BRIGHTNESS, adjusts the brightness of the circles.</p>
<p>You may mess around with it, but for now, i want you to set the HUE To,  125, the SATURATION to, 100, and the BRIGHTNESS, to -25. Your white screen should now have a pale green, and the circles will now be dark.<br>
<span class="bbcode-b"><br>
LESSON 3 1/4 COMPLETE!</span></p>
<p>Now your going to learn how to use distortion to make cool edits to the picture.</p>
<p>I want you to click Filters&gt;Distorts&gt;Emboss<br>
A box is displayed, this basically deeply BOLDS a brush, i want you to set the Function to BumpMap<br>
then change the AZIMUTH to 190, the ELEVATION to 70 and the DEPTH to 30, click ok.</p>
<p>Your circles are now more larger, deeper, and bolder.</p>
<p>Now click Filters &gt; Lights and Shadows&gt; Super Nova.</p>
<p>A new box is displayed, it shows a bright blue light on your picture, on the example box, you may click with your mouse to change the position of the Lighting.</p>
<p>You may mess around with it, but for now i want you to change the settings to:</p>
<p>X: 175<br>
Y: 120<br>
Click Colour, a new box is displayed<br>
You may mess around with the colour, but for now, where you see: “HTML notation” paste this into it.<br>
4eff00<br>
It should be a greenish yellow, select ok, then ok again to close the Lighting box.</p>
<p>Your image now has a Super Nova lighting in it.</p>
<p>Now i want you to click Filters &gt; Distorts &gt; Lens Distortion.</p>
<p>A box is displayed.</p>
<p>You may mess around to see what the functions are, but for now, set yours to mine, the only ones i list are the only ones that need changing:<br>
Main: -1.500<br>
Edge: -7.000<br>
Brighten: -100.000</p>
<p>Click ok to close the box and change your picture.<br>
The picture now has a faint darkness enclosing the picture, the Super Nova and colouring makes it harder to notice. You may also notice, the image is a bit more stretched.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">STEP THREE 2/4 COMPLETE!!</span></p>
<p>Finding Your render -<br>
Difficulty - 5/10<br>
Understanding - 5/10</p>
<p>In this half way point, you are going to learn how to get an image off PlanetRenders, and place it on your image.</p>
<p>First, go to <a href="http://planetrenders.net/" rel="nofollow noopener">http://planetrenders.net/</a> Search for Yoshi.</p>
<p>You should hopefully generate results with many Yoshies, with black backrounds.</p>
<p>We are going to use this one for today: <a href="http://planetrenders.net/renders/displayimage.php?album=search&amp;cat=0&amp;pos=18" rel="nofollow noopener">http://planetrenders.net/renders/displayimage.php?album=search&amp;cat=0&amp;pos=18</a></p>
<p>Simply save the picture to your documents, or where ever you find necessary.</p>
<p>Now that the easy part is done, click “File&gt;OPEN” Then open your image.</p>
<p>Now, your probably wondering, how do i get rid of that black stuff, well the answer is : Magic Wand.</p>
<p>On your toolbox on the left hand side where you found your brush options, select the button that looks like a Magic Wand it should be on the top row, fourth one going right.</p>
<p>Now on your right side tool bar, right click the box that shows a small image of the picture, and click “add to alpha channel” in the right click option.</p>
<p>Now i want you to select the black part with your mouse above his tail, IN THE BLACK SPOT, and click and hold your mouse, now, this is a hard render to do, because once you figure out how this works, it’ll be stuck in your head, as you click, you’ll notice that Yoshi becomes Outline with a dotted line, if you move your mouse around it moves. i want you to click above the tail, and slowly move your mouse left, if you see that the outlined becomes boxes, you went to far left, move it until the outline is on the outside of his eyes, so that his black eyes don’t get deleted with the black backround. when you have it selected, click CTRL+X on your keyboard to delete it. If that key doesn’t work, i believe right clicking the screen, then clicking file&gt;Cut, works as well.<br>
You’ll notice the backround is white with a whole bunch of black stuff around yoshi.<br>
<span class="bbcode-b"><br>
STEP THREE 3/4 COMPLETE, LAST STEP!!!</span></p>
<p>You finished the hard part, congratz, now you have to fix it up!</p>
<p>Beside the brush button on the toolbar to the left, select, the eraser, a pink rectangle.<br>
Now click, Brush: and change the brush style to the largest sized circle, now you can erase instead of brushing on yoshi to remove the BLACK fuzzy stuff outside of his body. if you find the brush is too big,  select a smaller one. a GOOD way to get exact details, is to hold the CTRL key on your keyboard, and with your mouse, Scroll up to increase the zoom. Remove all the black stuff.</p>
<p>When your done, simply save the picture and then go back to your old picture.<br>
NOTE: If you had trouble with that render, feel free to try this one! <a href="http://planetrenders.net/renders/displayimage.php?album=search&amp;cat=0&amp;pos=26" rel="nofollow noopener">http://planetrenders.net/renders/displayimage.php?album=search&amp;cat=0&amp;pos=26</a></p>
<p>You can do the steps with this render as well, although it might be a tad more confusing when i refer to “white blocks” etc.</p>
<p>Open your orignal picture, File&gt;OPEN AS LAYERS, open the new yoshi picture.<br>
You’ll notice that yoshi is EXTREMLY Big, and there is a white backround, simply repeat what you did last time, right click the little box in the right hand toolbar, add alpha channel, but this time, when you magic wand just click anywhere on the white, and delete, this will delete all the white, although there is some small rough white outline left.</p>
<p>Now when your done with that, on your left toolbar click the “rotate 90 degrees button” its a blue window showing it being rotated. Now click his big white cheek, then rotate his head upwards so that he’s looking in the top left corner. Click Rotate, your yoshi is now rotated.</p>
<p>Now to make him smaller, go Layer&gt;Scale Layer&gt; change the width to 300 and the height will automatically adjust, click ok. Your yoshi is now fit to the screen.<br>
Remove the rest of those white boxes now.</p>
<p>Now click the yoshi render in the right side toolbar so it goes blue, now above that, change the Opacity to 75.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b"><br>
STEP THREE 4/4 DONE!!</span></p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Step FOUR 1/2 - Making small adjustments, and adding text.<br>
Difficulty - 0/10<br>
Understanding - 1/10<br>
Your almost done!</span></p>
<p>Click Colours&gt;Brightness-Contrast&gt;Change the contrast to -20. Click ok.</p>
<p>Now change the opacity up to 85.</p>
<p>Now click the backround part on the right hand toolbar to select it, click Colours&gt;Colourize&gt;change the settings from top to bottom to<br>
115<br>
70<br>
-25</p>
<p>Click ok, you’ll notice the colour looks a tad bit similar to yoshi’s now.</p>
<p>Now select the yoshi render again, Select Filter&gt;Enhance&gt;Sharpen&gt; set it to 35, ok.<br>
Yoshi now looks bolder.<br>
<span class="bbcode-b"><br>
STEP FOUR 2/2 TEXT</span></p>
<p>Now on the left hand side toolbar, click the big A, that represents Text.</p>
<p>Now click to the right of yoshi’s head, a text box will display, type your name in. before you do anything after that, click the top of the browser, the bar where the “x” etc is, so you can display your options again, now where your brush options were, you’ll notice that they changed to text font etc.<br>
Change the text font to Segoe UI Bold Italic, change the colour to a dark green, and the font size to fit. Now on the left hand toolbar, click the button that has 4 arrows pointing out from eachother like<br>
so kinda -|-. This is the button that moves layers. now click DIRECTLY ON ANY LETTER, and move the text to fit.</p>
<p>Reclick the add text, but this time add it to say “Yoshi”. same font, but make it 2 sizes smaller, and make the green a tad lighter. Place it below your name.<br>
Now select your name box on the right hand side, set it’s opacity to 85 and change yoshi’s text to 70.</p>
<p>Now select Yoshi text box, select Layer&gt;Merge Down. ONCE. Now the boxes are combined.</p>
<p>Now click the box you made, click Filters&gt;Lights and Shadows, select Gradient Flare.<br>
Now in the example box place your mouse below the picture, in the grey area so that the flare top just sets in on the bottom of your name, and set the star picture to “Default”. make sure that the star goes in the bottom right corner as well. Select ok, you’ll notice there is a box around your text that has a brighter green shade.</p>
<p>Now select Layer&gt;Merge down Do that as many times as you can until the option isn’t availible.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b"><br>
STEP FIVE - THE END!!</span></p>
<p>Save your image as Yoshi.png, a box will pop up, do nothing but click “export”, another box pops up, do nothing but click save.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">YOUR FINISHED!<br>
WOOT!!</span></p>
<p>Now, upload your picture to a website and post your website to flaunt your skill about how well you did.</p>
<p>[b]BONUS!</p>
<p>Finding the right brushes.<br>
Difficulty 2/10<br>
Understanding 4/10[/b]</p>
<p>First go to the website i supplied at the top about brushes. Search for Gimp Brushes in the search box.</p>
<p>Find the one you want, download it, and go to the file where you downloaded it. Copy it and then go to Program Files, or where ever you installed gimp, oh, and be sure to extract the brushes using winRar if they are in that format.<br>
then open the folder go to Share&gt;Gimp&gt;2.0&gt;Brushes, and place the extracted brushes in there.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Reload gimp, and Voila.</span></p>
<p>I hope you enjoyed this tutorial, i realized i rushed the ends, but i have to go, i promise i’ll be back to fix this up. If you read this, and liked it, please write a small Revision, if there are any errors, and give me a rating out of 10 :D.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Here is what i made by my tutorial:</span><img src="http://img199.imageshack.us/img199/1483/yoshiz.png" alt width="" height=""></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/beginner-gimp-tutorial-descriptive-basics/314729/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/beginner-gimp-tutorial-descriptive-basics/314729/1</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 18 Nov 2009 01:18:48 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-314729-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/beginner-gimp-tutorial-descriptive-basics/314729.rss">Beginner GIMP Tutorial [ DESCRIPTIVE BASICS]</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
