<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Decompiling new clean client</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/decompiling-new-clean-client/555068</link>
    <description>Hello,

I&#39;ve been trying to decompile an clean client I got from Moparisthebest. After downloading the gamepack_dump I have tried different decompilers to try to decompile it to .java files. I&#39;ve tried so far:
- JAD
- Fernflower
- Procyon
- JDCore
- CFR
- others

The problem is that they always fail. Always the&#39;re errors, and i&#39;m not talking about a few. Complete files that failed to decompile, crashing, etc.

I have no prior experience in working on clients, so I though it could be that i&#39;m handling this wrong and there is a better way of doing this. Am I doing this right? I want to have an clean 618 client where I can start working on, and not one I download and use from someone else.

Wout</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 26 Mar 2016 16:02:52 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Game Development</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/decompiling-new-clean-client/555068.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Decompiling new clean client</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@woutiboy woutiboy]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/woutiboy">@woutiboy</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Hello,</p>
<p>I’ve been trying to decompile an clean client I got from Moparisthebest. After downloading the gamepack_dump I have tried different decompilers to try to decompile it to .java files. I’ve tried so far:</p>
<ul>
<li>JAD</li>
<li>Fernflower</li>
<li>Procyon</li>
<li>JDCore</li>
<li>CFR</li>
<li>others</li>
</ul>
<p>The problem is that they always fail. Always the’re errors, and i’m not talking about a few. Complete files that failed to decompile, crashing, etc.</p>
<p>I have no prior experience in working on clients, so I though it could be that i’m handling this wrong and there is a better way of doing this. Am I doing this right? I want to have an clean 618 client where I can start working on, and not one I download and use from someone else.</p>
<p>Wout</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/decompiling-new-clean-client/555068/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/decompiling-new-clean-client/555068/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 26 Mar 2016 16:02:52 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-555068-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/decompiling-new-clean-client/555068.rss">Decompiling new clean client</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
