<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>A brief essay</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/a-brief-essay/168584</link>
    <description>This was originally much longer. I removed most of it because it was far too personal.
	Look in a newspaper or watch your local news. What do you see? A fucked-up and downcast world, no doubt. Emotion is contagious; if you smile, someone else just might and if you frown, someone will have a mite worse of a day. Domestic animals have it figured out. If you have a pet, go feed it. You&#39;d think it was Christmas from their reaction. They ignore the bad things and celebrate every single good thing. It&#39;s the animal&#39;s way of satisfying their greatest desire: happiness. Unfortunately, we humans seem to have lost the ability to rejoice and ignore whatever misery we have. Instead, we revel in our unhappiness. You may notice that depression and obesity have become all too common in the short time that you&#39;ve lived. Why? Because we no longer can celebrate the work we do. Technology has stripped us of work. What satisfaction can be taken from watching a machine work? Turn the clock back a few centuries. People were happy because they had work to do. Grow a few plants and just pay attention to how you feel. Watching something you planted and cared for grow is pure ecstasy. Every inch those plants grow, you feel the most beautiful feeling you can humanly feel. 
	Our &quot;advancements&quot; have destroyed us. Teenagers are depressed to the point of self-mutilation (and somehow it&#39;s become trendy), terrorists kill themselves just to see the people who made them miserable die, and we continue to &quot;advance&quot;. Our doom is inevitable. We&#39;ve almost destroyed happiness entirely. Soon, we&#39;ll just accept what&#39;s going on to a greater degree and segment the world into Oceania, Eurasia, and Eastasia. Nowadays, you can be imprisoned for just saying something. What&#39;s that sound like? Oh, thoughtcrime. So prepare yourself. We&#39;re on the brink of either an Orwellian society or global anarchy. You can put a smile on your face and force yourself to be happy, and that&#39;s just great. But if you want true happiness, break away from it all. Fight technology, because it&#39;s your death sentence.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 29 Dec 2007 02:40:42 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>General Discussion</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/a-brief-essay/168584.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>A brief essay</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@I_Br3ndan_I I Br3ndan I]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/i_br3ndan_i">@I_Br3ndan_I</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>That’s amazing.  You’re English is great too sL, like I’ve said before.  This is pretty much common sense, but it’s nothing anyone would think about, or care about.  In most cases, humans would be embaressed to say this kind of stuff publically.  Which is horrible.  As I type this, I’m eating a cheeseburger and I’m obviously on the computer.  I don’t really care for what you’ve said here, but I agree with it.</p>
<p>I’m just sure that no matter what I do, nothing important will change.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/a-brief-essay/168584/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/a-brief-essay/168584/2</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 29 Dec 2007 02:40:42 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-168584-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/a-brief-essay/168584.rss">A brief essay</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>A brief essay</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Silver_Lining Silver Lining]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/silver_lining">@Silver_Lining</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>This was originally much longer. I removed most of it because it was far too personal.<br>
Look in a newspaper or watch your local news. What do you see? A fucked-up and downcast world, no doubt. Emotion is contagious; if you smile, someone else just might and if you frown, someone will have a mite worse of a day. Domestic animals have it figured out. If you have a pet, go feed it. You’d think it was Christmas from their reaction. They ignore the bad things and celebrate every single good thing. It’s the animal’s way of satisfying their greatest desire: happiness. Unfortunately, we humans seem to have lost the ability to rejoice and ignore whatever misery we have. Instead, we revel in our unhappiness. You may notice that depression and obesity have become all too common in the short time that you’ve lived. Why? Because we no longer can celebrate the work we do. Technology has stripped us of work. What satisfaction can be taken from watching a machine work? Turn the clock back a few centuries. People were happy because they had work to do. Grow a few plants and just pay attention to how you feel. Watching something you planted and cared for grow is pure ecstasy. Every inch those plants grow, you feel the most beautiful feeling you can humanly feel.<br>
Our “advancements” have destroyed us. Teenagers are depressed to the point of self-mutilation (and somehow it’s become trendy), terrorists kill themselves just to see the people who made them miserable die, and we continue to “advance”. Our doom is inevitable. We’ve almost destroyed happiness entirely. Soon, we’ll just accept what’s going on to a greater degree and segment the world into Oceania, Eurasia, and Eastasia. Nowadays, you can be imprisoned for just saying something. What’s that sound like? Oh, thoughtcrime. So prepare yourself. We’re on the brink of either an Orwellian society or global anarchy. You can put a smile on your face and force yourself to be happy, and that’s just great. But if you want true happiness, break away from it all. Fight technology, because it’s your death sentence.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/a-brief-essay/168584/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/a-brief-essay/168584/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 29 Dec 2007 02:02:44 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-168584-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/a-brief-essay/168584.rss">A brief essay</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
