<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Rule breakers</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rule-breakers/301132</link>
    <description>Almost every day you can see people breaking rule&#39;s constantly, mostly first time poster&#39;s, or people who fail to read the rules.

I think i came up with a solution, when a person register&#39;s for an account on the forum&#39;s they aren&#39;t told to read the rules, they just start posting.. Well why not make it so they cannot post unless they have been on the rule&#39;s topic for about the time it would take an average person to read all of them, maybe 1-3 minutes? This would make advertiser&#39;s leave, and allow moderator&#39;s/administrator&#39;s to mute/moderate/ban people for &quot;not reading&quot; the rule&#39;s, since that is one of the most used excuses to this day, it would be hard for them to find an excuse. Thus the rule&#39;s being force upon all member&#39;s, and beginner&#39;s to these forum&#39;s which will increase the population, and decrease the rule breaker&#39;s.

This is only a suggestion and everyone&#39;s opinion&#39;s matter.

(Note):
I will not put up with spammers/flamers, doing so will result in being reported, and the post being ignored.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 09 Sep 2009 03:36:36 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>General Discussion</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rule-breakers/301132.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Rule breakers</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@_Rich Rich]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/_rich">@_Rich</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>post it <a href="http://moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php/topic,389322.html" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">here</a></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rule-breakers/301132/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rule-breakers/301132/2</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 09 Sep 2009 03:36:36 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-301132-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rule-breakers/301132.rss">Rule breakers</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Rule breakers</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Explisionist Explisionist]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/explisionist">@Explisionist</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Almost every day you can see people breaking rule’s constantly, mostly first time poster’s, or people who fail to read the rules.</p>
<p>I think i came up with a solution, when a person register’s for an account on the forum’s they aren’t told to read the rules, they just start posting… Well why not make it so they cannot post unless they have been on the rule’s topic for about the time it would take an average person to read all of them, maybe 1-3 minutes? This would make advertiser’s leave, and allow moderator’s/administrator’s to mute/moderate/ban people for “not reading” the rule’s, since that is one of the most used excuses to this day, it would be hard for them to find an excuse. Thus the rule’s being force upon all member’s, and beginner’s to these forum’s which will increase the population, and decrease the rule breaker’s.</p>
<p>This is only a suggestion and everyone’s opinion’s matter.</p>
<p>(Note):<br>
I will not put up with spammers/flamers, doing so will result in being reported, and the post being ignored.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rule-breakers/301132/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rule-breakers/301132/1</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 09 Sep 2009 03:30:35 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-301132-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rule-breakers/301132.rss">Rule breakers</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
