<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Need a few tips</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/need-a-few-tips/438304</link>
    <description>Hey, i&#39;m going to start scripting a RSPS. I&#39;v currently scripted with PAWNO (For SA-MP) and now i&#39;m going to learn JAVA, can I get any tips such as useful links i&#39;ll most likely need, tutorials, etc etc.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 03 Apr 2012 04:39:53 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/need-a-few-tips/438304.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Need a few tips</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Skiire Skiire]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/skiire">@Skiire</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Java is one of the easier languages you can learn. Besides, within most RSPS you don’t even utilize the full potential of Java. The majority of “programming” within the RSPS scene is adding methods to work within pre-existing systems. You’ll do fine when it comes to this.</p>
<p>As for tutorials, I can’t think of any must-haves or need-to-reads. I can direct you to this pastie though:<br>
<a href="http://pastie.org/private/8shejcuv5ne9sgftlahrfw" class="onebox" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">http://pastie.org/private/8shejcuv5ne9sgftlahrfw</a></p>
<p>It’s the configs for farming, which will be quite useful when you do that task. Farming, in my opinion, was one of the more confusing things I’ve ever had to do within my server.</p>
<p>One thing you will need though is an attention to detail and dedication. As long as you have those two things you’ll be able to create and operate a successful server as most are owned by obnoxious, money-hungry teenagers who are ultimately in it for the money and the “power.” I mean power as in the ability to have ultimate control over their players. It’s disappointing to know that those are the motives for most server owners who are maintaining a server, but welcome to RSPS.</p>
<p>Also, the Server Development board is not an appropriate place to post this thread; so you’ll want to have this locked/moved to a more appropriate section, if there is any.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/need-a-few-tips/438304/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/need-a-few-tips/438304/2</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 03 Apr 2012 04:39:53 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-438304-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/need-a-few-tips/438304.rss">Need a few tips</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Need a few tips</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Rated_X_Razor Rated X Razor]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/rated_x_razor">@Rated_X_Razor</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Hey, i’m going to start scripting a RSPS. I’v currently scripted with PAWNO (For SA-MP) and now i’m going to learn JAVA, can I get any tips such as useful links i’ll most likely need, tutorials, etc etc.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/need-a-few-tips/438304/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/need-a-few-tips/438304/1</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 03 Apr 2012 03:15:10 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-438304-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/need-a-few-tips/438304.rss">Need a few tips</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
