<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Commitment</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/commitment/456068</link>
    <description>So recently, I have realized I lack all forms of commitment. In no way can I decide that I am going to do one thing and enjoy it. I&#39;m constantly attacked by the question &quot;so what do you want to do when you get older?&quot;. What I want to do is enjoy myself with the freedom to do what I like. But that&#39;s just it. I don&#39;t know what I like to do. I dont want to find out to late, and I especially don&#39;t want to commit to something that I A) dislike or B) will regret in the future. 

So how can I do it? How can I pick one thing and go for it? There are so many little things I can do, such as render models or play guitar, but there always seems to be that point where I permanently have that skill at a certain level and can&#39;t move on. I picked up a guitar for the first time in 4 weeks today and could play everything exactly the same as before. I&#39;m sure if I opened metaseq, I could go through the exact same process I always do. 

It&#39;s not just hobbies, though. I can barely decide what I want at a damn restaurant unless I know It&#39;s good or recommended. I just need some help on being able to commit and, hopefully, pick one fucking thing that society will attempt to make me enjoy for the rest of my shitty, and eventually forgotten, life.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 26 Aug 2012 16:29:49 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>General Discussion</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/commitment/456068.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Commitment</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@The_Un-Named The Un-Named]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/the_un-named">@The_Un-Named</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <div class="lazyYT" data-youtube-id="b6t4oe4ELoA" data-youtube-title="Daria - What are your goals?" data-width="480" data-height="270" data-parameters="feature=oembed&amp;wmode=opaque"></div>
<p>related</p>
<p>but on a serious note, I’m 20 and still have no idea what I want to do ‘when I grow up’, if you have anything you’re even remotely interested in I recommend you look further in to career options for that choice, I recommend looking in to what you need to study and what you need to do to get in to the field and if the field is any good for you, the worse thing is being indecisive so if there’s anything, anything at all you’re even remotely interested in doing look in to it further</p>
<p>one thing I regret is at least 4-5 years ago I’ve been interested in science and especially chemistry and/or biochemistry but I never looked into the field with any real thought and put it off as not having the grades for it, I regret that now because I’m 4-5 years behind the curve and even then I was behind the curve, and it’s getting to the point now where if I do want to get into those fields I’ll be ‘too old’ to do so, definitely a regret</p>
<p>and I realise you can’t be too old but if you’re doing that at 40, 10 years training give or take for a pitiful 10-20 year career as opposed to 30-40</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/commitment/456068/9">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/commitment/456068/9</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 26 Aug 2012 16:29:49 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-456068-9</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/commitment/456068.rss">Commitment</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Commitment</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Frell Frell]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/frell">@Frell</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I found <a href="http://www.polycount.com/forum/">http://www.polycount.com/forum/</a> and then I got really into modeling</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/commitment/456068/8">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/commitment/456068/8</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 26 Aug 2012 15:29:32 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-456068-8</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/commitment/456068.rss">Commitment</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Commitment</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@the_elve_age the elve age]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/the_elve_age">@the_elve_age</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Start modelling again and post your work in the RS Models section <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=5" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/commitment/456068/7">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/commitment/456068/7</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 26 Aug 2012 15:09:54 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-456068-7</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/commitment/456068.rss">Commitment</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Commitment</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@amy_webb1 amy_webb]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/amy_webb1">@amy_webb1</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>There are so many courses you can do that open a broad range of opportunistic, just talk to career advisers and such. You’ll be suprised what you find when you go looking. In the past year i’ve picked up 2 extra thing i might pursue when i am older and that was just from looking to courses and universities. Good luck. <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=5" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/commitment/456068/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/commitment/456068/6</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 26 Aug 2012 13:57:03 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-456068-6</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/commitment/456068.rss">Commitment</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Commitment</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Tree Tree]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/tree">@Tree</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Pick an occupation that is:</p>
<ol>
<li>Not highly repetitive.</li>
<li>Allows your opinions to be listened to.</li>
<li>Inspires you.</li>
<li>Plays on your strengths.</li>
</ol>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/commitment/456068/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/commitment/456068/5</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 26 Aug 2012 13:29:37 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-456068-5</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/commitment/456068.rss">Commitment</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Commitment</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@reyx7 reyx7]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/reyx7">@reyx7</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“Yz85Racer, post:3, topic:456068”]&gt; realizes lacks commitment</p>
<blockquote>
<p>posts on a RUNESCAPE CHEATING FORUM<br>
expects advice<br>
hasn’t realized most users here are under the age of 15<br>
???[/quote]<br>
Well you’re older, you could’ve helped and not made a smartass remark.</p>
</blockquote>
<p><a class="mention" href="/u/amy">@Amy</a> - thanks, but it seems like doing one thing is the only option, unless I get some really unspecified degree that can get me into multiple fields, but a lot of jobs demand either experience or the exact major for their position. I just don’t see where change is an option.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/commitment/456068/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/commitment/456068/4</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 26 Aug 2012 13:25:25 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-456068-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/commitment/456068.rss">Commitment</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Commitment</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Yz85Racer Yz85Racer]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/yz85racer">@Yz85Racer</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <blockquote>
<p>realizes lacks commitment<br>
posts on a RUNESCAPE CHEATING FORUM<br>
expects advice<br>
hasn’t realized most users here are under the age of 15<br>
???</p>
</blockquote>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/commitment/456068/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/commitment/456068/3</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 26 Aug 2012 05:15:03 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-456068-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/commitment/456068.rss">Commitment</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Commitment</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@amy_webb1 amy_webb]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/amy_webb1">@amy_webb1</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>The thing about choices is there are many of them, you don’t have to decide on one. I’m always having that ‘what do you want to do when you’re older?’ question pushed one me, i say at least 2 or 3 things i was to do. That way you never really commit, and it also beings up a broader range of topics for conversation.</p>
<p>When it comes to small things like food, you don’t need to be worried. The smallest things are always the most difficult. Instead of becoming frustrated, narrow it down. Then you can pick one of the others, maybe even the first on the list, and get the rest later. There is always time for the others, it isn’t a life or death situation.</p>
<p>When picking a future path, don’t get to picky. There are always opportunities that will allow you to change your job if you decide to, you’ll never be nailed down to one place forever.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/commitment/456068/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/commitment/456068/2</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 26 Aug 2012 04:44:05 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-456068-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/commitment/456068.rss">Commitment</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Commitment</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@reyx7 reyx7]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/reyx7">@reyx7</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>So recently, I have realized I lack all forms of commitment. In no way can I decide that I am going to do one thing and enjoy it. I’m constantly attacked by the question “so what do you want to do when you get older?”. What I want to do is enjoy myself with the freedom to do what I like. But that’s just it. I don’t know what I like to do. I dont want to find out to late, and I especially don’t want to commit to something that I A) dislike or B) will regret in the future.</p>
<p>So how can I do it? How can I pick one thing and go for it? There are so many little things I can do, such as render models or play guitar, but there always seems to be that point where I permanently have that skill at a certain level and can’t move on. I picked up a guitar for the first time in 4 weeks today and could play everything exactly the same as before. I’m sure if I opened metaseq, I could go through the exact same process I always do.</p>
<p>It’s not just hobbies, though. I can barely decide what I want at a damn restaurant unless I know It’s good or recommended. I just need some help on being able to commit and, hopefully, pick one fucking thing that society will attempt to make me enjoy for the rest of my shitty, and eventually forgotten, life.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/commitment/456068/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/commitment/456068/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 26 Aug 2012 04:22:01 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-456068-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/commitment/456068.rss">Commitment</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
