<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Godwars transfer</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/godwars-transfer/349520</link>
    <description>Hey, I have my own server and I just recently got a new source. The previous source was great but was a bit laggy.. My new source is even better with no lag. The only thing bad about my new source is at the gwd it only has bandos boss.. The previous source had all 4 bosses and it had new animations like when you click the stairs there was pics of the monsters and you click on them to teleport to them. What I was wondering is if I could transfer the godwars dungeon I had in my previous source to my current one. If I can please comment and tell me how.. I really need to transfer it. Thanks!!</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 17 Jul 2010 01:13:53 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/godwars-transfer/349520.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Godwars transfer</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@jake_cake jake cake]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/jake_cake">@jake_cake</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Hey, I have my own server and I just recently got a new source. The previous source was great but was a bit laggy… My new source is even better with no lag. The only thing bad about my new source is at the gwd it only has bandos boss… The previous source had all 4 bosses and it had new animations like when you click the stairs there was pics of the monsters and you click on them to teleport to them. What I was wondering is if I could transfer the godwars dungeon I had in my previous source to my current one. If I can please comment and tell me how… I really need to transfer it. Thanks!!</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/godwars-transfer/349520/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/godwars-transfer/349520/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jul 2010 01:13:53 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-349520-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/godwars-transfer/349520.rss">Godwars transfer</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
