<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>My future plans for RSCDEF with FreeScape 2</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-future-plans-for-rscdef-with-freescape-2/233881</link>
    <description>Hello!

I have been into this RSC private server-scene for quite some time by now, and I am still very interested in development of such. But, the thing is that time really does not allow me to do so, as I have many other projects going on at the same time. This in turn have made me decide that I probably should let this go. Though, I will still be visiting this site on and off, and perhaps even do smaller projects and/or work relating to the content on this site - MoparScape.org.

Since I really never got as far as I would want with my latest RSC private server project - FreeScape 2, using the RSCDEF &#39;server-framework&#39;, (which took very much time to get where I stand today), and I don&#39;t want this project to be in vain, I thought I should let people apply for continuation of this project. By this I don&#39;t mean I will release it to everyone that applies... I will only release the source etc. to people that I deem see fit for the particular purpose of continuation, and that I think that I can trust.

Why do I do it this way, and not just release it like everyone else? The answer to this question is fairly simple; I have seen alot of releases which have failed (I have done a few of them myself), due to the lack of continued development. Everyone just uses the latest and best source (not saying this is the best, but it is the latest - that is &quot;released&quot;), and they normally don&#39;t add new features to it either (the only code-change is the name of the server and client (if even that)).

Further down I will list what should be in this application of yours - a form of template. But before you read this, I would also like to point out that _I will_ omit any documentations that I currently have in this project. This due to most of which havn&#39;t been implemented yet, or fully thought through. Some of them are unique compared to other servers that I know, others not...

The Application Template-Form:

Name:
Age:
Experience:
Purpose:

Name - This because it is good to know the persons name to whom you&#39;re talking.
Age - Usually, the older you are, the more reliable and mature... Note: &#39;Usually&#39;!
Experience - This is only for experience within programming, not how to bake a cake etc. The more, the better.
Purpose - You have to have a purpose, else there is no need... Say, for instance, you only want to see the code - That is not a valid reason for continuation and to obtain the source.

When you have filled this Application, please either PM it to me, send me it in an E-mail (my E-mail can be viewed in my profile), or just write it in this topic. Do not create a new topic about it. :)

Last, but not least, some of you might wounder what RSCDEF stands for, and as I have omitted that README file from the released version, I will write it here:

RSCDEF = RuneScape Classic Development &amp; Emulation Framework



Edit:

Here below I will list people that have made a successful application, and been granted access to the source:

1. Shangtsung1
2. Alex Levinson
3. dumm1s
4. xEnt

Edit: Plans changed, and I have now released it to the public. Please go [url=http://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php/topic,317718.0.html]here[/url] to see more information.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2008 13:06:53 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-future-plans-for-rscdef-with-freescape-2/233881.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>My future plans for RSCDEF with FreeScape 2</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@shangtsung1 shangtsung1]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/shangtsung1">@shangtsung1</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>just thought i would release my private information in this post <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=6" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"> give people an example to work from</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-future-plans-for-rscdef-with-freescape-2/233881/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-future-plans-for-rscdef-with-freescape-2/233881/5</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2008 13:06:53 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-233881-5</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-future-plans-for-rscdef-with-freescape-2/233881.rss">My future plans for RSCDEF with FreeScape 2</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>My future plans for RSCDEF with FreeScape 2</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@system system]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/system">@system</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>shangtsung1: You’ve already been granted access to it, so there is really no need to post an Application, unless you want a copy of the same one, yet again? <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=6" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
<p>xEnt: Yes, I will grant access for you aswell… Seeing as you were about to help in the process of making it before, but really didn’t have time (aswell as you already got an earlier version of it). <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=6" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-future-plans-for-rscdef-with-freescape-2/233881/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-future-plans-for-rscdef-with-freescape-2/233881/4</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2008 10:39:06 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-233881-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-future-plans-for-rscdef-with-freescape-2/233881.rss">My future plans for RSCDEF with FreeScape 2</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>My future plans for RSCDEF with FreeScape 2</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@xEnt xEnt]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/xent">@xEnt</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Ill take it just to see what you’ve done and possibly use it as a reference in some things, but I cant say I’m going to develop it, I’m too busy with other things and I just don’t have that RSC fever any more.</p>
<p>I’ve got an older version of this, so I am sure you won’t mind.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-future-plans-for-rscdef-with-freescape-2/233881/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-future-plans-for-rscdef-with-freescape-2/233881/3</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2008 04:32:11 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-233881-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-future-plans-for-rscdef-with-freescape-2/233881.rss">My future plans for RSCDEF with FreeScape 2</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>My future plans for RSCDEF with FreeScape 2</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@shangtsung1 shangtsung1]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/shangtsung1">@shangtsung1</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Name:Shang Tsung <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=6" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"> yup thats my real name <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/open_mouth.png?v=6" title=":open_mouth:" class="emoji" alt=":open_mouth:"><br>
Age:7<br>
Experience:4 years java(including 2 year java TAFE course)<br>
Purpose:why the hell not ?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-future-plans-for-rscdef-with-freescape-2/233881/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-future-plans-for-rscdef-with-freescape-2/233881/2</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2008 04:06:35 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-233881-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-future-plans-for-rscdef-with-freescape-2/233881.rss">My future plans for RSCDEF with FreeScape 2</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>My future plans for RSCDEF with FreeScape 2</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@system system]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/system">@system</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Hello!</p>
<p>I have been into this RSC private server-scene for quite some time by now, and I am still very interested in development of such. But, the thing is that time really does not allow me to do so, as I have many other projects going on at the same time. This in turn have made me decide that I probably should let this go. Though, I will still be visiting this site on and off, and perhaps even do smaller projects and/or work relating to the content on this site - <a href="http://MoparScape.org" rel="nofollow noopener">MoparScape.org</a>.</p>
<p>Since I really never got as far as I would want with my latest RSC private server project - FreeScape 2, using the RSCDEF ‘server-framework’, (which took very much time to get where I stand today), and I don’t want this project to be in vain, I thought I should let people apply for continuation of this project. By this I don’t mean I will release it to everyone that applies… I will only release the source etc. to people that I deem see fit for the particular purpose of continuation, and that I think that I can trust.</p>
<p>Why do I do it this way, and not just release it like everyone else? The answer to this question is fairly simple; I have seen alot of releases which have failed (I have done a few of them myself), due to the lack of continued development. Everyone just uses the latest and best source (not saying this is the best, but it is the latest - that is “released”), and they normally don’t add new features to it either (the only code-change is the name of the server and client (if even that)).</p>
<p>Further down I will list what should be in this application of yours - a form of template. But before you read this, I would also like to point out that <em>I will</em> omit any documentations that I currently have in this project. This due to most of which havn’t been implemented yet, or fully thought through. Some of them are unique compared to other servers that I know, others not…</p>
<p>The Application Template-Form:</p>
<p>Name:<br>
Age:<br>
Experience:<br>
Purpose:</p>
<p>Name - This because it is good to know the persons name to whom you’re talking.<br>
Age - Usually, the older you are, the more reliable and mature… Note: ‘Usually’!<br>
Experience - This is only for experience within programming, not how to bake a cake etc. The more, the better.<br>
Purpose - You have to have a purpose, else there is no need… Say, for instance, you only want to see the code - That is not a valid reason for continuation and to obtain the source.</p>
<p>When you have filled this Application, please either PM it to me, send me it in an E-mail (my E-mail can be viewed in my profile), or just write it in this topic. Do not create a new topic about it. <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=6" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
<p>Last, but not least, some of you might wounder what RSCDEF stands for, and as I have omitted that README file from the released version, I will write it here:</p>
<p>RSCDEF = RuneScape Classic Development &amp; Emulation Framework</p>
<p>Edit:</p>
<p>Here below I will list people that have made a successful application, and been granted access to the source:</p>
<ol>
<li>Shangtsung1</li>
<li>Alex Levinson</li>
<li>dumm1s</li>
<li>xEnt</li>
</ol>
<p>Edit: Plans changed, and I have now released it to the public. Please go <a href="http://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php/topic,317718.0.html" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">here</a> to see more information.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-future-plans-for-rscdef-with-freescape-2/233881/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-future-plans-for-rscdef-with-freescape-2/233881/1</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2008 15:10:33 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-233881-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-future-plans-for-rscdef-with-freescape-2/233881.rss">My future plans for RSCDEF with FreeScape 2</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
