<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Those of you who have a problem with me?</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/those-of-you-who-have-a-problem-with-me/300375</link>
    <description>All of you that have a problem with me, come on in and explain why, don&#39;t just keep your grudge and call me an idiot about everything I do and say.

I&#39;ll bet it&#39;s because you think that I think I&#39;m a Java Guru. Ugh, no, I&#39;m far from a Java Guru. Although, I&#39;m not your &quot;average noob&quot; around here. I know a lot more about programming in java then most of the people in these communitys, but there are also a lot of people that know way more about not just java but other languages, but I tend to stick with object oriented programming languages, such as java.

Followed on from that, you still see me as the moparscape noob from 2007/2008, even me reading back on some of my first posts makes me want to slap myself a few times and maybe even pull the trigger. However I learn more and more every day because I&#39;m one of the few people who actually want to become a great programmer some day not a moron who rips off from other people, everyone starts out dumb then works up to a smarter and smarter position. Right now that&#39;s what I&#39;m doing I&#39;m working my way up, and rather, eh, slowly. Not many people realize what I have learned and such over the past year. I guess where I went wrong is being isolated to my friends on MSN, and not being more open sourced to show people my work.

I do expect more flame from this thread, obviously, but I would appreciate it if you just realize I&#39;m not still that moron from years ago.

So explain to me what you&#39;re issue is with me.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 06 Sep 2009 03:17:19 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>General Discussion</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/those-of-you-who-have-a-problem-with-me/300375.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Those of you who have a problem with me?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Mopman Mopman]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/mopman">@Mopman</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>useless posts like this i reckon</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/those-of-you-who-have-a-problem-with-me/300375/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/those-of-you-who-have-a-problem-with-me/300375/2</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 06 Sep 2009 03:17:19 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-300375-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/those-of-you-who-have-a-problem-with-me/300375.rss">Those of you who have a problem with me?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Those of you who have a problem with me?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Gnarly3 Gnarly...]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/gnarly3">@Gnarly3</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>All of you that have a problem with me, come on in and explain why, don’t just keep your grudge and call me an idiot about everything I do and say.</p>
<p>I’ll bet it’s because you think that I think I’m a Java Guru. Ugh, no, I’m far from a Java Guru. Although, I’m not your “average noob” around here. I know a lot more about programming in java then most of the people in these communitys, but there are also a lot of people that know way more about not just java but other languages, but I tend to stick with object oriented programming languages, such as java.</p>
<p>Followed on from that, you still see me as the moparscape noob from 2007/2008, even me reading back on some of my first posts makes me want to slap myself a few times and maybe even pull the trigger. However I learn more and more every day because I’m one of the few people who actually want to become a great programmer some day not a moron who rips off from other people, everyone starts out dumb then works up to a smarter and smarter position. Right now that’s what I’m doing I’m working my way up, and rather, eh, slowly. Not many people realize what I have learned and such over the past year. I guess where I went wrong is being isolated to my friends on MSN, and not being more open sourced to show people my work.</p>
<p>I do expect more flame from this thread, obviously, but I would appreciate it if you just realize I’m not still that moron from years ago.</p>
<p>So explain to me what you’re issue is with me.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/those-of-you-who-have-a-problem-with-me/300375/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/those-of-you-who-have-a-problem-with-me/300375/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 06 Sep 2009 03:15:09 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-300375-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/those-of-you-who-have-a-problem-with-me/300375.rss">Those of you who have a problem with me?</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
