<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Dced every 15 Seconds from ALL servers</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/dced-every-15-seconds-from-all-servers/447189</link>
    <description>I know it has something to do with my wireless router because i hooked it up direct to the modem and it&#39;s fine, if only I could keep it there but I cant. My router works fine and I&#39;m hooked up lan to it but whenever I connect to any mopar server I can do everything just fine but get disconnected after about 15-20 seconds. Short lapse in connection thats just long enough to dc me? It&#39;s not a firewall or anything because that&#39;s disabled on the router. My pc has no firewall so that&#39;s not it either. The same thing happens with internet downloads, I have to keep pausing and resuming them every 30 seconds.

I just got internet from Charter today and hooked it all up. I have a belkin router. I don&#39;t know what info could be useful since it&#39;s not a pc issue so if you need any info just ask.

Update:
It&#39;s definatly a router issue because it&#39;s ending songs on pandora halfway through and skipping to another one on my phone thats connected to wifi.

I live in an apartment complex btw, I have the router on a seperate channel than everything i&#39;ve found on inSSIDer so it shouldn&#39;t be interferance..</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 28 Jun 2012 05:25:41 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>General Discussion</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/dced-every-15-seconds-from-all-servers/447189.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Dced every 15 Seconds from ALL servers</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Cowarooroo Cowarooroo]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/cowarooroo">@Cowarooroo</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I know it has something to do with my wireless router because i hooked it up direct to the modem and it’s fine, if only I could keep it there but I cant. My router works fine and I’m hooked up lan to it but whenever I connect to any mopar server I can do everything just fine but get disconnected after about 15-20 seconds. Short lapse in connection thats just long enough to dc me? It’s not a firewall or anything because that’s disabled on the router. My pc has no firewall so that’s not it either. The same thing happens with internet downloads, I have to keep pausing and resuming them every 30 seconds.</p>
<p>I just got internet from Charter today and hooked it all up. I have a belkin router. I don’t know what info could be useful since it’s not a pc issue so if you need any info just ask.</p>
<p>Update:<br>
It’s definatly a router issue because it’s ending songs on pandora halfway through and skipping to another one on my phone thats connected to wifi.</p>
<p>I live in an apartment complex btw, I have the router on a seperate channel than everything i’ve found on inSSIDer so it shouldn’t be interferance…</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/dced-every-15-seconds-from-all-servers/447189/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/dced-every-15-seconds-from-all-servers/447189/1</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 28 Jun 2012 05:25:41 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-447189-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/dced-every-15-seconds-from-all-servers/447189.rss">Dced every 15 Seconds from ALL servers</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
