<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Legion-X | 719/738 | New Eco Server!</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/legion-x-719-738-new-eco-server/541122</link>
    <description>[center][img]http://i59.tinypic.com/afixvk.jpg[/img]
Forums: [url=http://www.legion-x.net/]http://www.legion-x.net/[/url]
Websclient: [url=http://www.legion-x.net/play.php]http://www.legion-x.net/play.php[/url]
JAR File: [url=https://dl.dropbox.com/s/q87b16lw8hl59dq/LegionX.jar]https://dl.dropbox.com/s/q87b16lw8hl59dq/LegionX.jar[/url]



[url=https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=d5EV8v8SQ64]https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=d5EV8v8SQ64[/url]
[code=java5]Welcome to our advertisement thread. Legion-X is a Matrix based server that has been coded for a very long time, removing all bugs and glitches known. What started out as a small project has turned into a diverse and advanced server. The server is coded on a daily basis and has been tested months for bugs. We have been in the beta stage since August 2013 and have just come out to the finalized release of the server March 2014. This is an economy based server, where you have to work for your items and stats. This is not your typical &quot;easy&quot; server, although it is not as hard as actual Rs. We encourage competition between players so that there is a point for players to continue and work hard. We have coded this server so it is possible to obtain thousands of items through many things such as quests, skilling, minigames, etc. rather than just instantly obtaining everything from a silly Grand Exchange. While having unique features that you wouldn&#39;t find anywhere else, we strive to bring many of Rs features that we all love. Our staff are always online and are willing to assist you with a friendly hand. I hope you all enjoy the server![/code]


Switch Items Look
[img]http://i.imgur.com/KbCBj53.png]http://i.imgur.com/KbCBj53.png[/img]

[img]http://i.imgur.com/6L8o7V2.png]http://i.imgur.com/6L8o7V2.png[/img]
Working money pouch
[img]http://i.imgur.com/QvacpVr.png]http://i.imgur.com/QvacpVr.png[/img]

[img]http://i.imgur.com/2rsv0B5.png]http://i.imgur.com/2rsv0B5.png[/img]
Quick prayer/curses
[img=http://i.imgur.com/1Ey4y6x.png]http://i.imgur.com/1Ey4y6x.png[/img]
Loyalty points
[img]http://i.imgur.com/xEvS0s7.png]http://i.imgur.com/xEvS0s7.png[/img]
Slayer
[img]http://i.imgur.com/K0Jtwu9.png]http://i.imgur.com/K0Jtwu9.png[/img]
Panel
[img]http://i.imgur.com/ugWMFvu.png]http://i.imgur.com/ugWMFvu.png[/img]
Boss
[img]http://i.imgur.com/z5ol2sT.png]http://i.imgur.com/z5ol2sT.png[/img]
[img]http://i.imgur.com/ROKwa7W.png]http://i.imgur.com/ROKwa7W.png[/img]

[size=14pt]PvM Features [/size]
Our community is largely based on PvM. This is one of the most fun and entertaining ways to obtain many items, whether it be loot to be sold for cash, or some new armor to take on bosses in. There are more than 20 full dungeons to explore, which include everything from stair cases to resource dungeons. We also have many training locations for new users to level up in, so they are ready to take on what this server has to throw at them. Now for you hard core users, this server is filled with bosses. With over 30 bosses and still counting, you will have a monolithic hit list to solo or take on with friends. PvM&#39;ers will never be bored on Legion-X!
-Forinthry Dungeon - The ancient wilderness cavern of all those ghostly revants
-Ancient Cavern - Accessed after completing the barcrawl and barbarian training
-Resource Dungeons - Whole new areas unlocked with the dungeoneering skill
-Fremmenick Slayer Dungeon - To find all your slayer monsters
-Polypore Dungeon - Explore this massive dungeon for some of the best mage armor
-Grotworm Lair - Sludge through grotworms to reach the queen black dragon
-Slayer Tower - Climb to the top and get your abyssal whip
-Chaos Tunnels - Explore the most popular dungeon filled with over 200 monsters
-15+ More Dungeons and Locations to Explore!
-Blink - The greatly feared man with powers beyond out understanding
-Yk&#39;Lagor the Thunderous - The most horrifying demon from the deep dungeons below
-Party Demon - A dangerously tough flash mob that appears attacking home often
-Mercenary Mage - Leader of the notorious band of wizards who attacks cities
-Godwars Bosses - The classic runescape dungeon filled with the 5 gods and their soldiers
-Pest Queen - The ultimate boss to the minigame pest invasion
-Wildy Wyrm - The most dreaded creature in the wilderness
-Corporeal Beast - What should not have come back from the dead
-NPC Champions - Bosses accessible if recieved a champions scroll

[size=12pt]Skilling[/size]
What makes our server different from the other servers is that, in all honesty, the exp rates are not too easy. This is because we want to make the high levels worth it, which is why we coded in more custom things at such high levels, so that there is a motive to train these skills hard. We currently have every skill working and expand them each and every day. The community is competitive in leveling, so make sure to keep an eye out to see where you are on the highscores! 
-Elite Guilds - Designed for players to reach max exp and gain extra benefits
-All 25 Skills - Wait.. Really? All of them? Hell Yeah!
-Dungeoneering - Custom Dungeoneering system!
-Advanced Farming - With every patch working and almost every location
-Player Owned Houses - Thats right, you can buy and build your own houses
-Expansive Hunter - A variety of creatures to catch from falconry to chincompas
-Mystical RuneCrafting - With every altar, including the nifty abyss
-Enduring Slayer - With 5 different masters and 200+ tasks, plus get rewarded with slayer points
-Rigerous Agility - Train on any of our 5 courses, plus the bonus 2 advanced courses
-Slick Thieving - Earn some extra money by stealing from many npcs and stalls all over the server
-The other skills have nearly everything coded to RuneScape, so not much is needed to be explained
-Barbarian Skills - Train many skills the Barbarian Way
-Bonus Exp - Enjoy automatic double exp when 20+ are online
-Tasks/Challenges - Complete these on a daily basis to earn rewards for your skilling
-Highscores - To keep track and bypass your fellow players on the ladder to fame
-Selective Skilling Emotes - Earn and activate brand new cosmetic skilling emotes
-Thousands of opportunities, the skilling in this community is mind blowing!

[size=12pt]Minigames[/size]
There is nothing more fun to do than gather around with the community and play some minigames. This can get you new rewards, spots on the leaderboard, new content, you name it! We have added player&#39;s favorite minigames from RuneScape along with some of our custom minigames for you guys to enjoy. These are meant to bring the community together for some fun, so everyone isn&#39;t so isolated.
-Crucible - Nothing better than this sick PvP minigame
-Zombie Waves - Survive the night in an abandoned city against zombies
-Dark Invasion - Use the items you have to battle a wave of the undead
-Pest Invasion - Help the void night defeat the foul creatures escaping the portal
-Dominion Tower - Fight the bosses you loved to work your way up the tower
-Sorceress&#39; Garden - Try to sneak past the gaurdians to gain your amazing rewards
-Castle Wars - Chose zamorak or saradomin and capture the other team&#39;s flag
-Clan Wars - Whether its free for all, safe, or whatever, theres always someone to fight
-Troll Invasion - Save taverly from the invasion of trolls
-10+ More Minigames to Play!

[size=12pt]Community[/size]
We have a friendly and opening community. All players will feel welcomed when joining. We strive to build close relationships with our players, so that they are enjoying themselves and feel right at home. Unlike other servers, the players will get to know the owner not only as a host, but as a friend. Now there is not much more to add, but here are our highlights about the community.

-Active Forums
-Skype Calls
-Automated Events
-Boss Raids
-Friends Chat
-Player Assistance
-Proper Welcoming


[size=12pt]Other Information[/size]
-Full Lootshare
-Gravestones
-Vote4Rewards 
-Clue Scrolls
-Sheating
-Transportation 
-Squeal of Fortune
-Quests
-Amazing PvP
-Player Owned Shops
-DDoS Protection 
-Daily Updates

[/center]</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2014 20:36:22 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/legion-x-719-738-new-eco-server/541122.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Legion-X | 719/738 | New Eco Server!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@morterdestroyer morterdestroyer]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/morterdestroyer">@morterdestroyer</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[center]<img src="http://i59.tinypic.com/afixvk.jpg" alt width="" height=""><br>
Forums: <a href="http://www.legion-x.net/" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">http://www.legion-x.net/</a><br>
Websclient: <a href="http://www.legion-x.net/play.php" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">http://www.legion-x.net/play.php</a><br>
JAR File: <a href="https://dl.dropbox.com/s/q87b16lw8hl59dq/LegionX.jar" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">https://dl.dropbox.com/s/q87b16lw8hl59dq/LegionX.jar</a></p>
<p><a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=d5EV8v8SQ64" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=d5EV8v8SQ64</a></p>
<pre><code class="lang-auto"></code></pre>
<p>Switch Items Look<br>
<img src="http://i.imgur.com/KbCBj53.png%5Dhttp://i.imgur.com/KbCBj53.png" alt width="" height=""></p>
<p><img src="http://i.imgur.com/6L8o7V2.png%5Dhttp://i.imgur.com/6L8o7V2.png" alt width="" height=""><br>
Working money pouch<br>
<img src="http://i.imgur.com/QvacpVr.png%5Dhttp://i.imgur.com/QvacpVr.png" alt width="" height=""></p>
<p><img src="http://i.imgur.com/2rsv0B5.png%5Dhttp://i.imgur.com/2rsv0B5.png" alt width="" height=""><br>
Quick prayer/curses<br>
<img src="http://i.imgur.com/1Ey4y6x.png" alt width="" height=""><br>
Loyalty points<br>
<img src="http://i.imgur.com/xEvS0s7.png%5Dhttp://i.imgur.com/xEvS0s7.png" alt width="" height=""><br>
Slayer<br>
<img src="http://i.imgur.com/K0Jtwu9.png%5Dhttp://i.imgur.com/K0Jtwu9.png" alt width="" height=""><br>
Panel<br>
<img src="http://i.imgur.com/ugWMFvu.png%5Dhttp://i.imgur.com/ugWMFvu.png" alt width="" height=""><br>
Boss<br>
<img src="http://i.imgur.com/z5ol2sT.png%5Dhttp://i.imgur.com/z5ol2sT.png" alt width="" height=""><br>
<img src="http://i.imgur.com/ROKwa7W.png%5Dhttp://i.imgur.com/ROKwa7W.png" alt width="" height=""></p>
<p>[size=14pt]PvM Features [/size]<br>
Our community is largely based on PvM. This is one of the most fun and entertaining ways to obtain many items, whether it be loot to be sold for cash, or some new armor to take on bosses in. There are more than 20 full dungeons to explore, which include everything from stair cases to resource dungeons. We also have many training locations for new users to level up in, so they are ready to take on what this server has to throw at them. Now for you hard core users, this server is filled with bosses. With over 30 bosses and still counting, you will have a monolithic hit list to solo or take on with friends. PvM’ers will never be bored on Legion-X!<br>
-Forinthry Dungeon - The ancient wilderness cavern of all those ghostly revants<br>
-Ancient Cavern - Accessed after completing the barcrawl and barbarian training<br>
-Resource Dungeons - Whole new areas unlocked with the dungeoneering skill<br>
-Fremmenick Slayer Dungeon - To find all your slayer monsters<br>
-Polypore Dungeon - Explore this massive dungeon for some of the best mage armor<br>
-Grotworm Lair - Sludge through grotworms to reach the queen black dragon<br>
-Slayer Tower - Climb to the top and get your abyssal whip<br>
-Chaos Tunnels - Explore the most popular dungeon filled with over 200 monsters<br>
-15+ More Dungeons and Locations to Explore!<br>
-Blink - The greatly feared man with powers beyond out understanding<br>
-Yk’Lagor the Thunderous - The most horrifying demon from the deep dungeons below<br>
-Party Demon - A dangerously tough flash mob that appears attacking home often<br>
-Mercenary Mage - Leader of the notorious band of wizards who attacks cities<br>
-Godwars Bosses - The classic runescape dungeon filled with the 5 gods and their soldiers<br>
-Pest Queen - The ultimate boss to the minigame pest invasion<br>
-Wildy Wyrm - The most dreaded creature in the wilderness<br>
-Corporeal Beast - What should not have come back from the dead<br>
-NPC Champions - Bosses accessible if recieved a champions scroll</p>
<p>[size=12pt]Skilling[/size]<br>
What makes our server different from the other servers is that, in all honesty, the exp rates are not too easy. This is because we want to make the high levels worth it, which is why we coded in more custom things at such high levels, so that there is a motive to train these skills hard. We currently have every skill working and expand them each and every day. The community is competitive in leveling, so make sure to keep an eye out to see where you are on the highscores!<br>
-Elite Guilds - Designed for players to reach max exp and gain extra benefits<br>
-All 25 Skills - Wait… Really? All of them? Hell Yeah!<br>
-Dungeoneering - Custom Dungeoneering system!<br>
-Advanced Farming - With every patch working and almost every location<br>
-Player Owned Houses - Thats right, you can buy and build your own houses<br>
-Expansive Hunter - A variety of creatures to catch from falconry to chincompas<br>
-Mystical RuneCrafting - With every altar, including the nifty abyss<br>
-Enduring Slayer - With 5 different masters and 200+ tasks, plus get rewarded with slayer points<br>
-Rigerous Agility - Train on any of our 5 courses, plus the bonus 2 advanced courses<br>
-Slick Thieving - Earn some extra money by stealing from many npcs and stalls all over the server<br>
-The other skills have nearly everything coded to RuneScape, so not much is needed to be explained<br>
-Barbarian Skills - Train many skills the Barbarian Way<br>
-Bonus Exp - Enjoy automatic double exp when 20+ are online<br>
-Tasks/Challenges - Complete these on a daily basis to earn rewards for your skilling<br>
-Highscores - To keep track and bypass your fellow players on the ladder to fame<br>
-Selective Skilling Emotes - Earn and activate brand new cosmetic skilling emotes<br>
-Thousands of opportunities, the skilling in this community is mind blowing!</p>
<p>[size=12pt]Minigames[/size]<br>
There is nothing more fun to do than gather around with the community and play some minigames. This can get you new rewards, spots on the leaderboard, new content, you name it! We have added player’s favorite minigames from RuneScape along with some of our custom minigames for you guys to enjoy. These are meant to bring the community together for some fun, so everyone isn’t so isolated.<br>
-Crucible - Nothing better than this sick PvP minigame<br>
-Zombie Waves - Survive the night in an abandoned city against zombies<br>
-Dark Invasion - Use the items you have to battle a wave of the undead<br>
-Pest Invasion - Help the void night defeat the foul creatures escaping the portal<br>
-Dominion Tower - Fight the bosses you loved to work your way up the tower<br>
-Sorceress’ Garden - Try to sneak past the gaurdians to gain your amazing rewards<br>
-Castle Wars - Chose zamorak or saradomin and capture the other team’s flag<br>
-Clan Wars - Whether its free for all, safe, or whatever, theres always someone to fight<br>
-Troll Invasion - Save taverly from the invasion of trolls<br>
-10+ More Minigames to Play!</p>
<p>[size=12pt]Community[/size]<br>
We have a friendly and opening community. All players will feel welcomed when joining. We strive to build close relationships with our players, so that they are enjoying themselves and feel right at home. Unlike other servers, the players will get to know the owner not only as a host, but as a friend. Now there is not much more to add, but here are our highlights about the community.</p>
<p>-Active Forums<br>
-Skype Calls<br>
-Automated Events<br>
-Boss Raids<br>
-Friends Chat<br>
-Player Assistance<br>
-Proper Welcoming</p>
<p>[size=12pt]Other Information[/size]<br>
-Full Lootshare<br>
-Gravestones<br>
-Vote4Rewards<br>
-Clue Scrolls<br>
-Sheating<br>
-Transportation<br>
-Squeal of Fortune<br>
-Quests<br>
-Amazing PvP<br>
-Player Owned Shops<br>
-DDoS Protection<br>
-Daily Updates</p>
<p>[/center]</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/legion-x-719-738-new-eco-server/541122/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/legion-x-719-738-new-eco-server/541122/1</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2014 20:36:22 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-541122-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/legion-x-719-738-new-eco-server/541122.rss">Legion-X | 719/738 | New Eco Server!</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
