<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Basic help with getting server online</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/basic-help-with-getting-server-online/335702</link>
    <description>Ok, now before you all start yelling at me to do searches until I start shitting pickles, allow me to inform you, I HAVE. This question might have been answered 9000+ times but the search button sure doesn&#39;t help a lot. I have searched &quot;easyrsc how to start server&quot;, &quot;easyrsc server online&quot;, &quot;rsc server online&quot;, &quot;rsc online&quot;, &quot;how to get easyrsc online&quot;, &quot;easy rsc server help&quot;, &quot;help online easyrsc&quot;, &quot;help getting online easyrsc&quot;, and &quot;easy rsc online help&quot; but all of these searches tell me the EXACT SAME THING: to edit the server and settings files by replacing them with my ip addresses and then compiling. I have done that but I am still unable to connect to server. I keep getting the taskkill error message when trying to compile but when I search for help on that I dont get any proper answers or results either. I know I already posted a thread before but since now I need help with the server and not with java I think this merits a new thread. I&#39;m sure there is a very easy solution to this and there is just something I&#39;m missing. If any of you could tell me what it is I am doing wrong, it would be greatly appreciated.

This is the message I get when I try to compile in the Client file:
[img]http://img687.imageshack.us/img687/7890/problem1.jpg[/img]

and this is the message I get when trying to compile in the server file
[img]http://img691.imageshack.us/img691/275/problem2a.jpg[/img]

I have changed the i.p. addresses for Client, Distributed client, and the Server files. I have tried both the main client and the distributed client and both of them give the &quot;Sorry. Unable to connect. Check internet setting or try another world&quot; message

Now the problem might be that I am on a laptop connected to a wireless router but someone told me that it should work anyway. What do I do?</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 05 Apr 2010 22:03:29 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/basic-help-with-getting-server-online/335702.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Basic help with getting server online</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@da_real_hype da real hype]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/da_real_hype">@da_real_hype</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>unable to delete jar usually means that your server is in use u didnt close it before u tried to compile</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/basic-help-with-getting-server-online/335702/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/basic-help-with-getting-server-online/335702/2</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 05 Apr 2010 22:03:29 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-335702-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/basic-help-with-getting-server-online/335702.rss">Basic help with getting server online</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Basic help with getting server online</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@ninja_Strike ninja_Strike]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/ninja_strike">@ninja_Strike</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Ok, now before you all start yelling at me to do searches until I start shitting pickles, allow me to inform you, I HAVE. This question might have been answered 9000+ times but the search button sure doesn’t help a lot. I have searched “easyrsc how to start server”, “easyrsc server online”, “rsc server online”, “rsc online”, “how to get easyrsc online”, “easy rsc server help”, “help online easyrsc”, “help getting online easyrsc”, and “easy rsc online help” but all of these searches tell me the EXACT SAME THING: to edit the server and settings files by replacing them with my ip addresses and then compiling. I have done that but I am still unable to connect to server. I keep getting the taskkill error message when trying to compile but when I search for help on that I dont get any proper answers or results either. I know I already posted a thread before but since now I need help with the server and not with java I think this merits a new thread. I’m sure there is a very easy solution to this and there is just something I’m missing. If any of you could tell me what it is I am doing wrong, it would be greatly appreciated.</p>
<p>This is the message I get when I try to compile in the Client file:<br>
<img src="http://img687.imageshack.us/img687/7890/problem1.jpg" alt width="" height=""></p>
<p>and this is the message I get when trying to compile in the server file<br>
<img src="http://img691.imageshack.us/img691/275/problem2a.jpg" alt width="" height=""></p>
<p>I have changed the i.p. addresses for Client, Distributed client, and the Server files. I have tried both the main client and the distributed client and both of them give the “Sorry. Unable to connect. Check internet setting or try another world” message</p>
<p>Now the problem might be that I am on a laptop connected to a wireless router but someone told me that it should work anyway. What do I do?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/basic-help-with-getting-server-online/335702/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/basic-help-with-getting-server-online/335702/1</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 05 Apr 2010 21:11:52 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-335702-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/basic-help-with-getting-server-online/335702.rss">Basic help with getting server online</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
