<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Jagex has the best support ever? No, off-topic noobs!</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/jagex-has-the-best-support-ever-no-off-topic-noobs/165928</link>
    <description>I sent them some question because I can&#39;t play RS at school.
I asked them if they knew how to fix it.
And guess what, I got an off-topic again rofl.
What the heck, they didn&#39;t even read my message.
&quot;If you&#39;re writing in about the recent changes to trading and the Wilderness&quot;
If they actually read it they should know I didn&#39;t....also why did they use to &#39;Dear&#39;s?


&lt;blockquote&gt;Dear &#39;MyName&#39;,

Thank you for contacting RuneScape Customer Support.

Dear Player,

Thank you very much for your feedback. 

All game updates are designed to enhance our game for the majority of players. It&#39;s great to hear from players who appreciate our updates, but if you&#39;re not quite as happy or you have your own suggestions then you are welcome to post on our Rants Forum, or Suggestions Forum, depending on what you would like to say.

If you&#39;re writing in about the recent changes to trading and the Wilderness, please know that Jagex has been working hard on a number of ideas to remove the threat of RWT from the game.

I am sure you will have seen several &quot;bots&quot;, or other automated tools, in-game. This is simply the &quot;tip of the iceberg&quot;. We receive hundred of reports each day of many bots and sweatshop workers gathering resources for these RWT sites. Each day we receive many letters complaining of the threat that these macroers pose and how unfair it is that that they are &quot;getting away&quot; with it. These cheats devalue what is most important to the game: the efforts of our players.

Jagex has taken a stand against these rule-breakers. We are taking the fight to the RWT sites by removing their ability to do business. In doing so we are also adding new and exciting content for our loyal players, so that they know we care about them.

I would like to encourage you to read the &quot;Development Diaries&quot; which detail our battle with RWT, and are available on our main page (www.runescape.com). It is only through partnership with you, the loyal and good players of RuneScape, that we will be able to bring RWT to an end. If you place your trust in us, and support these initiatives, we promise to deliver a better RuneScape experience over the years to come.

We take pride in that no other online game has the depth of communication that we do with our players. We want hear from you, so please express your feelings on the RuneScape Forums. Please use any sticky post that is relevant to what you wish to say so that our content team can consider your thoughts and feelings.

Here&#39;s how to make your thoughts heard by other players and Jagex staff:

1. Find the Forum - Click on the &quot;Forums&quot; link on the RuneScape homepage.

2. Login - Click the &quot;Login (Members Only)&quot; button at the top of the page.

3. Read the Code of Conduct - Click &quot;Code of Conduct&quot; at the top of the Forum.

4. Enter the relevant forum.

5. Add a new thread - Click the &quot;Create a New Thread&quot; button at the top of the Forum.

Be sure to read the &quot;Do Not Suggest&quot; sticky in the Suggestions Forum before posting a suggestion - there are certain suggestions that belong in special places, and certain suggestions aren&#39;t suitable for the Forum at all.

Note that you have to be a member in order to post on the Forums - but if you&#39;re not a member, or are banned from the Forums, you will still be able to read them.

Although we can&#39;t comment on unreleased updates, there&#39;s always *fantastic* new content - both for members and for free players - just around the corner!

I hope this helps, and I thank you once again for your feedback. Please do write back if there&#39;s anything else we can do for you, and we&#39;ll be happy to assist you.

Yours truly,
RuneScape Player Support

Good Luck. :)

Please always refer to the RuneScape Knowledge Base to find the answer to your queries quicker.

You can also find help on all free player and all new member quests through the QuestHelp system.

Yours Sincerely
Mod Fnord&lt;/blockquote&gt;</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 25 Jan 2008 09:28:07 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/jagex-has-the-best-support-ever-no-off-topic-noobs/165928.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Jagex has the best support ever? No, off-topic noobs!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@dragonfire455 dragonfire455]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/dragonfire455">@dragonfire455</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Dear Lst Stand42,</p>
<p>Thank you for contacting RuneScape Customer Support.</p>
<p>At Fagex we always aim to respond to every message we receive from our players individually and as quickly as possible.</p>
<p>Unfortunately, due to the massive growth in NO popularity of RuneScape and the increasing number of faggots that brings, we have not been able to keep up, and are not able to offer a personal response this time. We are increasing the size of our customer support unit and hopefully the next time you need help you will be able to get a quick answer!</p>
<p>We always give priority to answering all member queries personally, but we are now aiming to answer NO more free player queries. This number will increase even more in the coming weeks.</p>
<p>Why not consider becoming a member and help support the continued development of the game? Plus you’ll also get a range of extra features and benefits like four extra bank pages, exclusive quests and you get no adverts that can sometimes put you off your game.</p>
<p>As a Member you also get access to the Forums which can usually answer any query you have allowing you more time to play the game.</p>
<p>Furthermore, <a href="http://RuneScape.com" rel="nofollow noopener">RuneScape.com</a> has a wealth of information available to players in the knowledge base section. You will find the answers to most questions in here, whether it be billing, technical, or game related.</p>
<p>Once again many thanks for your query, and apologies that we cannot give a personal response at this time.</p>
<p>Good Luck. <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=6" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
<p>Please always refer to the RuneScape Knowledge Base to find the answer to your queries quicker.</p>
<p>You can also find help on all free player and all new member quests through the QuestHelp system.</p>
<p>Remember, because we updated our server, we are all gay! That’s right, GAYGAYGAYGAYGAYGAYGAYGAYGAYGAYGAYGAYGAYGAYYYYYYYYYYYYYYYYYYYYY!!!</p>
<p>Yours Sincerely<br>
Mod Adam</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/jagex-has-the-best-support-ever-no-off-topic-noobs/165928/20">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/jagex-has-the-best-support-ever-no-off-topic-noobs/165928/20</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jan 2008 09:28:07 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-165928-20</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/jagex-has-the-best-support-ever-no-off-topic-noobs/165928.rss">Jagex has the best support ever? No, off-topic noobs!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Jagex has the best support ever? No, off-topic noobs!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@god_of_ikiliki god of ikiliki]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/god_of_ikiliki">@god_of_ikiliki</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Nah the ‘What is moparscape’ one makes no sense and has nothing to do with the topic.<br>
The first post is the thing.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/jagex-has-the-best-support-ever-no-off-topic-noobs/165928/19">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/jagex-has-the-best-support-ever-no-off-topic-noobs/165928/19</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Dec 2007 17:55:53 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-165928-19</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/jagex-has-the-best-support-ever-no-off-topic-noobs/165928.rss">Jagex has the best support ever? No, off-topic noobs!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Jagex has the best support ever? No, off-topic noobs!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Mr.Chris Mr.Chris]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/mr.chris">@Mr.Chris</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>But the client supports them. That’s the reason people use Moparscape. If you’re trying to make Jagex’s customer support look even worse, you’re failing in every aspect.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/jagex-has-the-best-support-ever-no-off-topic-noobs/165928/18">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/jagex-has-the-best-support-ever-no-off-topic-noobs/165928/18</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Dec 2007 17:43:44 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-165928-18</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/jagex-has-the-best-support-ever-no-off-topic-noobs/165928.rss">Jagex has the best support ever? No, off-topic noobs!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Jagex has the best support ever? No, off-topic noobs!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@god_of_ikiliki god of ikiliki]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/god_of_ikiliki">@god_of_ikiliki</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“Mr.Chris, post:16, topic:165928”]Moparscape is a site…[/quote]and a client.<br>
Just the shitty part of them is.<br>
‘such as the site you mention’, I didn’t tell them a site.<br>
If I did I should say the domain name aswel.<br>
“Private servers”, Moparscape is not a private server.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/jagex-has-the-best-support-ever-no-off-topic-noobs/165928/17">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/jagex-has-the-best-support-ever-no-off-topic-noobs/165928/17</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Dec 2007 05:24:27 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-165928-17</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/jagex-has-the-best-support-ever-no-off-topic-noobs/165928.rss">Jagex has the best support ever? No, off-topic noobs!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Jagex has the best support ever? No, off-topic noobs!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Mr.Chris Mr.Chris]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/mr.chris">@Mr.Chris</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Moparscape is a site…</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/jagex-has-the-best-support-ever-no-off-topic-noobs/165928/16">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/jagex-has-the-best-support-ever-no-off-topic-noobs/165928/16</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 27 Dec 2007 21:56:25 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-165928-16</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/jagex-has-the-best-support-ever-no-off-topic-noobs/165928.rss">Jagex has the best support ever? No, off-topic noobs!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Jagex has the best support ever? No, off-topic noobs!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@god_of_ikiliki god of ikiliki]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/god_of_ikiliki">@god_of_ikiliki</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I lolled.<br>
I asked what a moparscape is and they reply with “such as the site you mention”, I didn’t even talk about a site??</p>
<p>[quote=“Me”]Hello jagex,<br>
What is a moparscape?<br>
Is it an item or npc?<br>
Thanks[/quote]</p>
<p>[quote=“Jagex”]Dear Myacc,</p>
<p>Thank you for contacting Jagex.</p>
<p>Private servers (such as the site you mention) are unauthorised versions of our game. Most of them are badly made, and attempt to imitate images, creatures and characters from RuneScape. Many parts of the game will lack all the features you will find in the real thing, such as quests, skills, and areas of the world map.</p>
<p>Private servers also carry a big security risk; many of them will ask you for your RuneScape password and the owner of the server can then see what your password is and try to access your real RuneScape account. Many also ask you to download files to enable you to run their private server. This is a huge security risk as they maybe keyloggers, spyware or viruses.</p>
<p>However, when it comes to reporting these servers to us, we would be very grateful! We do try and keep track of all such servers, and make sure they are not causing undue harm to our players through malicious software or other nefarious means!</p>
<p>There is nothing like the real RuneScape, and we recommend that instead of taking a risk with private servers that will only disappoint, you play the real RuneScape, because nothing will ever come close.</p>
<p>If you ever witness players breaking the rules in-game, we would ask you to use the ‘Report Abuse’ function. The reports generated in this way provide us with the evidence that we need to take action against rule-breakers. Remember to use the ‘Ignore List’ if you continue to receive abuse from other players.</p>
<p>Good Luck. <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=6" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
<p>Please always refer to the RuneScape Knowledge Base to find the answer to your queries quicker.</p>
<p>You can also find help on all free player and all new member quests through the QuestHelp system.</p>
<p>Yours Sincerely<br>
Mod Abi[/quote]</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/jagex-has-the-best-support-ever-no-off-topic-noobs/165928/15">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/jagex-has-the-best-support-ever-no-off-topic-noobs/165928/15</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 27 Dec 2007 15:56:31 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-165928-15</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/jagex-has-the-best-support-ever-no-off-topic-noobs/165928.rss">Jagex has the best support ever? No, off-topic noobs!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Jagex has the best support ever? No, off-topic noobs!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@nohope nohope]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/nohope">@nohope</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“Casey., post:13, topic:165928”][quote]Hello H0110w33n,</p>
<p>Thank you for contacting Jagex.</p>
<p>I am sorry that you were not satisfied with my previous response. Rest assured that it was not automated.[/quote]</p>
<p>They seem to like me.[/quote]What did you send to get that response?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/jagex-has-the-best-support-ever-no-off-topic-noobs/165928/14">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/jagex-has-the-best-support-ever-no-off-topic-noobs/165928/14</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 27 Dec 2007 10:24:31 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-165928-14</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/jagex-has-the-best-support-ever-no-off-topic-noobs/165928.rss">Jagex has the best support ever? No, off-topic noobs!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Jagex has the best support ever? No, off-topic noobs!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@gothic_queen casey.]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/gothic_queen">@gothic_queen</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <blockquote>Hello H0110w33n,
<p>Thank you for contacting Jagex.</p>
<p>I am sorry that you were not satisfied with my previous response. Rest assured that it was not automated.</p>
</blockquote>
<p>They seem to like me.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/jagex-has-the-best-support-ever-no-off-topic-noobs/165928/13">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/jagex-has-the-best-support-ever-no-off-topic-noobs/165928/13</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 27 Dec 2007 08:37:01 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-165928-13</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/jagex-has-the-best-support-ever-no-off-topic-noobs/165928.rss">Jagex has the best support ever? No, off-topic noobs!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Jagex has the best support ever? No, off-topic noobs!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@mvp566 mvp566]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/mvp566">@mvp566</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>yup this is what i ALWAYS get</p>
<blockquote>Dear Hia 2 U Der,
<p>Thank you for contacting RuneScape Customer Support.</p>
<p>At Jagex we always aim to respond to every message we receive from our players individually and as quickly as possible.</p>
<p>Unfortunately, due to the massive growth in popularity of RuneScape and the increasing number of queries that brings, we have not been able to keep up, and are not able to offer a personal response this time. We are increasing the size of our customer support unit and hopefully the next time you need help you will be able to get a quick answer!</p>
<p>We always give priority to answering all member queries personally, but we are now aiming to answer more free player queries. This number will increase even more in the coming weeks.</p>
<p>Why not consider becoming a member and help support the continued development of the game? Plus you’ll also get a range of extra features and benefits like four extra bank pages, exclusive quests and you get no adverts that can sometimes put you off your game.</p>
<p>As a Member you also get access to the Forums which can usually answer any query you have allowing you more time to play the game.</p>
<p>Furthermore, <a href="http://RuneScape.com" rel="nofollow noopener">RuneScape.com</a> has a wealth of information available to players in the knowledge base section. You will find the answers to most questions in here, whether it be billing, technical, or game related.</p>
<p>Once again many thanks for your query, and apologies that we cannot give a personal response at this time.</p>
<p>Good Luck. <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=6" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
<p>Please always refer to the RuneScape Knowledge Base to find the answer to your queries quicker.</p>
<p>You can also find help on all free player and all new member quests through the QuestHelp system.</p>
<p>Yours Sincerely<br>
Mod Gabriel</p>
</blockquote>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/jagex-has-the-best-support-ever-no-off-topic-noobs/165928/12">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/jagex-has-the-best-support-ever-no-off-topic-noobs/165928/12</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 27 Dec 2007 08:27:19 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-165928-12</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/jagex-has-the-best-support-ever-no-off-topic-noobs/165928.rss">Jagex has the best support ever? No, off-topic noobs!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Jagex has the best support ever? No, off-topic noobs!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@nohope nohope]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/nohope">@nohope</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I am sorry for 3 day bumping but this is hilarious.</p>
<blockquote>Dear Darkarmor7,
<p>Thank you for your message.</p>
<p>At Jagex we always aim to respond to every message we receive from our players individually and as quickly as possible.</p>
<p>Unfortunately, due to the massive growth in popularity of RuneScape and the increasing number of queries that brings, we have not been able to keep up, and are not able to offer a personal response this time. We are increasing the size of our customer support unit and hopefully the next time you need help you will be able to get a quick answer!</p>
<p>We always give priority to answering all member queries personally, but we are now aiming to answer more free player queries. This number will increase even more in the coming weeks.</p>
<p>Why not consider becoming a member and help support the continued development of the game? Plus you’ll also get a range of extra features and benefits like four extra bank pages, exclusive quests and you get no adverts that can sometimes put you off your game.</p>
<p>As a Member you also get access to the Forums which can usually answer any query you have allowing you more time to play the game.</p>
<p>Furthermore, <a href="http://RuneScape.com" rel="nofollow noopener">RuneScape.com</a> has a wealth of information available to players in the knowledge base section. You will find the answers to most questions in here, whether it be billing, technical, or game related.</p>
<p>Once again many thanks for your query, and apologies that we cannot give a personal response at this time.</p>
<p>Hope this answers your query.</p>
<p>Don’t forget to use the RuneScape Knowledge Base to find the answer to your queries quicker.</p>
<p>You can also find help on all free player and all new member quests through the QuestHelp system.</p>
<p>Yours Sincerely<br>
Mod Fnord</p>
</blockquote><br>
This was the answer I got when I sent them this question
<blockquote>Hello. This is concerning Runescape classic. I do not know the amount of time since I last played it , and it would be aweful if i was unable to because I use to really enjoy it. If you could , notify me how long it has been since I last played it. I would not be pleased if I just recevied the message "anything concerning runescape classic please go to that part of the site" . Thank you. Good day.</blockquote> -I was trying to act civilized-
<p>This is radical.Jagex does not care one bit. They don’t even categorize the response depending on key words in the players message like “runescape classic”. But , what do you expect? It is jagex. And yeah with a name like fnord you wouldnt expect much either.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/jagex-has-the-best-support-ever-no-off-topic-noobs/165928/11">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/jagex-has-the-best-support-ever-no-off-topic-noobs/165928/11</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 24 Dec 2007 02:16:38 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-165928-11</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/jagex-has-the-best-support-ever-no-off-topic-noobs/165928.rss">Jagex has the best support ever? No, off-topic noobs!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Jagex has the best support ever? No, off-topic noobs!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@god_of_ikiliki god of ikiliki]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/god_of_ikiliki">@god_of_ikiliki</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“Taharok, post:5, topic:165928”]Of course they have an automated system. They say that like a billion times on their site. They probably just modified their system to only send a single type of message when a free player pms them temporarily because they have undoubtedly gotten a lot of pms relevant to the new updates.[/quote]If it’s really automated, their system sucks bad lol</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/jagex-has-the-best-support-ever-no-off-topic-noobs/165928/10">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/jagex-has-the-best-support-ever-no-off-topic-noobs/165928/10</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 20 Dec 2007 12:55:28 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-165928-10</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/jagex-has-the-best-support-ever-no-off-topic-noobs/165928.rss">Jagex has the best support ever? No, off-topic noobs!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Jagex has the best support ever? No, off-topic noobs!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@ninja_nub ninja nub]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/ninja_nub">@ninja_nub</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Person, that proxy is stupid, it links you to meatspin.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/jagex-has-the-best-support-ever-no-off-topic-noobs/165928/9">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/jagex-has-the-best-support-ever-no-off-topic-noobs/165928/9</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 20 Dec 2007 09:50:30 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-165928-9</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/jagex-has-the-best-support-ever-no-off-topic-noobs/165928.rss">Jagex has the best support ever? No, off-topic noobs!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Jagex has the best support ever? No, off-topic noobs!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@person1936 person1936]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/person1936">@person1936</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>you can play rs at school<br>
proxy <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=6" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"><br>
<a href="http://luckycrm.com" class="onebox" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">http://luckycrm.com</a><br>
goto <a href="http://runescape.com" rel="nofollow noopener">runescape.com</a> and then chose world<br>
when the world is loading keep pressing esc to not go to the invalid site page and then click on open whitout proxy<br>
it bypasses because its <a href="http://mn1.runescape.com/l0,p0,j1" rel="nofollow noopener">mn1.runescape.com/l0,p0,j1</a> or something like that<br>
it should work[br][br][size=1]Posted on: December 19, 2007, 10:38:52 PM[/size][hr]real mods for me<br>
i know that cuz they actually get annoyed when i wouldnt stop pming them abut letting me play rsc and then when i sent them back a message adressed to him they say hes out of the building<br>
im thinking wtf he was in the building 5 minuts ago</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/jagex-has-the-best-support-ever-no-off-topic-noobs/165928/8">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/jagex-has-the-best-support-ever-no-off-topic-noobs/165928/8</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 20 Dec 2007 09:35:58 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-165928-8</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/jagex-has-the-best-support-ever-no-off-topic-noobs/165928.rss">Jagex has the best support ever? No, off-topic noobs!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Jagex has the best support ever? No, off-topic noobs!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@ninja_nub ninja nub]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/ninja_nub">@ninja_nub</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I quit until it gets fun, which won’t really happen. Since training is boring, skilling is boring, and quests are boring. On top of that, I got hacked.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/jagex-has-the-best-support-ever-no-off-topic-noobs/165928/7">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/jagex-has-the-best-support-ever-no-off-topic-noobs/165928/7</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 20 Dec 2007 06:02:37 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-165928-7</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/jagex-has-the-best-support-ever-no-off-topic-noobs/165928.rss">Jagex has the best support ever? No, off-topic noobs!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Jagex has the best support ever? No, off-topic noobs!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@fellixombc fellixombc]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/fellixombc">@fellixombc</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>mod fnoard…that guy has no friends…</p>
<p>no but runescape sucks now these days…just quit…</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/jagex-has-the-best-support-ever-no-off-topic-noobs/165928/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/jagex-has-the-best-support-ever-no-off-topic-noobs/165928/6</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 20 Dec 2007 04:09:28 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-165928-6</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/jagex-has-the-best-support-ever-no-off-topic-noobs/165928.rss">Jagex has the best support ever? No, off-topic noobs!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Jagex has the best support ever? No, off-topic noobs!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@mod_taharok Taharok]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/mod_taharok">@mod_taharok</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Of course they have an automated system. They say that like a billion times on their site. They probably just modified their system to only send a single type of message when a free player pms them temporarily because they have undoubtedly gotten a lot of pms relevant to the new updates.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/jagex-has-the-best-support-ever-no-off-topic-noobs/165928/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/jagex-has-the-best-support-ever-no-off-topic-noobs/165928/5</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 20 Dec 2007 02:58:57 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-165928-5</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/jagex-has-the-best-support-ever-no-off-topic-noobs/165928.rss">Jagex has the best support ever? No, off-topic noobs!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Jagex has the best support ever? No, off-topic noobs!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Click_Here Click Here]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/click_here">@Click_Here</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>it’s probaly some cheap program which sends a random feedback to your messege, making sense or not <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=6" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"> and it just add’s a mod’s name at the end.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/jagex-has-the-best-support-ever-no-off-topic-noobs/165928/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/jagex-has-the-best-support-ever-no-off-topic-noobs/165928/4</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 20 Dec 2007 02:54:29 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-165928-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/jagex-has-the-best-support-ever-no-off-topic-noobs/165928.rss">Jagex has the best support ever? No, off-topic noobs!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Jagex has the best support ever? No, off-topic noobs!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@gothic_queen casey.]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/gothic_queen">@gothic_queen</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Now, message them back and say:</p>
<p>“This message is for Mod FnordD, Clearly you didn’t read my message”</p>
<p>And they will reply  “Yes we do, and sorry if I misread”</p>
<p>Something like that <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=6" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/jagex-has-the-best-support-ever-no-off-topic-noobs/165928/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/jagex-has-the-best-support-ever-no-off-topic-noobs/165928/3</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 19 Dec 2007 16:52:50 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-165928-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/jagex-has-the-best-support-ever-no-off-topic-noobs/165928.rss">Jagex has the best support ever? No, off-topic noobs!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Jagex has the best support ever? No, off-topic noobs!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@davidude36 Brolapse]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/davidude36">@davidude36</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Its no wonder with a name like “Mod fnord”</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/jagex-has-the-best-support-ever-no-off-topic-noobs/165928/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/jagex-has-the-best-support-ever-no-off-topic-noobs/165928/2</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 19 Dec 2007 16:14:19 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-165928-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/jagex-has-the-best-support-ever-no-off-topic-noobs/165928.rss">Jagex has the best support ever? No, off-topic noobs!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Jagex has the best support ever? No, off-topic noobs!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@god_of_ikiliki god of ikiliki]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/god_of_ikiliki">@god_of_ikiliki</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I sent them some question because I can’t play RS at school.<br>
I asked them if they knew how to fix it.<br>
And guess what, I got an off-topic again rofl.<br>
What the heck, they didn’t even read my message.<br>
“If you’re writing in about the recent changes to trading and the Wilderness”<br>
If they actually read it they should know I didn’t…also why did they use to 'Dear’s?</p>
<blockquote>Dear 'MyName',
<p>Thank you for contacting RuneScape Customer Support.</p>
<p>Dear Player,</p>
<p>Thank you very much for your feedback.</p>
<p>All game updates are designed to enhance our game for the majority of players. It’s great to hear from players who appreciate our updates, but if you’re not quite as happy or you have your own suggestions then you are welcome to post on our Rants Forum, or Suggestions Forum, depending on what you would like to say.</p>
<p>If you’re writing in about the recent changes to trading and the Wilderness, please know that Jagex has been working hard on a number of ideas to remove the threat of RWT from the game.</p>
<p>I am sure you will have seen several “bots”, or other automated tools, in-game. This is simply the “tip of the iceberg”. We receive hundred of reports each day of many bots and sweatshop workers gathering resources for these RWT sites. Each day we receive many letters complaining of the threat that these macroers pose and how unfair it is that that they are “getting away” with it. These cheats devalue what is most important to the game: the efforts of our players.</p>
<p>Jagex has taken a stand against these rule-breakers. We are taking the fight to the RWT sites by removing their ability to do business. In doing so we are also adding new and exciting content for our loyal players, so that they know we care about them.</p>
<p>I would like to encourage you to read the “Development Diaries” which detail our battle with RWT, and are available on our main page (<a href="http://www.runescape.com" rel="nofollow noopener">www.runescape.com</a>). It is only through partnership with you, the loyal and good players of RuneScape, that we will be able to bring RWT to an end. If you place your trust in us, and support these initiatives, we promise to deliver a better RuneScape experience over the years to come.</p>
<p>We take pride in that no other online game has the depth of communication that we do with our players. We want hear from you, so please express your feelings on the RuneScape Forums. Please use any sticky post that is relevant to what you wish to say so that our content team can consider your thoughts and feelings.</p>
<p>Here’s how to make your thoughts heard by other players and Jagex staff:</p>
<ol>
<li>
<p>Find the Forum - Click on the “Forums” link on the RuneScape homepage.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Login - Click the “Login (Members Only)” button at the top of the page.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Read the Code of Conduct - Click “Code of Conduct” at the top of the Forum.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Enter the relevant forum.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Add a new thread - Click the “Create a New Thread” button at the top of the Forum.</p>
</li>
</ol>
<p>Be sure to read the “Do Not Suggest” sticky in the Suggestions Forum before posting a suggestion - there are certain suggestions that belong in special places, and certain suggestions aren’t suitable for the Forum at all.</p>
<p>Note that you have to be a member in order to post on the Forums - but if you’re not a member, or are banned from the Forums, you will still be able to read them.</p>
<p>Although we can’t comment on unreleased updates, there’s always <em>fantastic</em> new content - both for members and for free players - just around the corner!</p>
<p>I hope this helps, and I thank you once again for your feedback. Please do write back if there’s anything else we can do for you, and we’ll be happy to assist you.</p>
<p>Yours truly,<br>
RuneScape Player Support</p>
<p>Good Luck. <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=6" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
<p>Please always refer to the RuneScape Knowledge Base to find the answer to your queries quicker.</p>
<p>You can also find help on all free player and all new member quests through the QuestHelp system.</p>
<p>Yours Sincerely<br>
Mod Fnord</p>
</blockquote>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/jagex-has-the-best-support-ever-no-off-topic-noobs/165928/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/jagex-has-the-best-support-ever-no-off-topic-noobs/165928/1</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 19 Dec 2007 14:46:52 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-165928-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/jagex-has-the-best-support-ever-no-off-topic-noobs/165928.rss">Jagex has the best support ever? No, off-topic noobs!</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
