<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>[474]Server but with 508 maps or what ever it is</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/474-server-but-with-508-maps-or-what-ever-it-is/516912</link>
    <description>Looking for a 474 server but with a 508 map. I don&#39;t mind the item base seeing as if like Torva or Chaotics are on there then I can just find a way of putting them into the game.

I don&#39;t mind if it&#39;s PI/Delta/Allstar or anything like that. I just need a stable base and client that I can work with just with a 474 game frame. I will go up to 508 game frame (only because of the Orbs). Also I don&#39;t want none of the item models to be higher then 508/525. It makes the game less laggy and makes the models more HD (If you think about it)

I don&#39;t care about the skills because I won&#39;t be editing them, but I would like to have all skills working if not like 2/3 of the skills. (Not Construction or Hunter or Summoning)

Anything will do for me, just a simple base that I can work with.

Any links i&#39;ll have a look</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 17 Apr 2013 19:45:38 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>General Discussion</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/474-server-but-with-508-maps-or-what-ever-it-is/516912.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>[474]Server but with 508 maps or what ever it is</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@john5689 john5689]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/john5689">@john5689</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Looking for a 474 server but with a 508 map. I don’t mind the item base seeing as if like Torva or Chaotics are on there then I can just find a way of putting them into the game.</p>
<p>I don’t mind if it’s PI/Delta/Allstar or anything like that. I just need a stable base and client that I can work with just with a 474 game frame. I will go up to 508 game frame (only because of the Orbs). Also I don’t want none of the item models to be higher then 508/525. It makes the game less laggy and makes the models more HD (If you think about it)</p>
<p>I don’t care about the skills because I won’t be editing them, but I would like to have all skills working if not like 2/3 of the skills. (Not Construction or Hunter or Summoning)</p>
<p>Anything will do for me, just a simple base that I can work with.</p>
<p>Any links i’ll have a look</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/474-server-but-with-508-maps-or-what-ever-it-is/516912/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/474-server-but-with-508-maps-or-what-ever-it-is/516912/1</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 17 Apr 2013 19:45:38 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-516912-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/474-server-but-with-508-maps-or-what-ever-it-is/516912.rss">[474]Server but with 508 maps or what ever it is</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
