<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Fedora share help. -Solved</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/fedora-share-help-solved/371441</link>
    <description>ok. in class we have an assignment to access windows shares from fedora and fedora shares from windows. i easily accessed the windows share from fedora, and i can &quot;access&quot; the fedora share, but all i can do is see the folders and open the folders but i cant view files inside any of the folders. i have followed tuts about samba. i have the set up the samba server like the tut said. i even set the account in the root group, &quot;chmod 777 -r&quot; the share folder. yet i dont have permissions from the windows computer to access the share, even after i login with the samba account. now i cant open the samba server configuration program, it worked b4 but the i manually edited the smb.conf file, which i have done b4 and not messed it up, and it will not open. i have restarted the VM, and reinstalled samba and the configuration program still nothing. from this experience i am not liking fedora very much and so far still prefer Ubuntu. thanks to whoever helps i need an answer by the end of the hour, but im guessing if we dont get it done today that my teacher will just say oh well lets move on we spent to much time on this..

Edit: a student in my class found the solution for this problem. You have to give samba premission through the SELinux Management program. i would of never thought of that in a million years. Not saying that i dont like linux but this would be a big reason why most people have not moved to linux. yes i know its built to be more secure but when you are on the root account and install something it should automatically fix the permissions needed to use that. sure if you knew what you were doing it wouldnt be a problem, but still it would save time and make things a lot simpler.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 02 Dec 2010 16:21:36 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>General Discussion</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/fedora-share-help-solved/371441.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Fedora share help. -Solved</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@xryz xryz]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/xryz">@xryz</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>ok. in class we have an assignment to access windows shares from fedora and fedora shares from windows. i easily accessed the windows share from fedora, and i can “access” the fedora share, but all i can do is see the folders and open the folders but i cant view files inside any of the folders. i have followed tuts about samba. i have the set up the samba server like the tut said. i even set the account in the root group, “chmod 777 -r” the share folder. yet i dont have permissions from the windows computer to access the share, even after i login with the samba account. now i cant open the samba server configuration program, it worked b4 but the i manually edited the smb.conf file, which i have done b4 and not messed it up, and it will not open. i have restarted the VM, and reinstalled samba and the configuration program still nothing. from this experience i am not liking fedora very much and so far still prefer Ubuntu. thanks to whoever helps i need an answer by the end of the hour, but im guessing if we dont get it done today that my teacher will just say oh well lets move on we spent to much time on this…</p>
<p>Edit: a student in my class found the solution for this problem. You have to give samba premission through the SELinux Management program. i would of never thought of that in a million years. Not saying that i dont like linux but this would be a big reason why most people have not moved to linux. yes i know its built to be more secure but when you are on the root account and install something it should automatically fix the permissions needed to use that. sure if you knew what you were doing it wouldnt be a problem, but still it would save time and make things a lot simpler.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/fedora-share-help-solved/371441/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/fedora-share-help-solved/371441/1</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 02 Dec 2010 16:21:36 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-371441-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/fedora-share-help-solved/371441.rss">Fedora share help. -Solved</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
