<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Learning about Panes</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/learning-about-panes/302155</link>
    <description>[b]Tutorial: Learning about Panes.
Difficulty: ?-10 (It varys)
Source to use on: It can be any type of source, 317, 508, etc.
Usage: To learn something new that may be helpful for the feature.[/b]

Before we begin, I want to start off with an introduction to the tutorial. This tutorial is to make, and learn about different Panes for your Server. Yes, this can have use for players, but it isn&#39;t nothing much except for a Box, with text and other options in it.


[b][size=10pt][font=Verdana][color=red]Chatper One: Setting up the Panes:[/font][/size][/b]

The panes will work in any type of file, so first open up the file you want to use this pane on, and make this Import:
[code]import javax.swing.JOptionPane;[/code]

This is importing the codes which will be usable throughout the file. Without the import, the codes will not work and give off errors to the compiler.

[b]Next[/b], we will need to make it to display for something. The pane will not display automatic, unless it&#39;s under a Command flow that requires the current user to do something to give off it&#39;s effect. You will need to place it under something like:
[code]public class Engine() {[/code]

I was just using that as an example, because putting it there will cause it to display automatically when you start the server.

[b]Next[/b], place this code under the above:
[code]JOptionPane.showMessageDialog(null, &quot;TEXT&quot;, &quot;TITLE&quot;, JOptionPane.INFORMATION_MESSAGE);[/code]

You must replace the &quot;TEXT&quot; with the message you want to display, and the &quot;TITLE&quot; with the title name. Also, if you want to make an additional seperate line in the Message box, put the following code right in the middle of the text:
[code]\r\n[/code]

Do not place a space after the n.


[b][size=10pt][font=Verdana][color=blue]Chatper Two: Learning the different panes:[/font][/size][/b]

There are about 3 different pane displays, and 4 different types. The three display types are: [b]MessageDialog, InputDialog, ConfirmDialog[/b].

The message dialog is just a simple box that displays Text-based messages. 
The input dialog is a Box that let&#39;s the user type something in a box.
The confirm dialog is like a &quot;Yes&quot; or &quot;No&quot; button clicking message.

To use one of these displays, use the following code:
[code]JOptionPane.showTYPE(null, &quot;TEXT&quot;, &quot;TITLE&quot;, JOptionPane.INFORMATION_MESSAGE);[/code]


[b]Next[/b], there are 4 different types, each type has an icon to the left of the Pane indetifying what kind of message it is. The message types are:

[b]ERROR_MESSAGE, INFORMATION_MESSAGE, QUESTION_MESSAGE, WARNING_MESSAGE[/b].

Each type is to be placed at the end of the Pane Command like this:
[code]JOptionPane.showMessageDialog(null, &quot;TEXT&quot;, &quot;TITLE&quot;, JOptionPane.TYPE_MESSAGE);[/code]



[b][size=10pt][font=Verdana][color=green]Summary:[/font][/size][/b]

This is just a basic tutorial for learning purposes. This can be used everywhere. If you need any help, PM me.

Credits: [b]ServerSoft[/b].</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 13 Sep 2009 22:26:21 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/learning-about-panes/302155.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Learning about Panes</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@508 508]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/508">@508</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p><span class="bbcode-b">Tutorial: Learning about Panes.<br>
Difficulty: ?-10 (It varys)<br>
Source to use on: It can be any type of source, 317, 508, etc.<br>
Usage: To learn something new that may be helpful for the feature.</span></p>
<p>Before we begin, I want to start off with an introduction to the tutorial. This tutorial is to make, and learn about different Panes for your Server. Yes, this can have use for players, but it isn’t nothing much except for a Box, with text and other options in it.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">[size=10pt][font=Verdana][color=red]Chatper One: Setting up the Panes:[/font][/size]</span></p>
<p>The panes will work in any type of file, so first open up the file you want to use this pane on, and make this Import:</p>
<pre><code class="lang-auto">import javax.swing.JOptionPane;</code></pre>
<p>This is importing the codes which will be usable throughout the file. Without the import, the codes will not work and give off errors to the compiler.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Next</span>, we will need to make it to display for something. The pane will not display automatic, unless it’s under a Command flow that requires the current user to do something to give off it’s effect. You will need to place it under something like:</p>
<pre><code class="lang-auto">public class Engine() {</code></pre>
<p>I was just using that as an example, because putting it there will cause it to display automatically when you start the server.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Next</span>, place this code under the above:</p>
<pre><code class="lang-auto">JOptionPane.showMessageDialog(null, "TEXT", "TITLE", JOptionPane.INFORMATION_MESSAGE);</code></pre>
<p>You must replace the “TEXT” with the message you want to display, and the “TITLE” with the title name. Also, if you want to make an additional seperate line in the Message box, put the following code right in the middle of the text:</p>
<pre><code class="lang-auto">\r\n</code></pre>
<p>Do not place a space after the n.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">[size=10pt][font=Verdana][color=blue]Chatper Two: Learning the different panes:[/font][/size]</span></p>
<p>There are about 3 different pane displays, and 4 different types. The three display types are: <span class="bbcode-b">MessageDialog, InputDialog, ConfirmDialog</span>.</p>
<p>The message dialog is just a simple box that displays Text-based messages.<br>
The input dialog is a Box that let’s the user type something in a box.<br>
The confirm dialog is like a “Yes” or “No” button clicking message.</p>
<p>To use one of these displays, use the following code:</p>
<pre><code class="lang-auto">JOptionPane.showTYPE(null, "TEXT", "TITLE", JOptionPane.INFORMATION_MESSAGE);</code></pre>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Next</span>, there are 4 different types, each type has an icon to the left of the Pane indetifying what kind of message it is. The message types are:</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">ERROR_MESSAGE, INFORMATION_MESSAGE, QUESTION_MESSAGE, WARNING_MESSAGE</span>.</p>
<p>Each type is to be placed at the end of the Pane Command like this:</p>
<pre><code class="lang-auto">JOptionPane.showMessageDialog(null, "TEXT", "TITLE", JOptionPane.TYPE_MESSAGE);</code></pre>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">[size=10pt][font=Verdana][color=green]Summary:[/font][/size]</span></p>
<p>This is just a basic tutorial for learning purposes. This can be used everywhere. If you need any help, PM me.</p>
<p>Credits: <span class="bbcode-b">ServerSoft</span>.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/learning-about-panes/302155/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/learning-about-panes/302155/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 13 Sep 2009 22:26:21 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-302155-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/learning-about-panes/302155.rss">Learning about Panes</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
