<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Changing skills xp [delta] &quot;most importantly crafting&quot;</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/changing-skills-xp-delta-most-importantly-crafting/394018</link>
    <description>Ok yall have helped me alot cause i was tryign to teach myself how to code n run a server and yall&#39;s tutorials and people talking to me and replying on my threads have been amazing help.(:
*i got my server online and i coded from the origional deltasource, ive got my home + shops moved n edited. custom skilling zone with ::skill command added. ::pure added. 1 wave jad. faster combat trainin. faster prayer xp, faster fishing, faster thieving, faster wcing and fming, webclient made, forums made, and much more. and id like to thank all the people who ive had help from.

-NOW.. for what ima working on now n currently needing help on:
ive changed some skills xp rates to be faster but some i could not find. since i found combat stats, prayer, thieving, wcing, fming, and fishing xp&#39;s all in client.java im guessing all skills are in client.java, but i can not find anymore then what i have done sofar.
-I need to know what i search to find the rest of the skills and if they aint in client.java then tell me were to search please. &quot;main important to me right now is crafting and cooking.

*for crafting ive alry searched: &quot;craft&quot;, &quot;crafting&quot;, the itemid&#39;s of the ammies you make, the itemid&#39;s of the gems you craft, and current xp for crafting a saphire and still couldnt find it. 
somebody please help
THX</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 06 May 2011 22:56:47 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/changing-skills-xp-delta-most-importantly-crafting/394018.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Changing skills xp [delta] &quot;most importantly crafting&quot;</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@krunt krunt]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/krunt">@krunt</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Ok yall have helped me alot cause i was tryign to teach myself how to code n run a server and yall’s tutorials and people talking to me and replying on my threads have been amazing help.(:<br>
*i got my server online and i coded from the origional deltasource, ive got my home + shops moved n edited. custom skilling zone with ::skill command added. ::pure added. 1 wave jad. faster combat trainin. faster prayer xp, faster fishing, faster thieving, faster wcing and fming, webclient made, forums made, and much more. and id like to thank all the people who ive had help from.</p>
<p>-NOW… for what ima working on now n currently needing help on:<br>
ive changed some skills xp rates to be faster but some i could not find. since i found combat stats, prayer, thieving, wcing, fming, and fishing xp’s all in client.java im guessing all skills are in client.java, but i can not find anymore then what i have done sofar.<br>
-I need to know what i search to find the rest of the skills and if they aint in client.java then tell me were to search please. "main important to me right now is crafting and cooking.</p>
<p>*for crafting ive alry searched: “craft”, “crafting”, the itemid’s of the ammies you make, the itemid’s of the gems you craft, and current xp for crafting a saphire and still couldnt find it.<br>
somebody please help<br>
THX</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/changing-skills-xp-delta-most-importantly-crafting/394018/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/changing-skills-xp-delta-most-importantly-crafting/394018/1</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 06 May 2011 22:56:47 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-394018-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/changing-skills-xp-delta-most-importantly-crafting/394018.rss">Changing skills xp [delta] &quot;most importantly crafting&quot;</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
