<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Wow....blue light rapist</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/wow-blue-light-rapist/16026</link>
    <description>This is direct quote from news..
&lt;blockquote&gt;Victim of ‘blue light rapist’ opposes clemency

By Hannah Farmer
Staff Writer

Robert Burmingham is in the Arkansas Department of Corrections’ Grimes Unit in Newport for keeping a blue light mounted on his dashboard posing as a police car, then pulling over women drivers and attacking them. 

Shannon Woods, who lives in Cabot, was one of those victims. It was on July 11, 1997, at about 9:30 p.m., as the then-17-year-old was on her way home from her boyfriend’s house in Lonoke. Woods was raped by Burmingham that night, and it was ultimately her testimony that led to his conviction. Known as the “blue light rapist,” Burmingham was sentenced to life plus 80 years in prison, but has now applied for reduction of his sentence.

“We were told when he was sentenced that he would have to serve at least 56 [years] of his … sentence,” said Woods in an interview this week.

Burmingham has served not quite eight years. Woods said she found out last Friday that he has applied for executive clemency, which could reduce his sentence. She said the state Parole Board will have the entire month of December to look over the case, and if they find merit they will call both her and Burmingham. 

“When they caught him and put him in prison, I was all for it,” said Woods.

Dina Tyler, spokesman for the Arkansas Department of Corrections, said that every inmate in the state prison system, regardless of their crime or how long they have served, has the legal right to apply for executive clemency, which is reviewed by the Parole Board but ultimately approved or denied by the governor. 

“It’s basically mercy from the governor,” she said. “There has to be a compelling reason.”

In other words, it can’t be based just on the inmate’s desire to be freed, but on something like facts not known at the time of the trial, if the ends of justice were not met, or if the sentence was excessive.

An inmate’s application for clemency is screened by the Parole Board, which considers the amount of time served and the inmate’s record during incarceration. 

“They also consider the nature of the crime, and obviously this is a very serious crime,” Tyler said. “You have someone posing as a law enforcement officer to lure young women to the side of the road to rape them.”

If no one on the board feels they need more information, the full board makes a non-binding recommendation and sends it to the governor for a final decision. However, if even one board member wants more information, then a hearing is set. The inmate and supporters of clemency will meet with one or more board members; and those opposing clemency will have a separate meeting with board members. From there, the full board makes its recommendation to the governor.

Tyler said that with Burmingham’s screening set for December, if it is decided to hold further hearings those won’t happen until January at the absolute earliest, likely later.

This is Burmingham’s first application for clemency, Tyler said. While she could not offer any prediction on the outcome of his application, she did observe that “you’re talking about someone who has done nine years on a life sentence, which isn’t much time.”

“A lot of inmates apply,” she added. “Very few get it.”

* * *

On the night of the rape, Woods said she was driving back late on a dark highway. She had her sunroof opened and her driver’s side window rolled down, and she said she was speeding, trying to get home. 

She recalled that she noticed that a blue light was flashing behind her, so she pulled over close to the intersection of Arkansas Highway 31 and Arkansas Highway 38, less than two miles from her house. Woods reached into her purse for her identification and, when she turned around to the window, found a gun pointed at her head and a man in a ski mask standing there. 

She said it was determined later that Burmingham probably followed her from the parking lot of the Lonoke Wal-Mart. The Arkansas State Police speculated that he probably stalked her because he drove past her parent’s house and knew where she lived. 

“He gave me a button-up shirt to put over my head and then yanked me from my car,” said Woods. 

She said she did not scream because she was in so much shock, and she thought he was going to kill her. She said that he wanted her eyes completely covered, and she did not actually see his face until she saw the news report on television when the arrested him. 

After he picked her up, he drove her to the Pine Tree Cult area in Cross County to one his father’s rent houses. 

“When I was in the back of his car, I made the decision that if he didn’t kill me, I was going remember everything I possibly could,” said Woods. 

And she did.

She said the State Police have told her that she is the one who caught Burmingham because of the details that she remembered. She remembered his eyes when she saw him in the ski mask, and she remembered the way he traveled to the house. She also remembered how many steps went up to the house and which way the door opened. She said he put her in a rocking chair when they got inside and he drank what she thought was a beer because she could smell it, and he smoked during that time. When he took her to a bedroom, and she remembered which side of the house it was on, as well. 

Once he got her into the bedroom, he placed duct tape on her eyes so tightly that, when he ripped it off about three hours later, it left bruises all around her eyes that clearly showed where the tape had been.

As a result of her experience, Woods said that the adage of blocking off one of the senses to heighten the rest is completely true, because she remembered nearly everything she heard during that attack while her eyes were covered. 

Woods said she did not think he was going to rape her until he told her to take off her clothes. At that point she said to him, “Why don’t you just go ahead and kill me?” But Burmingham responded, “If you don’t do what I tell you, I’m going to blow your [expletive] head off.”

Woods said that Burmingham raped her multiple times and sodomized her during this attack. She said she was completely conscious through the whole ordeal and heard everything he did while he was in the house. 

In a story printed in Arkansas Times newspaper on Aug. 1, 1997, reporter Judith Gallman said that Woods said she told the police she remembered hearing a radio station from Jonesboro during the drive, which helped investigators narrow down his location. Gallman quoted State Police spokesman Bill Sadler as saying Woods had likely been the most helpful of the blue light rapists’ victims.

After raping her, Woods said, Burmingham dropped her off, face-down, in a field in Cross County and told her to count to 100 and to wait until she heard his car leave. She said she got up after a long time because she was scared to think that he might still be around, and finally walked a mile until she reached a house that had lights on, and a couple answered the door. 

“A woman answered and I told her, ‘I’ve been attacked, you don’t have to let me in your house just call the police,’” remembered Woods.

But the couple did let her in and called a neighbor who was a constable; he then called the Augusta Sheriff’s Department. After saying the words “blue light” in her interview, detectives said they knew the attacker they were dealing with.

Woods’ parents were also called, despite her efforts to shield them from her incident.

“My dad thought that I was with my boyfriend and we had been drinking and he thought he was going to have come bail me out of jail,” said Woods. 

Her father found out what had happened from the State Police investigator, so Woods did not have to explain it to him. She was then transported to Arkansas Children’s Hospital for medical treatment and tests. Although Burmingham used a condom the first few times he raped Woods, he didn’t to later, which Woods said gave detectives the DNA they needed to identify him. 

Throughout the trial, Burmingham and his wife proclaimed his innocence. According to an Associated Press story on the trial, both maintained on the witness stand that they were at home together the night of this attack. 

In the years since the attack, Woods completed her degree at Arkansas State University in Beebe and now works as a respiratory therapist. But she still has flashbacks when she sees flashing blue lights.

“I still have a hard time being around men to this day,” she said. “Before they actually caught him, I couldn’t even leave the house.”&lt;/blockquote&gt;</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 24 Sep 2006 10:18:40 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>General Discussion</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/wow-blue-light-rapist/16026.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Wow....blue light rapist</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@usernamelol .Fusion]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/usernamelol">@usernamelol</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Crazy stuff, sorry ron i had to make another news thread :P… Well they still havnt put the article about my neihbors house being on fire, hopfully it will be on paper tommorow.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/wow-blue-light-rapist/16026/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/wow-blue-light-rapist/16026/3</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 24 Sep 2006 10:18:40 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-16026-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/wow-blue-light-rapist/16026.rss">Wow....blue light rapist</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Wow....blue light rapist</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@wall_of_fir wall of fir]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/wall_of_fir">@wall_of_fir</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>INSANE!theres a rapisnt near where i live hes raped over 200+ women and cops just figured out he’s been living with the monks helping them make their bread for 7 years (yes monks do make monks bread)</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/wow-blue-light-rapist/16026/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/wow-blue-light-rapist/16026/2</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 24 Sep 2006 10:16:19 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-16026-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/wow-blue-light-rapist/16026.rss">Wow....blue light rapist</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Wow....blue light rapist</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@usernamelol .Fusion]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/usernamelol">@usernamelol</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>This is direct quote from news…</p>
<blockquote>Victim of ‘blue light rapist’ opposes clemency
<p>By Hannah Farmer<br>
Staff Writer</p>
<p>Robert Burmingham is in the Arkansas Department of Corrections’ Grimes Unit in Newport for keeping a blue light mounted on his dashboard posing as a police car, then pulling over women drivers and attacking them.</p>
<p>Shannon Woods, who lives in Cabot, was one of those victims. It was on July 11, 1997, at about 9:30 p.m., as the then-17-year-old was on her way home from her boyfriend’s house in Lonoke. Woods was raped by Burmingham that night, and it was ultimately her testimony that led to his conviction. Known as the “blue light rapist,” Burmingham was sentenced to life plus 80 years in prison, but has now applied for reduction of his sentence.</p>
<p>“We were told when he was sentenced that he would have to serve at least 56 [years] of his … sentence,” said Woods in an interview this week.</p>
<p>Burmingham has served not quite eight years. Woods said she found out last Friday that he has applied for executive clemency, which could reduce his sentence. She said the state Parole Board will have the entire month of December to look over the case, and if they find merit they will call both her and Burmingham.</p>
<p>“When they caught him and put him in prison, I was all for it,” said Woods.</p>
<p>Dina Tyler, spokesman for the Arkansas Department of Corrections, said that every inmate in the state prison system, regardless of their crime or how long they have served, has the legal right to apply for executive clemency, which is reviewed by the Parole Board but ultimately approved or denied by the governor.</p>
<p>“It’s basically mercy from the governor,” she said. “There has to be a compelling reason.”</p>
<p>In other words, it can’t be based just on the inmate’s desire to be freed, but on something like facts not known at the time of the trial, if the ends of justice were not met, or if the sentence was excessive.</p>
<p>An inmate’s application for clemency is screened by the Parole Board, which considers the amount of time served and the inmate’s record during incarceration.</p>
<p>“They also consider the nature of the crime, and obviously this is a very serious crime,” Tyler said. “You have someone posing as a law enforcement officer to lure young women to the side of the road to rape them.”</p>
<p>If no one on the board feels they need more information, the full board makes a non-binding recommendation and sends it to the governor for a final decision. However, if even one board member wants more information, then a hearing is set. The inmate and supporters of clemency will meet with one or more board members; and those opposing clemency will have a separate meeting with board members. From there, the full board makes its recommendation to the governor.</p>
<p>Tyler said that with Burmingham’s screening set for December, if it is decided to hold further hearings those won’t happen until January at the absolute earliest, likely later.</p>
<p>This is Burmingham’s first application for clemency, Tyler said. While she could not offer any prediction on the outcome of his application, she did observe that “you’re talking about someone who has done nine years on a life sentence, which isn’t much time.”</p>
<p>“A lot of inmates apply,” she added. “Very few get it.”</p>
<hr>
<p>On the night of the rape, Woods said she was driving back late on a dark highway. She had her sunroof opened and her driver’s side window rolled down, and she said she was speeding, trying to get home.</p>
<p>She recalled that she noticed that a blue light was flashing behind her, so she pulled over close to the intersection of Arkansas Highway 31 and Arkansas Highway 38, less than two miles from her house. Woods reached into her purse for her identification and, when she turned around to the window, found a gun pointed at her head and a man in a ski mask standing there.</p>
<p>She said it was determined later that Burmingham probably followed her from the parking lot of the Lonoke Wal-Mart. The Arkansas State Police speculated that he probably stalked her because he drove past her parent’s house and knew where she lived.</p>
<p>“He gave me a button-up shirt to put over my head and then yanked me from my car,” said Woods.</p>
<p>She said she did not scream because she was in so much shock, and she thought he was going to kill her. She said that he wanted her eyes completely covered, and she did not actually see his face until she saw the news report on television when the arrested him.</p>
<p>After he picked her up, he drove her to the Pine Tree Cult area in Cross County to one his father’s rent houses.</p>
<p>“When I was in the back of his car, I made the decision that if he didn’t kill me, I was going remember everything I possibly could,” said Woods.</p>
<p>And she did.</p>
<p>She said the State Police have told her that she is the one who caught Burmingham because of the details that she remembered. She remembered his eyes when she saw him in the ski mask, and she remembered the way he traveled to the house. She also remembered how many steps went up to the house and which way the door opened. She said he put her in a rocking chair when they got inside and he drank what she thought was a beer because she could smell it, and he smoked during that time. When he took her to a bedroom, and she remembered which side of the house it was on, as well.</p>
<p>Once he got her into the bedroom, he placed duct tape on her eyes so tightly that, when he ripped it off about three hours later, it left bruises all around her eyes that clearly showed where the tape had been.</p>
<p>As a result of her experience, Woods said that the adage of blocking off one of the senses to heighten the rest is completely true, because she remembered nearly everything she heard during that attack while her eyes were covered.</p>
<p>Woods said she did not think he was going to rape her until he told her to take off her clothes. At that point she said to him, “Why don’t you just go ahead and kill me?” But Burmingham responded, “If you don’t do what I tell you, I’m going to blow your [expletive] head off.”</p>
<p>Woods said that Burmingham raped her multiple times and sodomized her during this attack. She said she was completely conscious through the whole ordeal and heard everything he did while he was in the house.</p>
<p>In a story printed in Arkansas Times newspaper on Aug. 1, 1997, reporter Judith Gallman said that Woods said she told the police she remembered hearing a radio station from Jonesboro during the drive, which helped investigators narrow down his location. Gallman quoted State Police spokesman Bill Sadler as saying Woods had likely been the most helpful of the blue light rapists’ victims.</p>
<p>After raping her, Woods said, Burmingham dropped her off, face-down, in a field in Cross County and told her to count to 100 and to wait until she heard his car leave. She said she got up after a long time because she was scared to think that he might still be around, and finally walked a mile until she reached a house that had lights on, and a couple answered the door.</p>
<p>“A woman answered and I told her, ‘I’ve been attacked, you don’t have to let me in your house just call the police,’” remembered Woods.</p>
<p>But the couple did let her in and called a neighbor who was a constable; he then called the Augusta Sheriff’s Department. After saying the words “blue light” in her interview, detectives said they knew the attacker they were dealing with.</p>
<p>Woods’ parents were also called, despite her efforts to shield them from her incident.</p>
<p>“My dad thought that I was with my boyfriend and we had been drinking and he thought he was going to have come bail me out of jail,” said Woods.</p>
<p>Her father found out what had happened from the State Police investigator, so Woods did not have to explain it to him. She was then transported to Arkansas Children’s Hospital for medical treatment and tests. Although Burmingham used a condom the first few times he raped Woods, he didn’t to later, which Woods said gave detectives the DNA they needed to identify him.</p>
<p>Throughout the trial, Burmingham and his wife proclaimed his innocence. According to an Associated Press story on the trial, both maintained on the witness stand that they were at home together the night of this attack.</p>
<p>In the years since the attack, Woods completed her degree at Arkansas State University in Beebe and now works as a respiratory therapist. But she still has flashbacks when she sees flashing blue lights.</p>
<p>“I still have a hard time being around men to this day,” she said. “Before they actually caught him, I couldn’t even leave the house.”</p>
</blockquote>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/wow-blue-light-rapist/16026/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/wow-blue-light-rapist/16026/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 24 Sep 2006 10:13:22 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-16026-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/wow-blue-light-rapist/16026.rss">Wow....blue light rapist</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
