<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Food delay and defence help please</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/food-delay-and-defence-help-please/221125</link>
    <description>Hi to start of YES I did search for other thread before I made this and didn&#39;t find anything so don&#39;t tell me to use search button second if you can help me explain correctly not just say something in short and leave cause I will consider it as spam so please give me a tut or something.

DEFENCE -
Well the defence doesn&#39;t work meaning if I&#39;m lvl 99 defence it counts as I&#39;m lvl 1 defence on npc&#39;s didnt test on players yet so the npc&#39;s never hit 0&#39;s mostly can someone explain how I can make it work like having 99 defence makes it harder for the npc to hit?

FOOD DELAY -
Can anyone please tell me how to change the food delay? For example when I click 5 times on 1 shark fast he eats 5 at a time, I want a food delay like real rs.

EDIT: I fixed the food delay but when I&#39;m fighting an npc I can&#39;t eat while in battle can anyone help??

NOTE: I am using project Czar

Thnx for reading/helping.[br][br][size=1]Posted on: July 18, 2008, 04:40:33 AM[/size][hr].</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 18 Jul 2008 12:12:21 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/food-delay-and-defence-help-please/221125.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Food delay and defence help please</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Jjamess123 Jjamess123]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/jjamess123">@Jjamess123</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Hi to start of YES I did search for other thread before I made this and didn’t find anything so don’t tell me to use search button second if you can help me explain correctly not just say something in short and leave cause I will consider it as spam so please give me a tut or something.</p>
<p>DEFENCE -<br>
Well the defence doesn’t work meaning if I’m lvl 99 defence it counts as I’m lvl 1 defence on npc’s didnt test on players yet so the npc’s never hit 0’s mostly can someone explain how I can make it work like having 99 defence makes it harder for the npc to hit?</p>
<p>FOOD DELAY -<br>
Can anyone please tell me how to change the food delay? For example when I click 5 times on 1 shark fast he eats 5 at a time, I want a food delay like real rs.</p>
<p>EDIT: I fixed the food delay but when I’m fighting an npc I can’t eat while in battle can anyone help??</p>
<p>NOTE: I am using project Czar</p>
<p>Thnx for reading/helping.[br][br][size=1]Posted on: July 18, 2008, 04:40:33 AM[/size][hr].</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/food-delay-and-defence-help-please/221125/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/food-delay-and-defence-help-please/221125/1</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 18 Jul 2008 12:12:21 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-221125-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/food-delay-and-defence-help-please/221125.rss">Food delay and defence help please</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
