<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Anyone help me with Port forwarding problem?</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/anyone-help-me-with-port-forwarding-problem/445029</link>
    <description>I&#39;ve tried every tutorial I can find, but none seem to work. I&#39;ve done it the way it says and the way everyone else does it. It just seems to not want to open 43594 port for me. I have a Linksys router, and had over 5 people try to port forward me but have failed. I know this isn&#39;t the place for this post but i&#39;m running out of idea&#39;s and no where else is helping the problem. If anyone thinks they could possibly help, please add me on Skype &quot;bgonzalez31&quot;. Also last night I used Hamachi to port forward, and for a second it said success, we can see your port. But i closed my laptop, then woke up this morning and checked canyouseeme.org and it said &quot;error we cannot see your port.........&quot; Can someone please help. I&#39;m not asking for flamers, so if you can&#39;t or wont help don&#39;t waste your time posting please. I wont pay attention to your post.

Thanks to whoever can help!</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 14 Jun 2012 00:13:03 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/anyone-help-me-with-port-forwarding-problem/445029.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Anyone help me with Port forwarding problem?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Gravity_pk Gravity pk]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/gravity_pk">@Gravity_pk</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>i had the same problem, then i realized it was my proxy’s. if you have a program thats hiding your ip (proxy server) it shows that ip, so when you go to port foward it just like mess’s up and isn’t recognized. i deleted my hidemyip program and other proxy shit i had and it works, lemme know if it helps</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/anyone-help-me-with-port-forwarding-problem/445029/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/anyone-help-me-with-port-forwarding-problem/445029/2</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 14 Jun 2012 00:13:03 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-445029-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/anyone-help-me-with-port-forwarding-problem/445029.rss">Anyone help me with Port forwarding problem?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Anyone help me with Port forwarding problem?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@EndlessKarma EndlessKarma]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/endlesskarma">@EndlessKarma</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I’ve tried every tutorial I can find, but none seem to work. I’ve done it the way it says and the way everyone else does it. It just seems to not want to open 43594 port for me. I have a Linksys router, and had over 5 people try to port forward me but have failed. I know this isn’t the place for this post but i’m running out of idea’s and no where else is helping the problem. If anyone thinks they could possibly help, please add me on Skype “bgonzalez31”. Also last night I used Hamachi to port forward, and for a second it said success, we can see your port. But i closed my laptop, then woke up this morning and checked <a href="http://canyouseeme.org" rel="nofollow noopener">canyouseeme.org</a> and it said “error we cannot see your port…” Can someone please help. I’m not asking for flamers, so if you can’t or wont help don’t waste your time posting please. I wont pay attention to your post.</p>
<p>Thanks to whoever can help!</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/anyone-help-me-with-port-forwarding-problem/445029/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/anyone-help-me-with-port-forwarding-problem/445029/1</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 13 Jun 2012 21:01:16 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-445029-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/anyone-help-me-with-port-forwarding-problem/445029.rss">Anyone help me with Port forwarding problem?</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
