<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>War in rs private servers</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/war-in-rs-private-servers/58196</link>
    <description>Ok, I&#39;m not quite sure if im in the right forum so please tell me if im not. This is what i had in mind. Have a quest that would split the 2 sides of runescape and make them go to war. For ex. If the West side of runescape invaded the east side of runescape, all hell would break loose right? This is where the quest part steps in. You would have the choice to Select a side to ally with (West or East). Then they would have different tasks for you to perform (depending on what side your on) to try to destroy the enemy or make them surrender. Each player would be marked with a certain color cape (which cannot be removed) to show their alliance. This is where Pkers come in :D! Players would come together and get in groups of 20+ and do an all out assault on the enemy every so often to try to weakin there army. Then, if you complete that, You GAIN CONTROL of the side that you conquer, then you own your own empire. Then you take on the East side and take out the kings over there, and then control all of runescape until more forces try to conquer you. 



***Basically Dictatorship (but it would be fun and mayb some things can be changed) 




I MADE THIS IDEA ENTIRELY BY MYSELF. PLEASE DONT STEAL MY IDEA!!! I WOULD LIKE A ADMIN/MOD TO COPY THIS DOWN AND MAKE SURE WHO MADE THE IDEA IF THIS THING EVER PULLS THREW!


Mayb some good coders should make this happen :D


THNX~
JORGAMLET</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2007 05:38:01 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/war-in-rs-private-servers/58196.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>War in rs private servers</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@jorgamlet jorgamlet]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/jorgamlet">@jorgamlet</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Ok, I’m not quite sure if im in the right forum so please tell me if im not. This is what i had in mind. Have a quest that would split the 2 sides of runescape and make them go to war. For ex. If the West side of runescape invaded the east side of runescape, all hell would break loose right? This is where the quest part steps in. You would have the choice to Select a side to ally with (West or East). Then they would have different tasks for you to perform (depending on what side your on) to try to destroy the enemy or make them surrender. Each player would be marked with a certain color cape (which cannot be removed) to show their alliance. This is where Pkers come in :D! Players would come together and get in groups of 20+ and do an all out assault on the enemy every so often to try to weakin there army. Then, if you complete that, You GAIN CONTROL of the side that you conquer, then you own your own empire. Then you take on the East side and take out the kings over there, and then control all of runescape until more forces try to conquer you.</p>
<p>***Basically Dictatorship (but it would be fun and mayb some things can be changed)</p>
<p>I MADE THIS IDEA ENTIRELY BY MYSELF. PLEASE DONT STEAL MY IDEA!!! I WOULD LIKE A ADMIN/MOD TO COPY THIS DOWN AND MAKE SURE WHO MADE THE IDEA IF THIS THING EVER PULLS THREW!</p>
<p>Mayb some good coders should make this happen <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/smiley.png?v=6" title=":smiley:" class="emoji" alt=":smiley:"></p>
<p>THNX~<br>
JORGAMLET</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/war-in-rs-private-servers/58196/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/war-in-rs-private-servers/58196/1</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2007 05:38:01 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-58196-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/war-in-rs-private-servers/58196.rss">War in rs private servers</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
