<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>-Thing-</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/thing/233594</link>
    <description>Well I have been working on a new quest for rs united and it called -thing-, whats it about?

its about a rich guy has had a secret mage guy bugging him at night and he is tired of it. He just made a new hat, you guys know it as a &quot;top hat&quot; So if you help him kill the -thing- he will give you 1 and the right to wear one.

So far I have the whole quest done but its too short. Ineed some ideas as of right now..

you go to ardy and talk to the rich guy, he tells you his story than he gives u a special teletab that teles you to the -thing- but you need a &quot;Rosemary&quot; leaf to attack him. So you get one, tele to him kill him than the quest is done and you recieve a tophat and the right to wear one. The -thing- can hit up to 25 and lowers you attack,str,def,range,and mage if he hits on you. He does like smite except by 8! But the quest takes up to 5 minutes.


I need some ideas to help make it longer and more fun. I will post pics/a vid of it when i am finished until than just post some ideas =)</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 28 Sep 2008 03:10:23 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/thing/233594.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>-Thing-</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@boomer4456 boomer4456]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/boomer4456">@boomer4456</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>what the fu…?[size=30pt]lmao[/size]</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/thing/233594/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/thing/233594/2</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 28 Sep 2008 03:10:23 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-233594-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/thing/233594.rss">-Thing-</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>-Thing-</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@sheeba sheeba]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/sheeba">@sheeba</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Well I have been working on a new quest for rs united and it called -thing-, whats it about?</p>
<p>its about a rich guy has had a secret mage guy bugging him at night and he is tired of it. He just made a new hat, you guys know it as a “top hat” So if you help him kill the -thing- he will give you 1 and the right to wear one.</p>
<p>So far I have the whole quest done but its too short. Ineed some ideas as of right now…</p>
<p>you go to ardy and talk to the rich guy, he tells you his story than he gives u a special teletab that teles you to the -thing- but you need a “Rosemary” leaf to attack him. So you get one, tele to him kill him than the quest is done and you recieve a tophat and the right to wear one. The -thing- can hit up to 25 and lowers you attack,str,def,range,and mage if he hits on you. He does like smite except by 8! But the quest takes up to 5 minutes.</p>
<p>I need some ideas to help make it longer and more fun. I will post pics/a vid of it when i am finished until than just post some ideas =)</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/thing/233594/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/thing/233594/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 28 Sep 2008 03:07:15 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-233594-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/thing/233594.rss">-Thing-</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
