<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Clearing a few things up</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/clearing-a-few-things-up/7444</link>
    <description>[quote=&quot;Pwnd, post:16, topic:491&quot;]Yeah.  He says he&#39;s taught Semaphore, and claims to know every flaw in all of the bots made public.[/quote]

I know I probably should not double post this, but this is something that I&#39;m not going to let sit at the bottom of some obscure thread.

First off, sorry for resurrecting an old post.

This had to be responded to. Let&#39;s make one thing clear:

Pplsuqbawlz knows quite a bit about java. He understands bytecode quite well. He has a theoretical understanding of architecture and design. He could make a career out of programming if he really wanted to.

There is only two things that he has to work on:

[ul][li]Truth is not transient.[/li]
[li]Talking the talk is not the same as walking the walk.[/li][/ul]


The truth is that pplsuqbawlz came to me literally as a result of my first post on kaits. We&#39;ve kept in IM correspondence ever since. I had a system before I met him and when we had met I was in the middle of rewriting my system to avoid more detection. He showed me savion&#39;s deobfuscator and I decided to implement that into the system. It was around this time that he became involved in my system. I would always call it &#39;my&#39; system because I was the one writing it. Truth be told, he wrote about 50 lines of code for the entire 10k line system. He wrote the &#39;Strange Box&#39; solver. I had to make some minor adjustments to it but it worked by-and-large. After that, he wrote a fighting bot and a nature rune bot to run on the framework. I was constantly disappointed at his contribution level. I sent him countless updates and encouraged him to make changes. He made one change. He added a graphical modification hook-set. Later it had to be removed because of hook-finding issues. That is it. That is the truth of how we came to be &#39;partners&#39; in that endeavor. He was constantly looking for more recognition than he deserved and I was constantly expecting him to contribute... something.

During our partnership we had decided that the best route to take would be a bytecode hook driven system. While I waited and waited for him to write an api that I could use to implement into the system, I started my own project on the side that was completely separate from &#39;our&#39; system. My system was completely bytecode based and did not use saev&#39;s deobfuscator any longer. I took some of the transformations that saev found and improved upon them for my own purposes. For example, what he called &#39;opaque eliminator&#39; I had found, though very useful and a great start, needed a great deal of work to make it more robust. I made many changes to his &#39;deobfuscator&#39; and in turn wrote my own package that reverses a vast amount of their obfuscation transformations. I also could not stand the weak &#39;transformMethod&#39; function paradigm so I changed how the transformations were done as well. In essence I came up with a completely different way of deobfuscating the game code/loader code. Pplsuqbawlz claimed that he had written the deobfuscator himself. I happened across saev&#39;s deobfuscator code and it just so happened that the code was a perfect match. Aside from a couple changes in a single class, the rest of the code was exactly the same. So it seems that I am not the first person to fall victim to him taking more credit than he is due.

Once my system was ready to go live, I told him that I was sending him the last update and that I wasn&#39;t going to be updating him anymore. I told him that it was fun working with him but that he had enough to take what we ([b]I[/b]) had written and make a separate system. I had no intentions of ever giving him or telling him about my bytecode system... I had enough of his [i]help[/i].. I felt like I could carry on just fine on my own. However, I had no problem talking to him every so often about design/architecture and various other things. I still liked the guy, he was kinda like a little brother to me.

I may have left out a few details, if so it was completely unintentional. I have to say I am a bit surprised that pplsuqbawlz didn&#39;t correct any implications that [i]he[/i] taught [i]me[/i]. The first time I had heard that rumor, I thought it was completely absurd. Now I see it has propogated even here. It&#39;s gone past absurd to downright funny.

Don&#39;t get me wrong, he&#39;s a great guy and I didn&#39;t mind [i]talking[/i] to him. It was just a pain to try and get him to actually [i]code[/i] something.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 09 Sep 2006 13:00:45 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Community Inside Talk</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/clearing-a-few-things-up/7444.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Clearing a few things up</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Sythe Sythe]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/sythe">@Sythe</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Hi to all,</p>
<p>Semaphore (interesting name for a java coder),  your story has eerily parallels to my own experience with Pplsuqbawlz back when we first developed scarscape. Keep in mind, of course, I did not know java at the time and neither did pplsuqbawlz.</p>
<p>First pplsuqbawlz contacted me about something concerning scar scripting. His basic problem was colour changes, he wanted to know if we could stop them. I remembered a post I had seen on rscheatnet (yes this was a year ago) about bytecode manipulation and decided to look into it.</p>
<p>What followed was a few weeks of what you might call research. Nearly immediately I had the idea of nulling all the Math.random calls by changing their multipliers to 0. That was the basic idea behind scarscape and always has been. We both did independent research into other possible features and how to get the modified client to load. Of course this is all very simple to me now but at the time we didn’t know what we were doing.</p>
<p>Eventually I managed to just reuse their (jagex’s) loader to load the new modified client. Then I wrote an automatic bytecode modifier (unfortunately it was writern in the only language I knew well at the time, visual basic. Meaning it relied on jfparse’s asm and disasm classes which are both slow and rather crappy) . Pplsuqbawlz kept promising to develop a loader and an updater but never managed it until 6 months later. So mine were used.</p>
<p>During the business aspects of scarscape I did most of the managerial work. We had decided to employ cheater’s services in securing hosting (as I had none at the time). We had a successful run, the client lasted about a month then cheater’s host pulled the plug in his server. Which it turns out he had not paid for. So the demise of scarscape, for at least that period was his fault. After closure I tried to reason with pplsuqbawlz to split the profits. Due to an unexpected random event I had managed to lose 75 mill of combined funds on a mule account (I was standing in a bank and changed windows to accept a paypal payment, when I flicked back I was dead. A swarm or something?). Aside from that I had been taking cash payments. Alex (pplsuqbawlz) emptied all the mules without my consent, I ended up with about 40% of the total profits (but at least it was in cash, not gp).</p>
<p>Much later (long after scarscape became free) pplsuqbawlz developed a loader and a bcel updater. At this time I had been studying java and managed to wrap  the loader and updater into a signed applet. I gave Alex full credit for his code.</p>
<p>Yet, despite all this, Alex still claims to this day he developed scarscape… and people believe him.</p>
<p>Finally he contacted me a third time, this time with regard to scarscape 2 which I had independently been developing. For those of you who do not know of this project it was basically a complete scar engine and my own scripting language (sythescript) and its interpreter sitting on top of scarscape 1. I used bytecode hooks to deliver the engine with graphical and textual input. When the project was around 90% complete runescape’s engine was updated and scarscape1’s loader/updater failed to load the new client. At this point I was completely sick of developing anything related to RS and flat out quit. <a href="http://sythe.org/ss2shots" rel="nofollow noopener">http://sythe.org/ss2shots</a> if you don’t believe me.</p>
<p>Before I told pplsuqbawlz to fuck the hell off once and for all he managed to con me out of the ss2 source code. Not that he can do much with it, or that I care, but its another example of what he does. He’s a social engineer, and he’s quite good at it. I don’t recommend anyone treat him as a friend, because he will take advantage of you quite directly.</p>
<p>Not that I really care, but I thought I’d just point out that his basic pattern of play is to find a project, get his barbs in and ride it until its dead. In three words I’d describe him as a “social engineering leech.”</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/clearing-a-few-things-up/7444/13">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/clearing-a-few-things-up/7444/13</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 09 Sep 2006 13:00:45 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-7444-13</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/clearing-a-few-things-up/7444.rss">Clearing a few things up</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Clearing a few things up</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@pplsuqbawlz pplsuqbawlz]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/pplsuqbawlz">@pplsuqbawlz</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p><img src="http://www.themot.org/gallery/d/1422-1/pope_lack_faithstarwars.jpg" alt width="" height=""></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/clearing-a-few-things-up/7444/12">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/clearing-a-few-things-up/7444/12</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 03 Sep 2006 10:19:26 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-7444-12</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/clearing-a-few-things-up/7444.rss">Clearing a few things up</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Clearing a few things up</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Pwnd Pwnd]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/pwnd">@Pwnd</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Lol, wow.  Leaves me speechless.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/clearing-a-few-things-up/7444/11">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/clearing-a-few-things-up/7444/11</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2006 00:52:01 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-7444-11</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/clearing-a-few-things-up/7444.rss">Clearing a few things up</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Clearing a few things up</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@ruler ruler]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/ruler">@ruler</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote no-group" data-post="9" data-topic="7444">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/xerxes/40/5_6259e4fa9dfe0dec282fb0955bb1974c.png" class="avatar"> Xerxes:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Ruler, congrats you are very cool you managed to find a way to say re<span class="bbcode-b"></span>p!!111 omg!1111111</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>THANKS!!!<br>
i was fixing his post. it had the filter in it</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/clearing-a-few-things-up/7444/10">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/clearing-a-few-things-up/7444/10</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2006 19:11:53 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-7444-10</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/clearing-a-few-things-up/7444.rss">Clearing a few things up</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Clearing a few things up</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Xerxes Xerxes]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/xerxes">@Xerxes</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Ruler, congrats you are very cool you managed to find a way to say re<span class="bbcode-b"></span>p!!111 omg!1111111</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/clearing-a-few-things-up/7444/9">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/clearing-a-few-things-up/7444/9</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2006 18:29:34 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-7444-9</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/clearing-a-few-things-up/7444.rss">Clearing a few things up</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Clearing a few things up</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@ruler ruler]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/ruler">@ruler</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote no-group quote-modified" data-post="7" data-topic="7444">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/swift/40/5_6259e4fa9dfe0dec282fb0955bb1974c.png" class="avatar"> Swift:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Haha, that pretty much ruins ppl’s r<span class="bbcode-b"></span>ep</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/clearing-a-few-things-up/7444/8">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/clearing-a-few-things-up/7444/8</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2006 17:51:37 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-7444-8</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/clearing-a-few-things-up/7444.rss">Clearing a few things up</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Clearing a few things up</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Swift Swift]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/swift">@Swift</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Haha, that pretty much ruins ppl’s re<span class="bbcode-b"></span>p.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/clearing-a-few-things-up/7444/7">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/clearing-a-few-things-up/7444/7</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2006 14:20:35 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-7444-7</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/clearing-a-few-things-up/7444.rss">Clearing a few things up</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Clearing a few things up</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@sdouble sdouble]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/sdouble">@sdouble</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>It’s been said in the past that psb taught semaphore everything he knows.  Evidentally, semaphore caught wind of this rumor and decided to set some things straight.</p>
<p>Edit, corected myself.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/clearing-a-few-things-up/7444/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/clearing-a-few-things-up/7444/6</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2006 14:10:29 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-7444-6</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/clearing-a-few-things-up/7444.rss">Clearing a few things up</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Clearing a few things up</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@USMC USMC]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/usmc">@USMC</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>wow, that was a long read, and best of all<br>
i dont know what the heck your going on about? / clearing up?! <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=9" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/clearing-a-few-things-up/7444/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/clearing-a-few-things-up/7444/5</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2006 13:37:02 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-7444-5</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/clearing-a-few-things-up/7444.rss">Clearing a few things up</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Clearing a few things up</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Freddy1990 Freddy1990]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/freddy1990">@Freddy1990</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Heh, yeah, that clears some things up <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=9" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"><br>
It rly is a pain to get anything out of him <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=9" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/clearing-a-few-things-up/7444/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/clearing-a-few-things-up/7444/4</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2006 12:32:41 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-7444-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/clearing-a-few-things-up/7444.rss">Clearing a few things up</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Clearing a few things up</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@ruler ruler]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/ruler">@ruler</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Sythe is not to thrilled with his activity.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/clearing-a-few-things-up/7444/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/clearing-a-few-things-up/7444/3</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2006 00:41:11 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-7444-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/clearing-a-few-things-up/7444.rss">Clearing a few things up</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Clearing a few things up</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Bebemycat2 Bebe]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/bebemycat2">@Bebemycat2</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Wow…</p>
<p>Thanks for clearing that up <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=9" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/clearing-a-few-things-up/7444/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/clearing-a-few-things-up/7444/2</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2006 00:23:36 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-7444-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/clearing-a-few-things-up/7444.rss">Clearing a few things up</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Clearing a few things up</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@semaphore semaphore]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/semaphore">@semaphore</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote no-group quote-modified" data-post="16" data-topic="491">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/pwnd/40/5_6259e4fa9dfe0dec282fb0955bb1974c.png" class="avatar"><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-bot-proposal-no-need-for-updating/491/16">New Bot Proposal (no need for updating)</a>
</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Yeah.  He says he’s taught Semaphore, and claims to know every flaw in all of the bots made public.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I know I probably should not double post this, but this is something that I’m not going to let sit at the bottom of some obscure thread.</p>
<p>First off, sorry for resurrecting an old post.</p>
<p>This had to be responded to. Let’s make one thing clear:</p>
<p>Pplsuqbawlz knows quite a bit about java. He understands bytecode quite well. He has a theoretical understanding of architecture and design. He could make a career out of programming if he really wanted to.</p>
<p>There is only two things that he has to work on:</p>
<p>[ul][li]Truth is not transient.[/li]<br>
[li]Talking the talk is not the same as walking the walk.[/li][/ul]</p>
<p>The truth is that pplsuqbawlz came to me literally as a result of my first post on kaits. We’ve kept in IM correspondence ever since. I had a system before I met him and when we had met I was in the middle of rewriting my system to avoid more detection. He showed me savion’s deobfuscator and I decided to implement that into the system. It was around this time that he became involved in my system. I would always call it ‘my’ system because I was the one writing it. Truth be told, he wrote about 50 lines of code for the entire 10k line system. He wrote the ‘Strange Box’ solver. I had to make some minor adjustments to it but it worked by-and-large. After that, he wrote a fighting bot and a nature rune bot to run on the framework. I was constantly disappointed at his contribution level. I sent him countless updates and encouraged him to make changes. He made one change. He added a graphical modification hook-set. Later it had to be removed because of hook-finding issues. That is it. That is the truth of how we came to be ‘partners’ in that endeavor. He was constantly looking for more recognition than he deserved and I was constantly expecting him to contribute… something.</p>
<p>During our partnership we had decided that the best route to take would be a bytecode hook driven system. While I waited and waited for him to write an api that I could use to implement into the system, I started my own project on the side that was completely separate from ‘our’ system. My system was completely bytecode based and did not use saev’s deobfuscator any longer. I took some of the transformations that saev found and improved upon them for my own purposes. For example, what he called ‘opaque eliminator’ I had found, though very useful and a great start, needed a great deal of work to make it more robust. I made many changes to his ‘deobfuscator’ and in turn wrote my own package that reverses a vast amount of their obfuscation transformations. I also could not stand the weak ‘transformMethod’ function paradigm so I changed how the transformations were done as well. In essence I came up with a completely different way of deobfuscating the game code/loader code. Pplsuqbawlz claimed that he had written the deobfuscator himself. I happened across saev’s deobfuscator code and it just so happened that the code was a perfect match. Aside from a couple changes in a single class, the rest of the code was exactly the same. So it seems that I am not the first person to fall victim to him taking more credit than he is due.</p>
<p>Once my system was ready to go live, I told him that I was sending him the last update and that I wasn’t going to be updating him anymore. I told him that it was fun working with him but that he had enough to take what we (<span class="bbcode-b">I</span>) had written and make a separate system. I had no intentions of ever giving him or telling him about my bytecode system… I had enough of his <span class="bbcode-i">help</span>… I felt like I could carry on just fine on my own. However, I had no problem talking to him every so often about design/architecture and various other things. I still liked the guy, he was kinda like a little brother to me.</p>
<p>I may have left out a few details, if so it was completely unintentional. I have to say I am a bit surprised that pplsuqbawlz didn’t correct any implications that <span class="bbcode-i">he</span> taught <span class="bbcode-i">me</span>. The first time I had heard that rumor, I thought it was completely absurd. Now I see it has propogated even here. It’s gone past absurd to downright funny.</p>
<p>Don’t get me wrong, he’s a great guy and I didn’t mind <span class="bbcode-i">talking</span> to him. It was just a pain to try and get him to actually <span class="bbcode-i">code</span> something.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/clearing-a-few-things-up/7444/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/clearing-a-few-things-up/7444/1</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2006 00:11:49 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-7444-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/clearing-a-few-things-up/7444.rss">Clearing a few things up</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
