<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Samuel Adams (Not the beer)</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/samuel-adams-not-the-beer/55958</link>
    <description>I always come to this site for help with my homework, since alot of people here are intelligent, so thats why I&#39;ve been asking for alot of help here lately.
Here&#39;s what I need help with now;
~~~---Samuel Adams---~~~
-What were some obstacles for this person, but did not deter him?
-Did this person experiance any type of tragedy in their life that made them want to participate in any sort of war or social movement?

-Choose one character trait that you feel best describes this person and give one example from their life to support your choice. (fortuitous, courageous, motivator, encourager, just, fair, honest, diligent)
-Identify at least one thing that you find admirable/remarkable about this person&#39;s life.

-Explain how you think this person&#39;s life experiances eventually influenced their choices in life regarding jobs held or participation in social movements.
-Did this person do things that caused people to dislike or resent him of that caused people to find fault with this person?

If you know atleast one thing, it would be a major help!
~~~---Thanks---~~~
~~~---NinjaSoD---~~~</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2007 07:03:48 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>General Discussion</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/samuel-adams-not-the-beer/55958.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Samuel Adams (Not the beer)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@ninjasod ninjasod]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/ninjasod">@ninjasod</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>…=\</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/samuel-adams-not-the-beer/55958/14">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/samuel-adams-not-the-beer/55958/14</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2007 07:03:48 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-55958-14</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/samuel-adams-not-the-beer/55958.rss">Samuel Adams (Not the beer)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Samuel Adams (Not the beer)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@0wn3d_n00b Ooo Java]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/0wn3d_n00b">@0wn3d_n00b</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“Mopman, post:12, topic:55958”][quote author=ninjasod link=topic=79451.msg883927#msg883927 date=1171107847]</p>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p>I always come to this site for help with my homework, since alot of people here are intelligent, so thats why I’ve been asking for alot of help here lately.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>a lot of intelligent people? bullshit, theres only one, which would be bobdole.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>So, I’m guessing that none of the people that are in college coming on this website, people passed college, and the <span class="bbcode-b">people that are making private servers</span> are intelligent?<br>
[/quote]</p>
<p>Haha![/quote]<br>
100% Agree! You Beat Me To It MopMan!</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/samuel-adams-not-the-beer/55958/13">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/samuel-adams-not-the-beer/55958/13</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2007 21:55:15 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-55958-13</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/samuel-adams-not-the-beer/55958.rss">Samuel Adams (Not the beer)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Samuel Adams (Not the beer)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Mopman Mopman]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/mopman">@Mopman</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“ninjasod, post:10, topic:55958”][quote author=lawl link=topic=79451.msg883714#msg883714 date=1171103434]</p>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p>I always come to this site for help with my homework, since alot of people here are intelligent, so thats why I’ve been asking for alot of help here lately.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>a lot of intelligent people? bullshit, theres only one, which would be bobdole.<br>
[/quote]<br>
So, I’m guessing that none of the people that are in college coming on this website, people passed college, and the <span class="bbcode-b">people that are making private servers</span> are intelligent?[/quote]</p>
<p>Haha!</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/samuel-adams-not-the-beer/55958/12">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/samuel-adams-not-the-beer/55958/12</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 11 Feb 2007 18:11:42 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-55958-12</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/samuel-adams-not-the-beer/55958.rss">Samuel Adams (Not the beer)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Samuel Adams (Not the beer)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@93dcthugs93 93dcthugs93]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/93dcthugs93">@93dcthugs93</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Oh don’t bother with lawl, he’s the local idiot.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/samuel-adams-not-the-beer/55958/11">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/samuel-adams-not-the-beer/55958/11</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 10 Feb 2007 20:15:38 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-55958-11</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/samuel-adams-not-the-beer/55958.rss">Samuel Adams (Not the beer)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Samuel Adams (Not the beer)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@ninjasod ninjasod]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/ninjasod">@ninjasod</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“lawl, post:1, topic:56876”][quote author=ninjasod link=topic=79451.msg874635#msg874635 date=1170897884]<br>
I always come to this site for help with my homework, since alot of people here are intelligent, so thats why I’ve been asking for alot of help here lately.<br>
[/quote]<br>
a lot of intelligent people? bullshit, theres only one, which would be bobdole.[/quote]<br>
So, I’m guessing that none of the people that are in college coming on this website, people passed college, and the people that are making private servers are intelligent?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/samuel-adams-not-the-beer/55958/10">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/samuel-adams-not-the-beer/55958/10</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 10 Feb 2007 11:44:07 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-55958-10</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/samuel-adams-not-the-beer/55958.rss">Samuel Adams (Not the beer)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Samuel Adams (Not the beer)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@ninjasod ninjasod]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/ninjasod">@ninjasod</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>It’s okay, class is almost over.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/samuel-adams-not-the-beer/55958/9">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/samuel-adams-not-the-beer/55958/9</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2007 01:55:22 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-55958-9</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/samuel-adams-not-the-beer/55958.rss">Samuel Adams (Not the beer)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Samuel Adams (Not the beer)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@93dcthugs93 93dcthugs93]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/93dcthugs93">@93dcthugs93</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Thanks ninja <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=6" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"> I can finish the rest if you want.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/samuel-adams-not-the-beer/55958/8">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/samuel-adams-not-the-beer/55958/8</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2007 01:50:09 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-55958-8</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/samuel-adams-not-the-beer/55958.rss">Samuel Adams (Not the beer)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Samuel Adams (Not the beer)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@ninjasod ninjasod]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/ninjasod">@ninjasod</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Thanks[br][size=1]Posted on: February 07, 2007, 03:32:24 PM[/size][hr]I’ve found a couple from here, but theres not alot of info. <a href="http://www.americanrevwar.homestead.com/files/ADAMS2.HTM%5Bbr%5D%5Bsize=1%5DPosted" rel="nofollow noopener">http://www.americanrevwar.homestead.com/files/ADAMS2.HTM[br][size=1]Posted</a> on: February 07, 2007, 03:37:53 PM[/size][hr]Thanks, thats enough for today, I’m ahead of everyone in the class by now.[br][size=1]Posted on: February 07, 2007, 03:48:25 PM[/size][hr][offtopic]<br>
You really deserve you’re rank, you help out alot of people <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=6" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"><br>
[/offtopic]<br>
=\</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/samuel-adams-not-the-beer/55958/7">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/samuel-adams-not-the-beer/55958/7</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2007 01:49:03 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-55958-7</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/samuel-adams-not-the-beer/55958.rss">Samuel Adams (Not the beer)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Samuel Adams (Not the beer)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@93dcthugs93 93dcthugs93]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/93dcthugs93">@93dcthugs93</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I’ll try finding the answers.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">-What kind of work did this person do for the majority of their life?</span></p>
<p>After he completed his college education, Adams and his father, Old Samuel Adams began a partnership in a brewery. He lost most of his inheritance by poor business management.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Turning his attention to politics,</span> Adams wrote political essays to the Independent Advertiser newspaper and joined a political club, the “Whipping Post Club,” as well as Boston’s South End Caucus, which was a powerful force in the selection of candidates for elective office. He served as tax collector of Boston 1756 through 1764, and used non-collection of taxes as a political bargaining chip. By 1764-65 he was a leader in Boston’s town meetings, drafting protests against the Stamp Act that protested British efforts to tax the colonists and called for a spirited defense of Americans’ “invaluable Rights &amp; Liberties.” Over the next decade he became an increasingly dominant leader of the town meeting. He repeatedly insisted on the “inherent and unalienable rights” of the people (Writings, vol. 1, pp. 25-26), a theme that became a core element of republicanism.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Conclusion</span>: He was in politics most of his life</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">-Did this person work to improve conditions for others? (give examples)</span></p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Samuel Adams is best remembered for helping organize the Boston Tea Party of December 16, 1773, in response to the Tea Act — a tax law passed in London that was simply an increase in the taxes on tea paid by American colonists.</span> As British tea-ships sat in Boston Harbor waiting for payment of the import tax, <span class="bbcode-b">Samuel Adams energized a large crowd that was gathered at the port and sent several men to dump all of the tea from the three ships into the Boston Harbor to the delight of the assembled spectators on shore.</span> In response to this escapade, Parliament passed the “Intolerable Acts,” which called for the revocation of the colonial charter of Massachusetts and the closing of the ports of Boston. The angry reaction from all the colonies was to expedite the opening of a Continental Congress, and when the Massachusetts legislature met in Salem on June 17, 1774, Adams locked the doors and made a motion for the formation of a colonial delegation to attend the Congress. A loyalist member, faking illness, was excused from the assembly and immediately went to the governor, who issued a writ for the legislature’s dissolution; however, when the legislator returned to find a locked door, he could do nothing.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Adams was one of the major proponents of the Suffolk Resolves, drafted in response to the Intolerable Acts, and adopted in September 1774. Whose “spirited” resolves called for disobedience to the Coercive Acts, endorsed military preparations for defense, and called for the meeting of an extralegal provincial congress.</span> Adams opposed a compromise offered by Joseph Galloway and advocated boycotts of British imports through the continental associations.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Conclusion</span>: Yes - He is best remembered for helping organize the Boston Tea party.  He also devised a system of Committees of Correspondence which was a committee that recorded the British activities, where the towns of Massachusetts would consult with each other concerning political matters via messages. He signed the bill of rights &amp; drafted the first Massachusetts state constitution in 1779, and the second one in 1788.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">-What were some obstacles for this person, but did not deter him?</span></p>
<p>This British troop presence in Boston, <span class="bbcode-b">aggravated by protest activities such as Adams’ formation of the Non-Importation Association, led to the Boston Massacre (a term coined by Adams) two years later.</span> After the incident Adams chaired a town meeting which formed a petition, presented to acting governor Thomas Hutchinson, demanding the removal of two British regiments from Boston proper. Hutchinson at first claimed no responsibility for the matter, owing to his temporary status as governor, but stated he would be willing to move one regiment; the meeting was re-convened and Adams successfully urged the crowd of over 5,000 present to stand firm on the terms: “Both regiments or none!” Fearing open warfare, Hutchinson had both regiments removed to Castle William, an old fort on an island in Boston Harbor. These regiments would thereafter be known in the British Parliament as “The Sam Adams Regiments.”</p>
<p>In 1772, after a British declaration that judges should be paid by the Crown rather than by the colonial legislatures, a demand from the people of Boston for a special session of the legislature to reconsider this matter was refused by Hutchinson. It was at this point Adams devised a system of Committees of Correspondence which was a committee that recorded the British activities, where the towns of Massachusetts would consult with each other concerning political matters via messages. Such a scheme was still technically legal under British law, but led to a de facto colonial legislative body. This system was adopted by each of the Thirteen Colonies, creating the Continental Congress.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Conclusion</span>: I’m getting a head ache <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/frowning.png?v=6" title=":frowning:" class="emoji" alt=":frowning:"> Find some stuff in that.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">-Did this person experiance any type of tragedy in their life that made them want to participate in any sort of war or social movement?<br>
</span></p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Conclusion</span>:No</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">-Choose one character trait that you feel best describes this person and give one example from their life to support your choice. (fortuitous, courageous, motivator, encourager, just, fair, honest, diligent)</span></p>
<p>At the time of the drafting of the United States Constitution, Adams was considered an anti-federalist, but more moderate than others of that political stripe. His contemporaries nicknamed him “the last Puritan” for his views; in 1788 he would write in his diary regarding the federalist and anti-federalist factions, “Neither Interest, I fear, display that Sobriety of Manners, Temperance, or Frugality—among other manly Virtues—which once were the Glory and Strength of our Christian Sparta on the Bay…”. He finally came in on the side of ratification, with the stipulation that a bill of rights be added. Additionally, Adams was a member of the conventions that drafted the first Massachusetts state constitution in 1779, and the second one in 1788.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Conclusion</span>: Fair - He believed in equal rights for everybody and tried his hardest to make sure his community was doing well.</p>
<p>Idk you can edit that if you want ^^</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/samuel-adams-not-the-beer/55958/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/samuel-adams-not-the-beer/55958/6</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2007 01:30:45 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-55958-6</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/samuel-adams-not-the-beer/55958.rss">Samuel Adams (Not the beer)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Samuel Adams (Not the beer)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@ninjasod ninjasod]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/ninjasod">@ninjasod</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>It would help if you could try to find them, but if you cant I can always do it from home.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/samuel-adams-not-the-beer/55958/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/samuel-adams-not-the-beer/55958/5</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2007 01:29:17 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-55958-5</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/samuel-adams-not-the-beer/55958.rss">Samuel Adams (Not the beer)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Samuel Adams (Not the beer)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@93dcthugs93 93dcthugs93]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/93dcthugs93">@93dcthugs93</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Can I post the Wiki here or do you want me to try finding the answers?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/samuel-adams-not-the-beer/55958/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/samuel-adams-not-the-beer/55958/4</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2007 01:28:41 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-55958-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/samuel-adams-not-the-beer/55958.rss">Samuel Adams (Not the beer)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Samuel Adams (Not the beer)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@ninjasod ninjasod]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/ninjasod">@ninjasod</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I’m in school right now, it’s blocked.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/samuel-adams-not-the-beer/55958/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/samuel-adams-not-the-beer/55958/3</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2007 01:27:15 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-55958-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/samuel-adams-not-the-beer/55958.rss">Samuel Adams (Not the beer)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Samuel Adams (Not the beer)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@93dcthugs93 93dcthugs93]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/93dcthugs93">@93dcthugs93</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Heres a Wiki on him. See if you can find answers here:</p>
<aside class="onebox wikipedia">
  <header class="source">
      <a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Samuel_Adams" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">en.wikipedia.org</a>
  </header>
  <article class="onebox-body">
    <div class="aspect-image" style="--aspect-ratio:220/285;"><img src="//upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/thumb/8/89/J_S_Copley_-_Samuel_Adams.jpg/220px-J_S_Copley_-_Samuel_Adams.jpg" class="thumbnail"></div>

<h3><a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Samuel_Adams" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Samuel Adams</a></h3>

<p>
 Samuel Adams (September 27 [O.S. September 16] 1722 – October 2, 1803) was an American statesman, political philosopher, and one of the Founding Fathers of the United States. He was a politician in colonial Massachusetts, a leader of the movement that became the American Revolution, and one of the architects of the principles of American republicanism that shaped the political culture of the United States. He was a second cousin to his fellow Founding Father, President John Adams.
 Adams was bo...</p>

  </article>
  <div class="onebox-metadata">
    
    
  </div>
  <div style="clear: both"></div>
</aside>

          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/samuel-adams-not-the-beer/55958/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/samuel-adams-not-the-beer/55958/2</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2007 01:26:32 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-55958-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/samuel-adams-not-the-beer/55958.rss">Samuel Adams (Not the beer)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Samuel Adams (Not the beer)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@ninjasod ninjasod]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/ninjasod">@ninjasod</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I always come to this site for help with my homework, since alot of people here are intelligent, so thats why I’ve been asking for alot of help here lately.<br>
Here’s what I need help with now;<br>
~<s>—Samuel Adams—</s>~<br>
-What were some obstacles for this person, but did not deter him?<br>
-Did this person experiance any type of tragedy in their life that made them want to participate in any sort of war or social movement?</p>
<p>-Choose one character trait that you feel best describes this person and give one example from their life to support your choice. (fortuitous, courageous, motivator, encourager, just, fair, honest, diligent)<br>
-Identify at least one thing that you find admirable/remarkable about this person’s life.</p>
<p>-Explain how you think this person’s life experiances eventually influenced their choices in life regarding jobs held or participation in social movements.<br>
-Did this person do things that caused people to dislike or resent him of that caused people to find fault with this person?</p>
<p>If you know atleast one thing, it would be a major help!<br>
~<s>—Thanks—</s>~<br>
~<s>—NinjaSoD—</s>~</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/samuel-adams-not-the-beer/55958/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/samuel-adams-not-the-beer/55958/1</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2007 01:24:44 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-55958-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/samuel-adams-not-the-beer/55958.rss">Samuel Adams (Not the beer)</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
