<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>[IMPORTANT!] How to Stop/Avoid Staff Abuse</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/important-how-to-stop-avoid-staff-abuse/455838</link>
    <description>I find this very important considering that most staff members that you hire, even if they seem loyal, all have a price and can somehow be broken down into rage quitting for any odd reason. This has happened a lot on ShadowPk, I learnt the hard way how to avoid it.

First off, only promote people you trust. I made sure to only promote active players that seemed very trustworthy and don&#39;t break rules, yet a lot of them still rage quitted if one of their friends got banned(for good reason) or any other things that can make them mad. But I was wrong a lot of those times. My old co owner, he was more active than I was, he had more posts on my own forums, he helped my players more than anyone could possible imagine, he was the best help I&#39;ve ever had, yet when I banned his friend(his friend kept raging me), he ragequitted. So you need to make sure they aren&#39;t immature.

Basically, don&#39;t hire staff members before you do some under cover work to find out if they are mature enough for the job. A mature staff member: They tell you why they are punishing you, punish you, then leave it at that. They don&#39;t cuss at the person, they don&#39;t argue with them, etc.

Secondly, if you have a secure server that can&#39;t get pwnd in the face by a hacker, then that means that a simple mute/ipmute will work fine in punishing rule breakers, therefor to avoid people ragebanning, you should only allow yourself to ban people. A lot of people will say this is stupid, but if your server can&#39;t be hacked/duped on, then it doesn&#39;t matter.

Thirdly, If you use Project Insanity, I recommend using my commands( I also have some cool stuff in there if u wanna keep those too )

I redid pretty much all of my commands to avoid power abuse. Here&#39;s the code
http://pastebin.com/LPUurWew

If you disagree with me on any of my suggestions, just go and start up a server for as long as mine has been up and you see how hard it is to keep a pristine record of no staff ever betraying you, trust me, it&#39;s impossible.

I hope this helps you in advancing your RSPS server.

-Cloudnine
:)</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 26 Aug 2012 06:27:04 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/important-how-to-stop-avoid-staff-abuse/455838.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>[IMPORTANT!] How to Stop/Avoid Staff Abuse</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Ix_Soulcist_xI Soulcist]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/ix_soulcist_xi">@Ix_Soulcist_xI</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Yes, redundant indeed I would call this. I would hope that people have the common sense when choosing their staff, however, people as stated above, “overlook” such matters, and it becomes a hideous disaster in the end if not taken care of.</p>
<p>I have a system of how I promote and maintain the staff team, something that I have used for two years so far, it’s been working out quite well for me and the staff in which I promote are quite the staff team when respecting the authority, and the community at all times.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/important-how-to-stop-avoid-staff-abuse/455838/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/important-how-to-stop-avoid-staff-abuse/455838/6</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 26 Aug 2012 06:27:04 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-455838-6</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/important-how-to-stop-avoid-staff-abuse/455838.rss">[IMPORTANT!] How to Stop/Avoid Staff Abuse</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[IMPORTANT!] How to Stop/Avoid Staff Abuse</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@The_Reaper_X The Reaper X]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/the_reaper_x">@The_Reaper_X</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Interesting. Somewhat redundant, however I suppose I could see a lot of people overlooking these small appendages when it comes to choosing your staff. Half of your success depends on who you’re working with, it’s always best to make sure they have the same interest as you.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/important-how-to-stop-avoid-staff-abuse/455838/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/important-how-to-stop-avoid-staff-abuse/455838/5</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 26 Aug 2012 06:19:03 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-455838-5</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/important-how-to-stop-avoid-staff-abuse/455838.rss">[IMPORTANT!] How to Stop/Avoid Staff Abuse</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[IMPORTANT!] How to Stop/Avoid Staff Abuse</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Ruby_Forums_Coder Ruby]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/ruby_forums_coder">@Ruby_Forums_Coder</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“Loveandpower, post:3, topic:455838”]I have a better solution:</p>
<p>-moderators or “player support” as I call them can only do a  temporary mute. Once I go into the vps I can view all temporary mutes. I can just change one number if I find the log that is provided ( very detailed log of all trades, chats, etc in a certain time period ) shows not enough proof then I will contact the moderator. if they cannot provide better evidence of the reason for the mute, the moderator gets a “strike” and the player gets unmuted. If I am in a good mood I may credit them with a couple of points to keep them happy ( not enough to buy anything of course )</p>
<p>I don’t have administrators. I have me, myself, and I. I do NOT trust anyone with my information when it comes to gaming in any type of server rsps or non-rsps. related. This means only I could spawn etc.[/quote]</p>
<p>I do mostly this, all moderators except a precious few can temp mute/ban. If something serious happens, they contact the fully powered mods.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/important-how-to-stop-avoid-staff-abuse/455838/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/important-how-to-stop-avoid-staff-abuse/455838/4</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 25 Aug 2012 09:26:47 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-455838-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/important-how-to-stop-avoid-staff-abuse/455838.rss">[IMPORTANT!] How to Stop/Avoid Staff Abuse</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[IMPORTANT!] How to Stop/Avoid Staff Abuse</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Loveandpower Loveandpower]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/loveandpower">@Loveandpower</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I have a better solution:</p>
<p>-moderators or “player support” as I call them can only do a  temporary mute. Once I go into the vps I can view all temporary mutes. I can just change one number if I find the log that is provided ( very detailed log of all trades, chats, etc in a certain time period ) shows not enough proof then I will contact the moderator. if they cannot provide better evidence of the reason for the mute, the moderator gets a “strike” and the player gets unmuted. If I am in a good mood I may credit them with a couple of points to keep them happy ( not enough to buy anything of course )</p>
<p>I don’t have administrators. I have me, myself, and I. I do NOT trust anyone with my information when it comes to gaming in any type of server rsps or non-rsps. related. This means only I could spawn etc.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/important-how-to-stop-avoid-staff-abuse/455838/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/important-how-to-stop-avoid-staff-abuse/455838/3</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 25 Aug 2012 02:13:02 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-455838-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/important-how-to-stop-avoid-staff-abuse/455838.rss">[IMPORTANT!] How to Stop/Avoid Staff Abuse</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[IMPORTANT!] How to Stop/Avoid Staff Abuse</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@CodeBest CodeBest]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/codebest">@CodeBest</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Most of this stuff is pretty common sense.</p>
<p>Took a couple of the commands though. Thanks.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/important-how-to-stop-avoid-staff-abuse/455838/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/important-how-to-stop-avoid-staff-abuse/455838/2</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 25 Aug 2012 01:40:14 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-455838-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/important-how-to-stop-avoid-staff-abuse/455838.rss">[IMPORTANT!] How to Stop/Avoid Staff Abuse</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[IMPORTANT!] How to Stop/Avoid Staff Abuse</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@belhelmiel belhelmiel]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/belhelmiel">@belhelmiel</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I find this very important considering that most staff members that you hire, even if they seem loyal, all have a price and can somehow be broken down into rage quitting for any odd reason. This has happened a lot on ShadowPk, I learnt the hard way how to avoid it.</p>
<p>First off, only promote people you trust. I made sure to only promote active players that seemed very trustworthy and don’t break rules, yet a lot of them still rage quitted if one of their friends got banned(for good reason) or any other things that can make them mad. But I was wrong a lot of those times. My old co owner, he was more active than I was, he had more posts on my own forums, he helped my players more than anyone could possible imagine, he was the best help I’ve ever had, yet when I banned his friend(his friend kept raging me), he ragequitted. So you need to make sure they aren’t immature.</p>
<p>Basically, don’t hire staff members before you do some under cover work to find out if they are mature enough for the job. A mature staff member: They tell you why they are punishing you, punish you, then leave it at that. They don’t cuss at the person, they don’t argue with them, etc.</p>
<p>Secondly, if you have a secure server that can’t get pwnd in the face by a hacker, then that means that a simple mute/ipmute will work fine in punishing rule breakers, therefor to avoid people ragebanning, you should only allow yourself to ban people. A lot of people will say this is stupid, but if your server can’t be hacked/duped on, then it doesn’t matter.</p>
<p>Thirdly, If you use Project Insanity, I recommend using my commands( I also have some cool stuff in there if u wanna keep those too )</p>
<p>I redid pretty much all of my commands to avoid power abuse. Here’s the code<br>
<a href="http://pastebin.com/LPUurWew" class="onebox" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">http://pastebin.com/LPUurWew</a></p>
<p>If you disagree with me on any of my suggestions, just go and start up a server for as long as mine has been up and you see how hard it is to keep a pristine record of no staff ever betraying you, trust me, it’s impossible.</p>
<p>I hope this helps you in advancing your RSPS server.</p>
<p>-Cloudnine<br>
<img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=5" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/important-how-to-stop-avoid-staff-abuse/455838/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/important-how-to-stop-avoid-staff-abuse/455838/1</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 24 Aug 2012 23:46:32 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-455838-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/important-how-to-stop-avoid-staff-abuse/455838.rss">[IMPORTANT!] How to Stop/Avoid Staff Abuse</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
