<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Can&#39;t find Main, Red X</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/cant-find-main-red-x/95138</link>
    <description>Edit: I&#39;m currently loading MoparS and it looks like it&#39;s going to run... I didn&#39;t have the most updated version of Java I guess.... My bad srry, it was an easy fix though luckly. Hope it runs now



So I tried running moparscape off the site, it shows the java icon for a bit, but then it switchs to a red X.  I am not sure what is causing this, going to see if there&#39;s an update right now that I need but I don&#39;t belive so.  I would like to play with other people and I belive this is where most play.

My other bigger problem is when I downloaded moparscape to run my own server it says it can&#39;t find the main class.  I run the .jar and .bat file types but nether of them work.  So if someone can please explain to me how to find the main class, or if I installed them wrong and how to fix it that would be great.  See I would also like to host a server so my buds can play, so this is important.  

Any help in ether of this problems would be greatly appreciated. Tyvm in advance. :)</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 16 May 2007 02:49:47 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/cant-find-main-red-x/95138.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Can&#39;t find Main, Red X</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@elfavice elfavice]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/elfavice">@elfavice</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Edit: I’m currently loading MoparS and it looks like it’s going to run… I didn’t have the most updated version of Java I guess… My bad srry, it was an easy fix though luckly. Hope it runs now</p>
<p>So I tried running moparscape off the site, it shows the java icon for a bit, but then it switchs to a red X.  I am not sure what is causing this, going to see if there’s an update right now that I need but I don’t belive so.  I would like to play with other people and I belive this is where most play.</p>
<p>My other bigger problem is when I downloaded moparscape to run my own server it says it can’t find the main class.  I run the .jar and .bat file types but nether of them work.  So if someone can please explain to me how to find the main class, or if I installed them wrong and how to fix it that would be great.  See I would also like to host a server so my buds can play, so this is important.</p>
<p>Any help in ether of this problems would be greatly appreciated. Tyvm in advance. <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=6" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/cant-find-main-red-x/95138/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/cant-find-main-red-x/95138/1</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 16 May 2007 02:49:47 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-95138-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/cant-find-main-red-x/95138.rss">Can&#39;t find Main, Red X</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
