<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>To hell and back</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/to-hell-and-back/107463</link>
    <description>Well, first of I would like to say the private server community is turning into crap... Everyone one thinks they can code because they copy and paste tutorials into a server source that somebody else built for them. Well News flash thats not coding, people wonder why there servers lagg so much and or crash all the time... its because you are all putting unstable crap coding into your servers before perfecting what is already there...


In my opinion i think someone or a group of someones (im working on one myself) should create a source that even if it has little or no features has little or no glitches.. what im saying is...

[code]
No massing easly fixed but most servers have it...
No Hp Glitches (i.e monsters hp bar refills if there hp is over 255..)
All Player and Npc Emotes(Attacking, Defending, Dieing,)
Fully Working Range (Perfectly timed and working projectiles)
Fully Working Mage (all proper effects, Projectiles, Graphics, and Requirments all perfectly timed)
Base for all skills with a basic xp rate so skills all lvl up at same rate...(players don&#39;t get bored as quick)
Fully Working Prayer (With all glitched ironed out so nobody gets an unfair advantage
[/code]
This is only a small list of the many things that need to be fixed in Rs2 Servers

Think about it people the above list is only small but with those several things fixed private servers would be much more advanced then they already are..




It&#39;s things like this that even though they may not be simple will bring private servers out of the hell there in and back to the real world

The question is why add Quests, and Mini Games when your server is flawed in 150 million ways? Private servers will never be perfect but with some of the talent around here they can be much, much, better.

Then people can start to work on there own Quests, and Mini games. 

[b]Second Note:[/b]

Don&#39;t add every single code into client.java...
For starters this will cause lots and lots of lag...
secondly it makes your servers coding look horrable try being a bit more neat people

Add Handlers!! people your server can have so much less lagg if you add things properly dont cram it all into one file...

Thats All for now hope somebody hears me</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 08 Jun 2007 04:05:30 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/to-hell-and-back/107463.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>To hell and back</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@anarchy anarchy]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/anarchy">@anarchy</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>nothing is impossable, just because you cant do it does not mean others can not</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/to-hell-and-back/107463/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/to-hell-and-back/107463/3</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Jun 2007 04:05:30 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-107463-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/to-hell-and-back/107463.rss">To hell and back</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>To hell and back</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Nightz Nightz]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/nightz">@Nightz</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Impossible…unless you were moparisthebest lol</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/to-hell-and-back/107463/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/to-hell-and-back/107463/2</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Jun 2007 04:03:47 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-107463-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/to-hell-and-back/107463.rss">To hell and back</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>To hell and back</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@anarchy anarchy]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/anarchy">@anarchy</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Well, first of I would like to say the private server community is turning into crap… Everyone one thinks they can code because they copy and paste tutorials into a server source that somebody else built for them. Well News flash thats not coding, people wonder why there servers lagg so much and or crash all the time… its because you are all putting unstable crap coding into your servers before perfecting what is already there…</p>
<p>In my opinion i think someone or a group of someones (im working on one myself) should create a source that even if it has little or no features has little or no glitches… what im saying is…</p>
<pre><code class="lang-auto">No massing easly fixed but most servers have it...
No Hp Glitches (i.e monsters hp bar refills if there hp is over 255..)
All Player and Npc Emotes(Attacking, Defending, Dieing,)
Fully Working Range (Perfectly timed and working projectiles)
Fully Working Mage (all proper effects, Projectiles, Graphics, and Requirments all perfectly timed)
Base for all skills with a basic xp rate so skills all lvl up at same rate...(players don't get bored as quick)
Fully Working Prayer (With all glitched ironed out so nobody gets an unfair advantage</code></pre>
<p>This is only a small list of the many things that need to be fixed in Rs2 Servers</p>
<p>Think about it people the above list is only small but with those several things fixed private servers would be much more advanced then they already are…</p>
<p>It’s things like this that even though they may not be simple will bring private servers out of the hell there in and back to the real world</p>
<p>The question is why add Quests, and Mini Games when your server is flawed in 150 million ways? Private servers will never be perfect but with some of the talent around here they can be much, much, better.</p>
<p>Then people can start to work on there own Quests, and Mini games.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Second Note:</span></p>
<p>Don’t add every single code into client.java…<br>
For starters this will cause lots and lots of lag…<br>
secondly it makes your servers coding look horrable try being a bit more neat people</p>
<p>Add Handlers!! people your server can have so much less lagg if you add things properly dont cram it all into one file…</p>
<p>Thats All for now hope somebody hears me</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/to-hell-and-back/107463/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/to-hell-and-back/107463/1</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Jun 2007 03:49:20 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-107463-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/to-hell-and-back/107463.rss">To hell and back</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
