<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>A story</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/a-story/2714</link>
    <description>Shannon could hear the footsteps behind her as she walked toward home. The thought of being followed made her heart beat faster. &quot;You&#39;re being silly,&quot; she told herself, &quot;no one is following you.&quot; To be safe, she began to walk faster, but the footsteps kept up with her pace. She was afraid to look back and she was glad she was almost home. Shannon said a quick prayer, &quot;God please get me home safe.&quot; She saw the porch light burning and she leaned against the door for a moment, relieved to be in the safety of her home. She glanced out the window to see if anyone was there. The sidewalk was empty. After tossing her books on the sofa, she decided to grab a snack and ~get on-line.~ She logged on under her screen name ByAngel213. She checked her Buddy List and saw GoTo123 was on. She sent him an instant message:

ByAngel213: Hi. Where do you live? I think som1 was following me today

GoTo123: LOL You watch too much TV. Why would someone be following you? Don&#39;t you live in a safe neighborhood?

ByAngel213 Of course I do. LOL I was actually following som1 myself

GoTo123: Unless you gave your name out on-line. You haven&#39;t done that have you?

ByAngel213: Nope, im a stalker

GoTo123: Did you have a softball game after school today?

ByAngel213: Yes and we won!!

GoTo123: That&#39;s great! Who did you play?
ByAngel213: We played the Hornets. LOL. Their uniforms are so gross! They look like bees. LOL

GoTo123: What is your team called?

ByAngel213: We are the Canton Cats. We have tiger paws on our uniforms. They are really cool.

GoTo123: Did you pitch?

ByAngel213: No I play second base. I got to go. My homework has to be done before my parents get home. I don&#39;t want them mad at me. Bye!

GoTo123: Catch you later. Bye.

Meanwhile......GoTo123 went to the member menu and began to search for her profile. When it came up, he highlighted it and printed it out. He took out a pen and began to write down what he knew about Angel so far. Her name: Shannon. Birthday: Jan. 3, 1985. Age:13. State where she lived: North Carolina. Hobbies: softball, chorus, skating and going to the mall. Besides this information, he knew she lived in Canton because she had just told him. He knew she stayed by herself until 6:30 p.m. every afternoon until her parents came home from work. He knew she played softball on Thursday afternoons on the school team, and the team was named the Canton Cats. Her favorite number 7 was printed on her jersey. He knew she was in the seventh grade at the Canton Junior High School. She had told him all this in the conversations they had on-line. He had enough information to find her now.

While at the same time Shannon Not actually being 13 (actually an undercover policewomen)looked up goto123&#39;s profile.
Finding out about him.

By Thursday, Shannon had forgotten about the footsteps following her. Her game was in full swing when suddenly she felt someone staring at her. It was then that the memory came back. She glanced up from her second base position to see a man watching her closely. He was leaning against the fence behind first base and he smiled when she looked at him.
She realised it was him(The One She Had Lured)

He didn&#39;t look scary and she quickly dismissed the fear she had felt. After the game, he sat on a bleacher while she talked to the coach. She noticed his smile once again as she walked past him. He nodded and she smiled back. He noticed her name on the back of her shirt. He knew he had found her.

Quietly, he walked a safe distance behind her. It was only a few blocks to Shannon&#39;s home, and once he saw where she lived he quickly returned to the park to get his car.

Now he had to wait. He decided to get a bite to eat until the time came to go to Shannon&#39;s house. He drove to a fast food restaurant and sat there until it was time to make his move.

Shannon was in her room later that evening when she heard voices in the living room. &quot;Shannon, come here,&quot; her father called. He sounded upset and she couldn&#39;t imagine why. She went into the room to see the man from the ballpark sitting on the sofa.

&quot;Sit down,&quot; her father began, &quot;this man has just told us a most interesting story about you.&quot; Shannon sat back. How could he tell her parents anything? She had never seen him before today! &quot;Do you know who I am, Shannon?&quot; the man asked. &quot;No,&quot; Shannon answered. &quot;I am a police officer and your online friend, GoTo123.&quot;
Shannon replies : &quot;i am also a police officer&quot;
Wha replied goto123.

Both were part of an experiment gone wrong , to crack down on internet stalkers.

Soz, this was a story i found and i edited .
Im bored</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 12 May 2006 20:18:35 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>General Discussion</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/a-story/2714.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>A story</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Brad Brad]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/brad">@Brad</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>yeah wheres the unedited ?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/a-story/2714/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/a-story/2714/3</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 12 May 2006 20:18:35 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-2714-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/a-story/2714.rss">A story</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>A story</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@arraness14 arraness14]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/arraness14">@arraness14</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>can you tell me where to find the unedited version?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/a-story/2714/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/a-story/2714/2</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 12 May 2006 19:28:10 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-2714-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/a-story/2714.rss">A story</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>A story</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Mmmk Mmmk]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/mmmk">@Mmmk</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Shannon could hear the footsteps behind her as she walked toward home. The thought of being followed made her heart beat faster. “You’re being silly,” she told herself, “no one is following you.” To be safe, she began to walk faster, but the footsteps kept up with her pace. She was afraid to look back and she was glad she was almost home. Shannon said a quick prayer, “God please get me home safe.” She saw the porch light burning and she leaned against the door for a moment, relieved to be in the safety of her home. She glanced out the window to see if anyone was there. The sidewalk was empty. After tossing her books on the sofa, she decided to grab a snack and ~get on-line.~ She logged on under her screen name ByAngel213. She checked her Buddy List and saw GoTo123 was on. She sent him an instant message:</p>
<p>ByAngel213: Hi. Where do you live? I think som1 was following me today</p>
<p>GoTo123: LOL You watch too much TV. Why would someone be following you? Don’t you live in a safe neighborhood?</p>
<p>ByAngel213 Of course I do. LOL I was actually following som1 myself</p>
<p>GoTo123: Unless you gave your name out on-line. You haven’t done that have you?</p>
<p>ByAngel213: Nope, im a stalker</p>
<p>GoTo123: Did you have a softball game after school today?</p>
<p>ByAngel213: Yes and we won!!</p>
<p>GoTo123: That’s great! Who did you play?<br>
ByAngel213: We played the Hornets. LOL. Their uniforms are so gross! They look like bees. LOL</p>
<p>GoTo123: What is your team called?</p>
<p>ByAngel213: We are the Canton Cats. We have tiger paws on our uniforms. They are really cool.</p>
<p>GoTo123: Did you pitch?</p>
<p>ByAngel213: No I play second base. I got to go. My homework has to be done before my parents get home. I don’t want them mad at me. Bye!</p>
<p>GoTo123: Catch you later. Bye.</p>
<p>Meanwhile…GoTo123 went to the member menu and began to search for her profile. When it came up, he highlighted it and printed it out. He took out a pen and began to write down what he knew about Angel so far. Her name: Shannon. Birthday: Jan. 3, 1985. Age:13. State where she lived: North Carolina. Hobbies: softball, chorus, skating and going to the mall. Besides this information, he knew she lived in Canton because she had just told him. He knew she stayed by herself until 6:30 p.m. every afternoon until her parents came home from work. He knew she played softball on Thursday afternoons on the school team, and the team was named the Canton Cats. Her favorite number 7 was printed on her jersey. He knew she was in the seventh grade at the Canton Junior High School. She had told him all this in the conversations they had on-line. He had enough information to find her now.</p>
<p>While at the same time Shannon Not actually being 13 (actually an undercover policewomen)looked up goto123’s profile.<br>
Finding out about him.</p>
<p>By Thursday, Shannon had forgotten about the footsteps following her. Her game was in full swing when suddenly she felt someone staring at her. It was then that the memory came back. She glanced up from her second base position to see a man watching her closely. He was leaning against the fence behind first base and he smiled when she looked at him.<br>
She realised it was him(The One She Had Lured)</p>
<p>He didn’t look scary and she quickly dismissed the fear she had felt. After the game, he sat on a bleacher while she talked to the coach. She noticed his smile once again as she walked past him. He nodded and she smiled back. He noticed her name on the back of her shirt. He knew he had found her.</p>
<p>Quietly, he walked a safe distance behind her. It was only a few blocks to Shannon’s home, and once he saw where she lived he quickly returned to the park to get his car.</p>
<p>Now he had to wait. He decided to get a bite to eat until the time came to go to Shannon’s house. He drove to a fast food restaurant and sat there until it was time to make his move.</p>
<p>Shannon was in her room later that evening when she heard voices in the living room. “Shannon, come here,” her father called. He sounded upset and she couldn’t imagine why. She went into the room to see the man from the ballpark sitting on the sofa.</p>
<p>“Sit down,” her father began, “this man has just told us a most interesting story about you.” Shannon sat back. How could he tell her parents anything? She had never seen him before today! “Do you know who I am, Shannon?” the man asked. “No,” Shannon answered. “I am a police officer and your online friend, GoTo123.”<br>
Shannon replies : “i am also a police officer”<br>
Wha replied goto123.</p>
<p>Both were part of an experiment gone wrong , to crack down on internet stalkers.</p>
<p>Soz, this was a story i found and i edited .<br>
Im bored</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/a-story/2714/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/a-story/2714/1</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 12 May 2006 18:05:22 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-2714-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/a-story/2714.rss">A story</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
