<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Authentication method</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/authentication-method/387445</link>
    <description>I&#39;m looking for a few suggestions on an authentication method, I am considering doing something similar to amazon payments where a user has a key and a secret that they use in the applications api for a payment gateway.

What I have is a server that continuously grabs the Runescape grand exchange data for current prices of items and have it setup for users to submit recent grand exchange transactions buy/sell requests so on. I considered many forms of authentication but I don&#39;t know if choosing the key,secret method is best for this project.

What I want: the ability to have both public access and private access sessions with public access session being throttled and limited to what they can do (for example a public session should not be able to submit data due to risk of poisoning) 

What I don&#39;t want to use for authentication methods:
1. proprietary account - this seems like a waste of time to setup and maintain just for something so simple.
2. Forum account - Although I would probably attach private sessions to an account for banning and identification purposes I couldn&#39;t use this method for both public and private sessions
3. toolbar_hash - I considered accepting the runescape toolbar hash and username but I have no way of reversing this information so really does not provide any authentication at all and can be easily spoofed. I also want to keep this information private to the user as it is confidential with the users runescape account.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 22 Mar 2011 04:02:32 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>General Programming</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/authentication-method/387445.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Authentication method</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@silabsoft RuneAgent]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/silabsoft">@silabsoft</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>It does not need to be that complicated I don’t believe basically I want the simplest form of authentication for public and private sessions (private sessions being linked to a forum account) public sessions just being a table with as I suggested a key and secret secret similar to amazon payments api (does not have to be nearly as complicated) as this authentication is only for throttling public sessions and having some recourse incase a private session submits poisoned data.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/authentication-method/387445/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/authentication-method/387445/3</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 22 Mar 2011 04:02:32 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-387445-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/authentication-method/387445.rss">Authentication method</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Authentication method</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@zyle1992 Zymus]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/zyle1992">@zyle1992</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I’m confused as to what you want. Do you mean like an implementation of SRP-6 or some other authentication protocol, or am I reading it incorrectly?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/authentication-method/387445/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/authentication-method/387445/2</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 22 Mar 2011 03:54:25 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-387445-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/authentication-method/387445.rss">Authentication method</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Authentication method</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@silabsoft RuneAgent]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/silabsoft">@silabsoft</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I’m looking for a few suggestions on an authentication method, I am considering doing something similar to amazon payments where a user has a key and a secret that they use in the applications api for a payment gateway.</p>
<p>What I have is a server that continuously grabs the Runescape grand exchange data for current prices of items and have it setup for users to submit recent grand exchange transactions buy/sell requests so on. I considered many forms of authentication but I don’t know if choosing the key,secret method is best for this project.</p>
<p>What I want: the ability to have both public access and private access sessions with public access session being throttled and limited to what they can do (for example a public session should not be able to submit data due to risk of poisoning)</p>
<p>What I don’t want to use for authentication methods:</p>
<ol>
<li>proprietary account - this seems like a waste of time to setup and maintain just for something so simple.</li>
<li>Forum account - Although I would probably attach private sessions to an account for banning and identification purposes I couldn’t use this method for both public and private sessions</li>
<li>toolbar_hash - I considered accepting the runescape toolbar hash and username but I have no way of reversing this information so really does not provide any authentication at all and can be easily spoofed. I also want to keep this information private to the user as it is confidential with the users runescape account.</li>
</ol>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/authentication-method/387445/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/authentication-method/387445/1</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 22 Mar 2011 00:59:11 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-387445-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/authentication-method/387445.rss">Authentication method</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
