<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Headicons get pushed down if you have a skull and prayer!</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/headicons-get-pushed-down-if-you-have-a-skull-and-prayer/257368</link>
    <description>Hello! After I finished fixing most of the clients errors, I came up to the very last one that I know of.

The title of this thread sort of describes it. First of all, if you have just a skull and NOTHING else, then you&#39;re fine, the skull is above the HP bar as it is supposed to be. Same with a prayer headicon. But this is where the problem comes in. If you have a skull AND you turn on a headicon prayer(Smite, for example) the skull sinks into the characters head and the HP bar is in between. Here is a picture that I took so you can visually see what I&#39;m trying to explain.

[IMG]http://i268.photobucket.com/albums/jj23/FfsDied/Prayerglitch.jpg[/img]

Does anyone have ANY idea on how to fix this?

Post any ideas that YOU THINK may fix this. It doesn&#39;t have to be a dead-on answer, who knows, maybe the ideas will spark my brain for an answer :P.

Thanks in advance!
-Skullator</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2009 15:03:40 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/headicons-get-pushed-down-if-you-have-a-skull-and-prayer/257368.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Headicons get pushed down if you have a skull and prayer!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Skullator Skullator]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/skullator">@Skullator</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Hello! After I finished fixing most of the clients errors, I came up to the very last one that I know of.</p>
<p>The title of this thread sort of describes it. First of all, if you have just a skull and NOTHING else, then you’re fine, the skull is above the HP bar as it is supposed to be. Same with a prayer headicon. But this is where the problem comes in. If you have a skull AND you turn on a headicon prayer(Smite, for example) the skull sinks into the characters head and the HP bar is in between. Here is a picture that I took so you can visually see what I’m trying to explain.</p>
<p><img src="http://i268.photobucket.com/albums/jj23/FfsDied/Prayerglitch.jpg" alt width="165" height="194"></p>
<p>Does anyone have ANY idea on how to fix this?</p>
<p>Post any ideas that YOU THINK may fix this. It doesn’t have to be a dead-on answer, who knows, maybe the ideas will spark my brain for an answer :P.</p>
<p>Thanks in advance!<br>
-Skullator</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/headicons-get-pushed-down-if-you-have-a-skull-and-prayer/257368/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/headicons-get-pushed-down-if-you-have-a-skull-and-prayer/257368/1</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2009 15:03:40 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-257368-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/headicons-get-pushed-down-if-you-have-a-skull-and-prayer/257368.rss">Headicons get pushed down if you have a skull and prayer!</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
