<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Virus Problem?</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/virus-problem/241292</link>
    <description>For some reason I can&#39;t download the installation file... I go to the uppit link and press download, and then it goes all the way but at the end, a message comes up saying it &quot;could not be completed for an unknown reason. Try saving to another location&quot;. And then my virus software picks it up and drops it in the quarantine... I restored the file but it comes out corrupted. Is there another link to get the file? I tried the other link but my computer&#39;s virus software blocks the entire website... I&#39;m hesitant to lower the shield around my computer because I&#39;ve had many problems with viruses and such in the past.

I&#39;m running on firefox if that makes a difference.

EDIT: never mind, got it :)</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2008 18:21:23 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/virus-problem/241292.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Virus Problem?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@ZoraRuler ZoraRuler]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/zoraruler">@ZoraRuler</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>For some reason I can’t download the installation file… I go to the uppit link and press download, and then it goes all the way but at the end, a message comes up saying it “could not be completed for an unknown reason. Try saving to another location”. And then my virus software picks it up and drops it in the quarantine… I restored the file but it comes out corrupted. Is there another link to get the file? I tried the other link but my computer’s virus software blocks the entire website… I’m hesitant to lower the shield around my computer because I’ve had many problems with viruses and such in the past.</p>
<p>I’m running on firefox if that makes a difference.</p>
<p>EDIT: never mind, got it <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=6" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/virus-problem/241292/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/virus-problem/241292/1</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2008 18:21:23 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-241292-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/virus-problem/241292.rss">Virus Problem?</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
