<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>New Community</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-community/549838</link>
    <description>Hey guys!

Sorry if my typing is not the greatest i typing this off my iPhone while parked off to the side on the highway.

I am looking to start up a small rsps community, I have already purchased a vps and a website to get it slowly going. I&#39;ve wanted to do this project for quite some time but I was a lot younger and didn&#39;t have the means to get the ball rolling.

What I am looking for is client side and server side developers. I am looking for two server side and one client side to start. 

I do not have a decision yet whether I want a pk server or an npc grind, but this can be discussed and chosen based off what everyone thinks. I&#39;d like to build a relationship with the people I am working with.

I will handle the funds of the vps and the website, I just dont have knowledge when it comes to coding and such.

Now the question comes, will I be paying? To start, no I will not be able to pay right off the bat, but when the community launches and we have a player base and some people start to donate I would be more then happy to throw some of the donation money your way as a thank you. I&#39;d also like to keep people who are interested in working long term.

I know everyone may not agree with all my decisions, but I am open to suggestions and I hope we can get something worked out!

Feel free to pm me on the forums, but you can email or skype me at anytime.

Email: tylerss@hotmail.com
Skype: firecrandor

Thanks again for reading this post, can&#39;t wait to talk!</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2015 17:48:15 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-community/549838.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>New Community</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Tylerscs Tylerscs]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/tylerscs">@Tylerscs</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Hey guys!</p>
<p>Sorry if my typing is not the greatest i typing this off my iPhone while parked off to the side on the highway.</p>
<p>I am looking to start up a small rsps community, I have already purchased a vps and a website to get it slowly going. I’ve wanted to do this project for quite some time but I was a lot younger and didn’t have the means to get the ball rolling.</p>
<p>What I am looking for is client side and server side developers. I am looking for two server side and one client side to start.</p>
<p>I do not have a decision yet whether I want a pk server or an npc grind, but this can be discussed and chosen based off what everyone thinks. I’d like to build a relationship with the people I am working with.</p>
<p>I will handle the funds of the vps and the website, I just dont have knowledge when it comes to coding and such.</p>
<p>Now the question comes, will I be paying? To start, no I will not be able to pay right off the bat, but when the community launches and we have a player base and some people start to donate I would be more then happy to throw some of the donation money your way as a thank you. I’d also like to keep people who are interested in working long term.</p>
<p>I know everyone may not agree with all my decisions, but I am open to suggestions and I hope we can get something worked out!</p>
<p>Feel free to pm me on the forums, but you can email or skype me at anytime.</p>
<p>Email: <a href="mailto:tylerss@hotmail.com">tylerss@hotmail.com</a><br>
Skype: firecrandor</p>
<p>Thanks again for reading this post, can’t wait to talk!</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-community/549838/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-community/549838/1</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2015 17:48:15 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-549838-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-community/549838.rss">New Community</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
