<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Ban list</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/ban-list/432642</link>
    <description>I&#39;d like the entire ban list to be reviewed, all of it since the earliest ban. I think we should do this every year or so to ensure no one is left banned who shouldn&#39;t be. I&#39;d also like to discuss Pure2Ownage and friends and why they should be unbanned.

First of all, P2O was banned for something not even relating to Moparcraft in the slightest which makes no sense whatsoever. If we&#39;re going to continue using this forum integration system then we need separate ban lists because the traffic is being banned for something not even relating to the server...

I believe in another chance for everybody, and what exactly can they do harm wise? Nothing is the answer. It&#39;s a win win situation for us. 

We need a new method to keep track of bans as well.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 12 Feb 2012 01:07:57 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Games</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/ban-list/432642.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Ban list</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@zuppers zuppers]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/zuppers">@zuppers</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I was hoping for some sort of automated ban system plugin but that is highly unlikely.<br>
We don’t really have access to the ban list (I don’t at least) but most of the bans I’ve made are permanent(e.g first time posters who just come on to hack or grief) most of the important people probably have already had a second chance but I see no harm in wiping most of the bans.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/ban-list/432642/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/ban-list/432642/2</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 12 Feb 2012 01:07:57 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-432642-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/ban-list/432642.rss">Ban list</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Ban list</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Tom Tom]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/tom">@Tom</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I’d like the entire ban list to be reviewed, all of it since the earliest ban. I think we should do this every year or so to ensure no one is left banned who shouldn’t be. I’d also like to discuss Pure2Ownage and friends and why they should be unbanned.</p>
<p>First of all, P2O was banned for something not even relating to Moparcraft in the slightest which makes no sense whatsoever. If we’re going to continue using this forum integration system then we need separate ban lists because the traffic is being banned for something not even relating to the server…</p>
<p>I believe in another chance for everybody, and what exactly can they do harm wise? Nothing is the answer. It’s a win win situation for us.</p>
<p>We need a new method to keep track of bans as well.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/ban-list/432642/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/ban-list/432642/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 12 Feb 2012 00:11:28 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-432642-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/ban-list/432642.rss">Ban list</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
