<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>[Emulous] Player No Action [Emulous]</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/emulous-player-no-action-emulous/444429</link>
    <description>Hey MoparScape,

I added a little introduction to the beginning when a new player logs into the server. They read all the dialogues then it gives them a starter, the after that they can change their character. But the problem is if they do any action the dialog goes away, meaning they can&#39;t get there starter and get the introduction about the server. Can someone please tell me how to make it so while you&#39;re in the introduction mode you can&#39;t do anything but accept the dialogues. They must be able to not Move, teleport, do emotes, drop anything run, and when they click something in game or the minimap it doesn&#39;t register until they&#39;ve past the introduction. I&#39;ve added the introduction variable and added it to the player saving file so when they first start it&#39;s 0 then when they do the introduction it changes to 1 and saves. I really need this so I can finish adding my awesome feature.

Also, if players haven&#39;t completed it for any reason. i want the dialogue to pop up and make them need to do it like what I&#39;ve asked for above.

Thanks for you&#39;re time reading this.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 09 Jun 2012 08:16:56 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/emulous-player-no-action-emulous/444429.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>[Emulous] Player No Action [Emulous]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@ExtremeX-Scape Ryley]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/extremex-scape">@ExtremeX-Scape</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I believe there are packets that are meant to stop actions for a period of time.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/emulous-player-no-action-emulous/444429/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/emulous-player-no-action-emulous/444429/4</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 09 Jun 2012 08:16:56 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-444429-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/emulous-player-no-action-emulous/444429.rss">[Emulous] Player No Action [Emulous]</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Emulous] Player No Action [Emulous]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Onix Onix]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/onix">@Onix</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Or just make the has starter variable, or whatever you use stay false until they finish the dialogue, that way then can go back and talk to the NPC if they want their starter.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/emulous-player-no-action-emulous/444429/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/emulous-player-no-action-emulous/444429/3</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 09 Jun 2012 04:36:13 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-444429-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/emulous-player-no-action-emulous/444429.rss">[Emulous] Player No Action [Emulous]</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Emulous] Player No Action [Emulous]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Skiire Skiire]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/skiire">@Skiire</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Talked with you on Skype briefly about this… You have everything you need at your disposal, I don’t know why you are so afraid to tinker around.</p>
<p>Think of something that doesn’t allow movement while completing the action. Trading for example. See how that’s handled, it’s <span class="bbcode-i">probably</span> something as simple as:</p>
<pre><code class="lang-auto">if(inTrade) {
return false;
}</code></pre>
<p>Just do something very similar to that. Don’t be afraid to get your hands dirty and try something new.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/emulous-player-no-action-emulous/444429/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/emulous-player-no-action-emulous/444429/2</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 09 Jun 2012 02:20:21 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-444429-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/emulous-player-no-action-emulous/444429.rss">[Emulous] Player No Action [Emulous]</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Emulous] Player No Action [Emulous]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Skyro Arbe]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/skyro">@Skyro</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Hey MoparScape,</p>
<p>I added a little introduction to the beginning when a new player logs into the server. They read all the dialogues then it gives them a starter, the after that they can change their character. But the problem is if they do any action the dialog goes away, meaning they can’t get there starter and get the introduction about the server. Can someone please tell me how to make it so while you’re in the introduction mode you can’t do anything but accept the dialogues. They must be able to not Move, teleport, do emotes, drop anything run, and when they click something in game or the minimap it doesn’t register until they’ve past the introduction. I’ve added the introduction variable and added it to the player saving file so when they first start it’s 0 then when they do the introduction it changes to 1 and saves. I really need this so I can finish adding my awesome feature.</p>
<p>Also, if players haven’t completed it for any reason. i want the dialogue to pop up and make them need to do it like what I’ve asked for above.</p>
<p>Thanks for you’re time reading this.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/emulous-player-no-action-emulous/444429/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/emulous-player-no-action-emulous/444429/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 09 Jun 2012 00:09:01 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-444429-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/emulous-player-no-action-emulous/444429.rss">[Emulous] Player No Action [Emulous]</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
