<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Software Load Balancer</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/software-load-balancer/256597</link>
    <description>Just thought I&#39;d ask your opinion on some of these implementation ideas.
My web host recently shit a brick and threatened to shut me down for running a proxy, so I&#39;ve had to think of a new way to host it. I&#39;ve found a good free web host that seems to allow fsockopen and the like, so hopefully phproxy will run. Of course, this being free hosting, the bandwidth is somewhat limited. I intend to create multiple accounts, then simply iframe the one with the least load. I figure if I have 5 separate accounts, the load should even out enough as to not alert the server admins. The main idea here is to maintain the current URL of my proxy, without my paid host shutting me down.

Anyways, my problem is, how should I go about telling the central server (the one with the iframe page) how much load each server is under. I was thinking a central SQL db that keeps track of the requests then send new requests to the proxy with the lowest load, incrementing the number of connections for that proxy. I suppose I could use PHP sessions on the proxy servers, so I can maintain some kind of persistence between the same user&#39;s multiple requests. This would require the SQL db to be externally accessible, something that my host doesn&#39;t allow, so I&#39;d probably have to find a free SQL host that allows external connections.
SELECT * FROM `servers` ORDER BY `connections` ASC LIMIT 1
Or something along those lines.

What do you guys think?</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2009 13:52:07 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>General Programming</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/software-load-balancer/256597.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Software Load Balancer</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@error.login cane]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/error.login">@error.login</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>try <a href="http://plb.sunsite.dk/" rel="nofollow noopener">http://plb.sunsite.dk/</a></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/software-load-balancer/256597/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/software-load-balancer/256597/5</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2009 13:52:07 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-256597-5</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/software-load-balancer/256597.rss">Software Load Balancer</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Software Load Balancer</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Pwnd Pwnd]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/pwnd">@Pwnd</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Well, I don’t think you’d want a proxy hosted on the same site as something that doesn’t suck (Given that the other sites don’t suck).  Just find another set of hosting, idk.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/software-load-balancer/256597/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/software-load-balancer/256597/4</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2009 18:27:01 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-256597-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/software-load-balancer/256597.rss">Software Load Balancer</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Software Load Balancer</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Unhandled Unhandled]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/unhandled">@Unhandled</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Pfft, what’s the fun in that?</p>
<p>I already pay for 1TB a month bandwidth, but as I said, my host doesn’t like me running proxies. I don’t want to switch hosts, because I have a lot of other things set up already, that I cba to backup and upload again, plus transferring 6 domains will be a real bitch.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/software-load-balancer/256597/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/software-load-balancer/256597/3</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2009 12:26:45 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-256597-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/software-load-balancer/256597.rss">Software Load Balancer</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Software Load Balancer</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Mopman Mopman]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/mopman">@Mopman</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Could you not just pay for your own bandwidth?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/software-load-balancer/256597/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/software-load-balancer/256597/2</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2009 03:41:12 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-256597-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/software-load-balancer/256597.rss">Software Load Balancer</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Software Load Balancer</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Unhandled Unhandled]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/unhandled">@Unhandled</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Just thought I’d ask your opinion on some of these implementation ideas.<br>
My web host recently shit a brick and threatened to shut me down for running a proxy, so I’ve had to think of a new way to host it. I’ve found a good free web host that seems to allow fsockopen and the like, so hopefully phproxy will run. Of course, this being free hosting, the bandwidth is somewhat limited. I intend to create multiple accounts, then simply iframe the one with the least load. I figure if I have 5 separate accounts, the load should even out enough as to not alert the server admins. The main idea here is to maintain the current URL of my proxy, without my paid host shutting me down.</p>
<p>Anyways, my problem is, how should I go about telling the central server (the one with the iframe page) how much load each server is under. I was thinking a central SQL db that keeps track of the requests then send new requests to the proxy with the lowest load, incrementing the number of connections for that proxy. I suppose I could use PHP sessions on the proxy servers, so I can maintain some kind of persistence between the same user’s multiple requests. This would require the SQL db to be externally accessible, something that my host doesn’t allow, so I’d probably have to find a free SQL host that allows external connections.<br>
SELECT * FROM <code>servers</code> ORDER BY <code>connections</code> ASC LIMIT 1<br>
Or something along those lines.</p>
<p>What do you guys think?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/software-load-balancer/256597/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/software-load-balancer/256597/1</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2009 03:23:16 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-256597-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/software-load-balancer/256597.rss">Software Load Balancer</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
