<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>AD scripting</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/ad-scripting/477627</link>
    <description>I was wondering if anyone know anything about Active directory and scripting.

I am tired of manually creating student accounts at my job. If it wasn&#39;t so time consuming(like 100+ at a time) I wouldn&#39;t care.

currently I am:
copying a template
type their first name, last name, and username(first initial + last name [+ number if the first username exists])
give them a password, make sure the checkbox is checked for force password change and that the account is enabled.
Copy the username on the confirmation page and paste to excel doc
yay the account is created(I still have to add the email and description at the end of the batch) but that took like 30 seconds or longer if you have to keep throwing numbers behind the username until its a new username.

A coworker of mine created an excel doc that generates a commands for a batch file. problem is it doesn&#39;t create them correctly(some things are missing. it uses &quot;net user&quot;) and engineering gets upset.

I have been looking at using vbscript to make a simple but effective script that cycles through an excel doc row by row and creates accounts just with a first name and last name. thats easy enough. my question what is Common-name(cn)? it looks like its just the username but im not sure.

I was looking at this http://msdn.microsoft.com/en-us/library/ms974568.aspx I googled cn and it said something about its used for searching? I&#39;m trying to figure out what I need to put in cn if its just the username that easy enough. Or do I even need a cn value?

I also thought it looks like excel uses vbscript in it so why not just name an excel doc that access AD and does everything from inside excel instead of creating a separate vbs and excel files. so I&#39;m going to be looking through http://activexperts.com/activmonitor/windowsmanagement/scripts/msoffice/excel/

I am probably just going to do something like http://technet.microsoft.com/en-us/library/ee198800.aspx

Thx</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 05 Jan 2013 20:16:56 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>General Programming</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/ad-scripting/477627.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>AD scripting</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@xryz xryz]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/xryz">@xryz</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I was wondering if anyone know anything about Active directory and scripting.</p>
<p>I am tired of manually creating student accounts at my job. If it wasn’t so time consuming(like 100+ at a time) I wouldn’t care.</p>
<p>currently I am:<br>
copying a template<br>
type their first name, last name, and username(first initial + last name [+ number if the first username exists])<br>
give them a password, make sure the checkbox is checked for force password change and that the account is enabled.<br>
Copy the username on the confirmation page and paste to excel doc<br>
yay the account is created(I still have to add the email and description at the end of the batch) but that took like 30 seconds or longer if you have to keep throwing numbers behind the username until its a new username.</p>
<p>A coworker of mine created an excel doc that generates a commands for a batch file. problem is it doesn’t create them correctly(some things are missing. it uses “net user”) and engineering gets upset.</p>
<p>I have been looking at using vbscript to make a simple but effective script that cycles through an excel doc row by row and creates accounts just with a first name and last name. thats easy enough. my question what is Common-name(cn)? it looks like its just the username but im not sure.</p>
<p>I was looking at this <a href="http://msdn.microsoft.com/en-us/library/ms974568.aspx" rel="nofollow noopener">http://msdn.microsoft.com/en-us/library/ms974568.aspx</a> I googled cn and it said something about its used for searching? I’m trying to figure out what I need to put in cn if its just the username that easy enough. Or do I even need a cn value?</p>
<p>I also thought it looks like excel uses vbscript in it so why not just name an excel doc that access AD and does everything from inside excel instead of creating a separate vbs and excel files. so I’m going to be looking through <a href="http://activexperts.com/activmonitor/windowsmanagement/scripts/msoffice/excel/" rel="nofollow noopener">http://activexperts.com/activmonitor/windowsmanagement/scripts/msoffice/excel/</a></p>
<p>I am probably just going to do something like <a href="http://technet.microsoft.com/en-us/library/ee198800.aspx" rel="nofollow noopener">http://technet.microsoft.com/en-us/library/ee198800.aspx</a></p>
<p>Thx</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/ad-scripting/477627/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/ad-scripting/477627/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 05 Jan 2013 20:16:56 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-477627-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/ad-scripting/477627.rss">AD scripting</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
