<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Arc Kingdoms! 1.4.5 - PVP, Raid, Factions, Classes! Minecraft Server!</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/arc-kingdoms-1-4-5-pvp-raid-factions-classes-minecraft-server/469362</link>
    <description>[shadow=red,left][b]Arc Kingdoms: PVP[/b][/shadow]

[b]Join us at:[/b]

[shadow=red,left][b]pvp.ArcKingdoms.com[/b][/shadow]

[b]Website:[/b]
[b]http://arckingdoms.com/[/b]

Arc Kingdoms is a PvP server devoted to taking your Minecraft experience to another level. Our server provides many great aspects of the game and more to enhance the feel of Minecraft. Create a Faction with friends or by yourself and fight others with the intent to kill! Choose a class and dominate the battlefield with your enhanced skills. Arc Kingdoms PvP server also offers a economy system by killing mobs. No need to sell endless materials for minimal prices. If killing mobs isn&#39;t your cup of tea, you can trade items with the villagers at /spawn for many valuables and necessities. Griefing is 100% allowed on the Arc Kingdoms: PvP server meaning that any block you can break, is fare game. The server is hosted on a LAG FREE dedicated host to keep your game play clean!
[b]
Factions[/b]

Factions are a huge aspect to the Arc Kingdoms PvP atmosphere. Factions allow you to group together friends, claim land, create bases and fight together against other Factions.

[b]Classes[/b]

Our class system is a way to give a edge and a role-play feel to the regular player vs player combat. Use spells, attack perks and archery skills to defeat all that stands in your path. Partner or team up with other players with other classes to control all aspects of the class system. All classes can be purchased in game at /go Class.

[b]Tier 1 Classes [/b](1,000 in game coin cost):
[b]Wizard:[/b] Use spells to cast your players to death. Spells include confusion, teleport and cripple spells to slow down and harm your opponents.
[b]Bandit:[/b] Use &#39;super speed&#39; to attack or run away from players, Bandage yourself 3 hearts by right clicking with a paper in hand and XP levels to hit with extra damage to players.
[b]Archer:[/b] Use smoke arrows to blind and stun your target on impact, and use weak arrows to weaken your opponents attack. Use archer as a support class to a footman.

[b]Tier 2 Classes[/b] (7,500 in game coin cost):
[b]Magician:[/b] Includes all Wizard Perks.Has the ability to cast spells such as &#39;Firenova&#39; which causes a ring of fire to expand outwards to your opponents, &#39;Forcepush&#39; to push your opponents away from you and Leap to quickly jump in the air and fly forward away or towards a opponent.
[b]Warrior:[/b] Includes all Bandit Perks.Can &#39;Forcetoss&#39; players into the air dealing damage when hitting the ground and can also use &#39;Combust&#39; on players to ignite them on fire!
[b]Sharpshooter:[/b] Includes all archer Perks.Use Poison arrows to infect your targets with a harming poison and use Scatter arrows to shoot multiple arrows at once at a target.

[b]Raiding[/b]

No longer do you have do deal with the boring, unraidable Factions/Bases some servers have, but instead, every faction is fare game if the intruder knows what they are doing. Obsidian&#39;s damage rate has been changed to allow obsidianized bases to be accessed with 3 direct hits in a 5 minute period using TNT. Water has also been changed to allow blocks to be destroyed though it. With these two aspects added to the game, a whole new strategy is taken into play when creating and raiding bases. If you are having trouble finding a base, you can simple use your /f map locate the nearest Factions around you.

Donate

Donations are what keeps our server running day in and day out on our 24/7 basis. Provided that running a server is intensive labor and cost consuming, we need your help to keep it running. All profits go straight to help expand our server and for that, we offer you a few perks to help you out.

You can donate on our website @ http://arckingdoms.com/donate

Feedback:

​It is always nice to find out how the community enjoys our server. If you liked, enjoyed or even loved our server, feel free to reply below. Or visit our forums @ http://arckingdoms.com

Now get ready to crack some skulls on the most exhilarating PvP server in the business!

[shadow=red,left][b]pvp.ArcKingdoms.com[/b][/shadow]
[b]
Teamspeak Server:[/b]

[shadow=red,left][b]ts.arckingdoms.com[/b][/shadow]</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 21 Nov 2012 05:18:44 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Minecraft</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/arc-kingdoms-1-4-5-pvp-raid-factions-classes-minecraft-server/469362.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Arc Kingdoms! 1.4.5 - PVP, Raid, Factions, Classes! Minecraft Server!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@BlondeBeard BlondeBeard]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/blondebeard">@BlondeBeard</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[shadow=red,left]<span class="bbcode-b">Arc Kingdoms: PVP</span>[/shadow]</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Join us at:</span></p>
<p>[shadow=red,left]<span class="bbcode-b"><a href="http://pvp.ArcKingdoms.com" rel="nofollow noopener">pvp.ArcKingdoms.com</a></span>[/shadow]</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Website:</span><br>
<span class="bbcode-b"><a href="http://arckingdoms.com/" rel="nofollow noopener">http://arckingdoms.com/</a></span></p>
<p>Arc Kingdoms is a PvP server devoted to taking your Minecraft experience to another level. Our server provides many great aspects of the game and more to enhance the feel of Minecraft. Create a Faction with friends or by yourself and fight others with the intent to kill! Choose a class and dominate the battlefield with your enhanced skills. Arc Kingdoms PvP server also offers a economy system by killing mobs. No need to sell endless materials for minimal prices. If killing mobs isn’t your cup of tea, you can trade items with the villagers at /spawn for many valuables and necessities. Griefing is 100% allowed on the Arc Kingdoms: PvP server meaning that any block you can break, is fare game. The server is hosted on a LAG FREE dedicated host to keep your game play clean!<br>
<span class="bbcode-b"><br>
Factions</span></p>
<p>Factions are a huge aspect to the Arc Kingdoms PvP atmosphere. Factions allow you to group together friends, claim land, create bases and fight together against other Factions.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Classes</span></p>
<p>Our class system is a way to give a edge and a role-play feel to the regular player vs player combat. Use spells, attack perks and archery skills to defeat all that stands in your path. Partner or team up with other players with other classes to control all aspects of the class system. All classes can be purchased in game at /go Class.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Tier 1 Classes </span>(1,000 in game coin cost):<br>
<span class="bbcode-b">Wizard:</span> Use spells to cast your players to death. Spells include confusion, teleport and cripple spells to slow down and harm your opponents.<br>
<span class="bbcode-b">Bandit:</span> Use ‘super speed’ to attack or run away from players, Bandage yourself 3 hearts by right clicking with a paper in hand and XP levels to hit with extra damage to players.<br>
<span class="bbcode-b">Archer:</span> Use smoke arrows to blind and stun your target on impact, and use weak arrows to weaken your opponents attack. Use archer as a support class to a footman.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Tier 2 Classes</span> (7,500 in game coin cost):<br>
<span class="bbcode-b">Magician:</span> Includes all Wizard Perks.Has the ability to cast spells such as ‘Firenova’ which causes a ring of fire to expand outwards to your opponents, ‘Forcepush’ to push your opponents away from you and Leap to quickly jump in the air and fly forward away or towards a opponent.<br>
<span class="bbcode-b">Warrior:</span> Includes all Bandit Perks.Can ‘Forcetoss’ players into the air dealing damage when hitting the ground and can also use ‘Combust’ on players to ignite them on fire!<br>
<span class="bbcode-b">Sharpshooter:</span> Includes all archer Perks.Use Poison arrows to infect your targets with a harming poison and use Scatter arrows to shoot multiple arrows at once at a target.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Raiding</span></p>
<p>No longer do you have do deal with the boring, unraidable Factions/Bases some servers have, but instead, every faction is fare game if the intruder knows what they are doing. Obsidian’s damage rate has been changed to allow obsidianized bases to be accessed with 3 direct hits in a 5 minute period using TNT. Water has also been changed to allow blocks to be destroyed though it. With these two aspects added to the game, a whole new strategy is taken into play when creating and raiding bases. If you are having trouble finding a base, you can simple use your /f map locate the nearest Factions around you.</p>
<p>Donate</p>
<p>Donations are what keeps our server running day in and day out on our 24/7 basis. Provided that running a server is intensive labor and cost consuming, we need your help to keep it running. All profits go straight to help expand our server and for that, we offer you a few perks to help you out.</p>
<p>You can donate on our website @ <a href="http://arckingdoms.com/donate" rel="nofollow noopener">http://arckingdoms.com/donate</a></p>
<p>Feedback:</p>
<p>​It is always nice to find out how the community enjoys our server. If you liked, enjoyed or even loved our server, feel free to reply below. Or visit our forums @ <a href="http://arckingdoms.com" rel="nofollow noopener">http://arckingdoms.com</a></p>
<p>Now get ready to crack some skulls on the most exhilarating PvP server in the business!</p>
<p>[shadow=red,left]<span class="bbcode-b"><a href="http://pvp.ArcKingdoms.com" rel="nofollow noopener">pvp.ArcKingdoms.com</a></span>[/shadow]<br>
<span class="bbcode-b"><br>
Teamspeak Server:</span></p>
<p>[shadow=red,left]<span class="bbcode-b"><a href="http://ts.arckingdoms.com" rel="nofollow noopener">ts.arckingdoms.com</a></span>[/shadow]</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/arc-kingdoms-1-4-5-pvp-raid-factions-classes-minecraft-server/469362/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/arc-kingdoms-1-4-5-pvp-raid-factions-classes-minecraft-server/469362/1</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 21 Nov 2012 05:18:44 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-469362-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/arc-kingdoms-1-4-5-pvp-raid-factions-classes-minecraft-server/469362.rss">Arc Kingdoms! 1.4.5 - PVP, Raid, Factions, Classes! Minecraft Server!</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
