<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Looking for help/tut on getting a server up</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/looking-for-help-tut-on-getting-a-server-up/52705</link>
    <description>[b]Just to let you know I&#39;ve read the &#39;ultimate server guide&#39; twice and tried what he recommended but these are the problems I am having after not finding out how to fix them checking his guide over and over.[/b]

Ok a few problems im having, I used - http://ascape.bounceme.net/portcheck.php, to check if my router was set up properly but obviously not so I need help for setting up the port forwarding with a puretek pt-3812 router please (I used this to do it but it didnt work when I followed it - http://www.portforward.com/english/routers/port_forwarding/Etec/PT3812/PT3812index.htm)
so if you can tell me what im meant to put under &#39;public port - start&#39;, &#39;public port - end&#39;, &#39;private port&#39;, and tell me wheres I can find my computer ip address that will definitely be it, because I tried my default gateway ip address  that was under &#39;start menu, run, commands, ipconfig /all&#39;. and this other gateway ip address didnt work but might be because im typing the wrong thing under the ports. Im using the port 43594, I just typed the port number under all 3 port things.

[b]Just to let you know I dont understand complicated programming language so if you can make it as simple as possible (as some of you call as newbie as possible?)[/b]

[i][b](a link to a good source thats easy to use would be helpful, even if thats all you post)[/b][/i]
Ok next I need to know how to use a server source then link it to my domain that I created at - http://www.no-ip.com/. Also want to know how to change the server source I downloaded by giving it my servers name and change the port it uses as I download some server sources and everytime I run it its got the old servers port and name.

Then I&#39;ll add anything else if Im having more problems I hope someone can help me soon lol and if you do thanks very much for sparing your time for me.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 28 Jan 2007 16:49:25 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/looking-for-help-tut-on-getting-a-server-up/52705.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Looking for help/tut on getting a server up</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@driftxt driftxt]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/driftxt">@driftxt</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p><span class="bbcode-b">Just to let you know I’ve read the ‘ultimate server guide’ twice and tried what he recommended but these are the problems I am having after not finding out how to fix them checking his guide over and over.</span></p>
<p>Ok a few problems im having, I used - <a href="http://ascape.bounceme.net/portcheck.php" rel="nofollow noopener">http://ascape.bounceme.net/portcheck.php</a>, to check if my router was set up properly but obviously not so I need help for setting up the port forwarding with a puretek pt-3812 router please (I used this to do it but it didnt work when I followed it - <a href="http://www.portforward.com/english/routers/port_forwarding/Etec/PT3812/PT3812index.htm" rel="nofollow noopener">http://www.portforward.com/english/routers/port_forwarding/Etec/PT3812/PT3812index.htm</a>)<br>
so if you can tell me what im meant to put under ‘public port - start’, ‘public port - end’, ‘private port’, and tell me wheres I can find my computer ip address that will definitely be it, because I tried my default gateway ip address  that was under ‘start menu, run, commands, ipconfig /all’. and this other gateway ip address didnt work but might be because im typing the wrong thing under the ports. Im using the port 43594, I just typed the port number under all 3 port things.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Just to let you know I dont understand complicated programming language so if you can make it as simple as possible (as some of you call as newbie as possible?)</span></p>
<p><span class="bbcode-i"><span class="bbcode-b">(a link to a good source thats easy to use would be helpful, even if thats all you post)</span></span><br>
Ok next I need to know how to use a server source then link it to my domain that I created at - <a href="http://www.no-ip.com/" rel="nofollow noopener">http://www.no-ip.com/</a>. Also want to know how to change the server source I downloaded by giving it my servers name and change the port it uses as I download some server sources and everytime I run it its got the old servers port and name.</p>
<p>Then I’ll add anything else if Im having more problems I hope someone can help me soon lol and if you do thanks very much for sparing your time for me.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/looking-for-help-tut-on-getting-a-server-up/52705/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/looking-for-help-tut-on-getting-a-server-up/52705/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 28 Jan 2007 16:49:25 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-52705-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/looking-for-help-tut-on-getting-a-server-up/52705.rss">Looking for help/tut on getting a server up</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
