<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Stake Land</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/stake-land/535491</link>
    <description>http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=zNC2HwAaWWE
Ever heard of an apocalyptic zombie movie? Well this isn&#39;t one of them. This is a vampire movie bitches.

The journey of the movie is to get to a place called New Eden in which is supposedly free of the vampire Apocalypse because of the low population of people. Low population of people means less vampires while the other half of the country contains more vampires because of the higher population. The two main characters consist of a horn dog teenager whose name I never did catch and 40ish year old guy who has no back story but contains some serious survival skills, his name is mister. The start of the movie is great. Half way through is great. Then closer to the end I started to think damn, these guys really are alone. Shit happens and more shit happens and then you realise just how alone these two people are. This is where you develop a bond with the kid and mister. My expectations at the very start of the movie was that mister would die and the kid would go on all alone. I wont say if it happened or not but I will say its something you anticipate through 3/4 of the movie and then something happens. It leaves you thinking why and where the hell did he just... The ending was a bit rushed and it really pissed the movie for me. Everything but the ending was good. I dunno. Maybe you&#39;d like the ending if you like the type of endings where it doesn&#39;t tell you crap about one of the characters and what happened.

This movie is a really good movie. I&#39;d suggest it to anyone looking for a subtle apocalyptic horror movie. I&#39;d rate this movie 9 tabbies out of 10.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 11 Nov 2013 11:04:28 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>General Discussion</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/stake-land/535491.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Stake Land</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@TabbyKiller TabbyKiller]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/tabbykiller">@TabbyKiller</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p><a href="http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=zNC2HwAaWWE" class="onebox" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=zNC2HwAaWWE</a><br>
Ever heard of an apocalyptic zombie movie? Well this isn’t one of them. This is a vampire movie bitches.</p>
<p>The journey of the movie is to get to a place called New Eden in which is supposedly free of the vampire Apocalypse because of the low population of people. Low population of people means less vampires while the other half of the country contains more vampires because of the higher population. The two main characters consist of a horn dog teenager whose name I never did catch and 40ish year old guy who has no back story but contains some serious survival skills, his name is mister. The start of the movie is great. Half way through is great. Then closer to the end I started to think damn, these guys really are alone. Shit happens and more shit happens and then you realise just how alone these two people are. This is where you develop a bond with the kid and mister. My expectations at the very start of the movie was that mister would die and the kid would go on all alone. I wont say if it happened or not but I will say its something you anticipate through 3/4 of the movie and then something happens. It leaves you thinking why and where the hell did he just… The ending was a bit rushed and it really pissed the movie for me. Everything but the ending was good. I dunno. Maybe you’d like the ending if you like the type of endings where it doesn’t tell you crap about one of the characters and what happened.</p>
<p>This movie is a really good movie. I’d suggest it to anyone looking for a subtle apocalyptic horror movie. I’d rate this movie 9 tabbies out of 10.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/stake-land/535491/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/stake-land/535491/1</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 11 Nov 2013 11:04:28 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-535491-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/stake-land/535491.rss">Stake Land</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
