<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>JailBait</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/jailbait/163413</link>
    <description>I don&#39;t know if you guys have heard of this new porn thing that has come out, my friend showed me it, *Pedofile* Anyways.

If i&#39;m correct this is where the pictures came from, but most of them are real girls that are 14 and 15.

&lt;blockquote&gt;CONCORD, N.H. --Three female athletes whose school or team pictures were found among pornographic photos on the laptop computer of a former Concord High School official are suing him, the school district and the principal.

Article Tools
Printer friendly 
E-mail to a friend 
N.H. RSS feed 
Available RSS feeds 
Most e-mailed 
Share on Digg 
Share on Facebook 
 Save this article 
powered by Del.icio.us 
More:
Globe City/Region stories | 
Latest local news | 
Globe front page | 
Boston.com 
Sign up for: Globe Headlines e-mail | Breaking News Alerts According to the lawsuit, they want to see what school officials found on the computer of former Athletic Director Bill Haubrich and they are seeking an unspecified amount of money.

The athletes &quot;had every reason to believe that the athletic director would regard them as student-athletes and not as fantasy sex objects,&quot; reads the lawsuit, filed by Concord attorney Rick Lehmann. &quot;They also had every reason to expect that the Concord School District would take reasonable steps to supervise its employees. The defendants utterly failed the (athletes) in this regard.&quot;

Neither school officials nor Haubrich&#39;s attorney, Jim Rosenberg of Concord, have filed a response with the court. The district&#39;s lawyer said he could not comment because he had not yet seen the lawsuit.

Haubrich resigned suddenly last month, after serving 27 years with the district.

Several days later, school officials informed the families of a dozen female athletes that inappropriate images concerning their daughters had been found on Haubrich&#39;s school-issued laptop.

Parents of two of the athletes told the Concord Monitor that school officials told them Haubrich had school or team photographs of their daughters as well as pornographic images of look-alike women.

School officials would not let the parents see all the photos they found on the laptop. The parents said they have also not been told if and how their daughter&#39;s images were linked with the pornographic images.

The Concord police began investigating last week after one parent filed a complaint. School officials said they did not notify police because they did not believe any laws had been broken.

In the lawsuit, the three unnamed athletes said they went to court to get answers.

&quot;The fact that these families are being kept completely in the dark by the school constitutes irreparable and ongoing harm,&quot; the lawsuit said.

By not contacting the police, the school has risked losing valuable evidence, the lawsuit said. The lawsuit also faults the district for allegedly taking Haubrich at his word that he had no other similar images and for not investigating Haubrich&#39;s home.

The athletes said one of their primary concerns is the possibility that their images and the pornographic images were linked and shared on the internet.

&quot;In short, the affected parties were simply told to trust Haubrich, who had already violated their trust, and to trust the school, which had already made clear its intent not to share all the information in its possession&quot; with the students or their parents, the lawsuit argues.

Lehmann would not say how much money the athletes are seeking because they don&#39;t know yet the extent of the damage done.&lt;/blockquote&gt;

http://www.boston.com/news/local/new_hampshire/articles/2007/09/08/students_suing_former_school_official_over_photos/

Its old, from september, but i just found out.

I can&#39;t post pictures due to rules, but some of the girls are fine.

No i&#39;m not a pedofile.


What do you think about this, and/or the photos?

(Search google, keywords &quot;JailBait&quot; No quotes.)</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 09 Dec 2007 02:11:15 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>General Discussion</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/jailbait/163413.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>JailBait</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Java_Is_My_Bitch Java Is My Bitch™]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/java_is_my_bitch">@Java_Is_My_Bitch</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>The girls are older than me, im 14 their 15 <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=6" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/jailbait/163413/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/jailbait/163413/5</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 09 Dec 2007 02:11:15 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-163413-5</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/jailbait/163413.rss">JailBait</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>JailBait</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@ninja_nub ninja nub]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/ninja_nub">@ninja_nub</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Well, your age <span class="bbcode-b">is</span> hidden…</p>
<p>Then wait, you 39 <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=6" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/jailbait/163413/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/jailbait/163413/4</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 09 Dec 2007 02:08:57 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-163413-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/jailbait/163413.rss">JailBait</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>JailBait</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Java_Is_My_Bitch Java Is My Bitch™]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/java_is_my_bitch">@Java_Is_My_Bitch</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Nah, im not 40.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/jailbait/163413/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/jailbait/163413/3</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 09 Dec 2007 02:08:13 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-163413-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/jailbait/163413.rss">JailBait</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>JailBait</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@_cake _cake]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/_cake">@_cake</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>wow, pedo.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/jailbait/163413/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/jailbait/163413/2</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 09 Dec 2007 02:07:19 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-163413-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/jailbait/163413.rss">JailBait</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>JailBait</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Java_Is_My_Bitch Java Is My Bitch™]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/java_is_my_bitch">@Java_Is_My_Bitch</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I don’t know if you guys have heard of this new porn thing that has come out, my friend showed me it, <em>Pedofile</em> Anyways.</p>
<p>If i’m correct this is where the pictures came from, but most of them are real girls that are 14 and 15.</p>
<blockquote>CONCORD, N.H. --Three female athletes whose school or team pictures were found among pornographic photos on the laptop computer of a former Concord High School official are suing him, the school district and the principal.
<p>Article Tools<br>
Printer friendly<br>
E-mail to a friend<br>
N.H. RSS feed<br>
Available RSS feeds<br>
Most e-mailed<br>
Share on Digg<br>
Share on Facebook<br>
Save this article<br>
powered by <a href="http://Del.icio.us" rel="nofollow noopener">Del.icio.us</a><br>
More:<br>
Globe City/Region stories |<br>
Latest local news |<br>
Globe front page |<br>
<a href="http://Boston.com" rel="nofollow noopener">Boston.com</a><br>
Sign up for: Globe Headlines e-mail | Breaking News Alerts According to the lawsuit, they want to see what school officials found on the computer of former Athletic Director Bill Haubrich and they are seeking an unspecified amount of money.</p>
<p>The athletes “had every reason to believe that the athletic director would regard them as student-athletes and not as fantasy sex objects,” reads the lawsuit, filed by Concord attorney Rick Lehmann. “They also had every reason to expect that the Concord School District would take reasonable steps to supervise its employees. The defendants utterly failed the (athletes) in this regard.”</p>
<p>Neither school officials nor Haubrich’s attorney, Jim Rosenberg of Concord, have filed a response with the court. The district’s lawyer said he could not comment because he had not yet seen the lawsuit.</p>
<p>Haubrich resigned suddenly last month, after serving 27 years with the district.</p>
<p>Several days later, school officials informed the families of a dozen female athletes that inappropriate images concerning their daughters had been found on Haubrich’s school-issued laptop.</p>
<p>Parents of two of the athletes told the Concord Monitor that school officials told them Haubrich had school or team photographs of their daughters as well as pornographic images of look-alike women.</p>
<p>School officials would not let the parents see all the photos they found on the laptop. The parents said they have also not been told if and how their daughter’s images were linked with the pornographic images.</p>
<p>The Concord police began investigating last week after one parent filed a complaint. School officials said they did not notify police because they did not believe any laws had been broken.</p>
<p>In the lawsuit, the three unnamed athletes said they went to court to get answers.</p>
<p>“The fact that these families are being kept completely in the dark by the school constitutes irreparable and ongoing harm,” the lawsuit said.</p>
<p>By not contacting the police, the school has risked losing valuable evidence, the lawsuit said. The lawsuit also faults the district for allegedly taking Haubrich at his word that he had no other similar images and for not investigating Haubrich’s home.</p>
<p>The athletes said one of their primary concerns is the possibility that their images and the pornographic images were linked and shared on the internet.</p>
<p>“In short, the affected parties were simply told to trust Haubrich, who had already violated their trust, and to trust the school, which had already made clear its intent not to share all the information in its possession” with the students or their parents, the lawsuit argues.</p>
<p>Lehmann would not say how much money the athletes are seeking because they don’t know yet the extent of the damage done.</p>
</blockquote>
<p><a href="http://www.boston.com/news/local/new_hampshire/articles/2007/09/08/students_suing_former_school_official_over_photos/" class="onebox" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">http://www.boston.com/news/local/new_hampshire/articles/2007/09/08/students_suing_former_school_official_over_photos/</a></p>
<p>Its old, from september, but i just found out.</p>
<p>I can’t post pictures due to rules, but some of the girls are fine.</p>
<p>No i’m not a pedofile.</p>
<p>What do you think about this, and/or the photos?</p>
<p>(Search google, keywords “JailBait” No quotes.)</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/jailbait/163413/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/jailbait/163413/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 09 Dec 2007 02:02:05 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-163413-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/jailbait/163413.rss">JailBait</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
