<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Nontitle&#39;s Al Kharid SilverCrafter! [V. 0.85]</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/nontitles-al-kharid-silvercrafter-v-0-85/118444</link>
    <description>A long time ago, before SRL was out, I tried to make this same script, but had so much trouble with randoms and changing colors that i just decided to give up.

   When I found out about SRL, I was very excited. The last version I released took me about 4 days, but it had very inaccurate map walking, it didn&#39;t check for randoms, and the code was very dirty. Well, that&#39;s all over. Say hello to version 0.85!

[B]-=-What It Does-=-[/B]
   This script is very unique from many other scripts. You have to start in the Al Kharid bank with any equipped pickaxe and a Saradomin Symbol mould in your inventory, anywhere but the last slot.

   It will start at the bank, and move it&#39;s way up to the silver in the mining pit. Once it reaches the silver patch, it will mine the silver. Once the inventory is full, it will maneuver it&#39;s way to the furnace and smelt the silver into bars. Afterwards, it moulds them into saradomin symbols and goes back to the bank to store them. Then the loop will start back over and move up to the mine. You can do what you want with the holy symbols gathered, whether that is to string them and/or sell them, you can make good money from them.

[B]-=-What&#39;s New-=-[/B]
   I have fixed many, many things in the script since the last release. First, the mapwalks are much more accurate than before. If you go for 10 rounds, 9 of them will work perfectly.
   This will also detect the randoms in the mine that it wouldn&#39;t detect before. If the pick head falls off, it will detect it right away and look for it. Also, if gas is detected, it will walk to the side and wait until it&#39;s over.
   I&#39;ve also fixed the differences in this script that occurred from the recent runescape update. You will still need SRL 3.81 though.

[B]-=-What&#39;s Left-=-[/B]

-[I]MultiPlayer[/I].
Right now I only have this set up so it works with one character. In the next version I will have MultiPlayer Support.

-[I]Gain Levels[/I].
When you gain a level at the furnace, it will completely stop. If you are nearby while the script is running in the background, then you should be just fine.


[B]-=-Download Links-=-[/B]
I have it in two formats: Colorful HTML and just normal SCAR Pascal text.

HTML: [URL=http://&quot;http://www.nxtitle.net/SilverCrafter/AlKhSilverCrafter085.html&quot;]Al Kharid SilverCrafter 0.85[/URL]
SCAR: [URL=http://&quot;http://www.nxtitle.net/SilverCrafter/AlKhSilverCrafter085.scar&quot;]Al Kharid SilverCrafter 0.85[/URL]

(Old Versions)
HTML: [URL=http://&quot;http://www.nxtitle.net/SilverCrafter/AlKhSilverCrafter020.html&quot;]Al Kharid SilverCrafter 0.20[/URL]
SCAR: [URL=http://&quot;http://www.nxtitle.net/SilverCrafter/AlKhSilverCrafter020.scar&quot;]Al Kharid SilverCrafter 0.20[/URL]

Just a reminder, but make sure you have the latest SCAR and SRL libs when you use this.

[B]-=-More Information-=-[/B]
I am mainly posting this here if anyone wants to help out with this script. Also, if it helps at all, here is some information with the Loc Values:

[I]FirstRun[/I] - Start in bank, and this will bring you to the mine.

[I]GoToMine[/I] - Don&#39;t use this directly. This is the one that actually brings you to the mine.

[I]GetMySilver[/I] - Start beside silver patch. This one mines the silver for you.

[I]GoToFurnace[/I] - Don&#39;t use this directly. This will bring you to the furnace for smelting and crafting.

[I]SmeltMySilver[/I] - Start in Furnace Room. This will smelt your silver into bars.

[I]SilverHolyize[/I] - Start in Furnace Room. This will make your silver bars into holy symbols.

[I]BankJog[/I] - Do not use this directly. This will bring you back to the bank.

[I]StoreInBank[/I] - Start in bank. This will store the symbols in your bank.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 01 Jul 2007 03:34:41 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/nontitles-al-kharid-silvercrafter-v-0-85/118444.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Nontitle&#39;s Al Kharid SilverCrafter! [V. 0.85]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@nontitle nontitle]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/nontitle">@nontitle</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>A long time ago, before SRL was out, I tried to make this same script, but had so much trouble with randoms and changing colors that i just decided to give up.</p>
<p>When I found out about SRL, I was very excited. The last version I released took me about 4 days, but it had very inaccurate map walking, it didn’t check for randoms, and the code was very dirty. Well, that’s all over. Say hello to version 0.85!</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">-=-What It Does-=-</span><br>
This script is very unique from many other scripts. You have to start in the Al Kharid bank with any equipped pickaxe and a Saradomin Symbol mould in your inventory, anywhere but the last slot.</p>
<p>It will start at the bank, and move it’s way up to the silver in the mining pit. Once it reaches the silver patch, it will mine the silver. Once the inventory is full, it will maneuver it’s way to the furnace and smelt the silver into bars. Afterwards, it moulds them into saradomin symbols and goes back to the bank to store them. Then the loop will start back over and move up to the mine. You can do what you want with the holy symbols gathered, whether that is to string them and/or sell them, you can make good money from them.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">-=-What’s New-=-</span><br>
I have fixed many, many things in the script since the last release. First, the mapwalks are much more accurate than before. If you go for 10 rounds, 9 of them will work perfectly.<br>
This will also detect the randoms in the mine that it wouldn’t detect before. If the pick head falls off, it will detect it right away and look for it. Also, if gas is detected, it will walk to the side and wait until it’s over.<br>
I’ve also fixed the differences in this script that occurred from the recent runescape update. You will still need SRL 3.81 though.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">-=-What’s Left-=-</span></p>
<p>-<span class="bbcode-i">MultiPlayer</span>.<br>
Right now I only have this set up so it works with one character. In the next version I will have MultiPlayer Support.</p>
<p>-<span class="bbcode-i">Gain Levels</span>.<br>
When you gain a level at the furnace, it will completely stop. If you are nearby while the script is running in the background, then you should be just fine.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">-=-Download Links-=-</span><br>
I have it in two formats: Colorful HTML and just normal SCAR Pascal text.</p>
<p>HTML: <a data-bbcode="true">Al Kharid SilverCrafter 0.85</a><br>
SCAR: <a data-bbcode="true">Al Kharid SilverCrafter 0.85</a></p>
<p>(Old Versions)<br>
HTML: <a data-bbcode="true">Al Kharid SilverCrafter 0.20</a><br>
SCAR: <a data-bbcode="true">Al Kharid SilverCrafter 0.20</a></p>
<p>Just a reminder, but make sure you have the latest SCAR and SRL libs when you use this.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">-=-More Information-=-</span><br>
I am mainly posting this here if anyone wants to help out with this script. Also, if it helps at all, here is some information with the Loc Values:</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-i">FirstRun</span> - Start in bank, and this will bring you to the mine.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-i">GoToMine</span> - Don’t use this directly. This is the one that actually brings you to the mine.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-i">GetMySilver</span> - Start beside silver patch. This one mines the silver for you.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-i">GoToFurnace</span> - Don’t use this directly. This will bring you to the furnace for smelting and crafting.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-i">SmeltMySilver</span> - Start in Furnace Room. This will smelt your silver into bars.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-i">SilverHolyize</span> - Start in Furnace Room. This will make your silver bars into holy symbols.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-i">BankJog</span> - Do not use this directly. This will bring you back to the bank.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-i">StoreInBank</span> - Start in bank. This will store the symbols in your bank.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/nontitles-al-kharid-silvercrafter-v-0-85/118444/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/nontitles-al-kharid-silvercrafter-v-0-85/118444/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 01 Jul 2007 03:34:41 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-118444-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/nontitles-al-kharid-silvercrafter-v-0-85/118444.rss">Nontitle&#39;s Al Kharid SilverCrafter! [V. 0.85]</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
