<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>How Do i Compile?</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-do-i-compile/408994</link>
    <description>Okay I have no idea how to explain this but I will do my best. I was coding Delta for a few past days and a friend told me I should use PI know for Project Insanity for my Base Source. I just downloaded a shitty Server from the Downloads Section from this website. When I open the source file it has, Bin, Data, deps , src, run, compile and other files that are not worth mentioning. When I go src&gt;server&gt;model&gt;players and/or into packets I get files like ItemonItem, ItemonNPC, ClanChat, Client, Potions. You may wonder whats the problem, so here it is. When I Change something in those .JAVA files I dont see a compiler, I tried Putting a compiler inside the folder with the .JAVA files but I get 100 Errors. I dont understand how I&#39;m suppose to Compile those Files without the compiler being in that folder, but if I go back to the Bin, Data, deps , src, run, compile and compile there, restart server and I see no Changes can somebody please track me on the right road, I got no idea what I&#39;m doing, and also can somebody link me to a good PI Source+Client.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 08 Aug 2011 20:39:15 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-do-i-compile/408994.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>How Do i Compile?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@freshintake freshintake]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/freshintake">@freshintake</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Okay I have no idea how to explain this but I will do my best. I was coding Delta for a few past days and a friend told me I should use PI know for Project Insanity for my Base Source. I just downloaded a shitty Server from the Downloads Section from this website. When I open the source file it has, Bin, Data, deps , src, run, compile and other files that are not worth mentioning. When I go src&gt;server&gt;model&gt;players and/or into packets I get files like ItemonItem, ItemonNPC, ClanChat, Client, Potions. You may wonder whats the problem, so here it is. When I Change something in those .JAVA files I dont see a compiler, I tried Putting a compiler inside the folder with the .JAVA files but I get 100 Errors. I dont understand how I’m suppose to Compile those Files without the compiler being in that folder, but if I go back to the Bin, Data, deps , src, run, compile and compile there, restart server and I see no Changes can somebody please track me on the right road, I got no idea what I’m doing, and also can somebody link me to a good PI Source+Client.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-do-i-compile/408994/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-do-i-compile/408994/1</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 08 Aug 2011 20:39:15 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-408994-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-do-i-compile/408994.rss">How Do i Compile?</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
