<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>317 help about npcs! 317</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/317-help-about-npcs-317/287989</link>
    <description>Hey guys... Yesterday I made my first RS Private server (317) and NPC&#39;s were coded in server. I DIDN&#39;T move any of them or either spawn any. I was playing server and doing some coding in &quot;client.java&quot; but I DIDN&#39;T touch anything about NPC&#39;s. My friend teleported to shops and he asked me where are NPC&#39;s. I teleported there and NPC&#39;s weren&#39;t there. I teleported to home and NPC&#39;s weren&#39;t there either. So i was thinking maybe they moved somewhere, but ALL NPC&#39;s are gone!!! I unpacked source again with no my editing, but NPC&#39;s weren&#39;t there.

I need help with coding them back to server... I&#39;m new to this so I&#39;ll need some extra explanation with it... I only need what files I have to edit and what to edit in them... 

Please help

-Vedran</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 10 Jul 2009 11:27:01 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Game Development</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/317-help-about-npcs-317/287989.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>317 help about npcs! 317</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@HiddenPker HiddenPker]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/hiddenpker">@HiddenPker</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>tis isnt client help move to server help.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/317-help-about-npcs-317/287989/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/317-help-about-npcs-317/287989/2</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jul 2009 11:27:01 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-287989-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/317-help-about-npcs-317/287989.rss">317 help about npcs! 317</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>317 help about npcs! 317</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@CroBunny CroBunny]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/crobunny">@CroBunny</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Hey guys… Yesterday I made my first RS Private server (317) and NPC’s were coded in server. I DIDN’T move any of them or either spawn any. I was playing server and doing some coding in “client.java” but I DIDN’T touch anything about NPC’s. My friend teleported to shops and he asked me where are NPC’s. I teleported there and NPC’s weren’t there. I teleported to home and NPC’s weren’t there either. So i was thinking maybe they moved somewhere, but ALL NPC’s are gone!!! I unpacked source again with no my editing, but NPC’s weren’t there.</p>
<p>I need help with coding them back to server… I’m new to this so I’ll need some extra explanation with it… I only need what files I have to edit and what to edit in them…</p>
<p>Please help</p>
<p>-Vedran</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/317-help-about-npcs-317/287989/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/317-help-about-npcs-317/287989/1</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jul 2009 11:11:26 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-287989-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/317-help-about-npcs-317/287989.rss">317 help about npcs! 317</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
