<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Construction Map Data (REP+)</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/construction-map-data-rep/350205</link>
    <description>Alright, so I have a basic 508 server from the source Berky-Scape.  Now I really like the source because it has almost every skill.  (Including Summoning and Construction)  The construction has a few bugs, and some rooms still need to be added.  One thing that is unrealistic to the construction skill in RuneScape, is that the skill takes place on the mage arena.  So I want to change the coordinates to the normal construction spot/setting, which is 1884 5106 0.  The only thing is when I do the ::tele command to those coordinates, my client freezes.  So I found some topics saying that you need map data to teleport there.  And of coarse, none of those topics provided download links.  I have also tried google and the whole shabang.  So I was wondering if anyone could provide me with a download link with the map data and where to put it, or if you could please tell me how I can get it.  I am kind of new to all of this so if you give me a link, please tell me where I can put it in my client or source....  Thanks so much!  :)</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 20 Jul 2010 16:09:23 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/construction-map-data-rep/350205.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Construction Map Data (REP+)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@drew876567 drew876567]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/drew876567">@drew876567</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Alright, so I have a basic 508 server from the source Berky-Scape.  Now I really like the source because it has almost every skill.  (Including Summoning and Construction)  The construction has a few bugs, and some rooms still need to be added.  One thing that is unrealistic to the construction skill in RuneScape, is that the skill takes place on the mage arena.  So I want to change the coordinates to the normal construction spot/setting, which is 1884 5106 0.  The only thing is when I do the ::tele command to those coordinates, my client freezes.  So I found some topics saying that you need map data to teleport there.  And of coarse, none of those topics provided download links.  I have also tried google and the whole shabang.  So I was wondering if anyone could provide me with a download link with the map data and where to put it, or if you could please tell me how I can get it.  I am kind of new to all of this so if you give me a link, please tell me where I can put it in my client or source…  Thanks so much!  <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=5" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/construction-map-data-rep/350205/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/construction-map-data-rep/350205/1</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jul 2010 16:09:23 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-350205-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/construction-map-data-rep/350205.rss">Construction Map Data (REP+)</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
