<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Famous War Quotes</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/famous-war-quotes/81349</link>
    <description>A country cannot simultaneously prevent and prepare for war.
Albert Einstein

A lot of wonderful people love their country and hate the military.
Bill Clinton

A soldier will fight long and hard for a bit of colored ribbon.
Napoleon Bonaparte

All men are brothers, like the seas throughout the world; So why do winds and waves clash so fiercely everywhere?
Emperor Hirohito

All they that take the sword, shall perish with the sword.
The Bible
Matthew

All war represents a failure of diplomacy.
Tony Benn

All warfare is based on deception.
Sun Tzu
The Art of War

An eye for an eye only makes the whole world blind.
Mahatma Gandhi

An unjust peace is better than a just war.
Cicero

Are bombs the only way of setting fire to the spirit of a people? Is the human will as inert as the past two world-wide wars would indicate?
Gregory Clark

As far as I&#39;m concerned, war always means failure.
Jacques Chirac

As soon as war is looked upon as wicked, it will always have its fascination. When it is looked upon as vulgar, it will cease to be popular.
Oscar Wilde

Britain and France had to choose between war and dishonor. They chose dishonor. They will have war.
Winston Churchill

Come you masters of war
You that build all the guns
You that build the death planes
You that build the big bombs
You that hide behind walls
You that hide behind desks
I just want you to know I can see through your masks.
Bob Dylan

Darkness cannot drive out darkness; only light can do that. Hate cannot drive out hate; only love can do that.
Martin Luther King, Jr.

Either war is obsolete or men are.
R. Buckminster Fuller

England has been offered a choice between war and shame. She has chosen shame and will get war.
Winston Churchill

Every gun that is made, every warship launched, every rocket fired signifies, in the final sense, a theft from those who hunger and are not fed, those who are cold and not clothed.
Dwight D. Eisenhower

God is not on the side of the big battalions, but on the side of those who shoot best.
Voltaire

History teaches that war begins when governments believe the price of aggression is cheap.
Ronald Reagan

History teaches us that war begins when governments believe the price of aggression is cheap.
Ronald Reagan

I ain&#39;t got no quarrel with the Vietcong.
Muhammad Ali (Cassius Clay)

I don&#39;t feel we did wrong in taking this great country away from them. There were great numbers of people who needed new land, and the Indians were selfishly trying to keep it for themselves.
John Wayne

I have seen enough of one war never to wish to see another.
Thomas Jefferson

I know not with what weapons World War III will be fought, but World War IV will be fought with sticks and stones.
Albert Einstein

I love the smell of Napalm in the morning.
Apocalypse Now, movie

I venture to say no war can be long carried on against the will of the people.
Edmund Burke

If we have no peace, it is because we have forgotten that we belong to each other.
Mother Teresa

I&#39;m fed up to the ears with old men dreaming up wars for young men to die in.
George McGovern

In Italy, for thirty years under the Borgias, they had warfare, terror, murder and bloodshed, but they produced Michelangelo, Leonardo da Vinci, and the Renaissance. In Switzerland they had brotherly love, they had five hundred years of democracy and peace, what did they produce? The cuckoo clock.
Orson Welles

In war there is no prize for the runner-up.
General Omar Bradley

In war, resolution; in defeat, defiance; in victory, magnanimity.
Winston Churchill

It is fatal to enter any war without the will to win it.
General Douglas MacArthur

It is only the dead who have seen the end of war.
Plato

It is well that war is so terrible, or we should grow too fond of it.
Robert E. Lee

Kings had always been involving and impoverishing their people in wars, pretending generally, if not always, that the good of the people was the object.
Abraham Lincoln

&quot;Let someone else get killed!&quot;
&quot;Suppose everyone on our side felt that way?&quot;
&quot;Well then I&#39;d certainly be a damned fool to feel any other way, wouldn&#39;t I?&quot;
&quot;Englishmen are dying for England, American&#39;s are dying for America, Germans are dying for Germany, Russians are dying for Russia. There are now fifty or sixty countries fighting in this war. Surely so many countries can all be worth dying for?&quot;
&quot;Anything worth living for,&quot; said Nately, &quot;is worth dying for.&quot;
&quot;And anything worth dying for,&quot; answered the old man, &quot;is certainly worth living for.&quot;
Joseph Heller
Catch 22

Let us therefore brace ourselves to our duties and so bear ourselves that, if the British Empire and its Commonwealth last for a thousand years, men will still say, &#39;This was their finest hour.&#39;
Winston Churchill

Man is the only animal that deals in that atrocity of atrocities, War. He is the only one that gathers his brethren about him and goes forth in cold blood and calm pulse to exterminate his kind. He is the only animal that for sordid wages will march out and help to slaughter strangers of his own species who have done him no harm and with whom he has no quarrel . . . And in the intervals between campaigns he washes the blood off his hands and works for &quot;the universal brotherhood of man&quot; - with his mouth.
Mark Twain

Mankind must put an end to war before war puts an end to mankind.
John F. Kennedy

Never in the field of human conflict was so much owed by so many to so few.
Winston Churchill

Never think that war, no matter how necessary, nor how justified, is not a crime. Ask the infantry and ask the dead.
Ernest Hemingway

No one ever goes into battle thinking God is on the other side.
Terry Goodkind

Of course the people don&#39;t want war. Why should some poor slob on a farm want to risk his life in a war when the best he can get out of it is to come back to his farm in one piece? Naturally, the common people don&#39;t want war: neither in Russia, nor in England, nor for that matter in Germany. That is understood. But after all it is the leaders of the country who determine the policy, and it is always a simple matter to drag the people along, whether it is a democracy, or a fascist dictatorship, or a parliament, or a communist dictatorship . . . Voice or no voice, the people can always be brought to the bidding of the leaders. That is easy. All you have to do is to tell them they are being attacked, and denounce the pacifists for lack of patriotism and exposing the country to danger. (at the Nuremberg Trials, shortly before being sentenced to death)
Hermann Goering

Older men declare war. But it&#39;s the youth who must fight and die!
Herbert Hoover

Once more unto the breach, dear friends, once more, Or close the wall up with our English dead! In peace there&#39;s nothing so becomes a man As modest stillness and humility; But when the blast of war blows in our ears, Then imitate the action of the tiger: Stiffen the sinews, summon up the blood.
William Shakespeare

Only the dead have seen the end of war.
Plato

Politics is war without bloodshed, while war is politics with bloodshed.
Mao Zedong

Put your trust in God; but be sure to keep your powder dry.
Oliver Cromwell

Sixteen hours ago an American airplane dropped one bomb on Hiroshima . . . The force from which the sun draws its power has been loosed against those who brought war to the Far East. (First announcement of the atomic bomb, August 6, 1945)
Harry S Truman

The art of war is simple enough. Find out where your enemy is. Get at him as soon as you can. Strike him as hard as you can, and keep moving.
Ulysses S Grant

The battle of Waterloo was won on the playing fields of Eton.
Arthur Wellesley, Duke of Wellington

The death of one man is a tragedy. The death of millions is a statistic.
Josef Stalin

The Lord is a man of war.
Bible, Exodus

The object of war is not to die for your country but to make the other bastard die for his.
George S. Patton, Jr.

The only winner in the War of 1812 was Tchaikovsky.
Solomon Short

The purple testament of bleeding war.
William Shakespeare

The victor will never be asked if he told the truth.
Adolf Hitler

The War That Will End War.
H. G. Wells

The whole art of war consists of guessing at what is on the other side of the hill.
Arthur Wellesley, Duke of Wellington

The words of his mouth were smoother than butter, but war was in his heart: his words were softer than oil, yet were they drawn swords.
Bible, Psalms

Their sword will become our plow, and from the tears of war the daily bread of future generations will grow.
Adolf Hitler

There never was a good war or a bad peace.
Benjamin Franklin

They wrote in the old days that it is sweet and fitting to die for one&#39;s country. But in modern war, there is nothing sweet nor fitting in your dying. You will die like a dog for no good reason.
Ernest Hemmingway

To be prepared for war is one of the most effectual means of preserving peace.
George Washington

To jaw-jaw is always better than to war-war.
Winston Churchill

Today we did what we had to do. They counted on America to be passive. They were wrong.
Ronald Reagan

Victory at all costs, victory in spite of all terror, victory however long and hard the road may be; for without victory there is no survival.
Winston Churchill

Violence is the last refuge of the incompetent.
Isaac Asimov

War can only be abolished through war, and in order to get rid of the gun it is necessary to take up the gun.
Mao Zedong

War does not determine who is right - only who is left.
Bertrand Russell

War is a bloody, killing business. You&#39;ve got to spill their blood, or they will spill yours. Rip them up the belly. Shoot them in the guts.
George S. Patton, Jr.

War is hell.
William Tecumseh Sherman

&quot;War is Peace&quot; &quot;Freedom is Slavery&quot; &quot;Ignorance is Strength.&quot;
George Orwell
Nineteen Eighty-Four

War is too serious a matter to entrust to military men.
Georges Clemenceau

War may sometimes be a necessary evil. But no matter how necessary, it is always an evil, never a good. We will not learn how to live together in peace by killing each other&#39;s children.
Jimmy Carter

War will exist until that distant day when the conscientious objector enjoys the same reputation and prestige that the warrior does today.
John F. Kennedy

We have the finest food, the finest equipment, the best spirit, and the best men in the world. Why, by God, I actually pity those poor sons-of-bitches we&#39;re going up against. By God, I do.
George S. Patton, Jr.

We have to face the fact that either all of us are going to die together or we are going to learn to live together and if we are to live together we have to talk.
Eleanor Roosevelt

We live in a time where fictitious election results give us a fictitious president. We are now fighting a war for fictitious reasons. Whether it&#39;s the fiction of duct tape or the fictitious &#39;Orange Alerts,&#39; we are against this war, Mr. Bush. Shame on you, Mr. Bush, shame on you. And, whenever you&#39;ve got the Pope and the Dixie Chicks against you, your time is up.
Michael Moore

We make war that we may live in peace.
Aristotle

We shall not flag or fail. We shall go on to the end. We shall fight in France. We shall fight on the seas and oceans. We shall fight, with growing confidence and strength in the air. We shall defend our island, whatever the cost may be. We shall fight on the beaches, we shall fight on the landing grounds, we shall fight in the fields and in the streets. We shall fight in the hills. We shall never surrender.
Winston Churchill

What difference does it make to the dead, the orphans, and the homeless, whether the mad destruction is wrought under the name of totalitarianism or the holy name of liberty and democracy?
Gandhi

When engaged in combat, the vanquishing of thine enemy can be the warrior&#39;s only concern...
This is the first and cardinal rule of combat...
Suppress all human emotion and compassion...
Kill whoever stands in thy way, even if that be Lord God, or Buddha himself...
This truth lies at the heart of the art of combat. Once it is mastered... Thou shall fear no one... Though the devil himself may bar thy way...
Kill Bill, Vol. 1, movie

When people speak to you about a preventive war, you tell them to go and fight it. After my experience, I have come to hate war. War settles nothing.
Dwight D. Eisenhower

When the enemy advances, withdraw; when he stops, harass; when he tires, strike; when he retreats, pursue.
Mao Zedong

When the rich wage war, it&#39;s the poor who die.
Jean-Paul Sartre

When war is declared, Truth is the first casualty.
Arthur Ponsonby

When you have to kill a man it costs nothing to be polite.
Winston Churchill

You can no more win a war than you can win an earthquake.
Jeannette Rankin

You can&#39;t say that civilization don&#39;t advance, however, for in every war they kill you in a new way.
Will Rogers

Let them hate us as long as they fear us -
Caligula

In peace, sons bury their fathers; in war, fathers bury their sons -
Herodotus

I am more afraid of our own mistakes than of our enemies&#39; designs -
Pericles

I came, I saw, I conquered -
Gaius Julius Caesar

The Spartans do not ask how many but where they are -
Agis II of Sparta</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 22 Apr 2007 21:07:59 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>General Discussion</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/famous-war-quotes/81349.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Famous War Quotes</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@pko pko]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/pko">@pko</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“gikid, post:1, topic:81552”][quote author=Moparisthebest link=topic=119568.msg1173978#msg1173978 date=1176859653]<br>
My favorite is:</p>
<p>[quote]The object of war is not to die for your country but to make the other bastard die for his.<br>
George S. Patton, Jr.[/quote]<br>
[/quote]</p>
<p>Lol. Yeah I know.</p>
<p>Anyways Winter Ice, you bore me.</p>
<p>Jeeze guys, it looks like we have another ilyaostr9 on our hands.[/quote]</p>
<p>Ilyaostr was a good member of the community :(…</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/famous-war-quotes/81349/18">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/famous-war-quotes/81349/18</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 22 Apr 2007 21:07:59 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-81349-18</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/famous-war-quotes/81349.rss">Famous War Quotes</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Famous War Quotes</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@jason_x jason_x]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/jason_x">@jason_x</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“The Un-Named, post:16, topic:81349”]Let them hate us as long as they fear us -<br>
Caligula</p>
<p>In peace, sons bury their fathers; in war, fathers bury their sons -<br>
Herodotus</p>
<p>I am more afraid of our own mistakes than of our enemies’ designs -<br>
Pericles</p>
<p>I came, I saw, I conquered -<br>
Gaius Julius Caesar</p>
<p>The Spartans do not ask how many but where they are -<br>
Agis II of Sparta[/quote]</p>
<p>I like these.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/famous-war-quotes/81349/17">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/famous-war-quotes/81349/17</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 22 Apr 2007 21:05:05 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-81349-17</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/famous-war-quotes/81349.rss">Famous War Quotes</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Famous War Quotes</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@The_Un-Named The Un-Named]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/the_un-named">@The_Un-Named</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Let them hate us as long as they fear us -<br>
Caligula</p>
<p>In peace, sons bury their fathers; in war, fathers bury their sons -<br>
Herodotus</p>
<p>I am more afraid of our own mistakes than of our enemies’ designs -<br>
Pericles</p>
<p>I came, I saw, I conquered -<br>
Gaius Julius Caesar</p>
<p>The Spartans do not ask how many but where they are -<br>
Agis II of Sparta</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/famous-war-quotes/81349/16">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/famous-war-quotes/81349/16</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 18 Apr 2007 20:29:06 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-81349-16</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/famous-war-quotes/81349.rss">Famous War Quotes</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Famous War Quotes</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@exe626 exe626]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/exe626">@exe626</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>‘Either war is obsolete or man is’</p>
<p>Did you get these from call of duty? lols I see them when I do something in the game.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/famous-war-quotes/81349/15">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/famous-war-quotes/81349/15</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 18 Apr 2007 15:58:51 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-81349-15</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/famous-war-quotes/81349.rss">Famous War Quotes</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Famous War Quotes</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@pookey71 Pookey71]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/pookey71">@pookey71</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>“Least i got chicken”<br>
'Nuff said.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/famous-war-quotes/81349/14">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/famous-war-quotes/81349/14</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 18 Apr 2007 11:03:43 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-81349-14</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/famous-war-quotes/81349.rss">Famous War Quotes</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Famous War Quotes</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@LegendaryLoser .Flair]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/legendaryloser">@LegendaryLoser</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>If we cannot fight in the day, we shall fight in the dark</p>
<p>Or what ever</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/famous-war-quotes/81349/13">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/famous-war-quotes/81349/13</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 18 Apr 2007 10:41:10 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-81349-13</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/famous-war-quotes/81349.rss">Famous War Quotes</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Famous War Quotes</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@exps35 exps35]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/exps35">@exps35</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>“Dulce et Decorum est<br>
Pro patria mori.”</p>
<p>Wilfred Owen - World war I<br>
<a href="http://www.english.emory.edu/LostPoets/Dulce.html" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">“Dulce et Decorum Est”</a></p>
<p>I’ve always liked that poem.</p>
<p>Oh yea, it basically translates to 'It’s sweet and right to die for ones country"</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/famous-war-quotes/81349/12">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/famous-war-quotes/81349/12</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 18 Apr 2007 08:33:42 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-81349-12</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/famous-war-quotes/81349.rss">Famous War Quotes</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Famous War Quotes</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@zoltanman zoltanman]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/zoltanman">@zoltanman</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>the one by Eleanor Roosevelt<br>
We have to face the fact that either all of us are going to die together or we are going to learn to live together and if we are to live together we have to talk.</p>
<p>That’s actually and excellent quote.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/famous-war-quotes/81349/11">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/famous-war-quotes/81349/11</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 18 Apr 2007 04:27:47 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-81349-11</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/famous-war-quotes/81349.rss">Famous War Quotes</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Famous War Quotes</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Dell451 Dell451]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/dell451">@Dell451</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Demoralize the enemy from within by surprise, terror, sabotage, assassination. This is the war of the future.<br>
-Adolf Hitler</p>
<p>I do not see why man should not be just as cruel as nature.<br>
-Adoulf Hitler</p>
<p>In a man-to-man fight, the winner is he who has one more round in his magazine.<br>
-Erwin Rommel</p>
<p>Don’t worry when you are not recognized, but strive to be worthy of recognition.<br>
-Abraham Lincoln</p>
<p>I am sure you have seen for yourselves and sensed how the Korean people feel towards the United States here in our country.<br>
-Kim Jong Il</p>
<p>The CIA worked very closely with them and United States supported Saddam Hussein at every level - gave him arms, gave him money, gave him political backing, the military helped him; none of this is really fully understood by the American people.<br>
-Peter Camejo</p>
<p>See signature</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/famous-war-quotes/81349/10">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/famous-war-quotes/81349/10</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 18 Apr 2007 04:20:59 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-81349-10</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/famous-war-quotes/81349.rss">Famous War Quotes</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Famous War Quotes</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Gotta_Catch_Them_All Gotta Catch Them All]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/gotta_catch_them_all">@Gotta_Catch_Them_All</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I like this one:</p>
<p>A country cannot simultaneously prevent and prepare for war.<br>
Albert Einstein</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/famous-war-quotes/81349/9">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/famous-war-quotes/81349/9</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 18 Apr 2007 01:51:42 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-81349-9</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/famous-war-quotes/81349.rss">Famous War Quotes</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Famous War Quotes</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@yakman yakman]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/yakman">@yakman</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>thats a <span class="bbcode-b">very</span> nice collection, how long did it take to find them all?</p>
<p>heres an extract from a nice poem</p>
<p>We are the Dead. Short days ago<br>
We lived, felt dawn, saw sunset glow,<br>
Loved and were loved, and now we lie<br>
In Flanders fields.</p>
<p>this is a famous poem, the poet was in a World War One trench, and died while writing it<br>
source: <a href="http://www.arlingtoncemetery.net/flanders.htm" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">Flanders Fields</a></p>
<p>i do like this once</p>
<blockquote>Let us therefore brace ourselves to our duties and so bear ourselves that, if the British Empire and its Commonwealth last for a thousand years, men will still say, 'This was their finest hour.'
Winston Churchill</blockquote>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/famous-war-quotes/81349/8">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/famous-war-quotes/81349/8</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 18 Apr 2007 01:45:30 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-81349-8</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/famous-war-quotes/81349.rss">Famous War Quotes</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Famous War Quotes</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@moparisthebest Moparisthebest]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/moparisthebest">@moparisthebest</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>My favorite is:</p>
<blockquote>The object of war is not to die for your country but to make the other bastard die for his.
George S. Patton, Jr.</blockquote>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/famous-war-quotes/81349/7">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/famous-war-quotes/81349/7</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 18 Apr 2007 01:27:33 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-81349-7</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/famous-war-quotes/81349.rss">Famous War Quotes</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Famous War Quotes</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@goatee goatee]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/goatee">@goatee</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“jason_x, post:5, topic:81349”]When the rich wage war, it’s the poor who die.<br>
Jean-Paul Sartre</p>
<p>This about sums up the United States I wont need any arguments from anyone on this.[/quote]</p>
<p>Rich people join the army…</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/famous-war-quotes/81349/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/famous-war-quotes/81349/6</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 18 Apr 2007 01:15:25 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-81349-6</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/famous-war-quotes/81349.rss">Famous War Quotes</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Famous War Quotes</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@jason_x jason_x]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/jason_x">@jason_x</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>When the rich wage war, it’s the poor who die.<br>
Jean-Paul Sartre</p>
<p>This about sums up the United States I wont need any arguments from anyone on this.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/famous-war-quotes/81349/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/famous-war-quotes/81349/5</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 18 Apr 2007 01:14:14 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-81349-5</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/famous-war-quotes/81349.rss">Famous War Quotes</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Famous War Quotes</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@goatee goatee]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/goatee">@goatee</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“Winter Ice, post:1, topic:81349”]Man is the only animal that deals in that atrocity of atrocities, War. He is the only one that gathers his brethren about him and goes forth in cold blood and calm pulse to exterminate his kind. He is the only animal that for sordid wages will march out and help to slaughter strangers of his own species who have done him no harm and with whom he has no quarrel . . . And in the intervals between campaigns he washes the blood off his hands and works for “the universal brotherhood of man” - with his mouth.<br>
Mark Twain[/quote]</p>
<p>Ever heard of meerkats?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/famous-war-quotes/81349/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/famous-war-quotes/81349/4</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 18 Apr 2007 01:11:18 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-81349-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/famous-war-quotes/81349.rss">Famous War Quotes</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Famous War Quotes</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Winter_Ice Winter Ice]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/winter_ice">@Winter_Ice</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>yeah <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=6" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"> im using one of those in my auto bot <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=6" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/famous-war-quotes/81349/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/famous-war-quotes/81349/3</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 17 Apr 2007 20:42:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-81349-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/famous-war-quotes/81349.rss">Famous War Quotes</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Famous War Quotes</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@ltipt ltipt]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/ltipt">@ltipt</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>nice, some of those are pretty “wise” lol</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/famous-war-quotes/81349/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/famous-war-quotes/81349/2</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 17 Apr 2007 20:38:13 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-81349-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/famous-war-quotes/81349.rss">Famous War Quotes</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Famous War Quotes</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Winter_Ice Winter Ice]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/winter_ice">@Winter_Ice</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>A country cannot simultaneously prevent and prepare for war.<br>
Albert Einstein</p>
<p>A lot of wonderful people love their country and hate the military.<br>
Bill Clinton</p>
<p>A soldier will fight long and hard for a bit of colored ribbon.<br>
Napoleon Bonaparte</p>
<p>All men are brothers, like the seas throughout the world; So why do winds and waves clash so fiercely everywhere?<br>
Emperor Hirohito</p>
<p>All they that take the sword, shall perish with the sword.<br>
The Bible<br>
Matthew</p>
<p>All war represents a failure of diplomacy.<br>
Tony Benn</p>
<p>All warfare is based on deception.<br>
Sun Tzu<br>
The Art of War</p>
<p>An eye for an eye only makes the whole world blind.<br>
Mahatma Gandhi</p>
<p>An unjust peace is better than a just war.<br>
Cicero</p>
<p>Are bombs the only way of setting fire to the spirit of a people? Is the human will as inert as the past two world-wide wars would indicate?<br>
Gregory Clark</p>
<p>As far as I’m concerned, war always means failure.<br>
Jacques Chirac</p>
<p>As soon as war is looked upon as wicked, it will always have its fascination. When it is looked upon as vulgar, it will cease to be popular.<br>
Oscar Wilde</p>
<p>Britain and France had to choose between war and dishonor. They chose dishonor. They will have war.<br>
Winston Churchill</p>
<p>Come you masters of war<br>
You that build all the guns<br>
You that build the death planes<br>
You that build the big bombs<br>
You that hide behind walls<br>
You that hide behind desks<br>
I just want you to know I can see through your masks.<br>
Bob Dylan</p>
<p>Darkness cannot drive out darkness; only light can do that. Hate cannot drive out hate; only love can do that.<br>
Martin Luther King, Jr.</p>
<p>Either war is obsolete or men are.<br>
R. Buckminster Fuller</p>
<p>England has been offered a choice between war and shame. She has chosen shame and will get war.<br>
Winston Churchill</p>
<p>Every gun that is made, every warship launched, every rocket fired signifies, in the final sense, a theft from those who hunger and are not fed, those who are cold and not clothed.<br>
Dwight D. Eisenhower</p>
<p>God is not on the side of the big battalions, but on the side of those who shoot best.<br>
Voltaire</p>
<p>History teaches that war begins when governments believe the price of aggression is cheap.<br>
Ronald Reagan</p>
<p>History teaches us that war begins when governments believe the price of aggression is cheap.<br>
Ronald Reagan</p>
<p>I ain’t got no quarrel with the Vietcong.<br>
Muhammad Ali (Cassius Clay)</p>
<p>I don’t feel we did wrong in taking this great country away from them. There were great numbers of people who needed new land, and the Indians were selfishly trying to keep it for themselves.<br>
John Wayne</p>
<p>I have seen enough of one war never to wish to see another.<br>
Thomas Jefferson</p>
<p>I know not with what weapons World War III will be fought, but World War IV will be fought with sticks and stones.<br>
Albert Einstein</p>
<p>I love the smell of Napalm in the morning.<br>
Apocalypse Now, movie</p>
<p>I venture to say no war can be long carried on against the will of the people.<br>
Edmund Burke</p>
<p>If we have no peace, it is because we have forgotten that we belong to each other.<br>
Mother Teresa</p>
<p>I’m fed up to the ears with old men dreaming up wars for young men to die in.<br>
George McGovern</p>
<p>In Italy, for thirty years under the Borgias, they had warfare, terror, murder and bloodshed, but they produced Michelangelo, Leonardo da Vinci, and the Renaissance. In Switzerland they had brotherly love, they had five hundred years of democracy and peace, what did they produce? The cuckoo clock.<br>
Orson Welles</p>
<p>In war there is no prize for the runner-up.<br>
General Omar Bradley</p>
<p>In war, resolution; in defeat, defiance; in victory, magnanimity.<br>
Winston Churchill</p>
<p>It is fatal to enter any war without the will to win it.<br>
General Douglas MacArthur</p>
<p>It is only the dead who have seen the end of war.<br>
Plato</p>
<p>It is well that war is so terrible, or we should grow too fond of it.<br>
Robert E. Lee</p>
<p>Kings had always been involving and impoverishing their people in wars, pretending generally, if not always, that the good of the people was the object.<br>
Abraham Lincoln</p>
<p>“Let someone else get killed!”<br>
“Suppose everyone on our side felt that way?”<br>
“Well then I’d certainly be a damned fool to feel any other way, wouldn’t I?”<br>
“Englishmen are dying for England, American’s are dying for America, Germans are dying for Germany, Russians are dying for Russia. There are now fifty or sixty countries fighting in this war. Surely so many countries can all be worth dying for?”<br>
“Anything worth living for,” said Nately, “is worth dying for.”<br>
“And anything worth dying for,” answered the old man, “is certainly worth living for.”<br>
Joseph Heller<br>
Catch 22</p>
<p>Let us therefore brace ourselves to our duties and so bear ourselves that, if the British Empire and its Commonwealth last for a thousand years, men will still say, ‘This was their finest hour.’<br>
Winston Churchill</p>
<p>Man is the only animal that deals in that atrocity of atrocities, War. He is the only one that gathers his brethren about him and goes forth in cold blood and calm pulse to exterminate his kind. He is the only animal that for sordid wages will march out and help to slaughter strangers of his own species who have done him no harm and with whom he has no quarrel . . . And in the intervals between campaigns he washes the blood off his hands and works for “the universal brotherhood of man” - with his mouth.<br>
Mark Twain</p>
<p>Mankind must put an end to war before war puts an end to mankind.<br>
John F. Kennedy</p>
<p>Never in the field of human conflict was so much owed by so many to so few.<br>
Winston Churchill</p>
<p>Never think that war, no matter how necessary, nor how justified, is not a crime. Ask the infantry and ask the dead.<br>
Ernest Hemingway</p>
<p>No one ever goes into battle thinking God is on the other side.<br>
Terry Goodkind</p>
<p>Of course the people don’t want war. Why should some poor slob on a farm want to risk his life in a war when the best he can get out of it is to come back to his farm in one piece? Naturally, the common people don’t want war: neither in Russia, nor in England, nor for that matter in Germany. That is understood. But after all it is the leaders of the country who determine the policy, and it is always a simple matter to drag the people along, whether it is a democracy, or a fascist dictatorship, or a parliament, or a communist dictatorship . . . Voice or no voice, the people can always be brought to the bidding of the leaders. That is easy. All you have to do is to tell them they are being attacked, and denounce the pacifists for lack of patriotism and exposing the country to danger. (at the Nuremberg Trials, shortly before being sentenced to death)<br>
Hermann Goering</p>
<p>Older men declare war. But it’s the youth who must fight and die!<br>
Herbert Hoover</p>
<p>Once more unto the breach, dear friends, once more, Or close the wall up with our English dead! In peace there’s nothing so becomes a man As modest stillness and humility; But when the blast of war blows in our ears, Then imitate the action of the tiger: Stiffen the sinews, summon up the blood.<br>
William Shakespeare</p>
<p>Only the dead have seen the end of war.<br>
Plato</p>
<p>Politics is war without bloodshed, while war is politics with bloodshed.<br>
Mao Zedong</p>
<p>Put your trust in God; but be sure to keep your powder dry.<br>
Oliver Cromwell</p>
<p>Sixteen hours ago an American airplane dropped one bomb on Hiroshima . . . The force from which the sun draws its power has been loosed against those who brought war to the Far East. (First announcement of the atomic bomb, August 6, 1945)<br>
Harry S Truman</p>
<p>The art of war is simple enough. Find out where your enemy is. Get at him as soon as you can. Strike him as hard as you can, and keep moving.<br>
Ulysses S Grant</p>
<p>The battle of Waterloo was won on the playing fields of Eton.<br>
Arthur Wellesley, Duke of Wellington</p>
<p>The death of one man is a tragedy. The death of millions is a statistic.<br>
Josef Stalin</p>
<p>The Lord is a man of war.<br>
Bible, Exodus</p>
<p>The object of war is not to die for your country but to make the other bastard die for his.<br>
George S. Patton, Jr.</p>
<p>The only winner in the War of 1812 was Tchaikovsky.<br>
Solomon Short</p>
<p>The purple testament of bleeding war.<br>
William Shakespeare</p>
<p>The victor will never be asked if he told the truth.<br>
Adolf Hitler</p>
<p>The War That Will End War.<br>
H. G. Wells</p>
<p>The whole art of war consists of guessing at what is on the other side of the hill.<br>
Arthur Wellesley, Duke of Wellington</p>
<p>The words of his mouth were smoother than butter, but war was in his heart: his words were softer than oil, yet were they drawn swords.<br>
Bible, Psalms</p>
<p>Their sword will become our plow, and from the tears of war the daily bread of future generations will grow.<br>
Adolf Hitler</p>
<p>There never was a good war or a bad peace.<br>
Benjamin Franklin</p>
<p>They wrote in the old days that it is sweet and fitting to die for one’s country. But in modern war, there is nothing sweet nor fitting in your dying. You will die like a dog for no good reason.<br>
Ernest Hemmingway</p>
<p>To be prepared for war is one of the most effectual means of preserving peace.<br>
George Washington</p>
<p>To jaw-jaw is always better than to war-war.<br>
Winston Churchill</p>
<p>Today we did what we had to do. They counted on America to be passive. They were wrong.<br>
Ronald Reagan</p>
<p>Victory at all costs, victory in spite of all terror, victory however long and hard the road may be; for without victory there is no survival.<br>
Winston Churchill</p>
<p>Violence is the last refuge of the incompetent.<br>
Isaac Asimov</p>
<p>War can only be abolished through war, and in order to get rid of the gun it is necessary to take up the gun.<br>
Mao Zedong</p>
<p>War does not determine who is right - only who is left.<br>
Bertrand Russell</p>
<p>War is a bloody, killing business. You’ve got to spill their blood, or they will spill yours. Rip them up the belly. Shoot them in the guts.<br>
George S. Patton, Jr.</p>
<p>War is hell.<br>
William Tecumseh Sherman</p>
<p>“War is Peace” “Freedom is Slavery” “Ignorance is Strength.”<br>
George Orwell<br>
Nineteen Eighty-Four</p>
<p>War is too serious a matter to entrust to military men.<br>
Georges Clemenceau</p>
<p>War may sometimes be a necessary evil. But no matter how necessary, it is always an evil, never a good. We will not learn how to live together in peace by killing each other’s children.<br>
Jimmy Carter</p>
<p>War will exist until that distant day when the conscientious objector enjoys the same reputation and prestige that the warrior does today.<br>
John F. Kennedy</p>
<p>We have the finest food, the finest equipment, the best spirit, and the best men in the world. Why, by God, I actually pity those poor sons-of-bitches we’re going up against. By God, I do.<br>
George S. Patton, Jr.</p>
<p>We have to face the fact that either all of us are going to die together or we are going to learn to live together and if we are to live together we have to talk.<br>
Eleanor Roosevelt</p>
<p>We live in a time where fictitious election results give us a fictitious president. We are now fighting a war for fictitious reasons. Whether it’s the fiction of duct tape or the fictitious ‘Orange Alerts,’ we are against this war, Mr. Bush. Shame on you, Mr. Bush, shame on you. And, whenever you’ve got the Pope and the Dixie Chicks against you, your time is up.<br>
Michael Moore</p>
<p>We make war that we may live in peace.<br>
Aristotle</p>
<p>We shall not flag or fail. We shall go on to the end. We shall fight in France. We shall fight on the seas and oceans. We shall fight, with growing confidence and strength in the air. We shall defend our island, whatever the cost may be. We shall fight on the beaches, we shall fight on the landing grounds, we shall fight in the fields and in the streets. We shall fight in the hills. We shall never surrender.<br>
Winston Churchill</p>
<p>What difference does it make to the dead, the orphans, and the homeless, whether the mad destruction is wrought under the name of totalitarianism or the holy name of liberty and democracy?<br>
Gandhi</p>
<p>When engaged in combat, the vanquishing of thine enemy can be the warrior’s only concern…<br>
This is the first and cardinal rule of combat…<br>
Suppress all human emotion and compassion…<br>
Kill whoever stands in thy way, even if that be Lord God, or Buddha himself…<br>
This truth lies at the heart of the art of combat. Once it is mastered… Thou shall fear no one… Though the devil himself may bar thy way…<br>
Kill Bill, Vol. 1, movie</p>
<p>When people speak to you about a preventive war, you tell them to go and fight it. After my experience, I have come to hate war. War settles nothing.<br>
Dwight D. Eisenhower</p>
<p>When the enemy advances, withdraw; when he stops, harass; when he tires, strike; when he retreats, pursue.<br>
Mao Zedong</p>
<p>When the rich wage war, it’s the poor who die.<br>
Jean-Paul Sartre</p>
<p>When war is declared, Truth is the first casualty.<br>
Arthur Ponsonby</p>
<p>When you have to kill a man it costs nothing to be polite.<br>
Winston Churchill</p>
<p>You can no more win a war than you can win an earthquake.<br>
Jeannette Rankin</p>
<p>You can’t say that civilization don’t advance, however, for in every war they kill you in a new way.<br>
Will Rogers</p>
<p>Let them hate us as long as they fear us -<br>
Caligula</p>
<p>In peace, sons bury their fathers; in war, fathers bury their sons -<br>
Herodotus</p>
<p>I am more afraid of our own mistakes than of our enemies’ designs -<br>
Pericles</p>
<p>I came, I saw, I conquered -<br>
Gaius Julius Caesar</p>
<p>The Spartans do not ask how many but where they are -<br>
Agis II of Sparta</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/famous-war-quotes/81349/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/famous-war-quotes/81349/1</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 17 Apr 2007 20:34:23 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-81349-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/famous-war-quotes/81349.rss">Famous War Quotes</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
