<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Nevada to vote on legalizing marijuana</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/nevada-to-vote-on-legalizing-marijuana/18763</link>
    <description>[url=http://news.yahoo.com/s/ap/20061017/ap_on_el_st_lo/marijuana_initiative]Nevada to vote on legalizing marijuana[/url]

&lt;blockquote&gt;RENO, Nev. - Gambling, prostitution, and now pot? Organizers of a Nevada ballot measure hope voters in a state where almost everything goes will go one better and legalize marijuana.

If it passes Nov. 7, Nevada will be the first state to allow adults to possess up to an ounce of pot that they could buy at government-regulated marijuana shops.

The Committee to Regulate and Control Marijuana, which has pushed medical marijuana and decriminalization laws around the country, thinks Nevada — with its embrace of certain vices and its streak of Western independence — is a perfect venue.

In an editorial last spring, the rural Lahontan Valley News argued that gambling, Nevada&#39;s most powerful industry, caters to &quot;visceral pleasures,&quot; and that it would hypocritical to oppose the legalization of marijuana on moral grounds.

Proponents of the measure also argue that the legal system wastes time and money on low-level marijuana offenses, and that taxing and regulating pot would put drug dealers out of business while freeing law enforcement to focus on violent crime and more dangerous drugs such as methamphetamine.

&quot;Put it into a tightly controlled and regulated environment. We think that makes a lot of sense,&quot; Neal Levine, executive director of the committee.

Opponents, including law enforcement, the nation&#39;s drug czar, and civic and business groups, argue the measure would encourage the use of other drugs, and they question whether it will even prove to be a good source of tax revenue.

&quot;The fact is, growing, distributing and warehousing marijuana will still be a federal offense,&quot; said Todd Raybuck, a Las Vegas police officer and spokesman for the Committee to Keep Nevada Respectable, which opposes the measure.

Question 7 allows people 21 and older to possess an ounce of marijuana in their homes — the same amount allowed under Nevada&#39;s medical marijuana law. Currently, possession of an ounce or less is a misdemeanor punishable by a $600 fine.

Twelve states have decriminalized small amounts of marijuana — that is, possession is punishable by a ticket and a fine — and 11 allow its use for medical purposes. Possession of up to an ounce at home is legal in Alaska under a court ruling there, but the case is under appeal.

Colorado residents will vote next month on whether to legalize possession of up to an ounce of marijuana by those 21 and older, similar to an ordinance Denver voters approved last year.

But the Nevada measure goes further. It directs Nevada&#39;s Department of Taxation to set up procedures to license and regulate marijuana growers, distributors and retailers. At the same time, it doubles penalties for selling or giving pot to minors and for vehicular manslaughter while under the influence of drugs or alcohol.

The legislation also imposes a $45-per-ounce excise tax, with some of the proceeds going toward the budget and alcohol, tobacco and drug abuse programs. An ounce of pot on the street costs upwards of $300, depending on the quality.

A 2002 study by researchers at the University of Nevada, Las Vegas estimated taxing and regulating marijuana would generate $28.6 million in revenue.

The Justice Department in Washington did not respond to calls and e-mails seeking comment. In June, the
U.S. Supreme Court ruled people who smoke marijuana for medical reasons can be prosecuted under federal drug laws, and Raybuck said it is doubtful federal agents would tolerate commercial pot ventures in Nevada.

In 2002, Nevada voters overwhelmingly rejected a move to legalize up to three ounces of marijuana. The latest measure got onto the ballot after 86,000 people signed petitions.

A poll conducted in September for the Las Vegas Review-Journal found 51 percent of voters opposed Question 7, while 42 percent supported it and 7 percent were undecided.

The measure has found some surprising allies.

&quot;Make no mistake, I don&#39;t think using marijuana is a wise choice for anyone,&quot; said the Rev. William C. Webb, a Baptist minister who joined dozens of other religious leaders in announcing their backing. But &quot;if there has to be a market in marijuana, I&#39;d rather it be regulated with sensible safeguards than run by violent gangs and dangerous drug dealers.&quot;&lt;/blockquote&gt;

It&#39;s a step towards legalized marijuana! :D

So if Nevada goes with this, people can buy up to one ounce of marijuana. Money on cops wasting their time and effors on low level marijuana crimes would diminish and we would have more money to throw at the Iraq War or some other bullshit. Marijuana will be controlled so it won&#39;t be laced with heroin, cocain, meth, pcp or some other drug or narcotic. 

Marijuana would definitely be taxed by the government so Uncle Sam gets his cut out of it. I don&#39;t know how much they would tax, they may tax as much as cigarettes and beer get taxed, which is tons. FYI drug taxes are called &quot;sin taxes&quot;. Obviously this drug will only be sold to people of the age of 21 and older.

People are arguing that this may encourage drug use, but that&#39;s bullshit. Because when marijuana was made illegal (in 1910 in the state of Utah, and after the other 49 states joined in and made it illegal. By the 1930s Marijuana was officially illegal in the USA.) people started using it a lot more, just because it was illegal. This didn&#39;t happen right away, this happened starting in the early 1960s during the hippie movement (against society and all).  People just used it because it was illegal. Even now people at my school use it not just to get high, but because it&#39;s bad and the fact that society says it&#39;s dangerous just makes us even happier when we smoke or drink or chew forms of marijuana. It&#39;s been a protest since the 1960s and it&#39;s going to be that way for a long time until it&#39;s legalized everywhere.

Also the debate of medical marijuana plays in, so people will start heading to Nevada to solve their problems. Such as Alzheimer’s disease, would be cured and prevented by using small doses of marijuana. 

I totally agree with this. I hope they do legalize it. 

~Ron</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2006 23:55:49 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>General Discussion</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/nevada-to-vote-on-legalizing-marijuana/18763.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Nevada to vote on legalizing marijuana</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@R.I.P_RSC R.I.P RSC]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/r.i.p_rsc">@R.I.P_RSC</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Woohoo proud to be dutch  <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/smiley.png?v=9" title=":smiley:" class="emoji" alt=":smiley:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/nevada-to-vote-on-legalizing-marijuana/18763/24">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/nevada-to-vote-on-legalizing-marijuana/18763/24</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2006 23:55:49 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-18763-24</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/nevada-to-vote-on-legalizing-marijuana/18763.rss">Nevada to vote on legalizing marijuana</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Nevada to vote on legalizing marijuana</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Yz85Racer Yz85Racer]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/yz85racer">@Yz85Racer</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“junior, post:22, topic:18763”][quote author=lockedmonkey link=topic=28401.msg346748#msg346748 date=1161755828]<br>
if they do legalize it hell im movin to nevada and i will sit on my porch with a few dubees  sayin ha bith ass cops its legal now so fuck you!<br>
[/quote]<br>
Dam your cool…[/quote]<br>
Lol. I think they would sit there and laugh. Have fun smoking boys. I like my brethe natural.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/nevada-to-vote-on-legalizing-marijuana/18763/23">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/nevada-to-vote-on-legalizing-marijuana/18763/23</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2006 14:26:23 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-18763-23</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/nevada-to-vote-on-legalizing-marijuana/18763.rss">Nevada to vote on legalizing marijuana</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Nevada to vote on legalizing marijuana</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@junior junior]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/junior">@junior</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote no-group" data-post="21" data-topic="18763">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/lockedmonkey/40/5_6259e4fa9dfe0dec282fb0955bb1974c.png" class="avatar"> lockedmonkey:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>if they do legalize it hell im movin to nevada and i will sit on my porch with a few dubees  sayin ha bith ass cops its legal now so fuck you!</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Dam your cool…</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/nevada-to-vote-on-legalizing-marijuana/18763/22">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/nevada-to-vote-on-legalizing-marijuana/18763/22</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2006 08:14:41 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-18763-22</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/nevada-to-vote-on-legalizing-marijuana/18763.rss">Nevada to vote on legalizing marijuana</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Nevada to vote on legalizing marijuana</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@lockedmonkey lockedmonkey]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/lockedmonkey">@lockedmonkey</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>if they do legalize it hell im movin to nevada and i will sit on my porch with a few dubees  sayin ha bith ass cops its legal now so fuck you!</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/nevada-to-vote-on-legalizing-marijuana/18763/21">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/nevada-to-vote-on-legalizing-marijuana/18763/21</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2006 05:57:08 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-18763-21</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/nevada-to-vote-on-legalizing-marijuana/18763.rss">Nevada to vote on legalizing marijuana</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Nevada to vote on legalizing marijuana</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Ron Ron]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/ron">@Ron</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote no-group" data-post="1" data-topic="19346">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/lawl/40/5_6259e4fa9dfe0dec282fb0955bb1974c.png" class="avatar"><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/19346/1">On another topic</a>
</div>
<blockquote>
<p>i partially agree with you, but as long as there is weed there will be people smoking weed, if they choose to ruin their life its not anyone elses problem.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>That’s what everyone’s view should be! MADD keeps changing all these laws for the worse. Grr… feminists…</p>
<p>[quote=“jme_009, post:17, topic:18763”]Sitting at your computer – Now thats just as dangerous. All that radiation coming off your computer screen, etc… Oh wait, computers are fun, and dangerous, yet they are legal!</p>
<p>Read this, <a href="http://www.world-mysteries.com/marijuana1.htm" rel="nofollow noopener">http://www.world-mysteries.com/marijuana1.htm</a><br>
Thats why it is illegal.[/quote]</p>
<p>Sitting at your cojmputer will just ruin your eyes unless you have an LCD screen, no radiation though. <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=9" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"> Hey nice Marijuana link. Yeah I was thinking it was more like the politicians getting cuts off marijuana and people going to jail more than legal drug businesses. It does make a point though. Marijuana is just as dangerous as Smoking or Drinking. If they want to make marijuana illegal, then make all drugs illegal, and watch how many rioters put the politicians’ head on a stick. :eek:</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-post="18" data-topic="18763">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/scar/40/5_6259e4fa9dfe0dec282fb0955bb1974c.png" class="avatar"> Scar:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>EVERYTHING here that is made on earth and is eatable(or smoke-able) is good for humans unless you eat/smoke to much of it&lt;=== thats how i see it</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Just follow what Buddha said and you will live a happy life.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-i">“Moderation is the key”</span> - (I wonder how he got so fat if he believed in moderation? :P)</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-post="19" data-topic="18763">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/jcs_double/40/5_6259e4fa9dfe0dec282fb0955bb1974c.png" class="avatar"> jcs_double:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Dammit i wish it was legal in victoria, Austraila. In 2 states it legal here.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Isn’t it legal in New Zealand? Just swim over. <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/smiley.png?v=9" title=":smiley:" class="emoji" alt=":smiley:"> Naw jk lol, but maybe soon those 2 states will be 3 states that have legalized it. Plus, your family or friends can always get in a car and go on a road trip for some socializing fun.</p>
<p>~Ron</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/nevada-to-vote-on-legalizing-marijuana/18763/20">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/nevada-to-vote-on-legalizing-marijuana/18763/20</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 22 Oct 2006 18:18:33 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-18763-20</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/nevada-to-vote-on-legalizing-marijuana/18763.rss">Nevada to vote on legalizing marijuana</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Nevada to vote on legalizing marijuana</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@jcs_double jcs_double]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/jcs_double">@jcs_double</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Dammit i wish it was legal in victoria, Austraila. In 2 states it legal here.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/nevada-to-vote-on-legalizing-marijuana/18763/19">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/nevada-to-vote-on-legalizing-marijuana/18763/19</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 22 Oct 2006 16:10:32 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-18763-19</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/nevada-to-vote-on-legalizing-marijuana/18763.rss">Nevada to vote on legalizing marijuana</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Nevada to vote on legalizing marijuana</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Scar Scar]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/scar">@Scar</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>EVERYTHING here that is made on earth and is eatable(or smoke-able) is good for humans unless you eat/smoke to much of it&lt;=== thats how i see it</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/nevada-to-vote-on-legalizing-marijuana/18763/18">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/nevada-to-vote-on-legalizing-marijuana/18763/18</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 22 Oct 2006 16:02:19 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-18763-18</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/nevada-to-vote-on-legalizing-marijuana/18763.rss">Nevada to vote on legalizing marijuana</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Nevada to vote on legalizing marijuana</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@jme jme]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/jme">@jme</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote no-group quote-modified" data-post="16" data-topic="18763">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/thabest/40/5_6259e4fa9dfe0dec282fb0955bb1974c.png" class="avatar"> Thabest:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Only people who are fucking retards smoke weed. Dont give me that excuse “its good for you” because its pure bull shit.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>No one said it was good, butit’s hardly considered bad.</p>
<p>Sitting at your computer – Now thats just as dangerous. All that radiation coming off your computer screen, etc… Oh wait, computers are fun, and dangerous, yet they are legal!</p>
<p>Read this, <a href="http://www.world-mysteries.com/marijuana1.htm" rel="nofollow noopener">http://www.world-mysteries.com/marijuana1.htm</a><br>
Thats why it is illegal.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/nevada-to-vote-on-legalizing-marijuana/18763/17">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/nevada-to-vote-on-legalizing-marijuana/18763/17</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 22 Oct 2006 09:43:09 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-18763-17</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/nevada-to-vote-on-legalizing-marijuana/18763.rss">Nevada to vote on legalizing marijuana</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Nevada to vote on legalizing marijuana</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Thabest Thabest]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/thabest">@Thabest</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Only people who are fucking retards smoke weed. Dont give me that excuse “its good for you” because its pure bull shit.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/nevada-to-vote-on-legalizing-marijuana/18763/16">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/nevada-to-vote-on-legalizing-marijuana/18763/16</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 22 Oct 2006 09:38:32 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-18763-16</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/nevada-to-vote-on-legalizing-marijuana/18763.rss">Nevada to vote on legalizing marijuana</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Nevada to vote on legalizing marijuana</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Cheese_Police c|p]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/cheese_police">@Cheese_Police</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Only cool people smoke weed.</p>
<ul>
<li>Cheese_Police rolls another joint.</li>
</ul>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/nevada-to-vote-on-legalizing-marijuana/18763/15">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/nevada-to-vote-on-legalizing-marijuana/18763/15</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 22 Oct 2006 09:36:19 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-18763-15</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/nevada-to-vote-on-legalizing-marijuana/18763.rss">Nevada to vote on legalizing marijuana</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Nevada to vote on legalizing marijuana</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@bullzeye95 bullzeye]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/bullzeye95">@bullzeye95</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“Thabest, post:12, topic:18763”]what kind of fucking loser smokes weed[/quote]Jamie.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/nevada-to-vote-on-legalizing-marijuana/18763/14">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/nevada-to-vote-on-legalizing-marijuana/18763/14</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 22 Oct 2006 09:32:28 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-18763-14</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/nevada-to-vote-on-legalizing-marijuana/18763.rss">Nevada to vote on legalizing marijuana</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Nevada to vote on legalizing marijuana</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@jme jme]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/jme">@jme</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote no-group" data-post="12" data-topic="18763">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/thabest/40/5_6259e4fa9dfe0dec282fb0955bb1974c.png" class="avatar"> Thabest:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>what kind of fucking loser smokes weed</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Lol, funny. Please don’t come back to these forums until you manage to get rid of your ignorance.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/nevada-to-vote-on-legalizing-marijuana/18763/13">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/nevada-to-vote-on-legalizing-marijuana/18763/13</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 22 Oct 2006 09:20:01 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-18763-13</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/nevada-to-vote-on-legalizing-marijuana/18763.rss">Nevada to vote on legalizing marijuana</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Nevada to vote on legalizing marijuana</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Thabest Thabest]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/thabest">@Thabest</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>what kind of fucking loser smokes weed</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/nevada-to-vote-on-legalizing-marijuana/18763/12">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/nevada-to-vote-on-legalizing-marijuana/18763/12</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 22 Oct 2006 09:08:22 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-18763-12</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/nevada-to-vote-on-legalizing-marijuana/18763.rss">Nevada to vote on legalizing marijuana</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Nevada to vote on legalizing marijuana</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Ron Ron]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/ron">@Ron</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“junior, post:10, topic:18763”][quote author=Ron link=topic=28401.msg335388#msg335388 date=1161420166]<br>
NH = New Hampshire and it’s located right above Massachusetts in USA  in the north east corner.<br>
[/quote]<br>
I live in NYC your not that far.[/quote]<br>
I’ve been there a bunch of times. NYC is so much fun. For some reason, the people of NH and Mass(holes) don’t like NY cause they have some problem with the yankees. :rolleyes: NYC rules. <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=9" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/nevada-to-vote-on-legalizing-marijuana/18763/11">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/nevada-to-vote-on-legalizing-marijuana/18763/11</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 22 Oct 2006 05:32:08 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-18763-11</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/nevada-to-vote-on-legalizing-marijuana/18763.rss">Nevada to vote on legalizing marijuana</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Nevada to vote on legalizing marijuana</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@junior junior]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/junior">@junior</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote no-group quote-modified" data-post="7" data-topic="18763">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/ron/40/5_6259e4fa9dfe0dec282fb0955bb1974c.png" class="avatar"> Ron:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>NH = New Hampshire and it’s located right above Massachusetts in USA  in the north east corner.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I live in NYC your not that far.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/nevada-to-vote-on-legalizing-marijuana/18763/10">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/nevada-to-vote-on-legalizing-marijuana/18763/10</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 21 Oct 2006 10:35:38 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-18763-10</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/nevada-to-vote-on-legalizing-marijuana/18763.rss">Nevada to vote on legalizing marijuana</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Nevada to vote on legalizing marijuana</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@animefreak animefreak]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/animefreak">@animefreak</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I Do not use drugs however if it became legal then it would be a lot better for my community, because then they would just be selling stuff that is legal.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/nevada-to-vote-on-legalizing-marijuana/18763/9">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/nevada-to-vote-on-legalizing-marijuana/18763/9</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 21 Oct 2006 10:08:29 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-18763-9</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/nevada-to-vote-on-legalizing-marijuana/18763.rss">Nevada to vote on legalizing marijuana</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Nevada to vote on legalizing marijuana</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Daniel Daniel]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/daniel">@Daniel</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Jesus christ I must make my vote count ;o</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/nevada-to-vote-on-legalizing-marijuana/18763/8">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/nevada-to-vote-on-legalizing-marijuana/18763/8</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 21 Oct 2006 09:20:38 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-18763-8</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/nevada-to-vote-on-legalizing-marijuana/18763.rss">Nevada to vote on legalizing marijuana</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Nevada to vote on legalizing marijuana</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Ron Ron]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/ron">@Ron</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>NH = New Hampshire and it’s located right above Massachusetts in USA  in the north east corner.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/nevada-to-vote-on-legalizing-marijuana/18763/7">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/nevada-to-vote-on-legalizing-marijuana/18763/7</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 21 Oct 2006 08:42:46 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-18763-7</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/nevada-to-vote-on-legalizing-marijuana/18763.rss">Nevada to vote on legalizing marijuana</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Nevada to vote on legalizing marijuana</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@junior junior]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/junior">@junior</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <blockquote>The legislation also imposes a $45-per-ounce excise tax, with some of the proceeds going toward the budget and alcohol, tobacco and drug abuse programs. An ounce of pot on the street costs upwards of $300, depending on the quality.
<p>Average weed is around 175$ an ounce and KB is 200$. Only really haze shit is 300%body%.</p>
</blockquote>
<p>I can get o’s of haze for 225, ak and SourD for 260 or less, and purple for 230 or it depends on the drought.<br>
ak and SourD’s the shit.</p>
<blockquote>Not in my area. In my area it's about 30 dollars per ounce. You should come up to Salem NH, there are really cheap ones here. You buy from the pricey guys from Boston. :rolleyes: Such rip offs lol.</blockquote>
Are you sure its not dirt there selling for 30 bucks a pop?
i know this may sound stupid but wheres NH?
and i rather keep it illegal.
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/nevada-to-vote-on-legalizing-marijuana/18763/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/nevada-to-vote-on-legalizing-marijuana/18763/6</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 21 Oct 2006 07:09:38 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-18763-6</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/nevada-to-vote-on-legalizing-marijuana/18763.rss">Nevada to vote on legalizing marijuana</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Nevada to vote on legalizing marijuana</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Ron Ron]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/ron">@Ron</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote no-group quote-modified" data-post="4" data-topic="18763">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/pault/40/5_6259e4fa9dfe0dec282fb0955bb1974c.png" class="avatar"> PaulT:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>That’s pretty much right. Marijuana became illegal after charges that blacks and mexicans used it to rape white women and lure them into the evils of jazz music were widely spread by newspapers, who (the owner of the newspapers, who also owned paper and textile manufacturing plants, thats who) had much to lose from the modernization of hemp manufacturing techniques. Hemp is one of the most effective energy absorbing systems of life on this planet, and it can be used to create everything from clothing to synthetic steak to fuel for automobiles or manufacturing plants.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Yeah what was the name of the guy who was making up all that propoganda bullshit? Hold on… <em>looks online</em> Aha! His name was Anslinger. <a href="http://blogs.salon.com/0002762/stories/2003/12/22/whyIsMarijuanaIllegal.html" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">Source</a>. What a load of crap. And he was saying that marijuana was basically used only by the mexicans. This guy is such a biggot.</p>
<blockquote>Average weed is around 175$ an ounce and KB is 200$. Only really haze shit is 300.</blockquote>
Not in my area. In my area it's about 30 dollars per ounce. You should come up to Salem NH, there are really cheap ones here. You buy from the pricey guys from Boston. :rolleyes: Such rip offs lol.
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/nevada-to-vote-on-legalizing-marijuana/18763/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/nevada-to-vote-on-legalizing-marijuana/18763/5</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 21 Oct 2006 00:52:05 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-18763-5</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/nevada-to-vote-on-legalizing-marijuana/18763.rss">Nevada to vote on legalizing marijuana</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Nevada to vote on legalizing marijuana</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@PaulT PaulT]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/pault">@PaulT</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <blockquote>People are arguing that this may encourage drug use, but that's bullshit. Because when marijuana was made illegal (in 1910 in the state of Utah, and after the other 49 states joined in and made it illegal. By the 1930s Marijuana was officially illegal in the USA.) people started using it a lot more, just because it was illegal. This didn't happen right away, this happened starting in the early 1960s during the hippie movement (against society and all).  People just used it because it was illegal. Even now people at my school use it not just to get high, but because it's bad and the fact that society says it's dangerous just makes us even happier when we smoke or drink or chew forms of marijuana. It's been a protest since the 1960s and it's going to be that way for a long time until it's legalized everywhere.</blockquote>
<p>That’s pretty much right. Marijuana became illegal after charges that blacks and mexicans used it to rape white women and lure them into the evils of jazz music were widely spread by newspapers, who (the owner of the newspapers, who also owned paper and textile manufacturing plants, thats who) had much to lose from the modernization of hemp manufacturing techniques. Hemp is one of the most effective energy absorbing systems of life on this planet, and it can be used to create everything from clothing to synthetic steak to fuel for automobiles or manufacturing plants.</p>
<p>Oh, and:</p>
<blockquote>The legislation also imposes a $45-per-ounce excise tax, with some of the proceeds going toward the budget and alcohol, tobacco and drug abuse programs. An ounce of pot on the street costs upwards of $300, depending on the quality.</blockquote>
<p>Average weed is around 175$ an ounce and KB is 200$. Only really haze shit is 300$+.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/nevada-to-vote-on-legalizing-marijuana/18763/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/nevada-to-vote-on-legalizing-marijuana/18763/4</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 18 Oct 2006 05:15:29 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-18763-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/nevada-to-vote-on-legalizing-marijuana/18763.rss">Nevada to vote on legalizing marijuana</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Nevada to vote on legalizing marijuana</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@papetowe papetowe]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/papetowe">@papetowe</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Let them legalize it, if your over 18 be dumb enough to make your own mistakes and suffer the consiquences.</p>
<p>Your right about the “kids doing it cause they think its cool”</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/nevada-to-vote-on-legalizing-marijuana/18763/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/nevada-to-vote-on-legalizing-marijuana/18763/3</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 18 Oct 2006 04:13:47 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-18763-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/nevada-to-vote-on-legalizing-marijuana/18763.rss">Nevada to vote on legalizing marijuana</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Nevada to vote on legalizing marijuana</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@VG_Kobra VG_Kobra]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/vg_kobra">@VG_Kobra</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>AMERICA KNOWS NO BOUNDARY! :rolleyes:</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/nevada-to-vote-on-legalizing-marijuana/18763/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/nevada-to-vote-on-legalizing-marijuana/18763/2</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 18 Oct 2006 04:05:17 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-18763-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/nevada-to-vote-on-legalizing-marijuana/18763.rss">Nevada to vote on legalizing marijuana</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Nevada to vote on legalizing marijuana</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Ron Ron]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/ron">@Ron</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p><a href="http://news.yahoo.com/s/ap/20061017/ap_on_el_st_lo/marijuana_initiative" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">Nevada to vote on legalizing marijuana</a></p>
<blockquote>RENO, Nev. - Gambling, prostitution, and now pot? Organizers of a Nevada ballot measure hope voters in a state where almost everything goes will go one better and legalize marijuana.
<p>If it passes Nov. 7, Nevada will be the first state to allow adults to possess up to an ounce of pot that they could buy at government-regulated marijuana shops.</p>
<p>The Committee to Regulate and Control Marijuana, which has pushed medical marijuana and decriminalization laws around the country, thinks Nevada — with its embrace of certain vices and its streak of Western independence — is a perfect venue.</p>
<p>In an editorial last spring, the rural Lahontan Valley News argued that gambling, Nevada’s most powerful industry, caters to “visceral pleasures,” and that it would hypocritical to oppose the legalization of marijuana on moral grounds.</p>
<p>Proponents of the measure also argue that the legal system wastes time and money on low-level marijuana offenses, and that taxing and regulating pot would put drug dealers out of business while freeing law enforcement to focus on violent crime and more dangerous drugs such as methamphetamine.</p>
<p>“Put it into a tightly controlled and regulated environment. We think that makes a lot of sense,” Neal Levine, executive director of the committee.</p>
<p>Opponents, including law enforcement, the nation’s drug czar, and civic and business groups, argue the measure would encourage the use of other drugs, and they question whether it will even prove to be a good source of tax revenue.</p>
<p>“The fact is, growing, distributing and warehousing marijuana will still be a federal offense,” said Todd Raybuck, a Las Vegas police officer and spokesman for the Committee to Keep Nevada Respectable, which opposes the measure.</p>
<p>Question 7 allows people 21 and older to possess an ounce of marijuana in their homes — the same amount allowed under Nevada’s medical marijuana law. Currently, possession of an ounce or less is a misdemeanor punishable by a $600 fine.</p>
<p>Twelve states have decriminalized small amounts of marijuana — that is, possession is punishable by a ticket and a fine — and 11 allow its use for medical purposes. Possession of up to an ounce at home is legal in Alaska under a court ruling there, but the case is under appeal.</p>
<p>Colorado residents will vote next month on whether to legalize possession of up to an ounce of marijuana by those 21 and older, similar to an ordinance Denver voters approved last year.</p>
<p>But the Nevada measure goes further. It directs Nevada’s Department of Taxation to set up procedures to license and regulate marijuana growers, distributors and retailers. At the same time, it doubles penalties for selling or giving pot to minors and for vehicular manslaughter while under the influence of drugs or alcohol.</p>
<p>The legislation also imposes a $45-per-ounce excise tax, with some of the proceeds going toward the budget and alcohol, tobacco and drug abuse programs. An ounce of pot on the street costs upwards of $300, depending on the quality.</p>
<p>A 2002 study by researchers at the University of Nevada, Las Vegas estimated taxing and regulating marijuana would generate $28.6 million in revenue.</p>
<p>The Justice Department in Washington did not respond to calls and e-mails seeking comment. In June, the<br>
U.S. Supreme Court ruled people who smoke marijuana for medical reasons can be prosecuted under federal drug laws, and Raybuck said it is doubtful federal agents would tolerate commercial pot ventures in Nevada.</p>
<p>In 2002, Nevada voters overwhelmingly rejected a move to legalize up to three ounces of marijuana. The latest measure got onto the ballot after 86,000 people signed petitions.</p>
<p>A poll conducted in September for the Las Vegas Review-Journal found 51 percent of voters opposed Question 7, while 42 percent supported it and 7 percent were undecided.</p>
<p>The measure has found some surprising allies.</p>
<p>“Make no mistake, I don’t think using marijuana is a wise choice for anyone,” said the Rev. William C. Webb, a Baptist minister who joined dozens of other religious leaders in announcing their backing. But “if there has to be a market in marijuana, I’d rather it be regulated with sensible safeguards than run by violent gangs and dangerous drug dealers.”</p>
</blockquote>
<p>It’s a step towards legalized marijuana! <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/smiley.png?v=9" title=":smiley:" class="emoji" alt=":smiley:"></p>
<p>So if Nevada goes with this, people can buy up to one ounce of marijuana. Money on cops wasting their time and effors on low level marijuana crimes would diminish and we would have more money to throw at the Iraq War or some other bullshit. Marijuana will be controlled so it won’t be laced with heroin, cocain, meth, pcp or some other drug or narcotic.</p>
<p>Marijuana would definitely be taxed by the government so Uncle Sam gets his cut out of it. I don’t know how much they would tax, they may tax as much as cigarettes and beer get taxed, which is tons. FYI drug taxes are called “sin taxes”. Obviously this drug will only be sold to people of the age of 21 and older.</p>
<p>People are arguing that this may encourage drug use, but that’s bullshit. Because when marijuana was made illegal (in 1910 in the state of Utah, and after the other 49 states joined in and made it illegal. By the 1930s Marijuana was officially illegal in the USA.) people started using it a lot more, just because it was illegal. This didn’t happen right away, this happened starting in the early 1960s during the hippie movement (against society and all).  People just used it because it was illegal. Even now people at my school use it not just to get high, but because it’s bad and the fact that society says it’s dangerous just makes us even happier when we smoke or drink or chew forms of marijuana. It’s been a protest since the 1960s and it’s going to be that way for a long time until it’s legalized everywhere.</p>
<p>Also the debate of medical marijuana plays in, so people will start heading to Nevada to solve their problems. Such as Alzheimer’s disease, would be cured and prevented by using small doses of marijuana.</p>
<p>I totally agree with this. I hope they do legalize it.</p>
<p>~Ron</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/nevada-to-vote-on-legalizing-marijuana/18763/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/nevada-to-vote-on-legalizing-marijuana/18763/1</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 18 Oct 2006 03:57:53 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-18763-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/nevada-to-vote-on-legalizing-marijuana/18763.rss">Nevada to vote on legalizing marijuana</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
