<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Quick RSPS questionnaire</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/quick-rsps-questionnaire/548564</link>
    <description>Hello, I&#39;m doing a lot of research before starting my RSPS. I&#39;ve got experience in the past with running an RSPS and have played both Official Runescape and Private Servers on and off for an extremely long time.

The reason I&#39;ve made this topic is to get your opinions on some questions in order to make the server I will run the best it can be for you guys, the RSPS community!

1) How important is it to you that a server has a forum? (Rate 0-10)                            (0 = Not at all | 10 = Makes or breaks it)
2) How important is a good economy to you? (Rate 0-10)                                            (0 = Not at all | 10 = Makes or breaks it)
3) What XP rates do you prefer personally? (Time to MAX one stat)
4) Donator perks, good or bad? Explain if possible? (If not YES or NO)
5) Do you tend to donate on RSPS&#39;s? Explain if possible?? (If not YES or NO)
6) What&#39;s your favourite client version? (317, 377, 474, 503, 508 etc.)
7) When you first login to a new RSPS, what are the first things you check?
8) What are the basic &quot;Must haves&quot; on an RSPS?
9) What usually makes you stick around on an RSPS?
10) What&#39;s your favourite thing to do on an RSPS? (E.G PK, Quest, Skill etc.)

11) Anything you could tell me to help me win the RSPS community over when the server opens up?

Thank you ever so much for taking your time to read and hopefully answer my quick questionnaire! Every bit of feedback greatly helps me.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2014 03:12:33 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/quick-rsps-questionnaire/548564.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Quick RSPS questionnaire</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Jarker994 Jarker994]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/jarker994">@Jarker994</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote" data-post="15" data-topic="548564">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/chronicles/40/5_e05bb34c421432ee4d40de30c10af3e5.png" class="avatar"> Chronicles:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Make sure that you interact with your community. And you dont always want to act professionel and as the one in charge. Being one of your players creates a good relationship between players and owner. Most of all you want players that stay loyal to <span class="bbcode-b">you</span>.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Certainly, thank for you your feedback Chronicles. Also if you’re able to I would like to have a quick chat with you over Skype or failing that just talking over PM on here? Let me know - my Skype is Jamesbarker994, thank you.</p>
<p>Keep the responses coming in guys, they’re great!</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/quick-rsps-questionnaire/548564/16">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/quick-rsps-questionnaire/548564/16</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2014 03:12:33 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-548564-16</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/quick-rsps-questionnaire/548564.rss">Quick RSPS questionnaire</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Quick RSPS questionnaire</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Chronicles Chronicles]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/chronicles">@Chronicles</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Make sure that you interact with your community. And you dont always want to act professionel and as the one in charge. Being one of your players creates a good relationship between players and owner. Most of all you want players that stay loyal to <span class="bbcode-b">you</span>.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/quick-rsps-questionnaire/548564/15">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/quick-rsps-questionnaire/548564/15</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2014 01:48:48 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-548564-15</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/quick-rsps-questionnaire/548564.rss">Quick RSPS questionnaire</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Quick RSPS questionnaire</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Cres Cres]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/cres">@Cres</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p><span class="bbcode-b">1) How important is it to you that a server has a forum? (Rate 0-10)</span><br>
6/10<br>
Not the most important part but it helps organizing things (events, economy, news, …)</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">2) How important is a good economy to you? (Rate 0-10)</span><br>
8/10<br>
Make well use of money sinks.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">4) Donator perks, good or bad? Explain if possible? (If not YES or NO)</span><br>
Good, so long as they do not prohibit “free” players from getting at least as far as the donators. Also, donations should have<br>
no direct impact on gameplay or status. Members on Runescape don’t receive a crown next to their names either.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">5) Do you tend to donate on RSPS’s? Explain if possible?? (If not YES or NO)</span><br>
No, because that’s exactly what 99.99% of the greedy bastards want me to do. I would pay after playing for at least one year and if the community made me want to help in keeping it alive.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">6) What’s your favourite client version? (317, 377, 474, 503, 508 etc.)</span><br>
459. 474 otherwise.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">7) When you first login to a new RSPS, what are the first things you check?</span></p>
<p>[ul][li] Starting areas shouldn’t be too crowded (general areas shouldn’t be too crowded with features either)[/li]<br>
[li] Spammers/bots[/li]<br>
[li] Accessibility of content (shouldn’t be too easy, shouldn’t be too restricted)[/li]<br>
[li] Depth of content (put some thought into the dialogues, etc…)[/li]<br>
[li] Community (I can’t stand assholes, unless I’m in a position to fuck 'em back)[/li][/ul]</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">8) What are the basic “Must have’s” on an RSPS?</span><br>
Can’t think of anything directly. I guess “something the others don’t have” would be nice.<br>
Capable, active and dedicated staff team.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">9) What usually makes you stick around on an RSPS?</span><br>
Good community and the ability to race to the top position (albeit PK’ing, PvM’ing, skilling, I just need to be able to be the best at something).</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">10) What’s your favourite thing to do on an RSPS? (E.G PK, Quest, Skill etc.)</span><br>
Solo PvM’ing<br>
Anti FC’ing<br>
Tanking shitty pk’ers in multi</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">11) Anything you could tell me to help me win the RSPS community over when the server opens up?</span><br>
Events. Small things. Keep 'em entertained and keep talking with them.<br>
Create a certain atmosphere that the “original” people (the future oldfags of your server) will carry on.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/quick-rsps-questionnaire/548564/14">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/quick-rsps-questionnaire/548564/14</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2014 01:22:11 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-548564-14</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/quick-rsps-questionnaire/548564.rss">Quick RSPS questionnaire</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Quick RSPS questionnaire</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Jarker994 Jarker994]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/jarker994">@Jarker994</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Firstly thanks Matzie for taking your time to read the questions and answer them, that was certainly an interesting and honest survey; luckily I honestly used to be very much into doing the same thing as you so I’m very fixated on ensuring there are minimal or zero bugs (especially ones that effect the eco).</p>
<p>Thanks a lot though Matzie, there’s no such thing as wrong answers as long as you’re honest!</p>
<p>Secondly thanks a lot Lare69 for spending your time reading and answering the survey, my answers started off leaning towards favouritism for 718 servers but now it seems to be going back to around 317!</p>
<p>There was one answer you wrote and I was just wondering if you could possibly expand on just a little so it’s tangible? “3) Not too easy, not too hard.” How many minutes roughly should it take to max a skill? Thanks.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/quick-rsps-questionnaire/548564/13">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/quick-rsps-questionnaire/548564/13</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 21 Dec 2014 14:20:31 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-548564-13</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/quick-rsps-questionnaire/548564.rss">Quick RSPS questionnaire</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Quick RSPS questionnaire</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Clawz_fury lare69]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/clawz_fury">@Clawz_fury</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <ol>
<li>8</li>
<li>10</li>
<li>Not too easy, not too hard.</li>
<li>Depends on the perks, they shouldn’t have an advantage over non-donators.</li>
<li>Nope, waste of money.</li>
<li>Love anything between 317-464.</li>
<li>Home area, npcs in home area, etc.</li>
<li>Uniqueness.</li>
<li>Uniqueness.</li>
<li>Skill, PK, play minigames.</li>
</ol>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/quick-rsps-questionnaire/548564/12">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/quick-rsps-questionnaire/548564/12</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 21 Dec 2014 09:54:57 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-548564-12</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/quick-rsps-questionnaire/548564.rss">Quick RSPS questionnaire</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Quick RSPS questionnaire</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@matzie matzie]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/matzie">@matzie</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <pre><code class="lang-auto">1) How important is it to you that a server has a forum? (Rate 0-10)                            (0 = Not at all | 10 = Makes or breaks it)
2) How important is a good economy to you? (Rate 0-10)                                            (0 = Not at all | 10 = Makes or breaks it)
3) What XP rates do you prefer personally? (Time to MAX one stat)
4) Donator perks, good or bad? Explain if possible? (If not YES or NO)
5) Do you tend to donate on RSPS's? Explain if possible?? (If not YES or NO)
6) What's your favourite client version? (317, 377, 474, 503, 508 etc.)
7) When you first login to a new RSPS, what are the first things you check?
8) What are the basic "Must have's" on an RSPS?
9) What usually makes you stick around on an RSPS?
10) What's your favourite thing to do on an RSPS? (E.G PK, Quest, Skill etc.)</code></pre>
<ol>
<li>
<p>5 - Not really a set in stone thing. It depends how the forum is to be used. Marketing? Player/Bug reports? Appeals?</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>9 - I like to be able to work towards something, but i also like destroying them as well (at least I’m truthful).</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>A week of casual play should be enough to Max 1-2 stats. Obviously will vary by skill, and it should be like that to preserve the ECO.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Not bad. The ability to donate to a professional server is what keeps them alive. Donating for “slight” advantages (1.2x xp boost, Ring of Wealth) are not economy killers. (As long as the ring is well weighted) Also depending on the economy’s scale a cash bonus for every so many hours of gameplay could work. (5-10k/ 4 hours of play in a very low scale eco)</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>nope</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>317 by far - the good ole days of when i just started <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/wink.png?v=5" title=":wink:" class="emoji" alt=":wink:"> still love the noobie melody.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Exploits</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Exploits. lol</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Exploits</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>exploits…</p>
</li>
</ol>
<p>Don’t look at me like im “that” guy. I usually end up as a coder on the server as well <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue_winking_eye.png?v=5" title=":stuck_out_tongue_winking_eye:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue_winking_eye:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/quick-rsps-questionnaire/548564/11">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/quick-rsps-questionnaire/548564/11</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 21 Dec 2014 03:44:29 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-548564-11</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/quick-rsps-questionnaire/548564.rss">Quick RSPS questionnaire</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Quick RSPS questionnaire</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Jarker994 Jarker994]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/jarker994">@Jarker994</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Thank you Elrick, you’re response is very well detailed and helpful!</p>
<p>4 down, keep em’ coming please guys!</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/quick-rsps-questionnaire/548564/10">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/quick-rsps-questionnaire/548564/10</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 20 Dec 2014 15:01:15 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-548564-10</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/quick-rsps-questionnaire/548564.rss">Quick RSPS questionnaire</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Quick RSPS questionnaire</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Elrick Elrick]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/elrick">@Elrick</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <ol>
<li>
<p>How important is it to you that a server has a forum? (Rate 0-10)<br>
<span class="bbcode-b">7/10 - I think a good community doesn’t just exist on a platform that has no archival medium.</span></p>
</li>
<li>
<p>How important is a good economy to you? (Rate 0-10)<br>
[b]10/10 - You need to find the right way to put money in and pump money out, and tier your drops consistently and effectively. Do not make equipment or convenience based shops because they will ruin the economy for that skill or aspect of the game. Only do necessary things in a few shops IF NEEDED.[/B]</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>What XP rates do you prefer personally? (Time to MAX one stat)<br>
<span class="bbcode-b"> Anything from 10-50 for me is ideal. For longevity and difficulty purposes I think lower ended rates are superior because it keeps players from maxing quickly and quitting yourself. This is necessary if you wish to create an effective donation system. HOWEVER, if you are going to do something like a prestige system where players can prestige multiple times and gain perks through it or something then a higher rate may be appropriate. DO NOT do optional xp rates (Easy, Normal, Hard, Extreme) because then your server will suck like the rest of them. It is your server, set your exp rate and take a stand on it. If it is showing to be ineffective for your server then adjust as need be, but I wouldn’t give players the choice to vote on new exp rates and shit like that.</span></p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Donator perks, good or bad? Explain if possible? (If not YES or NO)<br>
<span class="bbcode-b">I think they’re necessary to keep your server going. But, there are right ways to do it. First of all, do donation packages not membership otherwise no one is going to give you money. Secondly, DO NOT SELL ITEMS, STATS, OR ANYTHING THAT WILL PUMP ITEMS/UNNECESSARY EXP INTO YOUR GAME. If you do this you might as well hold up a sign saying “Get rich quick scheme”.<br>
The best way to do it is to do a “premium” based package that provides players with a token system that allows them to purchase AESTHETICS, as well as easier access to publicly made content. At most I would say maybe a donator dungeon is appropriate that provides donators with some amenities for skilling and killing but is not overpowered.</span></p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Do you tend to donate on RSPS’s? Explain if possible?? (If not YES or NO)<br>
<span class="bbcode-b">I do not donate to RSPS because they never prove themselves to be stable or serious enough. If you prove you are serious about maintaining a full constructed server, people will stay and will donate to get those cool perks. I have donated on multiple Minecraft servers because they were able to prove themselves to worthy, so it is possible to get donations out of me lol</span></p>
</li>
<li>
<p>What’s your favourite client version? (317, 377, 474, 503, 508 etc.)<br>
<span class="bbcode-b">I prefer higher revisions, usually like a 718.</span></p>
</li>
<li>
<p>When you first login to a new RSPS, what are the first things you check?<br>
<span class="bbcode-b">I check exp rate, what the home base looks like, how many shops there are, and if there is a stupid teleport book that makes the game way too easy and convenient.</span></p>
</li>
<li>
<p>What are the basic “Must have’s” on an RSPS?<br>
<span class="bbcode-b">A stable economy, no unnecessary stores, no unnecessary teleports for convenience sake, active and humble staff.</span></p>
</li>
<li>
<p>What usually makes you stick around on an RSPS?<br>
<span class="bbcode-b">If a server owner follows the things I have mentioned above to some extent, I will stay and see how things progress.</span></p>
</li>
<li>
<p>What’s your favourite thing to do on an RSPS? (E.G PK, Quest, Skill etc.)<br>
<span class="bbcode-b">I enjoy skilling, which is why I always check to see how easy and stupidly convenient it is to do skills on a server. If you are trying to make the game easy and require no effort I will leave within the first 5 minutes. If I didn’t want to have to try then I would go play a spawn server.</span></p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Anything you could tell me to help me win the RSPS community over when the server opens up?<br>
[b]Choose a respectable name that makes sense. If you name your server DankGreenScape I won’t even click on your advert thread because I can tell the server will be immature and geared towards making people happy and screwing around, not creating a stable environment and economy.</p>
</li>
</ol>
<p>Create a well developed “Development” thread so we can see what your vision for the server is, what your current short and longterm goals are, and what progress has been made since the thread’s creation and in what timely fashion you are creating quality updates.</p>
<p>DO NOT jump the gun and try to show off your server before you have at least 25% of the server done. If you do then most people will get sick of your thread and seeing basic updates occurring.</p>
<p>Create a custom environment. Let’s be honest, most servers are leaching off a specific release. Don’t be one of those people who rip a server, change its name and loading screen image and upload it as your own. Take the time to pick and place unique training monsters and skilling areas. For monsters, look at ones that look cool and take the time to alter the stats to scale to what level you want to fight them. I would much rather fight a level 5 ice giant that has had his stats and loot tables changed, than fight the same boring shit over and over again like rock crabs.[/b]</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/quick-rsps-questionnaire/548564/9">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/quick-rsps-questionnaire/548564/9</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 20 Dec 2014 05:04:43 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-548564-9</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/quick-rsps-questionnaire/548564.rss">Quick RSPS questionnaire</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Quick RSPS questionnaire</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Jarker994 Jarker994]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/jarker994">@Jarker994</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Thank you for your brilliant response Pure_.</p>
<p>I’ve added your questionnaire into my spread sheet. <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=5" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
<p>3 down, hopefully more to come! Keep em’ coming people! I’ve added some new questions to help me better my research too.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/quick-rsps-questionnaire/548564/8">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/quick-rsps-questionnaire/548564/8</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 20 Dec 2014 03:51:15 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-548564-8</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/quick-rsps-questionnaire/548564.rss">Quick RSPS questionnaire</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Quick RSPS questionnaire</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@pure2ownage Pure_]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/pure2ownage">@pure2ownage</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <ol>
<li>How important is it to you that a server has a forum? (Rate 0-10)  8</li>
<li>When you first login to a new RSPS, what are the first things you check?  scim everything, is the game unique or not, are there quests, do i like the interfaces - then i decide to try it for a little longer or move on</li>
<li>What are the basic “Must have’s” on an RSPS? all skills, a few quests and minigames, responsible staff and decent eco</li>
<li>How important is a good economy to you? (Rate 0-10) 10</li>
<li>What usually makes you stick around on an RSPS? community, sense of longevity</li>
<li>Donator perks, good or bad? Explain if possible? bad if very advantageous, cosmetics etc are fine</li>
<li>What’s your favourite thing to do on an RSPS? skill while doing other stuff irl</li>
<li>Do you tend to donate on RSPS’s? Explain if possible?? no, why would i pay for a second-rate game which will probably go offline within a month</li>
<li>What XP rates do you prefer personally? 48hrs of no-lifing to max a skill seems reasonable</li>
</ol>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/quick-rsps-questionnaire/548564/7">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/quick-rsps-questionnaire/548564/7</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2014 22:54:15 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-548564-7</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/quick-rsps-questionnaire/548564.rss">Quick RSPS questionnaire</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Quick RSPS questionnaire</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Jarker994 Jarker994]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/jarker994">@Jarker994</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Thanks for your time and feedback Lil_Smok3r! Highly appreciated.</p>
<p>Keep them coming guys, Thanks!</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/quick-rsps-questionnaire/548564/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/quick-rsps-questionnaire/548564/6</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2014 21:37:04 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-548564-6</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/quick-rsps-questionnaire/548564.rss">Quick RSPS questionnaire</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Quick RSPS questionnaire</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@system system]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/system">@system</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <ol>
<li>How important is it to you that a server has a forum? 10</li>
<li>When you first login to a new RSPS, what are the first things you check?<br>
Starter, shops, training experience and players + staff (to see if they’re friendly)</li>
<li>What are the basic “Must have’s” on an RSPS?<br>
Really fun bosses, active players + staff and a decent EXP rate</li>
<li>How important is a good economy to you? 8</li>
<li>What usually makes you stick around on an RSPS?<br>
Fun players, amazing staff, really fun PVM and minigames</li>
<li>Donator perks, good or bad? Explain if possible? Good AND Bad<br>
Depends how you put it. If the perk was say something like a faster EXP rate, I’d hate that since they’re literally P2W.</li>
<li>What’s your favourite thing to do on an RSPS?<br>
I love to go PVM on RSPS</li>
<li>Do you tend to donate on RSPS’s? Explain if possible?? Nope. I only donate (rarely) if I see a server that’s dedicated and will last a long time (which is also really fun to play)</li>
<li>What XP rates do you prefer personally?<br>
A not too fast and not too slow one (for example, maybe longer than 30mins to max out)</li>
<li>Anything you could tell me to help me win the RSPS community over when the server opens up?<br>
Pick your staff wisely, decent EXP, fun in-game things to do after you’ve maxed like a minigame or something (so people don’t max and quit)</li>
</ol>
<p>Also, customs is one thing to keep in mind. Having SOME customs is cool, but when you overdo it; it kills the game <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/smiley.png?v=5" title=":smiley:" class="emoji" alt=":smiley:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/quick-rsps-questionnaire/548564/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/quick-rsps-questionnaire/548564/5</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2014 21:29:19 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-548564-5</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/quick-rsps-questionnaire/548564.rss">Quick RSPS questionnaire</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Quick RSPS questionnaire</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Jarker994 Jarker994]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/jarker994">@Jarker994</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>First of all thank you for your time Project Runescape, your feedback is a big help to me!</p>
<p>Secondly Pure, that’s fine where would you recommend I put these types of topics in the future?</p>
<p>Lastly, keep the answers coming in please guys I need as much feedback as possible for my research!</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/quick-rsps-questionnaire/548564/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/quick-rsps-questionnaire/548564/4</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2014 20:12:59 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-548564-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/quick-rsps-questionnaire/548564.rss">Quick RSPS questionnaire</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Quick RSPS questionnaire</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@pure2ownage Pure_]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/pure2ownage">@pure2ownage</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>i dont think this is the section for this</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/quick-rsps-questionnaire/548564/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/quick-rsps-questionnaire/548564/3</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2014 14:29:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-548564-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/quick-rsps-questionnaire/548564.rss">Quick RSPS questionnaire</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Quick RSPS questionnaire</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Project_Runescape Project Runescape]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/project_runescape">@Project_Runescape</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <ol>
<li>How important is it to you that a server has a forum? (Rate 0-10)                            (0 = Not at all | 10 = Makes or breaks it)<br>
Its very important to have a forum because most players want to make topics if something happens,ask questions and make guides and more.</li>
<li>When you first login to a new RSPS, what are the first things you check?<br>
The economy, xp rates, shops and the staffs</li>
<li>What are the basic “Must have’s” on an RSPS?<br>
Good economy, forum, active and helpful staffs not to many staffs</li>
<li>How important is a good economy to you? (Rate 0-10)                                            (0 = Not at all | 10 = Makes or breaks it)<br>
9</li>
<li>What usually makes you stick around on an RSPS?<br>
nice staffs, good eco, active pvp this is just my opinion</li>
<li>Donator perks, good or bad? Explain if possible? (If not YES or NO)<br>
not too many features should be donors only</li>
<li>What’s your favourite thing to do on an RSPS? (E.G PK, Quest, Skill etc.)<br>
Quests, pking</li>
<li>Do you tend to donate on RSPS’s? Explain if possible?? (If not YES or NO)<br>
i did donate alot money for rsps couple of years ago but im not playing rsps’s anymore im just doing offline coding when my internet doesnt work.<br>
Good Luck with your RSPS!</li>
</ol>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/quick-rsps-questionnaire/548564/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/quick-rsps-questionnaire/548564/2</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2014 14:23:23 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-548564-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/quick-rsps-questionnaire/548564.rss">Quick RSPS questionnaire</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Quick RSPS questionnaire</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Jarker994 Jarker994]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/jarker994">@Jarker994</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Hello, I’m doing a lot of research before starting my RSPS. I’ve got experience in the past with running an RSPS and have played both Official Runescape and Private Servers on and off for an extremely long time.</p>
<p>The reason I’ve made this topic is to get your opinions on some questions in order to make the server I will run the best it can be for you guys, the RSPS community!</p>
<ol>
<li>
<p>How important is it to you that a server has a forum? (Rate 0-10)                            (0 = Not at all | 10 = Makes or breaks it)</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>How important is a good economy to you? (Rate 0-10)                                            (0 = Not at all | 10 = Makes or breaks it)</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>What XP rates do you prefer personally? (Time to MAX one stat)</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Donator perks, good or bad? Explain if possible? (If not YES or NO)</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Do you tend to donate on RSPS’s? Explain if possible?? (If not YES or NO)</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>What’s your favourite client version? (317, 377, 474, 503, 508 etc.)</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>When you first login to a new RSPS, what are the first things you check?</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>What are the basic “Must haves” on an RSPS?</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>What usually makes you stick around on an RSPS?</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>What’s your favourite thing to do on an RSPS? (E.G PK, Quest, Skill etc.)</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Anything you could tell me to help me win the RSPS community over when the server opens up?</p>
</li>
</ol>
<p>Thank you ever so much for taking your time to read and hopefully answer my quick questionnaire! Every bit of feedback greatly helps me.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/quick-rsps-questionnaire/548564/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/quick-rsps-questionnaire/548564/1</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2014 03:58:22 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-548564-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/quick-rsps-questionnaire/548564.rss">Quick RSPS questionnaire</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
