<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>The God VS Satan religious debate</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-god-vs-satan-religious-debate/451479</link>
    <description>Original thread - http://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php/topic,554181.40.html

Purpose of this thread: there&#39;s just a few points I want to clear up which I can&#39;t do so in the previous thread for obvious reasons. 

&lt;blockquote&gt;Quote from &quot;Pink Phat&quot;, 
&gt;God is more of a peaceful character, who created the world.&lt;/blockquote&gt;

If we&#39;re talking about god of the bible here, god has killed millions more people than satan has. Satan killed 11 people, god killed millions directly or indirectly. Let&#39;s not forget the bible tells tales of god flooding the whole earth to start fresh (and look where that got us).

But by all accounts in the bible god is not peaceful, take the story of the tower of babel for instance, a united man all speaking one language attempted to build a tower that would reach the heavens, god not wanted any of this gave different groups different languages so they could no longer cooperate. Whether or not you interpret this literally or not, it says something about gods character, he would rather divide (and conqueror) man rather than have man cooperate. 

&lt;blockquote&gt;Quote from &quot;heatrn11&quot;, 
&gt;because you obviously don&#39;t understand the difference between God the father, God the son, and God the Holy spirit.&lt;/blockquote&gt;

Would now be a good time to remind you that other people who read and follow the bible don&#39;t believe in the son or holy spirit? There&#39;s several thousand sects of christianity because people who read and follow the bible can&#39;t make up how the bible should be interpreted. Divine word of god? Then why can&#39;t the followers decide on what should be and what shouldn&#39;t be followed. 
&lt;blockquote&gt;Quote from &quot;heatrn11&quot;, 
&gt;God loves, God wants everyone to come with him to heaven, and he gives everyone a choice to pick heaven or hell.&lt;/blockquote&gt;

It&#39;s not a choice though, is it? Do as I say or face eternal damnation of unimaginable agony. That&#39;s like a rapist telling his victim &quot;don&#39;t fight or I will stab you&quot;. I won&#39;t even bring up the idea of free will, either. 

&lt;blockquote&gt;Quote from &quot;heatrn11&quot;, 
&gt;To tell you the reason why God hasn&#39;t proven himself to Earth, is that, God has actually revealed himself in the past.&lt;/blockquote&gt;

But he hasn&#39;t. The bible is not proof that god has proven himself, the bible is the claim that requires the proof. The bible claims god flooded the earth and had 2 of every species of animal on one boat, this is demonstrably false on nearly every point. The bible claims that Jesus was born in nazareth, it has been shown through excavations that there is not and has never been a city on the site where nazareth is claimed to be. The bible claims plagues in Egypt (and was the bane of my childhood religious classes, seeing that I was interested in Egypt and knew that these claims were nothing more than fictional stories despite being 6), again this is demonstrably false as no evidence or historical records exist barring one book. There&#39;s dozens of other things in the bible that are contradictory or have been proven false, the only claims in the bible that can&#39;t be proven false are claims that can&#39;t be proven as well, such as the entity of god. A flying spaghetti monster or the pink unicorn or even a dragon in a garage all share the same properties as god, they cannot be proven and they cannot be proven. Just because you cannot disprove gods existence does not make the idea credible. 

&lt;blockquote&gt;Quote from &quot;heatrn11&quot;, 
&gt;For a future question &#39;Who created God if God created everything?&#39;. Simple answer God wasn&#39;t created he always was, always is and always will be.&lt;/blockquote&gt;

Pure speculation on your part. To quote Carl Sagan, &quot;In many cultures it is customary to answer that God created the universe out of nothing. But this is mere temporizing. If we wish courageously to pursue the question, we must, of course ask next where God comes from? And if we decide this to be unanswerable, why not save a step and conclude that the universe has always existed?&quot;.

&lt;blockquote&gt;Quote from &quot;heatrn11&quot;, 
&gt;Example, Hitler killed thousands of jews, what he did was wrong, but in his mind set he believe it to be right.&lt;/blockquote&gt;

Hitler also said he believed he was doing gods work. Because of the nature of the statement, you really can&#39;t say that he wasn&#39;t. 

&lt;blockquote&gt;Quote from &quot;heatrn11&quot;, 
&gt;So if the kitten was sick and the kitten was dieing, you&#39;d be happy and I&#39;d be in a state of depression.&lt;/blockquote&gt;

Any sane human being who feels empathy wouldn&#39;t feel happy at the suffering of another. This isn&#39;t what you said but it is relevant, some very influential christians have publicly stated that the only reason they do not kill people is because the bible tells them it is wrong. I find such a position saddening, I do not need a creator of a universe personally telling me what is right and wrong, and I do not need threat of punishment to refrain from doing bad things. I feel empathy therefore I do not attempt to place another person in a position of suffering. 

&lt;blockquote&gt;Quote from &quot;heatrn11&quot;, 
&gt;You can&#39;t try and criticize God if you Know close to nothing about his exists or how he thinks.&lt;/blockquote&gt;

But we have the bible that states what god has done and we can criticise those actions. We can prove that a lot of claims in the bible are demonstrably wrong but it doesn&#39;t change the fact that the bible claims that this is how god acts. The bible claims he would rather flood the whole earth and kill all its inhabitants rather than attempt to fix the problems. The bible tells us that because a woman (who had no knowledge of right or wrong, I might add) who ate from a tree, god decided that all humans born are born into sin and must repent. I find the act of blaming people for actions that they were not responsible for and could not have possibility prevented absolutely morally corrupt. 

&lt;blockquote&gt;Quote from &quot;heatrn11&quot;, 
&gt;Only an intelligent designer or creator rather, could put the universe together and make every single particle work with each other.&lt;/blockquote&gt;

If you&#39;re going down the &quot;intelligent design&quot; route, could you perhaps explain some problems with the &quot;intelligent design&quot;? Such as humans having a near useless appendix which can burst requiring people to have them surgically removed. Such as people having wisdom teeth that serve no current purpose, which cause people unnecessary pain and also require the person to have them surgically removed. 

&lt;blockquote&gt;Quote from &quot;heatrn11&quot;, 
&gt;Can i ask you a question? How was the universe formed?&lt;/blockquote&gt;

Well, we start with the big bang, where space-time expanded from an infinitely dense and hot point. Just kidding. This is a trick question, whether or not we know how the universe came to be is irrelevant. Scientists and people who do not believe in a religion do not generally claim to know how the universe came to be, and from a naturalistic standpoint we may never have the means to know. But as I said, it&#39;s irrelevant, as you yourself cannot claim to know how the universe came to be other than pure speculation that god did it, and in which case I want to refer you to the Carl Sagan quote I posted earlier. 

&lt;blockquote&gt;Quote from &quot;Pink Phat&quot;, 
&gt;From an atheist point of view, Satan wll obviously win.&lt;/blockquote&gt;

From an atheist point of view, god and satan are made up constructs found within a book and do not exist. However it&#39;s obvious that satan would win! Hail satan!

&lt;blockquote&gt;Quote from &quot;Loveandpower&quot;, 
&gt;If a person who does not believe in God states they believe in Satan then they are not a real atheist.&lt;/blockquote&gt;

The definition of an atheist is one who is not a theist. The phrase &quot;all babies are atheists&quot; comes about because babies have no knowledge of religion and therefore do not believe it therefore are not theists, so they are atheists. 

Minor nitpick but I feel the distinction has to be made when we&#39;re dealing with people some of whom are under the impression that atheism is a religion.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 05 Aug 2012 04:34:44 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>General Discussion</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-god-vs-satan-religious-debate/451479.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>The God VS Satan religious debate</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@the_elve_age the elve age]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/the_elve_age">@the_elve_age</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>About the great floods</p>
<aside class="onebox whitelistedgeneric">
  <header class="source">
      <img src="https://s.hswstatic.com/en-us/hsw/img/favicon-32x32.png" class="site-icon" width="32" height="32">
      <a href="https://science.howstuffworks.com/nature/climate-weather/storms/great-flood.htm" target="_blank" title="03:00AM - 14 July 2008" rel="nofollow noopener">HowStuffWorks – 14 Jul 08</a>
  </header>
  <article class="onebox-body">
    <div class="aspect-image" style="--aspect-ratio:250/150;"><img src="https://s.hswstatic.com/gif/great-flood-250x150.jpg" class="thumbnail"></div>

<h3><a href="https://science.howstuffworks.com/nature/climate-weather/storms/great-flood.htm" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Was there really a great flood?</a></h3>

<p>Many cultures have a flood myth -- an ancient story of a deluge that swallowed the Earth. So could a great flood really have happened, and how would we be able to tell?</p>


  </article>
  <div class="onebox-metadata">
    
    
  </div>
  <div style="clear: both"></div>
</aside>

<p>Basically it says multiple sources from ALL over the world of ancient cultures suggested that there had been a giant flood at some point. Another story outside of the bible suggests that a man (not Noah) built an arc to save animals and his family. Interesting read.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-god-vs-satan-religious-debate/451479/26">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-god-vs-satan-religious-debate/451479/26</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 05 Aug 2012 04:34:44 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-451479-26</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-god-vs-satan-religious-debate/451479.rss">The God VS Satan religious debate</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The God VS Satan religious debate</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@The_Un-Named The Un-Named]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/the_un-named">@The_Un-Named</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Sorry for the late reply, I’ve been a little preoccupied.</p>
<p>[quote=“the elve age, post:17, topic:451479”][quote]Quote from Niall<br>
If you’re going down the “intelligent design” route, could you perhaps explain some problems with the “intelligent design”? Such as humans having a near useless appendix which can burst requiring people to have them surgically removed. Such as people having wisdom teeth that serve no current purpose, which cause people unnecessary pain and also require the person to have them surgically removed.<br>
[/quote]Evolution.[/quote]</p>
<p>I am fully aware that wisdom teeth and the appendix both have previously had a use, but not necessarily as having a modern use. I am also aware that the appendix may have a modern use.</p>
<p>The argument that I was trying to get at is that it isn’t necessarily intelligent to have such examples as wisdom teeth or an appendix, the wisdom teeth currently serve no purpose and many people are required to have them removed, the appendix can be removed without problems, and while very rare it has been known for people to be born without an appendix. The Intelligent Design theory argues that rather than means such as natural selection, an intelligent design proponent is required, hence slapping an Intelligent Design label on evolution does not many any sense, evolution explains the appendix and wisdom teeth while Intelligent Design cannot.</p>
<p>For the record I am not denying evolution, I consider wisdom teeth and the appendix as two of many examples of evolution, I do not consider them examples of Intelligent Design and I do not consider evolution as a catalyst of Intelligent Design.</p>
<p>[quote=“the elve age, post:17, topic:451479”][quote]Quote from Niall<br>
The bible claims that Jesus was born in nazareth, it has been shown through excavations that there is not and has never been a city on the site where nazareth is claimed to be.[/quote]It is speculated that there was no city called Nazareth DURING biblical time periods. Nazareth was started around the 70 CE period (around the time of the First Jewish War). Artifacts have proven it’s existence.[/quote]</p>
<p>That’s contrary to what I heard, that the artefacts found on the supposed site of nazareth suggest the site was unlikely to be a city.</p>
<p>Let me know if you want to revisit this, I’m not particularly in the mood or capable of digging up sources right now.</p>
<p>[quote=“the elve age, post:17, topic:451479”][quote]Quote from Niall<br>
The bible claims plagues in Egypt (and was the bane of my childhood religious classes, seeing that I was interested in Egypt and knew that these claims were nothing more than fictional stories despite being 6), again this is demonstrably false as no evidence or historical records exist barring one book. [/quote]It has been proven that Egypt did experience plagues during the said biblical time period. Archaeologists do believe that the mythical ten plagues occurred in the ancient city of Pi-Ramses and they have uncovered evidence that leaves questions, as to why an entire capital just vanished? Stalagmites in caves have shown weather changes during the period, it is known that the Ramses environment was a warm, wet climate and had a dramatic shift to an incredible drought.[/quote]</p>
<p>I was under the impression that the only evidence archaeologists have found that would “support” the plagues of the bible was an example of how a chain of natural events could explain all the plagues of the bible. I was unaware that this was being proposed as what actually had happened. Again, please let me know if you want to revisit this as I am unable to dig up sources to clarify anything right now.</p>
<p>One thing I want to add however, the context of my original statement was that not everything the bible states is true or has been proven, the other example that I listed (which you neglected to reply to) was that of a global flood. There is no scientific consensus at all that a global flood ever occurred, there is no evidence to suggest that a global flood ever occurred, there is even evidence against a global flood occurring.</p>
<p>[quote=“the elve age, post:17, topic:451479”][quote]Quote from Niall<br>
I want to elaborate something, god kicked humans out of the garden of eden because eve ate the forbidden fruit, however god never gave adam and eve the knowledge of right and wrong, good and bad so while god forbid eve from eating from the tree she wouldn’t have known it was wrong to do so in the first place[/quote]I just read over Genesis 1-3 directly from the bible. The bible never said that when Adam or Eve were created that they had no knowledge of right or wrong, but had no knowledge of good or evil.[/quote]</p>
<p>Semantics, right and wrong, good and evil. I’ll come back to this shortly, I’m a little pressed for time today and want to try to reply to everyone.</p>
<aside class="quote" data-post="17" data-topic="451479">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 the elve age:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>My information has been gathered from various reliable sites, personal knowledge, research, and the bible. Some of your questions can be answered by research.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I just want to clarify (and this is no excuse heh) that I haven’t (yet) done any research prior to making a post in this thread, that is, I’m merely posting off of memory and what research I have done before. When I will do research for a post I’ll give sources at the bottom.</p>
<aside class="quote quote-modified" data-post="19" data-topic="451479">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/heatrn11/40/5_e05bb34c421432ee4d40de30c10af3e5.png" class="avatar"> heatrn11:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>What I am trying to say is that God gave them a choice, he knew the outcome, he knew every single detail, but yet he still gave them a choice.If that’s not love then I don’t know what is…</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Not much of a choice though is it? God knew and predestined it to happen, whatever eve did was meaningless since god knew beforehand what the outcome would have been. I’d say if he wanted to show love then he would have changed the outcome, not put the tree in the garden in the first place.</p>
<aside class="quote quote-modified" data-post="19" data-topic="451479">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/heatrn11/40/5_e05bb34c421432ee4d40de30c10af3e5.png" class="avatar"> heatrn11:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Not think in your head just this once, that God is real. Wouldn’t you think the death of the millions of humans that he himself created pains him, wouldn’t he hate to let his own ‘children’ go to hell and suffer eternal damnation of unimaginable agony. But God only makes one decision, he never changes his mind, he’s still the same God from the beginning of time, time doesn’t effect him.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I always thought that if god were real he would have to receive some sick and twisted jollies from sending people to hell. One issue I have is that there doesn’t need to be a hell, god could have dropped the whole hell thing and instantly would have been 100 times less evil for doing so, despite being responsible for some sicked up things.</p>
<p>Let me put hell into some perspective, if you do commit a crime in a finite world (earth), you will be punished for an infinite amount of time. You will never, ever stop being punished for this crime. Not only that, the punishment won’t be bad, it won’t be really bad, the punishment you will receive cannot ever be worse. So, for committing a crime you will be punished in the absolute worse way ever for all of eternity. There will never be a time you will not stopped being punished. Worse of all, the crime can be as bad as denying the existence of god.</p>
<p>So, when you say god is all loving I disagree. I say god is all evil for allowing hell to exist. God can remove hell and still leave us on this sick sad world and would merely be a bit of an asshole, instead we’re faced with hell which I think makes god evil.</p>
<aside class="quote quote-modified" data-post="19" data-topic="451479">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/heatrn11/40/5_e05bb34c421432ee4d40de30c10af3e5.png" class="avatar"> heatrn11:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Man will keep trying to understand God with no prevail, they’ll keep trying to get ‘physical’ evidence that he exists, to no prevail. But the evidence is right in your face, ‘ya’ know, but I guess you don’t :S.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>God is an entity that can never be proven to exist, or proven to not exist. Just like the pink unicorn or the flying spaghetti monster.</p>
<aside class="quote quote-modified" data-post="19" data-topic="451479">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/heatrn11/40/5_e05bb34c421432ee4d40de30c10af3e5.png" class="avatar"> heatrn11:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>oh yeah one more thing, I don’t have enough [font=arial black]faith[/font] to be an atheist, because to believe that something was created from nothing just requires A LOT of it.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Being an atheist requires absolutely no faith at all. The only requirement of being an atheist, despite popular opinion, is that you do not believe in a god or gods. One could argue that you are in fact an atheist of the Muslim interpretation of the abrahamic god, or of the Jewish interpretation. You’re definitely an atheist of the hindu gods.</p>
<p>Furthermore, “because to believe that something was created from nothing just requires A LOT of it.” is a strawman argument. The big bang theory does not claim that we were created from nothing. It’s a gross misinterpretation of the theory, which I have explained before and do not wish to explain again when I know it won’t be read. If you want to know more though, please press 1. I can dig the post up if you wish.</p>
<aside class="quote" data-post="22" data-topic="451479">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/m1lkman/40/5_e05bb34c421432ee4d40de30c10af3e5.png" class="avatar"> m1lkman:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>God gave an option and people used their own free will not to listen.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>That’s not free will though. The problem with such a thing as free will is that knowing that you have free will means you do not have free will. Did they use their free will to not be flooded? Nope. They were forced to go with noah or be flooded, they had a choice but they didn’t have free will in the matter.</p>
<p>One could also argue that if god has the power to know what will happen, then we don’t have free will.</p>
<aside class="quote quote-modified" data-post="22" data-topic="451479">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/m1lkman/40/5_e05bb34c421432ee4d40de30c10af3e5.png" class="avatar"> m1lkman:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>[quote]But by all accounts in the bible god is not peaceful, take the story of the tower of babel for instance, a united man all speaking one language attempted to build a tower that would reach the heavens, god not wanted any of this gave different groups different languages so they could no longer cooperate. Whether or not you interpret this literally or not, it says something about gods character, he would rather divide (and conqueror) man rather than have man cooperate. </p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>You are correct in say God is not peaceful. God sent the Israelites to wipe out entire nations of people.</p>
<p>I disagree when you say God “divided and conquered” man. In verse 5 and 6 of Genesis 11 we read that God recognized they could do anything as one. I do not know God’s plan but I would like to speculate; God realized if man learned they could do anything as one, they would put themselves on a pedestal equal with God. God knows the heart of man, we read in Jeremiah 17:9 that, “The heart is deceitful above all things, and desperately wicked: who can know it?”. God knows that man is proud and boastful. Once Man proclaimed they were equal with God, God would have to destroy him. God didn’t want this, instead he chose to give each man a separate tongue.[/quote]</p>
<p>I’m not quite sure what there is to disagree on, perhaps you can elaborate it. Humans under a common language cooperated to build a tower to the heavens, god divided them by separating them to the corners of the earth and giving them a separate tongue so they could no longer cooperate, effectively conquering their plans.</p>
<p>But the whole story is hypothetical, one of my favourite quotes often attributed to Yuri Gagarin, - “I see no God up here”. We’ve flown to the top of the clouds. We’ve exited Earth’s atmosphere into space. We’ve stepped foot on the moon. We’ve sent probes to Mars. We’ve had man made objects (nearly) exit the solar system. If there is a god, he doesn’t exist within our universe.</p>
<aside class="quote quote-modified" data-post="22" data-topic="451479">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/m1lkman/40/5_e05bb34c421432ee4d40de30c10af3e5.png" class="avatar"> m1lkman:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>[quote]Would now be a good time to remind you that other people who read and follow the bible don’t believe in the son or holy spirit? There’s several thousand sects of christianity because people who read and follow the bible can’t make up how the bible should be interpreted. Divine word of god? Then why can’t the followers decide on what should be and what shouldn’t be followed. </p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>If you follow the Bible then you must believe in Jesus Christ (the son). That is a fact, otherwise you are not a Christian. When Christ was baptized by John the Baptist what happened? God came down in the form of a dove and said, “This is my beloved Son, in whom I am well pleased.”</p>
<p>In John 4 23-24 Jesus says, “But the hour cometh, and now is, when the true worshippers shall worship the Father in spirit and in truth: for the Father seeketh such to worship him. God is a Spirit: and they that worship him must worship him in spirit and in truth.” KJV[/quote]</p>
<p>Arguably at least but that isn’t what I said. A definition of a christian is one who believes in the bible and follows the teachings of christ, and as such I consider anyone who believes in the christian god and follows the teachings of christ to be a christian, they don’t necessarily have to believe in jesus or that he existed.</p>
<p>The point I was getting at is that there are several thousand sects of christianity because they believe different things. You can be a christian and not believe in heaven or hell, you can be a christian and believe in heaven and hell. You can be a christian and not follow the 10 commandments, you can be a christian and not believe in angels etc. Christianity is merely a label that simplifies things, anyone remember the catholic-protestant war? If you guys went back to being catholics or protestants or whatever sect you belong to then there would be no unifying belief anymore.</p>
<aside class="quote quote-modified" data-post="22" data-topic="451479">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/m1lkman/40/5_e05bb34c421432ee4d40de30c10af3e5.png" class="avatar"> m1lkman:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>[quote]It’s not a choice though, is it? Do as I say or face eternal damnation of unimaginable agony. That’s like a rapist telling his victim “don’t fight or I will stab you”. I won’t even bring up the idea of free will, either.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>It is a choice. God gave us free will to decide what we want. Why did he give us free will, why not just make robots? God only knows. We read in Matthew 7 13 and 14, Jesus says, “Enter ye in at the strait gate: for wide is the gate, and broad is the way, that leadeth to destruction, and many there be which go in thereat: Because strait is the gate, and narrow is the way, which leadeth unto life, and few there be that find it.”</p>
<p>The Father works in all of our hearts. He gives every single man, woman, and child an option to accept eternal life and many reject him.[/quote]</p>
<p>It’s really not a choice though, is it? Choose between eternal happiness or eternal hellfire, either way you will live in the afterlife for all eternity. What if someone doesn’t want to live in all eternity? They have no choice in the matter, no free will regarding that.</p>
<p>It’s semantics but I feel it’s important, it’s not free will if you’re being forced to pick between either outcome when other options are available.</p>
<aside class="quote quote-modified" data-post="22" data-topic="451479">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/m1lkman/40/5_e05bb34c421432ee4d40de30c10af3e5.png" class="avatar"> m1lkman:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>[quote]The bible claims that Jesus was born in nazareth, it has been shown through excavations that there is not and has never been a city on the site where nazareth is claimed to be.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Jesus was born in Bethlehem but I’m sure that was an honest mistake on your part.  <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=5" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"></p>
<p>God hasn’t shown himself to people because faith cometh by hearing and hearing by the Word of God. I think I’ll just quote the whole of Hebrews 11;</p>
<p>There will come a day when people will accept a man for performing great works: making statues come to life, make fire come down from heaven, etc. People will be amazed and worship him. That man will be the AntiChrist[/quote]</p>
<p>Jesus being born in nazareth was a mistake, he was of course born in bethlehem as you corrected me and was mainly raised in nazareth.</p>
<p>But of course you say god hasn’t shown himself, if you go back and read what I was replying to you can see that heatrn11 has claimed that god has shown himself! Funny how you two can believe in the same thing but not the same thing!</p>
<p>I am of course content with there being no evidence of god not showing himself because he doesn’t choose to or because he doesn’t exist, it’s one of many reasons why I am an atheist. I cannot accept the idea of a god on faith alone.</p>
<aside class="quote quote-modified" data-post="22" data-topic="451479">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/m1lkman/40/5_e05bb34c421432ee4d40de30c10af3e5.png" class="avatar"> m1lkman:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>[quote]Pure speculation on your part. To quote Carl Sagan, “In many cultures it is customary to answer that God created the universe out of nothing. But this is mere temporizing. If we wish courageously to pursue the question, we must, of course ask next where God comes from? And if we decide this to be unanswerable, why not save a step and conclude that the universe has always existed?”.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Just to quote the Bible on this one;</p>
<p>[quote=John 1: 1-3]n the beginning was the Word, and the Word was with God, and the Word was God.</p>
<p>2 The same was in the beginning with God.</p>
<p>3 All things were made by him; and without him was not any thing made that was made.[/quote]<br>
Edit: Had to change the last quote up a little bit.[/quote]</p>
<p>That would of course be unanswerable, the bible says god exists, and the only evidence for this is the bible. The bible is the claim of gods existence, it is not the proof.</p>
<aside class="quote" data-post="22" data-topic="451479">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/m1lkman/40/5_e05bb34c421432ee4d40de30c10af3e5.png" class="avatar"> m1lkman:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>I enjoy these conversations Niall.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Likewise.</p>
<p>[quote=“Mitko, post:23, topic:451479”][quote author=Niall link=topic=554363.msg4060272#msg4060272 date=1343349896]</p>
<p>[quote]Quote from “heatrn11”,</p>
<blockquote>
<p>To tell you the reason why God hasn’t proven himself to Earth, is that, God has actually revealed himself in the past.[/quote]<br>
and knew that these claims were nothing more than fictional stories despite being 6), again this is demonstrably false as no evidence or historical records exist barring one book. There’s dozens of other things in the bible that are contradictory or have been proven false<br>
[/quote]<br>
<a href="http://articles.latimes.com/2012/may/23/science/la-sci-sn-bethlehem-seal-20120523" rel="nofollow noopener">http://articles.latimes.com/2012/may/23/science/la-sci-sn-bethlehem-seal-20120523</a><br>
<a href="http://articles.latimes.com/2004/dec/26/news/adfg-izpool26" rel="nofollow noopener">http://articles.latimes.com/2004/dec/26/news/adfg-izpool26</a></p>
</blockquote>
<p>Just wanted to point that out.[/quote]</p>
<p>I’ll come back to this later, but a news paper article? That’s a bit of a stretch for a credible source, and not the only stretch I can see.</p>
<blockquote>Israeli archaeologists digging near the city of Jerusalem have discovered an ancient clay bulla, about 2,700 years old, bearing the name Bethlehem. The artifact is the only known ancient reference to the city of Jesus' birth found outside the Bible, experts said. The find shows not only that the city existed, but that it probably also had a thriving commercial trade.</blockquote>
<p>Archaeologists discover a clay bulla with a name on it, and that is evidence of a city? You would think the remains of the city would be evidence.</p>
<p>and hooooooooly raptor jesus, if only double posting was permitted then I could have broken this post down into manageable chunks</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-god-vs-satan-religious-debate/451479/25">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-god-vs-satan-religious-debate/451479/25</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 01 Aug 2012 18:33:46 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-451479-25</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-god-vs-satan-religious-debate/451479.rss">The God VS Satan religious debate</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The God VS Satan religious debate</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@f_2_p_2_p_f f 2 p 2 p f]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/f_2_p_2_p_f">@f_2_p_2_p_f</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <blockquote>Quote from "Pink Phat", 
&gt;God is more of a peaceful character, who created the world.</blockquote>
<blockquote>If we're talking about god of the bible here, god has killed millions more people than satan has. Satan killed 11 people, god killed millions directly or indirectly. Let's not forget the bible tells tales of god flooding the whole earth to start fresh (and look where that got us).
<p>But by all accounts in the bible god is not peaceful, take the story of the tower of babel for instance, a united man all speaking one language attempted to build a tower that would reach the heavens, god not wanted any of this gave different groups different languages so they could no longer cooperate. Whether or not you interpret this literally or not, it says something about gods character, he would rather divide (and conqueror) man rather than have man cooperate.</p>
</blockquote>
<p>Apparently being A god gives him the rights over our life because he created us, although I’m not religious.<br>
If god did create man he gave up all rights on us after we began to reproduce &amp; spread, though we kill millions<br>
of animals - not arguing that fact just pointing it out</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-god-vs-satan-religious-debate/451479/24">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-god-vs-satan-religious-debate/451479/24</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 29 Jul 2012 04:20:54 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-451479-24</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-god-vs-satan-religious-debate/451479.rss">The God VS Satan religious debate</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The God VS Satan religious debate</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Mitko Mitko]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/mitko">@Mitko</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“Niall, post:1, topic:451479”][quote]Quote from “heatrn11”,</p>
<blockquote>
<p>To tell you the reason why God hasn’t proven himself to Earth, is that, God has actually revealed himself in the past.[/quote]<br>
and knew that these claims were nothing more than fictional stories despite being 6), again this is demonstrably false as no evidence or historical records exist barring one book. There’s dozens of other things in the bible that are contradictory or have been proven false[/quote]<br>
<a href="http://articles.latimes.com/2012/may/23/science/la-sci-sn-bethlehem-seal-20120523" rel="nofollow noopener">http://articles.latimes.com/2012/may/23/science/la-sci-sn-bethlehem-seal-20120523</a><br>
<a href="http://articles.latimes.com/2004/dec/26/news/adfg-izpool26" rel="nofollow noopener">http://articles.latimes.com/2004/dec/26/news/adfg-izpool26</a></p>
</blockquote>
<p>Just wanted to point that out.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-god-vs-satan-religious-debate/451479/23">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-god-vs-satan-religious-debate/451479/23</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jul 2012 18:51:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-451479-23</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-god-vs-satan-religious-debate/451479.rss">The God VS Satan religious debate</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The God VS Satan religious debate</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@m1lkman m1lkman]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/m1lkman">@m1lkman</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <blockquote>If we're talking about god of the bible here, god has killed millions more people than satan has. Satan killed 11 people, god killed millions directly or indirectly. Let's not forget the bible tells tales of god flooding the whole earth to start fresh (and look where that got us).</blockquote>
<p>Everything happens for a reason. I and nobody else knows God’s plans. We do know, according to the Bible, that the world was an evil place. People were committing sins left and right. God warned the people through Noah that they would die. Anyone who wanted to come onto the ark could, God gave an option and people used their own free will not to listen.</p>
<p>The story of Noah could be interpreted as a version 1.0 of the Rapture. God is giving people an option to either accept Jesus Christ and live eternal life or suffer eternal torture in the Lake of Fire.</p>
<blockquote>But by all accounts in the bible god is not peaceful, take the story of the tower of babel for instance, a united man all speaking one language attempted to build a tower that would reach the heavens, god not wanted any of this gave different groups different languages so they could no longer cooperate. Whether or not you interpret this literally or not, it says something about gods character, he would rather divide (and conqueror) man rather than have man cooperate.</blockquote>
<p>You are correct in say God is not peaceful. God sent the Israelites to wipe out entire nations of people.</p>
<p>I disagree when you say God “divided and conquered” man. In verse 5 and 6 of Genesis 11 we read that God recognized they could do anything as one. I do not know God’s plan but I would like to speculate; God realized if man learned they could do anything as one, they would put themselves on a pedestal equal with God. God knows the heart of man, we read in Jeremiah 17:9 that, “The heart is deceitful above all things, and desperately wicked: who can know it?”. God knows that man is proud and boastful. Once Man proclaimed they were equal with God, God would have to destroy him. God didn’t want this, instead he chose to give each man a separate tongue.</p>
<blockquote>Would now be a good time to remind you that other people who read and follow the bible don't believe in the son or holy spirit? There's several thousand sects of christianity because people who read and follow the bible can't make up how the bible should be interpreted. Divine word of god? Then why can't the followers decide on what should be and what shouldn't be followed.</blockquote>
<p>If you follow the Bible then you must believe in Jesus Christ (the son). That is a fact, otherwise you are not a Christian. When Christ was baptized by John the Baptist what happened? God came down in the form of a dove and said, “This is my beloved Son, in whom I am well pleased.”</p>
<p>In John 4 23-24 Jesus says, “But the hour cometh, and now is, when the true worshippers shall worship the Father in spirit and in truth: for the Father seeketh such to worship him. God is a Spirit: and they that worship him must worship him in spirit and in truth.” KJV</p>
<blockquote>It's not a choice though, is it? Do as I say or face eternal damnation of unimaginable agony. That's like a rapist telling his victim "don't fight or I will stab you". I won't even bring up the idea of free will, either.</blockquote>
<p>It is a choice. God gave us free will to decide what we want. Why did he give us free will, why not just make robots? God only knows. We read in Matthew 7 13 and 14, Jesus says, “Enter ye in at the strait gate: for wide is the gate, and broad is the way, that leadeth to destruction, and many there be which go in thereat: Because strait is the gate, and narrow is the way, which leadeth unto life, and few there be that find it.”</p>
<p>The Father works in all of our hearts. He gives every single man, woman, and child an option to accept eternal life and many reject him.</p>
<blockquote>The bible claims that Jesus was born in nazareth, it has been shown through excavations that there is not and has never been a city on the site where nazareth is claimed to be.</blockquote>
<p>Jesus was born in Bethlehem but I’m sure that was an honest mistake on your part.  <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=5" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"></p>
<p>God hasn’t shown himself to people because faith cometh by hearing and hearing by the Word of God. I think I’ll just quote the whole of Hebrews 11;</p>
<blockquote>Now faith is [the] substantiating of things hoped for, [the] conviction of things not seen.
<p>2 For in [the power of] this the elders have obtained testimony.</p>
<p>3 By faith we apprehend that the worlds were framed by [the] word of God, so that that which is seen should not take its origin from things which appear.</p>
<p>4 By faith Abel offered to God a more excellent sacrifice than Cain, by which he obtained testimony of being righteous, God bearing testimony to his gifts, and by it, having died, he yet speaks.</p>
<p>5 By faith Enoch was translated that he should not see death; and was not found, because God had translated him; for before [his] translation he has the testimony that he had pleased God.</p>
<p>6 But without faith [it is] impossible to please [him]. For he that draws near to God must believe that he is, and [that] he is a rewarder of them who seek him out.</p>
<p>7 By faith, Noah, oracularly warned concerning things not yet seen, moved with fear, prepared an ark for the saving of his house; by which he condemned the world, and became heir of the righteousness which [is] according to faith.</p>
<p>8 By faith Abraham, being called, obeyed to go out into the place which he was to receive for an inheritance, and went out, not knowing where he was going.</p>
<p>9 By faith he sojourned as a stranger in the land of promise as a foreign country, having dwelt in tents with Isaac and Jacob, the heirs with [him] of the same promise;</p>
<p>10 for he waited for the city which has foundations, of which God is [the] artificer and constructor.</p>
<p>11 By faith also Sarah herself received strength for [the] conception of seed, and [that] beyond a seasonable age; since she counted him faithful who promised.</p>
<p>12 Wherefore also there have been born of one, and that of one become dead, even as the stars of heaven in multitude, and as the countless sand which [is] by the sea shore.</p>
<p>13 All these died in faith, not having received the promises, but having seen them from afar off and embraced [them], and confessed that they were strangers and sojourners on the earth.</p>
<p>14 For they who say such things shew clearly that they seek [their] country.</p>
<p>15 And if they had called to mind that from whence they went out, they had had opportunity to have returned;</p>
<p>16 but now they seek a better, that is, a heavenly; wherefore God is not ashamed of them, to be called their God; for he has prepared for them a city.</p>
<p>17 By faith Abraham, [when] tried, offered up Isaac, and he who had received to himself the promises offered up his only begotten [son],</p>
<p>18 as to whom it had been said, In Isaac shall thy seed be called:</p>
<p>19 counting that God [was] able to raise [him] even from among [the] dead, whence also he received him in a figure.</p>
<p>20 By faith Isaac blessed Jacob and Esau concerning things to come.</p>
<p>21 By faith Jacob [when] dying blessed each of the sons of Joseph, and worshipped on the top of his staff.</p>
<p>22 By faith Joseph [when] dying called to mind the going forth of the sons of Israel, and gave commandment concerning his bones.</p>
<p>23 By faith Moses, being born, was hid three months by his parents, because they saw the child beautiful; and they did not fear the injunction of the king.</p>
<p>24 By faith Moses, when he had become great, refused to be called son of Pharaoh’s daughter;</p>
<p>25 choosing rather to suffer affliction along with the people of God than to have [the] temporary pleasure of sin;</p>
<p>26 esteeming the reproach of the Christ greater riches than the treasures of Egypt, for he had respect to the recompense.</p>
<p>27 By faith he left Egypt, not fearing the wrath of the king; for he persevered, as seeing him who is invisible.</p>
<p>28 By faith he celebrated the passover and the sprinkling of the blood, that the destroyer of the firstborn might not touch them.</p>
<p>29 By faith they passed through the Red sea as through dry land; of which the Egyptians having made trial were swallowed up.</p>
<p>30 By faith the walls of Jericho fell, having been encircled for seven days.</p>
<p>31 By faith Rahab the harlot did not perish along with the unbelieving, having received the spies in peace.</p>
<p>32 And what more do I say? For the time would fail me telling of Gideon, and Barak, and Samson, and Jephthah, and David and Samuel, and of the prophets:</p>
<p>33 who by faith overcame kingdoms, wrought righteousness, obtained promises, stopped lions’ mouths,</p>
<p>34 quenched [the] power of fire, escaped [the] edge of the sword, became strong out of weakness, became mighty in war, made [the] armies of strangers give way.</p>
<p>35 Women received their dead again by resurrection; and others were tortured, not having accepted deliverance, that they might get a better resurrection;</p>
<p>36 and others underwent trial of mockings and scourgings, yea, and of bonds and imprisonment.</p>
<p>37 They were stoned, were sawn asunder, were tempted, died by the death of the sword; they went about in sheepskins, in goatskins, destitute, afflicted, evil treated,</p>
<p>38 (of whom the world was not worthy,) wandering in deserts and mountains, and [in] dens and caverns of the earth.</p>
<p>39 And these all, having obtained witness through faith, did not receive the promise,</p>
<p>40 God having foreseen some better thing for us, that they should not be made perfect without us.</p>
</blockquote>
<p>All of those people went by faith. They didn’t need to see works.</p>
<p>There will come a day when people will accept a man for performing great works: making statues come to life, make fire come down from heaven, etc. People will be amazed and worship him. That man will be the AntiChrist</p>
<blockquote>Pure speculation on your part. To quote Carl Sagan, "In many cultures it is customary to answer that God created the universe out of nothing. But this is mere temporizing. If we wish courageously to pursue the question, we must, of course ask next where God comes from? And if we decide this to be unanswerable, why not save a step and conclude that the universe has always existed?".</blockquote>
<p>Just to quote the Bible on this one;</p>
<blockquote>n the beginning was the Word, and the Word was with God, and the Word was God.
<p>2 The same was in the beginning with God.</p>
<p>3 All things were made by him; and without him was not any thing made that was made.</p>
</blockquote><br>
Edit: Had to change the last quote up a little bit.
<p>I enjoy these conversations Niall.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-god-vs-satan-religious-debate/451479/22">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-god-vs-satan-religious-debate/451479/22</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jul 2012 18:22:11 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-451479-22</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-god-vs-satan-religious-debate/451479.rss">The God VS Satan religious debate</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The God VS Satan religious debate</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@heatrn11 heatrn11]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/heatrn11">@heatrn11</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote" data-post="20" data-topic="451479">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/m1lkman/40/5_e05bb34c421432ee4d40de30c10af3e5.png" class="avatar"> m1lkman:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>God already beat Lucifer when he cast him from heaven.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>^</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-god-vs-satan-religious-debate/451479/21">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-god-vs-satan-religious-debate/451479/21</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jul 2012 17:26:12 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-451479-21</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-god-vs-satan-religious-debate/451479.rss">The God VS Satan religious debate</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The God VS Satan religious debate</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@m1lkman m1lkman]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/m1lkman">@m1lkman</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>God already beat Lucifer when he cast him from heaven.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-god-vs-satan-religious-debate/451479/20">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-god-vs-satan-religious-debate/451479/20</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jul 2012 15:37:44 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-451479-20</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-god-vs-satan-religious-debate/451479.rss">The God VS Satan religious debate</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The God VS Satan religious debate</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@heatrn11 heatrn11]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/heatrn11">@heatrn11</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I made the thread to see if people actually knew the difference between both of them, let me reply to this in the fastest way possible hmmmm.</p>
<blockquote>Quote from "Niall", 
&gt;It's not a choice though, is it? Do as I say or face eternal damnation of unimaginable agony. That's like a rapist telling his victim "don't fight or I will stab you". I won't even bring up the idea of free will, either.</blockquote>
The reasons for human beings being here on the Earth in the first place was to worship him, so he created both Adam and eve the first human beings according to the Bible. Now Adam and eve were specifically told by God that they could eat from any tree in the Garden, but not to eat of the Tree of Knowledge and good an evil(If they hadn't eaten from the tree we wouldn't have our knowledge but there wouldn't be death either). But Eve was persuaded by a snake, AKA Satan to eat of the fruit. She ate the fruit, gave some to her husband Adam.
[font=arial black]So what am i trying to clarify?[/font]
What I am trying to say is that God gave them a choice, he knew the outcome, he knew every single detail, but yet he still gave them a choice.If that's not love then I don't know what is...... Maybe it's a father dieing for his family from a home intruder, a son pushing a mother out of the way of a incoming car. Maybe even a family putting a sick dog to rest. 
<p>Not think in your head just this once, that God is real. Wouldn’t you think the death of the millions of humans that he himself created pains him, wouldn’t he hate to let his own ‘children’ go to hell and suffer eternal damnation of unimaginable agony. But God only makes one decision, he never changes his mind, he’s still the same God from the beginning of time, time doesn’t effect him.</p>
<p>We’ll never understand this mainly because we’re mere human beings, we lack the intelligence to comprehend God, we barley understand him, and yet we always defile him. Man will keep trying to understand God with no prevail, they’ll keep trying to get ‘physical’ evidence that he exists, to no prevail. But the evidence is right in your face, ‘ya’ know, but I guess you don’t :S.</p>
<p>[font=arial]I’ll get back to you ‘None believers XD’ when I have the mental capability to(Because I stayed up all night on Black ops o.O) until then it’s sleepy time.[/font]</p>
<p>oh yeah one more thing, I don’t have enough [font=arial black]faith[/font] to be an atheist, because to believe that something was created from nothing just requires A LOT of it.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-god-vs-satan-religious-debate/451479/19">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-god-vs-satan-religious-debate/451479/19</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jul 2012 15:21:52 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-451479-19</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-god-vs-satan-religious-debate/451479.rss">The God VS Satan religious debate</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The God VS Satan religious debate</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Loveandpower Loveandpower]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/loveandpower">@Loveandpower</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I think the title should be changed honestly… you  can’t  just  say  God and  Satan and when  there are several deities out there. That’s like making this specific ally a fight against believers of the christian faith vs nonbelievers. While keeping other religions out.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-god-vs-satan-religious-debate/451479/18">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-god-vs-satan-religious-debate/451479/18</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jul 2012 14:11:15 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-451479-18</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-god-vs-satan-religious-debate/451479.rss">The God VS Satan religious debate</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The God VS Satan religious debate</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@the_elve_age the elve age]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/the_elve_age">@the_elve_age</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I would like to debate a few of your points, and don’t take anything said personally (as it’s a debate).</p>
<blockquote>Quote from Niall
If you're going down the "intelligent design" route, could you perhaps explain some problems with the "intelligent design"? Such as humans having a near useless appendix which can burst requiring people to have them surgically removed. Such as people having wisdom teeth that serve no current purpose, which cause people unnecessary pain and also require the person to have them surgically removed.</blockquote>Evolution. It is speculated among evolutionary researchers that over time humans have evolved, and it is proven. Humans have changed over time, and there are fossils of giant fossils, as with dwarven-like fossils. It's speculated that over time the cranium became smaller and wisdom teeth weren't needed. The appendix HAS been proven to have a use - which is that it creates endocrine cells which help with peptide hormones and other various chemicals. It's also considered a safe-house for bacteria essential for digestion in the stomach.
<blockquote>Quote from Niall
The bible claims that Jesus was born in nazareth, it has been shown through excavations that there is not and has never been a city on the site where nazareth is claimed to be.</blockquote>It is speculated that there was no city called Nazareth DURING biblical time periods. Nazareth was started around the 70 CE period (around the time of the First Jewish War). Artifacts have proven it's existence. 
<blockquote>Quote from Niall
The bible claims plagues in Egypt (and was the bane of my childhood religious classes, seeing that I was interested in Egypt and knew that these claims were nothing more than fictional stories despite being 6), again this is demonstrably false as no evidence or historical records exist barring one book.</blockquote>It has been proven that Egypt did experience plagues during the said biblical time period. Archaeologists do believe that the mythical ten plagues occurred in the ancient city of Pi-Ramses and they have uncovered evidence that leaves questions, as to why an entire capital just vanished? Stalagmites in caves have shown weather changes during the period, it is known that the Ramses environment was a warm, wet climate and had a dramatic shift to an incredible drought. 
<blockquote>Quote from Niall
I want to elaborate something, god kicked humans out of the garden of eden because eve ate the forbidden fruit, however god never gave adam and eve the knowledge of right and wrong, good and bad so while god forbid eve from eating from the tree she wouldn't have known it was wrong to do so in the first place</blockquote>I just read over Genesis 1-3 directly from the bible. The bible never said that when Adam or Eve were created that they had no knowledge of right or wrong, but had no knowledge of good or evil.
<p>My information has been gathered from various reliable sites, personal knowledge, research, and the bible. Some of your questions can be answered by research. I look forward to a well sought response.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-god-vs-satan-religious-debate/451479/17">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-god-vs-satan-religious-debate/451479/17</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jul 2012 06:19:50 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-451479-17</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-god-vs-satan-religious-debate/451479.rss">The God VS Satan religious debate</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The God VS Satan religious debate</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@The_Un-Named The Un-Named]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/the_un-named">@The_Un-Named</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“imsuperman05, post:15, topic:451479”][quote=Nial]<br>
she wouldn’t have known it was wrong to do so in the first place<br>
[/quote]<br>
That’s where you’re wrong though.  I remember learning that God told Adam and Eve to specifically not to eat from the tree of knowledge.[/quote]</p>
<p>yes but the knowledge of knowing that what she was doing was wrong wasn’t gained until she ate the fruit in the first place</p>
<p>she was told not to eat from the tree but wouldn’t have known that going against gods wishes was wrong, merely that it would be going against gods wishes</p>
<p>of course the garden of eden was a pointless exercise since god knew what was going to happen beforehand, I don’t view the garden of eden as gods divine test of humans, god created man in his image and man is inherently created imperfect and I find the garden of eden an extremely poor excuse to ignore the sins god commits because god is perfect and humans are the ones who created sin</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-god-vs-satan-religious-debate/451479/16">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-god-vs-satan-religious-debate/451479/16</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jul 2012 04:56:14 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-451479-16</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-god-vs-satan-religious-debate/451479.rss">The God VS Satan religious debate</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The God VS Satan religious debate</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@imsuperman05 imsuperman05]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/imsuperman05">@imsuperman05</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <blockquote>she wouldn't have known it was wrong to do so in the first place</blockquote>
That's where you're wrong though.  I remember learning that God told Adam and Eve to specifically not to eat from the tree of knowledge.
<aside class="quote quote-modified" data-post="13" data-topic="451479">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/tyb97/40/5_e05bb34c421432ee4d40de30c10af3e5.png" class="avatar"> tyb97:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>We reopened a thread full of nothing of argument why? Were all just going to try to disprove each other over and over again… Never going to go anywhere.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I like this.  I love reading all this, more knowledge for me.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-god-vs-satan-religious-debate/451479/15">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-god-vs-satan-religious-debate/451479/15</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jul 2012 04:27:39 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-451479-15</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-god-vs-satan-religious-debate/451479.rss">The God VS Satan religious debate</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The God VS Satan religious debate</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@The_Un-Named The Un-Named]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/the_un-named">@The_Un-Named</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote quote-modified" data-post="12" data-topic="451479">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 the elve age:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Niall, in all means it sounds like you are just being as defensive as you can to persuade your side more. It’s pretty clear you don’t believe in the bible so why do you care?</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>well, regarding the religious debate, I’m not trying to convert people as it were if that’s what your getting at, but I do care about attempting to give people a better perspective on things if they’re open to it</p>
<p>regarding the same-sex marriage debate, I consider same-sex marriage a civil right so long as marriage provides legal rights that no other status provides, while a civil partnership that provides all the legal rights marriage will do it’s still a huge discrimination against same-sex couples with absolutely no logical reasoning why, if a church wants to prohibit marrying two people of the same sex that’s their business but for the government to prohibit it is outrageous especially when there are churches open to the idea of allowing same-sex marriages</p>
<p>of course I only started this thread as I said because I don’t fully understand what heatrn11 is getting at and obviously can’t ask him in the other thread, personal curiosity is the only reason</p>
<aside class="quote quote-modified" data-post="13" data-topic="451479">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/tyb97/40/5_e05bb34c421432ee4d40de30c10af3e5.png" class="avatar"> tyb97:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Were all just going to try to disprove each other over and over again… Never going to go anywhere.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>well, you’ve yet to reply to any of my arguments in the previous thread without sidestepping them, you could start there I guess <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/wink.png?v=5" title=":wink:" class="emoji" alt=":wink:"></p>
<p>and a quick edit, I’m not particularly tied to ‘my side’, I’ve learned a hell of a lot from being exposed to opposite viewpoints or even viewpoints I am indifferent to and have changed my position a few times because of it, while I’m not particularly religious I do find some religious discussions on these forums to be quite educational</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-god-vs-satan-religious-debate/451479/14">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-god-vs-satan-religious-debate/451479/14</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jul 2012 04:03:13 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-451479-14</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-god-vs-satan-religious-debate/451479.rss">The God VS Satan religious debate</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The God VS Satan religious debate</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@tyb97 tyb97]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/tyb97">@tyb97</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>We reopened a thread full of nothing of argument why? Were all just going to try to disprove each other over and over again… Never going to go anywhere.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-god-vs-satan-religious-debate/451479/13">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-god-vs-satan-religious-debate/451479/13</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jul 2012 03:33:49 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-451479-13</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-god-vs-satan-religious-debate/451479.rss">The God VS Satan religious debate</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The God VS Satan religious debate</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@the_elve_age the elve age]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/the_elve_age">@the_elve_age</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Niall, in all means it sounds like you are just being as defensive as you can to persuade your side more. It’s pretty clear you don’t believe in the bible so why do you care?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-god-vs-satan-religious-debate/451479/12">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-god-vs-satan-religious-debate/451479/12</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jul 2012 03:28:58 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-451479-12</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-god-vs-satan-religious-debate/451479.rss">The God VS Satan religious debate</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The God VS Satan religious debate</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@The_Un-Named The Un-Named]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/the_un-named">@The_Un-Named</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote" data-post="8" data-topic="451479">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/user_avatar/forum.moparisthebest.com/whackatre/40/7608_1.png" class="avatar"> Whackatre:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>So you are stating that Satan killed eleven people? I am very interested in where your statistics come from.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>the bible, satan directly killed ten/eleven people where god flooded and directly killed almost all of earths inhabitants, among others</p>
<aside class="quote quote-modified" data-post="8" data-topic="451479">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/user_avatar/forum.moparisthebest.com/whackatre/40/7608_1.png" class="avatar"> Whackatre:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Due to the fact that sin as a whole is represented by Satan and his followers, factors of death such as murder (the biggest one) account for Satan’s ‘kills’ IF your extent is inferring that the flood is God’s ‘fault’ (it’s not, and like I previously stated, there was a completely reasonable choice, Noah was ridiculed for it). God doesn’t ‘threaten’ people; most atheists incorrectly interpret his actions.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I disagree, you see, it was god who damned humans to original sin and while satan may be the implement, god is ultimately responsible for the damnation of the human race</p>
<p>I want to elaborate something, god kicked humans out of the garden of eden because eve ate the forbidden fruit, however god never gave adam and eve the knowledge of right and wrong, good and bad so while god forbid eve from eating from the tree she wouldn’t have known it was wrong to do so in the first place</p>
<p>of course all this is ignoring the fact that god is responsible for humans committing sinful acts in the first place but that’s a whole mess of semantics which isn’t really what we are discussing</p>
<aside class="quote quote-modified" data-post="8" data-topic="451479">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/user_avatar/forum.moparisthebest.com/whackatre/40/7608_1.png" class="avatar"> Whackatre:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>I have no idea how the separation of the ToB relates to ‘cooperation’ or a lack thereof.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>like I hinted to, it was a divide and conqueror tactic from god hinting that he isn’t necessarily peaceful, since all humans spoke the same language before building the tower of babel and had to co-operate to do so, god took away their means to do so by removing their common language</p>
<p>I didn’t bring it up the first time but one could attribute gods actions to remove humans single common language as being directly responsible from all the resulting implications of that action, people may not have had wars over land and language if we all spoke the same language and shared the same land, and my reasoning for thinking this is that the bible tells that building the tower of babel was only possible because of the shared language and humans cooperated to do so, people at war generally don’t co-operate with each other</p>
<aside class="quote quote-modified" data-post="8" data-topic="451479">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/user_avatar/forum.moparisthebest.com/whackatre/40/7608_1.png" class="avatar"> Whackatre:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Also, keep in mind that you are pretty much judging Christians by a select few; either you misinterpreted what the influential ‘Christians’ said (note the quotation marks), <span class="bbcode-b">or they weren’t genuine Christians at all</span> (think WBC and Ronnie James Dio.)</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>that right there friend is the no true scotsman fallacy</p>
<p>the wbc are christians just like lutheranism are christians, they both follow and believe in the bible and the only difference is they interpret different parts differently, and since there is evidently no “true” way to interpret the bible, anyone who interprets the bible however they like and believes in the biblical god and jesus can be called a christian</p>
<aside class="quote quote-modified" data-post="8" data-topic="451479">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/user_avatar/forum.moparisthebest.com/whackatre/40/7608_1.png" class="avatar"> Whackatre:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Your murder theory is ridiculous and even if murder were not part of the ten commandments, it would still come into account with Jesus’s golden rule.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I have no idea what you are referring to</p>
<p>if you are referring to the “murder theory” as what you said before about satan being the representation of sin then allow me to give an analogy and then maybe some context would be provided</p>
<p>you say that god flooding the earth doesn’t mean god directly killed the people as satan is the representation of sin and therefore satan is responsible for the killings, what would you say then if someone kills another person with a gun? you could argue from your logic that the person didn’t kill the person but the gun killed the person, and going even further you could argue the person didn’t kill the person but it was satan as satan is a representation of sin and killing a person is a sin</p>
<p>however I quoted the floods as it is something everyone is familiar with and even people who are not familiar with christianity will know the tale, there are other verses in the bible which may have been more relevant to quote, and I’ll list one now</p>
<p>Genesis 38, New International Version (NIV), Judah and Tamar</p>
<p>38 At that time, Judah left his brothers and went down to stay with a man of Adullam named Hirah. 2 There Judah met the daughter of a Canaanite man named Shua. He married her and made love to her; 3 she became pregnant and gave birth to a son, who was named Er. 4 She conceived again and gave birth to a son and named him Onan. 5 She gave birth to still another son and named him Shelah. It was at Kezib that she gave birth to him. 6 Judah got a wife for Er, his firstborn, and her name was Tamar. 7 But Er, Judah’s firstborn, was wicked in the Lord’s sight; so the Lord put him to death. 8 Then Judah said to Onan, “Sleep with your brother’s wife and fulfill your duty to her as a brother-in-law to raise up offspring for your brother.” 9 But Onan knew that the child would not be his; so whenever he slept with his brother’s wife, he spilled his semen on the ground to keep from providing offspring for his brother. 10 What he did was wicked in the Lord’s sight; so the Lord put him to death also.</p>
<p>as you can see here, god viewed er as wicked and put him to death, and when onan refused to oblige the request of judah to impregnate his dead brothers wife and chose to waste his seed instead, god viewed this as wicked and put onan to death as well</p>
<p>the context of the quote may be debatable however god killed er as he viewed him as wicked, and killed onan for refusing to raise a child with his dead brothers wife, is satan responsible for this?</p>
<aside class="quote quote-modified" data-post="8" data-topic="451479">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/user_avatar/forum.moparisthebest.com/whackatre/40/7608_1.png" class="avatar"> Whackatre:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>I don’t see why you are labeling Christians as not ‘empathetic’.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>my bad for not providing full context of the quote, heatrn11 stated that someone who hated a cat may be happy at the sight of his death and that he would be depressed about it, I responded stating every human who isn’t a psychopath can feel empathy, of course the purpose of this thread was so I could get heatrn11 to elaborate on what he means so I may be hitting and missing but the point is I am not stating that christians cannot feel empathy</p>
<p>the sentence or two after what I posted wasn’t necessarily directed to anyone but I felt it was relevant to what I posted, and I made sure that I didn’t generalise at all hence the “<span class="bbcode-b">some </span>very influential christians” descriptor, I am not saying all christians feel the same way I am simply stating that I feel the fact that some (and a very small minority at that) do is saddening to me</p>
<aside class="quote" data-post="8" data-topic="451479">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/user_avatar/forum.moparisthebest.com/whackatre/40/7608_1.png" class="avatar"> Whackatre:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Does every organ have to specifically serve a purpose? Humans were not created perfectly, so I do not see how they have to be perfect.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>but humans were made in gods image, it says so in the bible!</p>
<p>I never brought up the issue of humans being perfect, merely that we are not intelligently designed, we can be intelligently designed and not be perfect</p>
<p>as an analogy imagine having a computer that has a heater fitted, the heater is a negative impact on the computer that serves no purpose for the heater, but if one were to remove the heater one could describe it as an intelligent design choice and it doesn’t necessarily mean that the computer is now perfect</p>
<p>but let me state I am at a loss for what you are quoting to in some situations, perhaps if you could provide context to what you are replying to I could give a better answer</p>
<p>[hr]</p>
<aside class="quote" data-post="10" data-topic="451479">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 Pink Phat:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>I understand that God has killed many more then Satan, but when I think of God I think of peace, wisdom, etc. Is that not the picture you get when you think of God?</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I do not believe god exists however what I think when I picture god is as described in the bible which is largely contradictory</p>
<p>I see that many christians believe that god is an ultimate source of good and happiness but at the same time I see that the all powerful all knowing inventor of everything created evil to begin with, and more specifically in the bible I see god punishing people for being wicked by killing them</p>
<p>ideas such as morals and ethics are human constructs, there is not and cannot be such a thing as absolute or universal morals even if they come from god, and as such based on my own morals and ethics I view some acts god does as stated in the bible to be morally and ethically wrong while other acts may be considered kind, but I view such inconsistent behaviour as very disturbing, akin to a crazed gunman who may kill one person but reward another person with riches and happiness</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-god-vs-satan-religious-debate/451479/11">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-god-vs-satan-religious-debate/451479/11</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jul 2012 02:49:21 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-451479-11</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-god-vs-satan-religious-debate/451479.rss">The God VS Satan religious debate</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The God VS Satan religious debate</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Pink_Phat Pink Phat]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/pink_phat">@Pink_Phat</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“Niall, post:1, topic:451479”]Original thread - <a href="http://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php/topic,554181.40.html" rel="nofollow noopener">http://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php/topic,554181.40.html</a></p>
<p>[quote]Quote from “Pink Phat”,</p>
<blockquote>
<p>God is more of a peaceful character, who created the world. [/quote]</p>
</blockquote>
<p>If we’re talking about god of the bible here, god has killed millions more people than satan has. Satan killed 11 people, god killed millions directly or indirectly. Let’s not forget the bible tells tales of god flooding the whole earth to start fresh (and look where that got us).</p>
<p>But by all accounts in the bible god is not peaceful, take the story of the tower of babel for instance, a united man all speaking one language attempted to build a tower that would reach the heavens, god not wanted any of this gave different groups different languages so they could no longer cooperate. Whether or not you interpret this literally or not, it says something about gods character, he would rather divide (and conqueror) man rather than have man cooperate.[/quote]</p>
<p>I understand that God has killed many more then Satan, but when I think of God I think of peace, wisdom, etc. Is that not the picture you get when you think of God?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-god-vs-satan-religious-debate/451479/10">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-god-vs-satan-religious-debate/451479/10</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jul 2012 02:32:18 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-451479-10</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-god-vs-satan-religious-debate/451479.rss">The God VS Satan religious debate</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The God VS Satan religious debate</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@T41 t4]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/t41">@T41</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>i saw dio rep++</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-god-vs-satan-religious-debate/451479/9">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-god-vs-satan-religious-debate/451479/9</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jul 2012 01:42:35 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-451479-9</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-god-vs-satan-religious-debate/451479.rss">The God VS Satan religious debate</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The God VS Satan religious debate</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@whackatre Whackatre]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/whackatre">@whackatre</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“Niall, post:1, topic:451479”][quote]Quote from “Pink Phat”,</p>
<blockquote>
<p>God is more of a peaceful character, who created the world. [/quote]</p>
</blockquote>
<p>If we’re talking about god of the bible here, god has killed millions more people than satan has. Satan killed 11 people, god killed millions directly or indirectly. Let’s not forget the bible tells tales of god flooding the whole earth to start fresh (and look where that got us).</p>
<p>But by all accounts in the bible god is not peaceful, take the story of the tower of babel for instance, a united man all speaking one language attempted to build a tower that would reach the heavens, god not wanted any of this gave different groups different languages so they could no longer cooperate. Whether or not you interpret this literally or not, it says something about gods character, he would rather divide (and conqueror) man rather than have man cooperate.</p>
<p>[quote]Quote from “heatrn11”,</p>
<blockquote>
<p>So if the kitten was sick and the kitten was dieing, you’d be happy and I’d be in a state of depression.[/quote]</p>
</blockquote>
<p>Any sane human being who feels empathy wouldn’t feel happy at the suffering of another. This isn’t what you said but it is relevant, some very influential christians have publicly stated that the only reason they do not kill people is because the bible tells them it is wrong. I find such a position saddening, I do not need a creator of a universe personally telling me what is right and wrong, and I do not need threat of punishment to refrain from doing bad things. I feel empathy therefore I do not attempt to place another person in a position of suffering.</p>
<p>[quote]Quote from “heatrn11”,</p>
<blockquote>
<p>Only an intelligent designer or creator rather, could put the universe together and make every single particle work with each other.[/quote]</p>
</blockquote>
<p>If you’re going down the “intelligent design” route, could you perhaps explain some problems with the “intelligent design”? Such as humans having a near useless appendix which can burst requiring people to have them surgically removed. Such as people having wisdom teeth that serve no current purpose, which cause people unnecessary pain and also require the person to have them surgically removed.[/quote]</p>
<p>So you are stating that Satan killed eleven people? I am very interested in where your statistics come from. Due to the fact that sin as a whole is represented by Satan and his followers, factors of death such as murder (the biggest one) account for Satan’s ‘kills’ IF your extent is inferring that the flood is God’s ‘fault’ (it’s not, and like I previously stated, there was a completely reasonable choice, Noah was ridiculed for it). God doesn’t ‘threaten’ people; most atheists incorrectly interpret his actions.</p>
<p>I have no idea how the separation of the ToB relates to ‘cooperation’ or a lack thereof.</p>
<p>Also, keep in mind that you are pretty much judging Christians by a select few; either you misinterpreted what the influential ‘Christians’ said (note the quotation marks), or they weren’t genuine Christians at all (think WBC and Ronnie James Dio.) Your murder theory is ridiculous and even if murder were not part of the ten commandments, it would still come into account with Jesus’s golden rule. I don’t see why you are labeling Christians as not ‘empathetic’. I don’t think there is any difference between the amount of empathetic Christians and empathetic atheists.</p>
<p>Does every organ have to specifically serve a purpose? Humans were not created perfectly, so I do not see how they have to be perfect.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-god-vs-satan-religious-debate/451479/8">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-god-vs-satan-religious-debate/451479/8</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jul 2012 01:40:14 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-451479-8</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-god-vs-satan-religious-debate/451479.rss">The God VS Satan religious debate</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The God VS Satan religious debate</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@T41 t4]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/t41">@T41</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>did any atheist in that thread believe in satan? :s</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-god-vs-satan-religious-debate/451479/7">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-god-vs-satan-religious-debate/451479/7</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jul 2012 01:29:48 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-451479-7</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-god-vs-satan-religious-debate/451479.rss">The God VS Satan religious debate</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The God VS Satan religious debate</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@The_Un-Named The Un-Named]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/the_un-named">@The_Un-Named</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote" data-post="4" data-topic="451479">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/loveandpower/40/5_e05bb34c421432ee4d40de30c10af3e5.png" class="avatar"> Loveandpower:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>If there is no faith, how can they say they believe in Satan then?</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>if someone believes in satan then by definition they are not an atheist</p>
<p>atheism is the lack of belief in a theism, theism is the belief in a diety, a diety is generally defined as a supernatural entity with superhuman powers</p>
<p>angels fit the definition of dieties and according to the bible satan/the devil/lucifer is a fallen angel hence a diety and believing in satan is belief in a diety which is theism which isn’t atheism</p>
<p>EDIT: of course there is such a thing as “atheistic satanism” in which the person does not necessarily believe in any deities or supernatural elements and merely follows the ritualisms and traditions but I don’t think it fits in to this argument, when someone claims to be a satanist and/or worship the devil they usually believe in it when it isn’t intended to be taken seriously</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-god-vs-satan-religious-debate/451479/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-god-vs-satan-religious-debate/451479/6</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jul 2012 01:27:58 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-451479-6</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-god-vs-satan-religious-debate/451479.rss">The God VS Satan religious debate</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The God VS Satan religious debate</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@bowserjr2 Bowser jr]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/bowserjr2">@bowserjr2</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>As Niall said, they can’t. Only way to believe in Satan is to also believe in God.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-god-vs-satan-religious-debate/451479/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-god-vs-satan-religious-debate/451479/5</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jul 2012 01:01:32 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-451479-5</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-god-vs-satan-religious-debate/451479.rss">The God VS Satan religious debate</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The God VS Satan religious debate</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Loveandpower Loveandpower]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/loveandpower">@Loveandpower</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>If there is no faith, how can they say they believe in Satan then?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-god-vs-satan-religious-debate/451479/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-god-vs-satan-religious-debate/451479/4</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jul 2012 00:57:52 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-451479-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-god-vs-satan-religious-debate/451479.rss">The God VS Satan religious debate</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The God VS Satan religious debate</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@bowserjr2 Bowser jr]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/bowserjr2">@bowserjr2</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Atheism is the antithesis of religion, nothing more. So take away religious belief and faith, and you are left with atheist. Nothing more, you could be an atheist and not believe in evolution, history, global warming, big bang…</p>
<p>Atheism is simple no faith, nothing more.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-god-vs-satan-religious-debate/451479/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-god-vs-satan-religious-debate/451479/3</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jul 2012 00:53:45 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-451479-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-god-vs-satan-religious-debate/451479.rss">The God VS Satan religious debate</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The God VS Satan religious debate</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Loveandpower Loveandpower]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/loveandpower">@Loveandpower</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <blockquote>The definition of an atheist is one who is not a theist. The phrase "all babies are atheists" comes about because babies have no knowledge of religion and therefore do not believe it therefore are not theists, so they are atheists. 
<p>Minor nitpick but I feel the distinction has to be made when we’re dealing with people some of whom are under the impression that atheism is a religion.</p>
</blockquote>
<p>I can see where your coming from but I still look at it in the sense that the classification <span class="bbcode-b">itself</span> about what an atheist believes in. Most people who say they do not believe in heaven claim to be atheist.</p>
<p>How can you believe in one part of the “fanatical world” and not the other.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-god-vs-satan-religious-debate/451479/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-god-vs-satan-religious-debate/451479/2</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jul 2012 00:48:54 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-451479-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-god-vs-satan-religious-debate/451479.rss">The God VS Satan religious debate</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
