<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>EVE Online</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/eve-online/466616</link>
    <description>Just curious if anyone else on the forum plays EVE Online.

EVE Online is a space themed MMORPG. However, it is most definitely not your typical MMO. Normally, an MMO would consist of grinding and levelling until you reach the top level, and then you would participate in end-game events. However, EVE is more of a sandbox game, with MMO elements. There is no &quot;end-game&quot; or &quot;levelling&quot; really. There are a number of skills that can be trained, but training does not involve doing the same repetitive task (like chopping trees, or grinding mobs). Instead, skills are &quot;injected&quot; into your characters mind, and to train the skills, you just put it in your skill queue, and after a certain amount of time has passed, your ability is increased.

There is no feasible way to get maxed skills in EVE. Since each skill is trained with time, to reach max level (5) in all skills, it would take about 27 years. It is for this reason, that most players spend more time on character development in a particular area, instead of trying to cover them all. For example, some people work the market, some are focused on asteroid mining and ship production, and some focus on becoming a pirate (high damage fast ships, salvaging the remains, and drug manufacturing).

If you&#39;d like to know more, you can check out the homepage at http://www.eveonline.com/universe/ Everyone gets a 14-day free trial, afterwards you can subscribe if you&#39;d like, or (depending on how successful you are) can spend ISK (the in-game currency) to buy basically a 30 or 60 day in-game time card. So if you&#39;re good at making money in-game, you can never have to pay to play at all.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 11 Nov 2012 04:05:59 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Games</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/eve-online/466616.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>EVE Online</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Team_Rocket Team_Rocket]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/team_rocket">@Team_Rocket</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>One of the better games of It’s Genre. They do the Pay2Play system right as well.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/eve-online/466616/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/eve-online/466616/4</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 11 Nov 2012 04:05:59 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-466616-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/eve-online/466616.rss">EVE Online</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>EVE Online</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@ox_random_xi ox random xi]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/ox_random_xi">@ox_random_xi</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I never had the money to play it, but I did like it.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/eve-online/466616/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/eve-online/466616/3</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 11 Nov 2012 01:48:51 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-466616-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/eve-online/466616.rss">EVE Online</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>EVE Online</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@bowserjr2 Bowser jr]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/bowserjr2">@bowserjr2</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I have consider to try it. But I will wait to after my last exam this semester (13. Des).</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/eve-online/466616/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/eve-online/466616/2</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 10 Nov 2012 22:59:58 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-466616-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/eve-online/466616.rss">EVE Online</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>EVE Online</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@zyle1992 Zymus]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/zyle1992">@zyle1992</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Just curious if anyone else on the forum plays EVE Online.</p>
<p>EVE Online is a space themed MMORPG. However, it is most definitely not your typical MMO. Normally, an MMO would consist of grinding and levelling until you reach the top level, and then you would participate in end-game events. However, EVE is more of a sandbox game, with MMO elements. There is no “end-game” or “levelling” really. There are a number of skills that can be trained, but training does not involve doing the same repetitive task (like chopping trees, or grinding mobs). Instead, skills are “injected” into your characters mind, and to train the skills, you just put it in your skill queue, and after a certain amount of time has passed, your ability is increased.</p>
<p>There is no feasible way to get maxed skills in EVE. Since each skill is trained with time, to reach max level (5) in all skills, it would take about 27 years. It is for this reason, that most players spend more time on character development in a particular area, instead of trying to cover them all. For example, some people work the market, some are focused on asteroid mining and ship production, and some focus on becoming a pirate (high damage fast ships, salvaging the remains, and drug manufacturing).</p>
<p>If you’d like to know more, you can check out the homepage at <a href="http://www.eveonline.com/universe/">http://www.eveonline.com/universe/</a> Everyone gets a 14-day free trial, afterwards you can subscribe if you’d like, or (depending on how successful you are) can spend ISK (the in-game currency) to buy basically a 30 or 60 day in-game time card. So if you’re good at making money in-game, you can never have to pay to play at all.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/eve-online/466616/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/eve-online/466616/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 10 Nov 2012 22:02:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-466616-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/eve-online/466616.rss">EVE Online</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
