<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Rationality and Belief in God</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rationality-and-belief-in-god/547957</link>
    <description>So I saw this topic...
https://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php/topic,666843.0.html
which does not really put a debate forth or anything, however I love the idea of debating the belief in God and the rationality in it... So let&#39;s begin.

First we need to define God. I&#39;m going to use the Western definition of God which is that God is a being who is all-powerful, all-knowing, and morally perfect.
I also need to define two types of rationality... there is an epistemic rationonality and prudential rationality. Epistemic rationality gives the subject good reason to think the belief is true whereas prudential rationality just shows that holding a certain belief maximizes one&#39;s practical interests. We will only be considering epistemic rationality in this argument but I will put forth a prudentially rational argument for the existence of God..

Premise 1: God either exists or he doesn&#39;t exist.
Premise 2: If God doesn&#39;t exist, and we don&#39;t believe in him, we lose nothing.
Premise 3: If God exists, and we don&#39;t believe in him, we lose paradise and gain eternal torment.
Conclusion: Therefore, it&#39;s better to believe that God exists.

We can see that this is a prudentially rational argument as it does not actually prove the existence of God, rather gives you a good reason to believe or act like he does to maximize one&#39;s practical interests.

The second most well-known argument is the design argument which basically states that many complex things we know today did not just come about to exist but have been designed by designers. In that sense we can assume that God must exist as the universe is a complex thing and therefore must have had a designer. The more formal argument goes like this...
Premise 1: The universe is a complex thing.
Premise 2: Complex things have designers.
Conclusion: It&#39;s likely that the universe had a designer.

Now there are three well-known objections to the design argument I will cover.

The first is Hume&#39;s Criticism. Hume says that we can infer that cameras and watches are complex things because we have had previous experience with them and can tell a well-designed watch from a poorly designed watch. However, we have not had any previous experience with the universe so we cannot state if it is or isn&#39;t a complex thing as we cannot tell if it is well-designed or not.

I personally have an objection with the first objection because although we may not have experience with any other universes we can imagine universes that have been constructed poorly. If a universe was created in which the electromagnetic force was a lot weaker than the gravitational force then we would fall through the floor and I would say this is a pretty poor design.

The second criticism is does the conclusion actually show that God exists. God is supposed to be a morally perfect, all-knowing, and all-powerful being. All the design argument shows is that something intelligent created the universe as it just takes something intelligent to design something. This being does not have to be morally perfect and probably not all-knowing and all-powerful to create a universe. Therefore it does not show that necessarily God created the universe.

The third and last criticism is that complex things can arise from non-complex things through evolution. Complex organisms which contain many organic systems and processes have evolved over time from simple single-celled organisms. The driving force behind the creation of these complex organisms is also a simple force known as natural selection so one cannot say that just because something is complex it had to be created or designed.

So let the debate begin for a rational argument for the existence of an all-knowing, morally perfect, all-powerful being. :)</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 26 Sep 2015 23:31:57 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>General Discussion</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rationality-and-belief-in-god/547957.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Rationality and Belief in God</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@jme jme]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/jme">@jme</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote" data-post="43" data-topic="547957">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/pault/40/5_e05bb34c421432ee4d40de30c10af3e5.png" class="avatar"> PaulT:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>So I simply ask you to observe life. From whence did life arise? Life only comes from other life. This leads to the inevitable conclusion that either life is infinite or that the original thesis is wrong and that life must have been formed from something other than life. And, as proven by Louis Pasteur, life cannot come from matter. This means that there is either an infinite life force in the universe, or something other than matter or life exists. Either way, you are left with the inevitable conclusion that God exists.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Do you mean the first life on earth/universe? Then you are wondering how we went from molecules to cells? It took over a billion years for the first rna molecule that could replicate itself. The rest is just natural selection and evolution.</p>
<p>Now when did the first consciousness arrive. This is something we might never understand. Even simple life forms can show signs of anxiety. I tend to assume that our consciousness too is a product of evolution. That there are different levels and scales of consciousness, cognition etc. For humans in particular it was our greatest survival feature.</p>
<p>So again I end up thinking that when we die, it’ll be just like before we were born. Non-existent in all forms.</p>
<p>Enjoy reading your posts as I’ve had my own experiences.<br>
Good night, don’t let the machine elves bite.</p>
<p><img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/wink.png?v=5" title=":wink:" class="emoji" alt=":wink:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rationality-and-belief-in-god/547957/44">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rationality-and-belief-in-god/547957/44</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 26 Sep 2015 23:31:57 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-547957-44</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rationality-and-belief-in-god/547957.rss">Rationality and Belief in God</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Rationality and Belief in God</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@PaulT PaulT]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/pault">@PaulT</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“Rodgerwilco, post:42, topic:547957”]On the other side, theories can be proven to be “true” and will move out of the “theory category”. Which never get accepted by Religons anyways because it is “Science”. Or better yet, they will claim that we have discovered some insight on “gods” creation.</p>
<p>Hundreds of years ago :<br>
The earth is the center of the universe (due to religious influence, specifically “Romen Catholics”)<br>
The sun is the center of our solar system (oh lets adapt it into our religion or accept it)</p>
<p>Now something that irritates me is that the “Bible” will promote gender equality AND female inferiority but never male inferiority. What are your thoughts on this?[/quote]</p>
<p>The bible is not a scientific text. It’s a spiritual text, about the heart of mankind, it’s not about quantifying the universe, it’s about qualifying it. Now there is no real conflict between science and religion. Copernicus proved the earth was the center of the universe, and it wasn’t really a big deal for the Catholic church at the time. Later, they fought Galileo tooth and nail over his political points, because he wasn’t afraid to make the political Church (not the true, invisible and universal Church) look stupid. This illustrative of the wider point that you have political dingbats in every religion, in every country, and in every school, who will fight and fuss and turn anything into a bureaucratic nightmare (ever read Kafka?). Science can measure an atom, it can help us to span the stars or conquer mother nature, but in the end it does not give any meaning or nuance to life, and that is what the spiritual pursuits of religion can do.</p>
<p>As far as gender equality, there are no laws in the new testament except the perfect law of love under Jesus Christ. Christians need not accept every word in the Pauline letters as a creed, and they need not even assume that Paul the Apostle is absolutely correct in everything he says, though some churches will push that opinion on to you. The epistles are, rather, an illustration of the early church and an exposition of how a group of people solves their disputes and issues through the grace and acceptance of a benevolent deity. So when Paul speaks of homosexuals burning in sin for one another or women not being allowed to speak in Church, he is talking about specific problems that his community was going through. You can’t really take these passages out of context and expect all Christians to understand them. Unfortunately many Christians will do just that. They don’t understand the historical context of what they are reading, and so they cannot perform a proper exegesis on the text and understand what the author was saying and why they were saying it.</p>
<blockquote>Atheists are simply categorized as "not beliving in god". Wouldn't my statements be classified as "Scientology". Lets recap on my statements and if you identify one that you do not agree with, point it out.
<p>The sun provides our Earth with a wonderful deadly ray which our Earth has the right material to protect itself from.</p>
<p>The sun fuels life.</p>
<p>Everything grows because of the sun.</p>
<p>It causes skin cancer</p>
<p>Grows your fruits and vegetables.</p>
<p>Thus we are a form of cancer constantly creating a fresh human so that we can battle the clock.</p>
<p>I am taking what I observe and coming to a conclusion, you on the other hand are reading a book and day dreaming about it. There is no proof for what you have to say, only a book that has been constantly rewritten and changed to keep the manipulated… well manipulated. But the book/transcripts have not been rewritten, how do you know? Have you gone back and found the original documents and have read the original words? Or do you trust a book and someone telling you that its legit to believe in it.</p>
<p>It’s the same concept with the internet, I don’t believe everything that is on the internet is correct or “true”. Yet all this information is posted here. My claim, I don’t need the internet for. I can simply go outside and observe it. The internet has been constantly updated/revised since its existence. Similar situations.</p>
</blockquote>
<p>I actually agree with you.</p>
<p>I would never ask you to believe anything that is not confirmed by empirical evidence.</p>
<p>So I simply ask you to observe life. From whence did life arise? Life only comes from other life. This leads to the inevitable conclusion that either life is infinite or that the original thesis is wrong and that life must have been formed from something other than life. And, as proven by Louis Pasteur, life cannot come from matter. This means that there is either an infinite life force in the universe, or something other than matter or life exists. Either way, you are left with the inevitable conclusion that God exists.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rationality-and-belief-in-god/547957/43">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rationality-and-belief-in-god/547957/43</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 17 Aug 2015 03:04:33 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-547957-43</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rationality-and-belief-in-god/547957.rss">Rationality and Belief in God</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Rationality and Belief in God</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Rodgerwilco Rodgerwilco]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/rodgerwilco">@Rodgerwilco</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <blockquote>A theory is never claimed to be true. That is why it is a theory. This is the scientific method, of course, which I wholeheartedly believe in. Science never says "We know for sure that X is Y." It says, "Our best method for understanding X is to model it as Y". So scientific theories are not "Proven Wrong" they are simply replaced by more accurate models and modes of understanding. It is a pragmatic approach to the universe, not an authoritarian one.</blockquote>
<p>On the other side, theories can be proven to be “true” and will move out of the “theory category”. Which never get accepted by Religons anyways because it is “Science”. Or better yet, they will claim that we have discovered some insight on “gods” creation.</p>
<p>Hundreds of years ago :<br>
The earth is the center of the universe (due to religious influence, specifically “Romen Catholics”)<br>
The sun is the center of our solar system (oh lets adapt it into our religion or accept it)</p>
<p>Now something that irritates me is that the “Bible” will promote gender equality AND female inferiority but never male inferiority. What are your thoughts on this?</p>
<blockquote>You are essentially expressing the basic idea of atheistic materialism, which has no answer for the law of Bio-genesis, or of consciousness.  "Omne vivum ex vivo" ?</blockquote>
<p>Atheists are simply categorized as “not beliving in god”. Wouldn’t my statements be classified as “Scientology”. Lets recap on my statements and if you identify one that you do not agree with, point it out.</p>
<p>The sun provides our Earth with a wonderful deadly ray which our Earth has the right material to protect itself from.</p>
<p>The sun fuels life.</p>
<p>Everything grows because of the sun.</p>
<p>It causes skin cancer</p>
<p>Grows your fruits and vegetables.</p>
<p>Thus we are a form of cancer constantly creating a fresh human so that we can battle the clock.</p>
<p>I am taking what I observe and coming to a conclusion, you on the other hand are reading a book and day dreaming about it. There is no proof for what you have to say, only a book that has been constantly rewritten and changed to keep the manipulated… well manipulated. But the book/transcripts have not been rewritten, how do you know? Have you gone back and found the original documents and have read the original words? Or do you trust a book and someone telling you that its legit to believe in it.</p>
<p>It’s the same concept with the internet, I don’t believe everything that is on the internet is correct or “true”. Yet all this information is posted here. My claim, I don’t need the internet for. I can simply go outside and observe it. The internet has been constantly updated/revised since its existence. Similar situations.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rationality-and-belief-in-god/547957/42">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rationality-and-belief-in-god/547957/42</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 16 Aug 2015 07:24:26 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-547957-42</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rationality-and-belief-in-god/547957.rss">Rationality and Belief in God</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Rationality and Belief in God</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@PaulT PaulT]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/pault">@PaulT</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Thanks for responding! To best answer your questions and address your points, I have broken down your statements, point by point.  <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=5" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
<aside class="quote" data-post="40" data-topic="547957">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/rodgerwilco/40/5_e05bb34c421432ee4d40de30c10af3e5.png" class="avatar"> Rodgerwilco:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>[quote]But why should death really be the end?</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>You’re devaluing what we call “life”. Why would life be oh so important if there is something after it? Pfft.[/quote]</p>
<p>Life doesn’t become less important if there is an afterlife, just like your meal is no less important if there is brandy and cigars afterward. Yet the question is not on the meaning, or purpose of life, but rather of the continuation of life after the destruction of the physical body. Many people feel that life is not sacred, and does not have value, but this does not affect the afterlife or the perception of the afterlife in a direct way. So a monk may renounce his physical body and fast from all solid foods, but he may still hold a tremendous value in human life, and believe steadfastly in the afterlife, and seek to feed the hungry and clothe the poor. In the same way a progressive humanist may feed the hungry and clothe the poor and hold all human life in high esteem, though they are atheistic and believe in the destruction of the consciousness as well as of the body. Therefore, it does not devalue life to believe in the afterlife, and I would even argue in most cases it increases our appreciation for life.</p>
<blockquote>I have yet to discover what I am, I will briefly describe my feelings towards the subject and you can kindly let me know.
<p>I don’t believe in god.</p>
<p>The bible was written by a genius or geniuses. Truly a master of manipulation.</p>
<p>The afterlife isn’t a “new birth” or “second chance” or “heaven”, when you die you come to acceptance with the fact that your time is up and that you took part of what we call “life”.</p>
<p>Time and life don’t give a fudge. Life will find a way and time continues to move forward, with or without you.</p>
</blockquote>
<p>I don’t disagree with your statement that time and life exist in objective reality, since that is self-evident. As far as what you believe, I cannot quarrel with that. I do take issue with the  statement on the authorship of the Bible. With a little research, one finds that the Bible has had many authors, Old and New Testament, and in fact represents only a small portion of the total extant writings on Judaism and Christianity. This canon or collection of books (Bible literally means “Books” or “Scrolls”) was collected and bound together to demonstrate the core truths of Monotheism or Yahwism and Christianity. I really don’t understand your characterization of the authorship as “Manipulative”, and I wish you would explain in more detail.</p>
<p>You can of course trace the origins of Genesis through early Mesopotamian creation myths and Exodus through the oral poetic tradition of Israel etc…The Bible was created by thousands of scribes and authors and poets and speech writers and priests, it’s not the work of one man trying to manipulate you into believing something.</p>
<blockquote>There is no such thing as "sins". Feel free to do the dirty, in some situations its perfectly fine to kill someone (self defense) and other times you're judged for it? Cmon. Don't give me that nonsense.</blockquote>
<p>The concept of sin, as taught by Jesus, is intensely focused on the heart condition of the individual. If you can lust after your friends wife and not feel bad about yourself, if you can lie for your own benefit and feel fine as long as you don’t get caught, then that’s great! But Jesus taught that sin begins in the heart. The New Testament definitively puts to death the idea of legalism, and focuses on the heart condition of men. You can always make ethical arguments against the “Absolute law of right and wrong” or the “Perfect justice of God”, but Jesus had a very simple teaching. Sin begins in the heart, and you reap what you sow. It is empirically evident that men hold themselves to a standard of honor and a code of moral purity which is indwelling in their hearts, and this is what leads to an understanding of sin and separation from the divine, and that they feel wretched and debased when they do not live up to this. As C.S. Lewis put it:</p>
<blockquote>Every one has heard people quarrelling. Sometimes it sounds funny and sometimes it sounds merely unpleasant; but however it sounds, I believe we can learn something very important from listening to the kind of things they say. They say things like this: "How'd you like it if anyone did the same to you?"—"That's my seat, I was there first"—"Leave him alone, he isn't doing you any harm"— "Why should you shove in first?"—"Give me a bit of your orange, I gave you a bit of mine"—"Come on, you promised." People say things like that every day, educated people as well as uneducated, and children as well as grown-ups.
<p>Now what interests me about all these remarks is that the man who makes diem is not merely saying that the other man’s behaviour does not happen to please him. He is appealing to some kind of standard of behaviour which he expects the other man to know about. And the other man very seldom replies: “To hell with your standard.” Nearly always he tries to make out that what he has been doing does not really go against the standard, or that if it does there is some special excuse. He pretends there is some special reason in this particular case why the person who took the seat first should not keep it, or that things were quite different when he was given the bit of orange, or that something has turned up which lets him off keeping his promise. It looks, in fact, very much as if both parties had in mind some kind of Law or Rule of fair play or decent behaviour or morality or whatever you like to call it, about which they really agreed. And they have. If they had not, they might, of course, fight like animals, but they could not quarrel in the human sense of the word. Quarrelling means trying to show that the other man is in the wrong. And there would be no sense in trying to do that unless you and he had some sort of agreement as to what Right and Wrong are; just as there would be no sense in saying that a footballer had committed a foul unless there was some agreement about the rules of football.</p>
</blockquote>
<blockquote>Life is not a "test", there are no second chances. A second chance simply takes away from value of "life".</blockquote>
<p>There is no claim in Christianity that life is a test, or that the afterlife is a second chance. In fact, focusing on this fallen world as some kind of mortal SAT is a terrible misunderstanding of Christianity, and leads to all manner of confusion. Jesus taught that we are to be a light to this world, a light shining in the darkness. We are to elevate and heal this world as much as possible, not “Get through it” or “Get passing marks”. As to your second point, I responded to that at the top of this post.</p>
<blockquote>The sun provides our Earth with a wonderful deadly ray which our Earth has the right material to protect itself from. The sun fuels life, everything grows because of the sun. It causes skin cancer but also grows your fruits and vegetables. Thus we are a form of cancer constantly creating a fresh human so that we can battle the clock.</blockquote>
<p>You are essentially expressing the basic idea of atheistic materialism, which has no answer for the law of Bio-genesis, or of consciousness.  “Omne vivum ex vivo” ?</p>
<blockquote>Religious people dislike astrology, but yet if you show them the word "god" or "faith" etc etc written using stars, they automatically go ape shit as if its a sign. fudgeing typical.
<p>As for the universe, I think a lot of theories about it are completely wrong and I think with enough time, we can figure it out. We are only at the beginning stage, give it another 10,000 years and I am sure we might know a little bit more.</p>
</blockquote>
<p>A theory is never claimed to be true. That is why it is a theory. This is the scientific method, of course, which I wholeheartedly believe in. Science never says “We know for sure that X is Y.” It says, “Our best method for understanding X is to model it as Y”. So scientific theories are not “Proven Wrong” they are simply replaced by more accurate models and modes of understanding. It is a pragmatic approach to the universe, not an authoritarian one.</p>
<blockquote>So where does it look like I stand? Is there a name for it? No i am not atheist or a Scientologist. I simply think that people fail to realize that the bible is wrong, science is all fudgeed up and there is a solution if people put their heads together rather than believing something that has already been written and manipulates people.</blockquote>
<p>It seems like you’re reaching for black and white explanations, but reality is always shades of gray. Some statements in the Bible are historically inaccurate, perhaps simply because of a scribe mis-copying a character or oral tradition going wrong, but whether the entire moral teaching and overall message of the Bible is wrong really depends on the conclusions that you personally are drawing from it. If you read the Bible, and your take-away from it is “I should not eat shell-fish because it is against the Mosaic covenant” then that doesn’t make the Bible wrong. If you read the Bible and your take-away is “I should give my money away to the poor because Jesus said so” that does not make the bible right.</p>
<p>As far as your point on Science being fudgeed up, see above where I address the Scientific method; which provides a <span class="bbcode-b">model and a method</span> not an authoritative answer.</p>
<blockquote>Heres my issue (for some people) : If I ask you right now, "Hey generate a new theory about life, death, god etc" you can't. You have already been manipulated to the point where you're unable to function without a "lead" or a "book" and thus you're fudgeed.</blockquote>
<p>I completely agree. It’s very scary to see how easily people are manipulated. There are constant assaults on the minds of young people, brainwashing them into accepting mindless consumerism, religious fanaticism, and all manner of unreasonable bullshit. As a seeker of the truth, you always have to be ready to come up with a new theory to explain what you see.</p>
<p>I’m not a Christian because of what I’ve been taught, because of tradition, because of what I read in a book, because of societal pressure. I’m a Christian because I have had a <span class="bbcode-b">real spiritual experience</span>. I have no trouble saying that if I had been visited by Vishnu and had been told authoritatively by him that Christianity was false, I would believe it, but I have not had that experience, so I do not renounce my faith.</p>
<blockquote>There runs a strange law through the length of human history — that men are continually tending to undervalue their environment, to undervalue their happiness, to undervalue themselves. The great sin of mankind, the sin typified by the fall of Adam, is the tendency, not towards pride, but towards this weird and horrible humility.
This is the great fall, the fall by which the fish forgets the sea, the ox forgets the meadow, the clerk forgets the city, every man forgets his environment and, in the fullest and most literal sense, forgets himself. This is the real fall of Adam, and it is a spiritual fall. It is a strange thing that many truly spiritual men, such as General Gordon, have actually spent some hours in speculating upon the precise location of the Garden of Eden. Most probably we are in Eden still. It is only our eyes that have changed.</blockquote>  :|
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rationality-and-belief-in-god/547957/41">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rationality-and-belief-in-god/547957/41</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 12 Aug 2015 17:31:28 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-547957-41</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rationality-and-belief-in-god/547957.rss">Rationality and Belief in God</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Rationality and Belief in God</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Rodgerwilco Rodgerwilco]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/rodgerwilco">@Rodgerwilco</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <blockquote>But why should death really be the end?</blockquote>
You're devaluing what we call "life". Why would life be oh so important if there is something after it? Pfft.
<p>I have yet to discover what I am, I will briefly describe my feelings towards the subject and you can kindly let me know.</p>
<p>I don’t believe in god.</p>
<p>The bible was written by a genius or geniuses. Truly a master of manipulation.</p>
<p>The afterlife isn’t a “new birth” or “second chance” or “heaven”, when you die you come to acceptance with the fact that your time is up and that you took part of what we call “life”.</p>
<p>Time and life don’t give a fudge. Life will find a way and time continues to move forward, with or without you.</p>
<p>There is no such thing as “sins”. Feel free to do the dirty, in some situations its perfectly fine to kill someone (self defense) and other times you’re judged for it? Cmon. Don’t give me that nonsense.</p>
<p>Life is not a “test”, there are no second chances. A second chance simply takes away from value of “life”.</p>
<p>The sun provides our Earth with a wonderful deadly ray which our Earth has the right material to protect itself from. The sun fuels life, everything grows because of the sun. It causes skin cancer but also grows your fruits and vegetables. Thus we are a form of cancer constantly creating a fresh human so that we can battle the clock.</p>
<p>Religious people dislike astrology, but yet if you show them the word “god” or “faith” etc etc written using stars, they automatically go ape shit as if its a sign. fudgeing typical.</p>
<p>As for the universe, I think a lot of theories about it are completely wrong and I think with enough time, we can figure it out. We are only at the beginning stage, give it another 10,000 years and I am sure we might know a little bit more.</p>
<p>So where does it look like I stand? Is there a name for it? No i am not atheist or a Scientologist. I simply think that people fail to realize that the bible is wrong, science is all fudgeed up and there is a solution if people put their heads together rather than believing something that has already been written and manipulates people.</p>
<p>Heres my issue (for some people) : If I ask you right now, “Hey generate a new theory about life, death, god etc” you can’t. You have already been manipulated to the point where you’re unable to function without a “lead” or a “book” and thus you’re fudgeed.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rationality-and-belief-in-god/547957/40">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rationality-and-belief-in-god/547957/40</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 12 Aug 2015 08:39:53 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-547957-40</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rationality-and-belief-in-god/547957.rss">Rationality and Belief in God</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Rationality and Belief in God</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@PaulT PaulT]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/pault">@PaulT</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>There are some interesting thoughts here. I love reading Pascal, what was his book, Principes, I think it was called? And Pascals wager is not really an argument for Gods existence, as OP said, it’s simple pragmatism. If doing X is claimed to cause Y, and there is no evidence except tradition, and if  Y were to not occur then it means death, then is there any logical reason to not do X? Why risk (eternal) death? There is a great reason for some; to find truth, even if it means death.</p>
<p>And this is the position of mystics or spiritual seekers. They ask every appariton of the diety to prove themselves; the shaman communes with many Gods, but trusts none of them. Only in death is the final analysis complete for the Hero archetype, he is always seeking. This is why those who have had near death experiences make great shamans. But why should death really be the end?</p>
<p>If religion is the ritual which binds spirituality into culturally appropriate outlets, then Mysticism is the lonesome pursuit of the individual towards union with God. If an individual dies, physics tells us that none of the matter or energy inside of them is destroyed, only trasferred. We don’t know what consciousness is. Science can only describe the patterns of energetic impulses in the brain. Is it so hard to see that the mystic is simply listening to a much larger energetic phenomenon, a bigger pattern.</p>
<p>I’m a Christian, I love Jesus. That doesnt stop me from saying there is alot of truth to Buddhist philosphy, Taoist philosolhy, Suffi mysticism, Hegelian dialectics, and many other religious texts. These are elements of truth, only a part of the revelation. Did you know Jesus said to his People “You are all Gods”? He also said “The eyes are the mirror to the soul”. And he said “If you have seen me, you have seen the Father.”</p>
<p>If you can look at another human with love, you are witness to the very face of God. If you give a drop of water to him that thirsts, you are feeding the Lord of creation. Do you not see that this is truth? That to transcend yourself is to take part in the life divine?</p>
<p>Let’s go back to the hero archetype. Jesus doesnt cheat death to be reincarnated an infinite number of times, like the Hero or Shaman archetype, he conquers it. This is expressed in the Buddha myth; reincarnation is a prison. That is to say, matter is the prison  of consciousness. Escape is only possible through transcendence. This is described perfecly as the Heavenly Bodies of Christian tradition. We are not dissolved into absolute unity, as in the incomplete Buddha myth says, rather we are perfected and completed by union with God, and made into what we always were.</p>
<p>I’m not sure if finding proofs is a good way to understand how religion works, as a model of the universe. God is evidenced, not by his creation, but by his very partners in creation. Each man has a spark of the one true flame.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rationality-and-belief-in-god/547957/39">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rationality-and-belief-in-god/547957/39</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 05 Aug 2015 03:57:48 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-547957-39</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rationality-and-belief-in-god/547957.rss">Rationality and Belief in God</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Rationality and Belief in God</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@malikz malikz]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/malikz">@malikz</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote" data-post="37" data-topic="547957">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/mike4ever/40/5_e05bb34c421432ee4d40de30c10af3e5.png" class="avatar"> mike4ever:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>As a whole we are god. We shape everything around us as well as the sun’s gravitational force keeps Earth in rotation around it. Energy in itself can not be created nor destory’d just change forms and if this is true, which I believe it to be so, that same powerful energy that created everything in existence is trying to balance itself out and become whole again; Just like the battery in your laptop is circulating energy through your monitor to release light which is then interpreted by your mind which is powered by what you eat, how much you sleep, and excising your body. The ideas shown by religions are a reflection of ourselves or how we would like to live in our environment to try and shape a better existence but the problem with this was there was many conflicting ideas and the energy be hide those ideas are still trying to balance each other out. Hence extremist in said religions and atheists. If we all just took a second to actually see things and just feel we would all be so much better off. Pride, greed, and ignorance has consumed us but truth be told that will all change, it’s just a matter of time. When we no longer want, our mind won’t be clouded from what we <span class="bbcode-b">actually need</span> .</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>But can you stop yourself from dying though?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rationality-and-belief-in-god/547957/38">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rationality-and-belief-in-god/547957/38</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 27 Jun 2015 03:42:21 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-547957-38</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rationality-and-belief-in-god/547957.rss">Rationality and Belief in God</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Rationality and Belief in God</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@mike4ever mike4ever]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/mike4ever">@mike4ever</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>As a whole we are god. We shape everything around us as well as the sun’s gravitational force keeps Earth in rotation around it. Energy in itself can not be created nor destory’d just change forms and if this is true, which I believe it to be so, that same powerful energy that created everything in existence is trying to balance itself out and become whole again; Just like the battery in your laptop is circulating energy through your monitor to release light which is then interpreted by your mind which is powered by what you eat, how much you sleep, and excising your body. The ideas shown by religions are a reflection of ourselves or how we would like to live in our environment to try and shape a better existence but the problem with this was there was many conflicting ideas and the energy be hide those ideas are still trying to balance each other out. Hence extremist in said religions and atheists. If we all just took a second to actually see things and just feel we would all be so much better off. Pride, greed, and ignorance has consumed us but truth be told that will all change, it’s just a matter of time. When we no longer want, our mind won’t be clouded from what we <span class="bbcode-b">actually need</span> .</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rationality-and-belief-in-god/547957/37">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rationality-and-belief-in-god/547957/37</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 03 Apr 2015 09:27:42 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-547957-37</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rationality-and-belief-in-god/547957.rss">Rationality and Belief in God</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Rationality and Belief in God</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@RiiPiiNFtW RiiPiiNFtW]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/riipiinftw">@RiiPiiNFtW</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“Vix, post:34, topic:547957”]I actually met God in a bathroom at an Avenged Sevenfold concert after a doctor who happened to be in the crowd gave me some unmarked pills.[/quote]ME TOO!</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rationality-and-belief-in-god/547957/36">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rationality-and-belief-in-god/547957/36</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 02 Apr 2015 22:59:31 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-547957-36</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rationality-and-belief-in-god/547957.rss">Rationality and Belief in God</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Rationality and Belief in God</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@ItsNateDuh ItsNateDuh]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/itsnateduh">@ItsNateDuh</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Quote from “God”, “Ehh I’m getting bored of starring at darkness, if I imagine it it’s sure to appear, oh there we go there’s the world. Yay time to create things that hate me!!! YAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAY”</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rationality-and-belief-in-god/547957/35">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rationality-and-belief-in-god/547957/35</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 05 Mar 2015 03:40:07 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-547957-35</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rationality-and-belief-in-god/547957.rss">Rationality and Belief in God</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Rationality and Belief in God</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Vix Vix]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/vix">@Vix</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I actually met God in a bathroom at an Avenged Sevenfold concert after a doctor who happened to be in the crowd gave me some unmarked pills.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rationality-and-belief-in-god/547957/34">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rationality-and-belief-in-god/547957/34</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2015 05:43:19 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-547957-34</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rationality-and-belief-in-god/547957.rss">Rationality and Belief in God</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Rationality and Belief in God</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Uncalled Uncalled]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/uncalled">@Uncalled</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“jme, post:16, topic:547957”]Not really. He is using the threat of hell as a logical reason to believe in God. I did the same thing to point out it’s absurdity.</p>
<p>You’re saying we should believe in the flying spaghetti monster?[/quote]Hey, pastafarianism is the real deal<br>
<a href="http://www.theregister.co.uk/2008/08/21/galactic_spaghetti_monster/" class="onebox" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">http://www.theregister.co.uk/2008/08/21/galactic_spaghetti_monster/</a></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rationality-and-belief-in-god/547957/33">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rationality-and-belief-in-god/547957/33</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2015 20:18:54 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-547957-33</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rationality-and-belief-in-god/547957.rss">Rationality and Belief in God</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Rationality and Belief in God</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@D3i7y D3i7y]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/d3i7y">@D3i7y</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I guess i’m one of those people who really could care less rather there is a god or there isn’t. Personally i usually stay out of these discussions but why not put my two cents in i’m sure people care right? no well i will explain why i don’t understand how an imaginary being in the sky or universe whatever has the power to create anything then allows his people to kill other people. now i have been told hail fire and brim stone preachers as well as hey god loves us all. He works in his own way.</p>
<p>I don’t believe there is a god nor does anyone else. If they do they are most likely a crazy prophet of some sort. I lost hope in the lord when i use to pray for him to help me. What this imaginary person gave me was a house fire. the death of my grand mother. the death of my dog &amp; cat. then allows my parents to become drug addicts all in 3 years time. So if there is a god he sure as hell doesn’t love my family. So if there was a god he is either irreverent or imaginary. He puts such “good”  where people see angels. or walk into the light and all the rubbish.</p>
<p>If your god loved his people in the bible why would he start a war in the end of days? how human is that just zap satan or who ever into a black hole or something if he is all powerful. remove all the nukes would be a good place to start if he isn’t a magician</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rationality-and-belief-in-god/547957/32">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rationality-and-belief-in-god/547957/32</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2015 19:23:38 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-547957-32</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rationality-and-belief-in-god/547957.rss">Rationality and Belief in God</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Rationality and Belief in God</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Tutorial Tutorial]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/tutorial">@Tutorial</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I believe we should all at the least be practical with our belief in God. I definitely think religion and science should play out together in an acceptable fashion. I like to think of the phenomena in the universe as a reason to strive and grasp a science-based explanation of things that would otherwise be considered as miracles.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rationality-and-belief-in-god/547957/31">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rationality-and-belief-in-god/547957/31</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2015 05:01:34 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-547957-31</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rationality-and-belief-in-god/547957.rss">Rationality and Belief in God</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Rationality and Belief in God</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@the_wanderer The Wanderer]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/the_wanderer">@the_wanderer</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“Bowser jr, post:11, topic:547957”]"all-powerful - having power over all"<br>
God can’t be all powerful since he can’t make something that is too heavy for him to lift. You need to make a meaningful definition of all-powerful before you say that God is all powerful.</p>
<p>"all-knowing - knowing everything"<br>
Do he knows the future? And how does he know what will happen in the future?</p>
<p>"moral - concerned with the principles of right and wrong behavior and the goodness or badness of human character"<br>
Right and wrong is a made up concept. Everyone who has some sense of what’s right and wrong is moral according to your definition. You can’t be morally perfect.</p>
<p>"perfect - having all the required or desirable elements, qualities, or characteristics; as good as it is possible to be"<br>
How do you know if something is perfect?[/quote]<br>
Perhaps then I’d say all-powerful is being as powerful as we can imagine. That would eliminate any paradoxes such as the one you proposed.</p>
<p>I don’t see any problems with someone knowing the future even if there are multiple futures as you could know all of the future possibilities.</p>
<p>Just for arguments sake say God actually did write the Ten Commandments and passed them onto Moses. These are the tenets according to God to live by. So being morally perfect would be maximizing these tenets in every action God performs. It is hard to know if something is perfect but if you know everything then surely you know what is perfect.</p>
<p>I feel slightly like Euthyphro trying to define a western God to Socrates. <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=5" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"> I believe that unlike Socrates you do have a concept of what a western God such as the christian God entails so maybe you could give me the definition I’m seeking for.</p>
<p>[quote=“Bowser jr, post:11, topic:547957”][quote author=mona lisa link=topic=666861.msg4459167#msg4459167 date=1416605214]<br>
I believe in the Law of Attraction, which states everything is made up of energy and energy attracts like things. Your feelings and thoughts send off waves there for by thinking positive and always believing in yourself you can have what ever you want.The images you project in your mind is what manifests in the outer self. By knowing what you want and believing that you can have it, it will come because it will be attracted to you. You ask a scientist what made everything they will say energy. Ask a scientist what energy is made up of he/she will say energy can not be created, can not be destroyed, it is for ever in existence, and could do anything. Ask a priest who made the world he will say god. Ask a priest what is god he will say god can not be created, can not be destroyed, he is for ever in existence, and can do anything. Same definitions…What is everything including yourself made up of? Energy… You are your own god and create your own world.<br>
[/quote]<br>
We can’t really say that energy exist, just like we can’t say that velocity exists. Potential and kinetic are properties of other objects. A flying cannon ball have energy because it is in a gravitational field and it is moving fast compared to the surface. It doesn’t mean that a cannonball has some inherit energyness.[/quote]<br>
Things do have inherit energyness as you stated, it’s called rest energy. A diatomic molecule of oxygen that is vibrating has slightly less mass than two non interacting oxygen molecules because some of that energy is used up in its vibrational kinetic energy. I agree with everything else you said though.</p>
<p>So I pretty much agree with everything that’s being said so far. But is it rational to believe in God for those that do believe in God? I don’t think I can create an argument that says God does not exist because as other’s have stated before we have only been able to explain through science how the expansion of the universe started. We are nowhere close to knowing how space and time itself was created and where the singularity came from (branes anyone?).</p>
<p>I personally believe people can be rational believing in God if that is their choice. I cannot give an argument for the existence of my hand, yet I believe it is rational to believe I do indeed have a hand based on my perceptual experiences. People also claim to have religious experiences that cause them to change their beliefs so therefore I think it is rational for them to believe in a God based on their experiences. The only difference is that I personally do not think it is rational for me to believe in God as I have not had any religious experiences so therefore I do not believe in God.</p>
<p>[quote=“jme, post:26, topic:547957”][quote author=Niall link=topic=666861.msg4463077#msg4463077 date=1418597553]<br>
P.S. Just FYI, the big bang theory only deals with the formation of the universe in the rapid expansion of space-time, the big bang theory does not cover anything before or the creation of the singularity that eventually expanded (and is still expanding) into the universe that we all know and love.<br>
[/quote]</p>
<p>And on this trippy note, there is no “before” the singularity, since time itself didn’t exist. If that’s not hard enough to wrap your head around, the thought of multiple universes kills my thinking power. Since there is no space outside of the universe, where do these multiple universes reside? What direction would you need to travel to them, it couldn’t be x,y,z. We know that the creation of our universe was possible, so there’s nothing to suggest the creation of other universes wouldn’t be possible. What if there’s something even bigger going on from there? (not in the literal sense)</p>
<p>so fun :D[/quote]<br>
I don’t want to derail this topic but I totally agree with this haha. I cannot encompass how the actual fabric of space and time was created and I wonder if it will ever be understood. Also on the side of multiple universes I believe you would need extra time dimensions. I’ve always wanted to ask a professor, but a lot of people use string theory as a proponent for multiple universes as there could exist multiple dimensions besides the four we experience. However, I think to have multiple universes you would need extra time dimensions rather than extra spatial dimensions. Any event in this universe can be described by a point with coordinates (x,y,z,t) right? Well I think of multiple universes as kinda of being like slideshows. Each slide is a dimension that has those four dimensions (x,y,z,t). In order to travel to the other universe we have to travel in a fifth dimension, say w. However, are we traveling in space or time? In another universe people say I may exist and be a millionaire. I don’t think that in that sense we would be traveling spatially as there are two “me’s”. In order for two me’s to exist I’d have to go to a different time plane. Maybe you’ve read more about this and can enlighten me but it just never made sense that you could just add dimensions and have multiple universes to me. To me you need to add multiple time dimensions.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rationality-and-belief-in-god/547957/30">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rationality-and-belief-in-god/547957/30</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2014 19:33:27 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-547957-30</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rationality-and-belief-in-god/547957.rss">Rationality and Belief in God</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Rationality and Belief in God</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@jme jme]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/jme">@jme</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“Pure_, post:28, topic:547957”][quote author=Seamen link=topic=666861.msg4463115#msg4463115 date=1418609698]<br>
<a class="mention" href="/u/jme">@jme</a>: See - <a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Multiverse">http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Multiverse</a><br>
[/quote]hes a crackhead, that comment was made while high<br>
tl;dr ignore him[/quote]</p>
<p>They were some hypothetical questions, I’ve read all multiverse explanations before.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rationality-and-belief-in-god/547957/29">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rationality-and-belief-in-god/547957/29</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2014 15:15:25 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-547957-29</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rationality-and-belief-in-god/547957.rss">Rationality and Belief in God</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Rationality and Belief in God</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@pure2ownage Pure_]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/pure2ownage">@pure2ownage</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“Seamen, post:27, topic:547957”]<a class="mention" href="/u/jme">@jme</a>: See - <a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Multiverse%5B/quote%5Dhes" rel="nofollow noopener">http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Multiverse[/quote]hes</a> a crackhead, that comment was made while high<br>
tl;dr ignore him</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rationality-and-belief-in-god/547957/28">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rationality-and-belief-in-god/547957/28</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2014 12:21:51 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-547957-28</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rationality-and-belief-in-god/547957.rss">Rationality and Belief in God</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Rationality and Belief in God</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Seamen Seamen]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/seamen">@Seamen</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p><a class="mention" href="/u/jme">@jme</a>: See - <a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Multiverse" rel="nofollow noopener">http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Multiverse</a></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rationality-and-belief-in-god/547957/27">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rationality-and-belief-in-god/547957/27</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2014 02:14:58 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-547957-27</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rationality-and-belief-in-god/547957.rss">Rationality and Belief in God</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Rationality and Belief in God</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@jme jme]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/jme">@jme</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote" data-post="22" data-topic="547957">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 Niall:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>P.S. Just FYI, the big bang theory only deals with the formation of the universe in the rapid expansion of space-time, the big bang theory does not cover anything before or the creation of the singularity that eventually expanded (and is still expanding) into the universe that we all know and love.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>And on this trippy note, there is no “before” the singularity, since time itself didn’t exist. If that’s not hard enough to wrap your head around, the thought of multiple universes kills my thinking power. Since there is no space outside of the universe, where do these multiple universes reside? What direction would you need to travel to them, it couldn’t be x,y,z. We know that the creation of our universe was possible, so there’s nothing to suggest the creation of other universes wouldn’t be possible. What if there’s something even bigger going on from there? (not in the literal sense)</p>
<p>so fun <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/smiley.png?v=5" title=":smiley:" class="emoji" alt=":smiley:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rationality-and-belief-in-god/547957/26">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rationality-and-belief-in-god/547957/26</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2014 01:30:22 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-547957-26</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rationality-and-belief-in-god/547957.rss">Rationality and Belief in God</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Rationality and Belief in God</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@pure2ownage Pure_]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/pure2ownage">@pure2ownage</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Protip: the big-bang isn’t the theory detailing the ‘earliest’ point in the process of creation, so even if the big bang does not explain something it doesn’t mean that science hasn’t tried to/has done so already.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rationality-and-belief-in-god/547957/25">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rationality-and-belief-in-god/547957/25</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 14 Dec 2014 22:58:36 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-547957-25</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rationality-and-belief-in-god/547957.rss">Rationality and Belief in God</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Rationality and Belief in God</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@The_Un-Named The Un-Named]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/the_un-named">@The_Un-Named</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>My apologies. Into the universe that we all know and some of us love.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rationality-and-belief-in-god/547957/24">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rationality-and-belief-in-god/547957/24</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 14 Dec 2014 22:57:01 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-547957-24</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rationality-and-belief-in-god/547957.rss">Rationality and Belief in God</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Rationality and Belief in God</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@bowserjr2 Bowser jr]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/bowserjr2">@bowserjr2</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I don’t love this universe, stop making up false facts.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rationality-and-belief-in-god/547957/23">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rationality-and-belief-in-god/547957/23</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 14 Dec 2014 22:54:50 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-547957-23</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rationality-and-belief-in-god/547957.rss">Rationality and Belief in God</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Rationality and Belief in God</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@The_Un-Named The Un-Named]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/the_un-named">@The_Un-Named</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“Ashi, post:18, topic:547957”][quote author=Niall link=topic=666861.msg4463069#msg4463069 date=1418595755]</p>
<aside class="quote">
<blockquote>
<p>Atheists are just people who don’t like not knowing things.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>That’s funny, because it’s almost exclusively religious people to claim to know how the universe was created.<br>
[/quote]<br>
How? Saying God created it doesn’t mean they know the whole creation process.[/quote]</p>
<p>But it does - “god did it” or “god set the plans in motion”, and that’s enough for some people. They’re content with knowing how the universe was created - “god did it” - and they’re content with not needing to know why the universe was created because they shift that burden onto god, followed by “you can’t comprehend god”.</p>
<p>It’s not even Atheists who are the ones who need to know things, it’s scientists, and they don’t even claim to know things, they aim to seek knowledge - to seek understanding, and are constantly trying to disprove their own ideas. It’s as much of a pursuit of knowledge as it is a pursuit of improving ones self and the self of the collective.</p>
<p>P.S. Just FYI, the big bang theory only deals with the formation of the universe in the rapid expansion of space-time, the big bang theory does not cover anything before or the creation of the singularity that eventually expanded (and is still expanding) into the universe that we all know and love.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rationality-and-belief-in-god/547957/22">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rationality-and-belief-in-god/547957/22</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 14 Dec 2014 22:52:33 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-547957-22</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rationality-and-belief-in-god/547957.rss">Rationality and Belief in God</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Rationality and Belief in God</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@pure2ownage Pure_]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/pure2ownage">@pure2ownage</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“Bowser jr, post:19, topic:547957”][quote author=Ashi link=topic=666861.msg4463072#msg4463072 date=1418596468]</p>
<aside class="quote">
<blockquote>
<aside class="quote">
<blockquote>
<p>Atheists are just people who don’t like not knowing things.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>That’s funny, because it’s almost exclusively religious people to claim to know how the universe was created.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>How? Saying God created it doesn’t mean they know the whole creation process.<br>
[/quote]<br>
Your Bible state the whole creation process. God speaks and stuff appears.[/quote]It’s more so that they want to think that there is a scientific (i.e. ‘logical’) reason to the whole creation process. They can’t/don’t want to comprehend the process, if it was as simple as a diety twirling their finger around for half a second.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rationality-and-belief-in-god/547957/21">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rationality-and-belief-in-god/547957/21</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 14 Dec 2014 22:43:56 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-547957-21</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rationality-and-belief-in-god/547957.rss">Rationality and Belief in God</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Rationality and Belief in God</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Ashi Ashi]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/ashi">@Ashi</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote" data-post="19" data-topic="547957">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 Bowser jr:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Your Bible state the whole creation process. God speaks and stuff appears.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I’d like to think of it as a development log <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/wink.png?v=5" title=":wink:" class="emoji" alt=":wink:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rationality-and-belief-in-god/547957/20">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rationality-and-belief-in-god/547957/20</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 14 Dec 2014 22:41:26 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-547957-20</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rationality-and-belief-in-god/547957.rss">Rationality and Belief in God</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
