<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Server Problem - Help</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/server-problem-help/247457</link>
    <description>Ok, so I&#39;ve gotten help on other threads, but now I&#39;m going to show you what I&#39;m doing through screenshots. I will post them in two posts, as there might be a lot. Take a look at the steps that I&#39;m doing, and see what I&#39;m doing wrong.

Step 1 Downloading JDK

Ok, so a few days ago I was searching the web at guides on making server, and a lot of them said it&#39;s required for JDK update 6u6 for the server, so I went ahead and downloaded that. Yesterday I recently downloaded 6u10 update for the server, which I beleive it&#39;s the recent one. So that was taken care of.

Step 2 

A few weeks ago I also went ahead and downloaded No-ip, and I am recently having problems with getting my server online with the no-ip address. Using Hamachi messed up my computer&#39;s connection so it took me a while to get it back online.


[img]http://runelocus.com/forums/attachment.php?attachmentid=267&amp;stc=1&amp;thumb=1&amp;d=1227970397[/img]

Now then I opened up the program for no-ip, and it&#39;s that little update thing for your host. 
[img]http://runelocus.com/forums/attachment.php?attachmentid=268&amp;d=1227970404[/img]

Step 3 

I currently opened my port by going to these settings

&gt; Start &gt; Search &gt; &quot;firewall&quot; &gt; Opened Windows Firewall &gt; Allow a program through firewall &gt; New Port &gt; Name: RSPS &gt; Port 43594 &gt; ok &gt; ok

[img]http://runelocus.com/forums/attachment.php?attachmentid=269&amp;d=1227970696[/img]

Step 4 Portforwarding

Now I don&#39;t have the Linkys network, but I use a program known as Utorrent. I currently have followed the guide into &quot;portforwarding&quot; there, with allowing the connection through and changing the settings, but let me go through on what I did.

Opened program &gt; Fire &gt; Prefences &gt; Connection, now this is what I&#39;ve done:

PORT NUMBER: 43594
PORT USED FOR INCOMING CONNECTIONS: 
ENABLE UPnP port mapping &gt; Enabled
ENABLE NAT-PMP port mapping &gt; Enabled 

Then I clicked on the expection of the firewall, and then I pressed ok. Now I&#39;m done with that.

Step 5 Downloading a soruce

Ok, so three days ago I downloaded a soruce from the 1000+ download views sticky here in the RuneLocus forums, and I downloaded Full Metalstscape. So I downloaded that etc.

Step 6: Error &#39;System path&#39;

Ok, this error when I try to complie my server always happens to me. Now while I was reading you have to change your CLASSPATH and PATH to a different code, but it also said it&#39;s required for Java 6u1 too. So I went ahead and downloaded Java 6u1. 

[img]http://runelocus.com/forums/attachment.php?attachmentid=276&amp;d=1227980371[/img]

Now that was the end of the guide, and I thought I was done. So I went on Silab put in my no-ip, made sure the port was correct, and then &quot;Error connecting to server&quot;.

Now some people might say &quot;Was your server running?&quot; Yes, it was...

So what am I doing wrong?

[br][br][size=1]Posted on: November 29, 2008, 11:58:10 am[/size][hr]Sorry about the images.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 21 Dec 2008 03:33:20 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/server-problem-help/247457.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Server Problem - Help</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@itfchaos itfchaos]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/itfchaos">@itfchaos</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>So your compiler isn’t working, well this maybe the problem…</p>
<p>Open your source, and right click your compiler and click on “Edit”.</p>
<p>you should see something like</p>
<p>set pro=%programfiles%\Java\jdk1.6.0_11<br>
set pro2=%programfiles%\Java\jdk1.6.0_11</p>
<p>should be the 3rd and 4th line down. you will have to change the jdk1.6.0_11 part of that to the type of jdk you got and your compiler should work just fine.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/server-problem-help/247457/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/server-problem-help/247457/2</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 21 Dec 2008 03:33:20 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-247457-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/server-problem-help/247457.rss">Server Problem - Help</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Server Problem - Help</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@KodGex KodGex]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/kodgex">@KodGex</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Ok, so I’ve gotten help on other threads, but now I’m going to show you what I’m doing through screenshots. I will post them in two posts, as there might be a lot. Take a look at the steps that I’m doing, and see what I’m doing wrong.</p>
<p>Step 1 Downloading JDK</p>
<p>Ok, so a few days ago I was searching the web at guides on making server, and a lot of them said it’s required for JDK update 6u6 for the server, so I went ahead and downloaded that. Yesterday I recently downloaded 6u10 update for the server, which I beleive it’s the recent one. So that was taken care of.</p>
<p>Step 2</p>
<p>A few weeks ago I also went ahead and downloaded No-ip, and I am recently having problems with getting my server online with the no-ip address. Using Hamachi messed up my computer’s connection so it took me a while to get it back online.</p>
<p><img src="http://runelocus.com/forums/attachment.php?attachmentid=267&amp;stc=1&amp;thumb=1&amp;d=1227970397" alt width="" height=""></p>
<p>Now then I opened up the program for no-ip, and it’s that little update thing for your host.<br>
<img src="http://runelocus.com/forums/attachment.php?attachmentid=268&amp;d=1227970404" alt width="" height=""></p>
<p>Step 3</p>
<p>I currently opened my port by going to these settings</p>
<blockquote>
<p>Start &gt; Search &gt; “firewall” &gt; Opened Windows Firewall &gt; Allow a program through firewall &gt; New Port &gt; Name: RSPS &gt; Port 43594 &gt; ok &gt; ok</p>
</blockquote>
<p><img src="http://runelocus.com/forums/attachment.php?attachmentid=269&amp;d=1227970696" alt width="" height=""></p>
<p>Step 4 Portforwarding</p>
<p>Now I don’t have the Linkys network, but I use a program known as Utorrent. I currently have followed the guide into “portforwarding” there, with allowing the connection through and changing the settings, but let me go through on what I did.</p>
<p>Opened program &gt; Fire &gt; Prefences &gt; Connection, now this is what I’ve done:</p>
<p>PORT NUMBER: 43594<br>
PORT USED FOR INCOMING CONNECTIONS:<br>
ENABLE UPnP port mapping &gt; Enabled<br>
ENABLE NAT-PMP port mapping &gt; Enabled</p>
<p>Then I clicked on the expection of the firewall, and then I pressed ok. Now I’m done with that.</p>
<p>Step 5 Downloading a soruce</p>
<p>Ok, so three days ago I downloaded a soruce from the 1000+ download views sticky here in the RuneLocus forums, and I downloaded Full Metalstscape. So I downloaded that etc.</p>
<p>Step 6: Error ‘System path’</p>
<p>Ok, this error when I try to complie my server always happens to me. Now while I was reading you have to change your CLASSPATH and PATH to a different code, but it also said it’s required for Java 6u1 too. So I went ahead and downloaded Java 6u1.</p>
<p><img src="http://runelocus.com/forums/attachment.php?attachmentid=276&amp;d=1227980371" alt width="" height=""></p>
<p>Now that was the end of the guide, and I thought I was done. So I went on Silab put in my no-ip, made sure the port was correct, and then “Error connecting to server”.</p>
<p>Now some people might say “Was your server running?” Yes, it was…</p>
<p>So what am I doing wrong?</p>
<p>[br][br][size=1]Posted on: November 29, 2008, 11:58:10 am[/size][hr]Sorry about the images.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/server-problem-help/247457/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/server-problem-help/247457/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 29 Nov 2008 17:32:57 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-247457-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/server-problem-help/247457.rss">Server Problem - Help</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
