<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Private Server Mindset</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/private-server-mindset/534034</link>
    <description>Just trying to provoke debate.

Too many of us are trying to be aspiring businessmen or professional MMORPG developers, when in reality we are very unprofessionally ripping off Jagex and RuneScape. 

What are we trying to achieve? Thinking back to the origin of private servers, they were more or less an accident. It was just a point of concept/place to test the earliest RuneScape bots. Not a place to emulate, customise or express our ideas and concepts of the real game. And definitely not a place to earn a modest living off.

So why are we still here? How has RSPS evolved over the years, and why is it at the stage we are at now? Private servers are shit, to be frank. They do not work, they look ugly most of the time and are usually an insult to the original game. Some people see it as a cash cow, and 9 times out of 10 fail miserably. Only a handful last for years. 

Don&#39;t get me wrong, I am a part of this, and I do get personal satisfaction messing around with servers and building a community, but we just need to remember who we are from a moral point of view.

So, why are we still here, doing what we are doing? Well, one does not simply quit private servers.

There is no general point to make in this topic, just wanted to hear people&#39;s views on the subject(s) raised.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 12 Oct 2013 21:43:48 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/private-server-mindset/534034.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Private Server Mindset</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@strucker Strucker]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/strucker">@strucker</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“Clawz fury, post:2, topic:534034”]why am i here: to express my creativity and to even make a few friends (and some bucks)</p>
<p>im currently developing on my own server and hopefully ill host it one day. i love doing this shit. its awesome being able to program whatever creative idea i come up with.[/quote]rep++ my friend</p>
<p>Ot:<br>
the first private server i played was most likely slashscape or sinzscape back in early 09, after that i made an account on mopar because i was interested in having my own server, and wow, i was like 10, i wanted to make money too!<br>
Yet it was hard, so i quitted a few times, or just stopped it, but I’ve learned so much and its so fun, i feel relaxed when im programming, also It’s cool as you make some friends, I havent known lare (clawzfury) for too long, in november itll be a year, but he’s really cool i have spent fun time with him, and the cool thing is that we dont only talk about this shit.<br>
I’ve made other friends like luna, tom(south-park), uhm and arham perhaps, Sk8r is cool too, but dont really talk to much with him, but I’m here to express and contribute to the community, i wouldn’t have like 40 snippets if it wasnt for it.</p>
<p>The thing is we are here to make our server but we do alotta other things on the way like clawz said.<br>
But what im trying to achieve is to make my programming knowledge bigger, make a few thruly friends and make a fun server.</p>
<p>Why am i still here? Well sometimes i leave rsps after being on it for like 4 months, and after other 4 months i dont know how i get back to it, but well, I think i’m still here because i enjoy it.</p>
<p>I swapped this from the bottom of my heart so not hating pl0’x</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/private-server-mindset/534034/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/private-server-mindset/534034/3</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 12 Oct 2013 21:43:48 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-534034-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/private-server-mindset/534034.rss">Private Server Mindset</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Private Server Mindset</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Clawz_fury lare69]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/clawz_fury">@Clawz_fury</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>why am i here: to express my creativity and to even make a few friends (and some bucks)</p>
<p>im currently developing on my own server and hopefully ill host it one day. i love doing this shit. its awesome being able to program whatever creative idea i come up with.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/private-server-mindset/534034/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/private-server-mindset/534034/2</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 12 Oct 2013 21:28:58 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-534034-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/private-server-mindset/534034.rss">Private Server Mindset</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Private Server Mindset</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@King_JC King JC]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/king_jc">@King_JC</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Just trying to provoke debate.</p>
<p>Too many of us are trying to be aspiring businessmen or professional MMORPG developers, when in reality we are very unprofessionally ripping off Jagex and RuneScape.</p>
<p>What are we trying to achieve? Thinking back to the origin of private servers, they were more or less an accident. It was just a point of concept/place to test the earliest RuneScape bots. Not a place to emulate, customise or express our ideas and concepts of the real game. And definitely not a place to earn a modest living off.</p>
<p>So why are we still here? How has RSPS evolved over the years, and why is it at the stage we are at now? Private servers are shit, to be frank. They do not work, they look ugly most of the time and are usually an insult to the original game. Some people see it as a cash cow, and 9 times out of 10 fail miserably. Only a handful last for years.</p>
<p>Don’t get me wrong, I am a part of this, and I do get personal satisfaction messing around with servers and building a community, but we just need to remember who we are from a moral point of view.</p>
<p>So, why are we still here, doing what we are doing? Well, one does not simply quit private servers.</p>
<p>There is no general point to make in this topic, just wanted to hear people’s views on the subject(s) raised.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/private-server-mindset/534034/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/private-server-mindset/534034/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 12 Oct 2013 17:15:20 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-534034-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/private-server-mindset/534034.rss">Private Server Mindset</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
