<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Kepler 22-b</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/kepler-22-b/424221</link>
    <description>
[font=arial][size=6]Kepler 22-b: Earth-like planet confirmed[/size][/font]

[font=arial][size=4]The planet lies about 15% closer to its star than the Earth is to the Sun[/size][/font]
[b]
[font=arial][size=4][img]http://news.bbcimg.co.uk/media/images/57141000/jpg/_57141085_57140831.jpg[/img][/size][/font][/b]


[font=arial][size=5][b]Astronomers have confirmed the existence of an Earth-like planet in the &quot;habitable zone&quot; around a star not unlike our own.[/b][/size][/font]

[font=arial][size=4]The planet, Kepler 22-b, lies about 600 light-years away and is about 2.4 times the size of Earth, and has a temperature of about 22C.[/size][/font]

[font=arial][size=4]It is the closest confirmed planet yet to one like ours - an &quot;Earth 2.0&quot;.[/size][/font]

[font=arial][size=4]However, the team does not yet know if Kepler 22-b is made mostly of rock, gas or liquid.[/size][/font]

[font=arial][size=4]During the conference at which the result was announced, the Kepler team said that it had spotted some 1,094 new candidate planets.[/size][/font]

[font=arial][size=4]The Kepler space telescope was designed to look at a fixed swathe of the night sky, staring intently at about 150,000 stars. The telescope is sensitive enough to see when a planet passes in front of its host star, dimming the star&#39;s light by a minuscule amount.[/size][/font]

[font=arial][size=4]Kepler identifies these slight changes in starlight as candidate planets, which are then confirmed by further observations by Kepler and other telescopes in orbit and on Earth.[/size][/font]
[font=arial][size=4]-------------------------------------------------------[/size][/font]
[font=arial][size=4]Kepler 22-b was one of 54 candidates reported by the Kepler team in February, and is just the first to be formally confirmed using other telescopes.[/size][/font]

[font=arial][size=4]More of these &quot;Earth 2.0&quot; candidates are likely to be confirmed in the near future, though a redefinition of the habitable zone&#39;s boundaries has brought that number down to 48.[/size][/font]

[font=arial][size=4]Kepler 22-b lies at a distance from its sun about 15% less than the distance from the Earth to the Sun, and its year takes about 290 days. However, its sun puts out about 25% less light, keeping the planet at its balmy temperature that would support the existence of liquid water.[/size][/font]

[font=arial][size=4]The Kepler team had to wait for three passes of the planet before upping its status from &quot;candidate&quot; to &quot;confirmed&quot;.[/size][/font]

[font=arial][size=4]&quot;Fortune smiled upon us with the detection of this planet,&quot; said William Borucki, Kepler principal investigator at Nasa&#39;s Ames Research Center.[/size][/font]

[font=arial][size=4]&quot;The first transit was captured just three days after we declared the spacecraft operationally ready. We witnessed the defining third transit over the 2010 holiday season.&quot;[/size][/font]

[font=arial][size=4]The results were announced at the Kepler telescope&#39;s first science conference, alongside the staggering number of new candidate planets. The total number of candidates spotted by the telescope is now 2,326 - of which 207 are approximately Earth-sized.[/size][/font]

[font=arial][size=4]In total, the results suggest that planets ranging from Earth-sized to about four times Earth&#39;s size - so-called &quot;super-Earths&quot; - may be more common than previously thought.[/size][/font]
[size=4][img]http://news.bbcimg.co.uk/media/images/57140000/jpg/_57140840_57140839.jpg[/img][/size]
[font=arial][size=4]-------------------------------------------------------[/size][/font]
[font=arial][size=4]Kepler Space Telescope[/size][/font]
[size=4][img]http://news.bbcimg.co.uk/media/images/51081000/jpg/_51081777__45486596_kepler_inf226-1.jpg[/img][/size]
[font=arial][size=4]- Stares fixedly at a patch corresponding to 1/400th of the sky[/size][/font]
[font=arial][size=4]- Looks at more than 155,000 stars[/size][/font]
[font=arial][size=4]- Has so far found 2,326 candidate planets[/size][/font]
[font=arial][size=4]- Among them are 207 Earth-sized planets, 10 of which are in the &quot;habitable zone&quot; where liquid water can exist[/size][/font]

[font=arial][size=4]Discuss:[/size][/font]

[size=4][font=arial]source: [/font][url=http://www.bbc.co.uk/news/science-environment-16040655]http://www.bbc.co.uk/news/science-environment-16040655[/url][/size]
[size=4](made a forum version for those that are to lazy to open a link)[/size]</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 12 Dec 2011 23:43:25 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>General Discussion</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/kepler-22-b/424221.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Kepler 22-b</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@The_Outsider The Outsider]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/the_outsider">@The_Outsider</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Plausible.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/kepler-22-b/424221/124">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/kepler-22-b/424221/124</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Dec 2011 23:43:25 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-424221-124</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/kepler-22-b/424221.rss">Kepler 22-b</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Kepler 22-b</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@MistaBigBoss MistaBigBoss]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/mistabigboss">@MistaBigBoss</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“MistaBigBoss, post:110, topic:424221”]Time traveling simply is not possible because there is no such thing as time. We have invented time, we addressed time to movement. The earth spins around the sun, we call it a year. A year consists of months, weeks, days, hours, minutes,…</p>
<p>But practically, it’s just, the earth moving around the sun because of gravitational pull.</p>
<p>Same goes with us, our DNA makes it so that cells die after they give off a certain amount of energy. Thus, we get older. We call it time, I call it, undeveloped DNA.</p>
<p>This thing we call “time” can be indeed bypassed. It, however, has limitations.</p>
<ol>
<li>It can only be manipulated to the future.</li>
<li>It is not a global manipulation.</li>
</ol>
<p>1 .Why only the future? Simple, if you understand why “time” traveling is possible, you will see why the past is the past, and there is nothing anyone can do to get it back.</p>
<p>[b][size=5]According to Einstein’s theory, when one reaches the speed of light, which is not possible because one cannot reach the speed of light (nature will make you go slower and slower as you reach the speed of light, thus you never actually reach it), things start to change.</p>
<p>When you “reach” the speed of light, your cells and everything you consist off will start working REALLY slow. Slow enough that when you move your hand up, your brain and body interpret that as 2 seconds. Everyone else, that is not going at the speed of light will interpret that as ex. 25 years. Thus, when slowing back down at a normal speed, everyone is 25 years older. Your cells/body has not aged, your brain has only experienced 2 seconds.[/size][/b]</p>
<p>But you’re freaking out because you time traveled into the future. You call it time traveling, I call it slowing down the particles you consist of.</p>
<p>That is why there is no way to go BACK in time. It’s the same as:</p>
<p>When you go to sleep at night, and you wake up in the morning. Oh it’s magic, we just time traveled. No we did not. We just didn’t experience time as someone would if they were awake.</p>
<p>Another way to “time” travel is by standing close to objects that have MASSIVE amounts of mass. Huge amounts of mass tend to slow you down, just as going at a really high speed would, causing what I described above.</p>
<ol start="2">
<li>I think you know by now what “it is not global manipulation” means. It means that when I go at the speed of light, and I magically get in the future, you won’t.</li>
</ol>
<h2>That’s my theory, that is what I believe, that is what my brain finds logical.</h2>
<p>There might be spelling errors in this post (I’m not going to re-read it), but I’m heading of to sleep, it’s 7AM here and I know I use the word “Thus” a lot, I don’t know if you English people find that normal or not, but I like “Thus”.[/quote]Rµne, read the bold text.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/kepler-22-b/424221/123">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/kepler-22-b/424221/123</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Dec 2011 16:42:32 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-424221-123</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/kepler-22-b/424221.rss">Kepler 22-b</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Kepler 22-b</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Hash1_Single Hash1 Single]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/hash1_single">@Hash1_Single</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote quote-modified" data-post="117" data-topic="424221">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/reyx7/40/5_e05bb34c421432ee4d40de30c10af3e5.png" class="avatar"> reyx7:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>I believe I once heard this theory that could cause what seems to be time travel. You basically fly around the earth in a reverse turning pattern at a certain speed for X amount of years. Because you are flying opposite to the earth’s rotation, aging would occur slower for you. So maybe 20 years of your aging around the earth at speed X could actually be 80 years for everyone else. Anyone hear that before?</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>How would aging slow down? Aging is completely natural, and the rotation of earth has nothing to do with it…</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/kepler-22-b/424221/122">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/kepler-22-b/424221/122</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Dec 2011 16:20:40 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-424221-122</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/kepler-22-b/424221.rss">Kepler 22-b</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Kepler 22-b</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@MistaBigBoss MistaBigBoss]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/mistabigboss">@MistaBigBoss</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“reyx7, post:117, topic:424221”]I believe I once heard this theory that could cause what seems to be time travel. You basically fly around the earth in a reverse turning pattern at a certain speed for X amount of years. Because you are flying opposite to the earth’s rotation, aging would occur slower for you. So maybe 20 years of your aging around the earth at speed X could actually be 80 years for everyone else. Anyone hear that before?[/quote]That’s actually the same thing I explained in a post above. That certain speed would equal to a speed as close to the speed of light as possible.<br>
And the speed is all that matters, not the rotation.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/kepler-22-b/424221/121">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/kepler-22-b/424221/121</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Dec 2011 14:08:15 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-424221-121</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/kepler-22-b/424221.rss">Kepler 22-b</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Kepler 22-b</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@R_ne Rμne]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/r_ne">@R_ne</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>So did the robot things on transformers.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/kepler-22-b/424221/120">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/kepler-22-b/424221/120</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Dec 2011 13:39:36 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-424221-120</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/kepler-22-b/424221.rss">Kepler 22-b</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Kepler 22-b</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@m1lkman m1lkman]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/m1lkman">@m1lkman</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote quote-modified" data-post="117" data-topic="424221">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/reyx7/40/5_e05bb34c421432ee4d40de30c10af3e5.png" class="avatar"> reyx7:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>I believe I once heard this theory that could cause what seems to be time travel. You basically fly around the earth in a reverse turning pattern at a certain speed for X amount of years. Because you are flying opposite to the earth’s rotation, aging would occur slower for you. So maybe 20 years of your aging around the earth at speed X could actually be 80 years for everyone else. Anyone hear that before?</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Superman done did that.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/kepler-22-b/424221/119">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/kepler-22-b/424221/119</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Dec 2011 13:24:57 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-424221-119</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/kepler-22-b/424221.rss">Kepler 22-b</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Kepler 22-b</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@whattehp406 whattehp406]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/whattehp406">@whattehp406</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Well i am pretty convinced that time travel (if possible) is only possible to the future.<br>
Why you say? Well else we would already know about it.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/kepler-22-b/424221/118">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/kepler-22-b/424221/118</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Dec 2011 12:00:46 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-424221-118</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/kepler-22-b/424221.rss">Kepler 22-b</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Kepler 22-b</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@reyx7 reyx7]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/reyx7">@reyx7</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I believe I once heard this theory that could cause what seems to be time travel. You basically fly around the earth in a reverse turning pattern at a certain speed for X amount of years. Because you are flying opposite to the earth’s rotation, aging would occur slower for you. So maybe 20 years of your aging around the earth at speed X could actually be 80 years for everyone else. Anyone hear that before?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/kepler-22-b/424221/117">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/kepler-22-b/424221/117</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Dec 2011 03:05:39 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-424221-117</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/kepler-22-b/424221.rss">Kepler 22-b</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Kepler 22-b</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@mod_taharok Taharok]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/mod_taharok">@mod_taharok</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote" data-post="115" data-topic="424221">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 The Outsider:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>^^ I can see from the thumbnail of that video that it talks about folding the fabric of space in half, so to speak?</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>If I recall correctly, that’s the core concept of a wormhole. Since the Universe is theorized to be two dimensional (such as a fabric), it could essentially be “folded in half” in order to jump from one area of the Universe to another far away in an extremely short amount of time. The application of time is a bit more complex, and I don’t remember it well enough to try and explain it.</p>
<p>[quote=“asshole_rule, post:113, topic:424221”][quote author=Taharok link=topic=526878.msg3845529#msg3845529 date=1323578984]</p>
<aside class="quote">
<blockquote>
<p>I saw someone say something about time travel being possible, but, the only ways we know of right know that will allow us to time travel involve Supernovas and Black Holes(either creating one, or at the end of one), which we won’t ever be able to overcome.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I would consider this statement heavily inconclusive. <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=5" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"> Black holes exist, yes, but traveling through time with them is entirely theoretical. In all practicality, all that happens when you go through a black hole is getting smashed into a billionth your size, along with everything else that goes in (including light!)</p>
<p>I think to relate black holes to time travel is just another allusion to humanities’ continual effort to changing the past or guessing the future.<br>
[/quote]</p>
<p>I’m not talking about traveling through time with black holes. I was watching a youtube video a few weeks ago and this Scientist found a way to travel through time, but in the same 1 millionth of a second a black hole is created directly on him (which he can’t survive :P). And the reason I talked about Supernovas is because I think it creates some worm hole that you’d have to go through, which creates a loop in space time allowing you to travel backwards in time, but also creating the black hole (that’s what supernovas make).</p>
<p>I’ll try and find the video, it’s quite interesting.</p>
<div class="lazyYT" data-youtube-id="EOi0xA9GvX8" data-youtube-title="Black Holes | National Geographic" data-width="480" data-height="270" data-parameters="feature=oembed&amp;wmode=opaque"></div>
<p>turns out I remembered barely anything from that video, lol.[/quote]</p>
<p>Taking one youtube video as absolute truth is bad scientific practice. It’s not even accurate to say that “some scientist found a way to travel through time.” This, in itself, is inconclusive. Even saying “travel through time” has its own invalidities. Unless experimentally proved, anything a scientist says is conclusive is a mere theory with whatever generic data he or she can apply to it.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/kepler-22-b/424221/116">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/kepler-22-b/424221/116</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 11 Dec 2011 18:15:58 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-424221-116</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/kepler-22-b/424221.rss">Kepler 22-b</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Kepler 22-b</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@The_Outsider The Outsider]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/the_outsider">@The_Outsider</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>^^ I can see from the thumbnail of that video that it talks about folding the fabric of space in half, so to speak?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/kepler-22-b/424221/115">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/kepler-22-b/424221/115</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 11 Dec 2011 18:03:20 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-424221-115</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/kepler-22-b/424221.rss">Kepler 22-b</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Kepler 22-b</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@whattehp406 whattehp406]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/whattehp406">@whattehp406</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“MistaBigBoss, post:87, topic:424221”][quote author=whattehp406 link=topic=526878.msg3843517#msg3843517 date=1323451408]</p>
<p>[quote author=The Outsider link=topic=526878.msg3843468#msg3843468 date=1323447872]</p>
<aside class="quote">
<blockquote>
<p>Wow this is a great find, i hope that one day we will be able to travel through wormholes (teleportation) and go to it.<br>
Maybe the civilisation on there has already found us and maybe even sent something.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Yeah, probably AIDs. So we kill ourselves off, lol.<br>
[/quote]Yeah lawl.</p>
<p>And MistaBigBoss,<br>
There are some Armenians on my school who are completely retarded so i’m happy that not every one is like that <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=5" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"><br>
[/quote]Every nationality has it’s retards I guess, so tell me, whats is causing their retardness?[/quote]They wanna be cool so they climb in trees and make weird noises…</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/kepler-22-b/424221/114">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/kepler-22-b/424221/114</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 11 Dec 2011 17:54:12 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-424221-114</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/kepler-22-b/424221.rss">Kepler 22-b</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Kepler 22-b</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@asshole_rule asshole_rule]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/asshole_rule">@asshole_rule</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“Taharok, post:106, topic:424221”][quote author=asshole_rule link=topic=526878.msg3845466#msg3845466 date=1323574155]<br>
I saw someone say something about time travel being possible, but, the only ways we know of right know that will allow us to time travel involve Supernovas and Black Holes(either creating one, or at the end of one), which we won’t ever be able to overcome.<br>
[/quote]</p>
<p>I would consider this statement heavily inconclusive. <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=5" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"> Black holes exist, yes, but traveling through time with them is entirely theoretical. In all practicality, all that happens when you go through a black hole is getting smashed into a billionth your size, along with everything else that goes in (including light!)</p>
<p>I think to relate black holes to time travel is just another allusion to humanities’ continual effort to changing the past or guessing the future.[/quote]</p>
<p>I’m not talking about traveling through time with black holes. I was watching a youtube video a few weeks ago and this Scientist found a way to travel through time, but in the same 1 millionth of a second a black hole is created directly on him (which he can’t survive :P). And the reason I talked about Supernovas is because I think it creates some worm hole that you’d have to go through, which creates a loop in space time allowing you to travel backwards in time, but also creating the black hole (that’s what supernovas make).</p>
<p>I’ll try and find the video, it’s quite interesting.</p>
<div class="lazyYT" data-youtube-id="EOi0xA9GvX8" data-youtube-title="Black Holes | National Geographic" data-width="480" data-height="270" data-parameters="feature=oembed&amp;wmode=opaque"></div>
<p>turns out I remembered barely anything from that video, lol.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/kepler-22-b/424221/113">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/kepler-22-b/424221/113</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 11 Dec 2011 13:58:31 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-424221-113</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/kepler-22-b/424221.rss">Kepler 22-b</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Kepler 22-b</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@The_Outsider The Outsider]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/the_outsider">@The_Outsider</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Time travel is possible I think. Imagine the black void of space as the fabric of space… take the Earth for example, as it is rolling around in the fabric of space it is putting a “dent” in the fabric.</p>
<p>Basically if we can bend the fabric of space enough, i.e. fold it in half, the travel from one end of the universe to the other could take seconds.</p>
<p>I think it’s very possible.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/kepler-22-b/424221/112">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/kepler-22-b/424221/112</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 11 Dec 2011 13:24:51 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-424221-112</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/kepler-22-b/424221.rss">Kepler 22-b</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Kepler 22-b</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@the_wanderer The Wanderer]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/the_wanderer">@the_wanderer</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>^Twin Paradox. <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=5" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/kepler-22-b/424221/111">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/kepler-22-b/424221/111</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 11 Dec 2011 07:11:31 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-424221-111</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/kepler-22-b/424221.rss">Kepler 22-b</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Kepler 22-b</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@MistaBigBoss MistaBigBoss]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/mistabigboss">@MistaBigBoss</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Time traveling simply is not possible because there is no such thing as time. We have invented time, we addressed time to movement. The earth spins around the sun, we call it a year. A year consists of months, weeks, days, hours, minutes,…</p>
<p>But practically, it’s just, the earth moving around the sun because of gravitational pull.</p>
<p>Same goes with us, our DNA makes it so that cells die after they give off a certain amount of energy. Thus, we get older. We call it time, I call it, undeveloped DNA.</p>
<p>This thing we call “time” can be indeed bypassed. It, however, has limitations.</p>
<ol>
<li>It can only be manipulated to the future.</li>
<li>It is not a global manipulation.</li>
</ol>
<p>1 .Why only the future? Simple, if you understand why “time” traveling is possible, you will see why the past is the past, and there is nothing anyone can do to get it back.</p>
<p>According to Einstein’s theory, when one reaches the speed of light, which is not possible because one cannot reach the speed of light (nature will make you go slower and slower as you reach the speed of light, thus you never actually reach it), things start to change.</p>
<p>When you “reach” the speed of light, your cells and everything you consist off will start working REALLY slow. Slow enough that when you move your hand up, your brain and body interpret that as 2 seconds. Everyone else, that is not going at the speed of light will interpret that as ex. 25 years. Thus, when slowing back down at a normal speed, everyone is 25 years older. Your cells/body has not aged, your brain has only experienced 2 seconds.</p>
<p>But you’re freaking out because you time traveled into the future. You call it time traveling, I call it slowing down the particles you consist of.</p>
<p>That is why there is no way to go BACK in time. It’s the same as:</p>
<p>When you go to sleep at night, and you wake up in the morning. Oh it’s magic, we just time traveled. No we did not. We just didn’t experience time as someone would if they were awake.</p>
<p>Another way to “time” travel is by standing close to objects that have MASSIVE amounts of mass. Huge amounts of mass tend to slow you down, just as going at a really high speed would, causing what I described above.</p>
<ol start="2">
<li>I think you know by now what “it is not global manipulation” means. It means that when I go at the speed of light, and I magically get in the future, you won’t.</li>
</ol>
<h2>That’s my theory, that is what I believe, that is what my brain finds logical.</h2>
<p>There might be spelling errors in this post (I’m not going to re-read it), but I’m heading of to sleep, it’s 7AM here and I know I use the word “Thus” a lot, I don’t know if you English people find that normal or not, but I like “Thus”.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/kepler-22-b/424221/110">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/kepler-22-b/424221/110</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 11 Dec 2011 06:22:05 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-424221-110</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/kepler-22-b/424221.rss">Kepler 22-b</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Kepler 22-b</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@eballer48 eballer48]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/eballer48">@eballer48</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>No… they dont know jack shit about Kepler 22-b yet. It <span class="bbcode-i">looks</span> earth like however scientist have never even seen Kepler’s surface yet (Google it)</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/kepler-22-b/424221/109">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/kepler-22-b/424221/109</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 11 Dec 2011 05:48:15 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-424221-109</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/kepler-22-b/424221.rss">Kepler 22-b</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Kepler 22-b</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@RiiPiiNFtW RiiPiiNFtW]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/riipiinftw">@RiiPiiNFtW</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Time travel is partly theorized by Einstein’s Thoery of Relativity</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/kepler-22-b/424221/108">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/kepler-22-b/424221/108</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 11 Dec 2011 05:44:22 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-424221-108</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/kepler-22-b/424221.rss">Kepler 22-b</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Kepler 22-b</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@marcbob marcbob]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/marcbob">@marcbob</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>The concept of time travel is way too complicated for anyone to try and grasp. It will take a very long time before even a firm theory can be accepted.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/kepler-22-b/424221/107">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/kepler-22-b/424221/107</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 11 Dec 2011 05:38:11 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-424221-107</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/kepler-22-b/424221.rss">Kepler 22-b</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Kepler 22-b</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@mod_taharok Taharok]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/mod_taharok">@mod_taharok</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote quote-modified" data-post="105" data-topic="424221">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/asshole_rule/40/5_e05bb34c421432ee4d40de30c10af3e5.png" class="avatar"> asshole_rule:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>I saw someone say something about time travel being possible, but, the only ways we know of right know that will allow us to time travel involve Supernovas and Black Holes(either creating one, or at the end of one), which we won’t ever be able to overcome.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I would consider this statement heavily inconclusive. <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=5" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"> Black holes exist, yes, but traveling through time with them is entirely theoretical. In all practicality, all that happens when you go through a black hole is getting smashed into a billionth your size, along with everything else that goes in (including light!)</p>
<p>I think to relate black holes to time travel is just another allusion to humanities’ continual effort to changing the past or guessing the future.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/kepler-22-b/424221/106">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/kepler-22-b/424221/106</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 11 Dec 2011 04:49:44 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-424221-106</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/kepler-22-b/424221.rss">Kepler 22-b</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Kepler 22-b</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@asshole_rule asshole_rule]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/asshole_rule">@asshole_rule</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I saw someone say something about time travel being possible, but, the only ways we know of right know that will allow us to time travel involve Supernovas and Black Holes(either creating one, or at the end of one), which we won’t ever be able to overcome.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/kepler-22-b/424221/105">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/kepler-22-b/424221/105</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 11 Dec 2011 03:29:15 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-424221-105</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/kepler-22-b/424221.rss">Kepler 22-b</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Kepler 22-b</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@MistaBigBoss MistaBigBoss]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/mistabigboss">@MistaBigBoss</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“The Wanderer, post:103, topic:424221”]That didn’t answer my question and I know for sure it isn’t 94, as I know for certain uranium is the element with the highest number of protons that occurs naturally. And that would leave a max for 92 elements. Wikipedia is just wrong. :P[/quote]Oh well, I bought this giant encyclopedia with pictures and everything. I’ll read it next year.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/kepler-22-b/424221/104">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/kepler-22-b/424221/104</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 11 Dec 2011 03:12:22 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-424221-104</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/kepler-22-b/424221.rss">Kepler 22-b</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Kepler 22-b</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@the_wanderer The Wanderer]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/the_wanderer">@the_wanderer</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>That didn’t answer my question and I know for sure it isn’t 94, as I know for certain uranium is the element with the highest number of protons that occurs naturally. And that would leave a max for 92 elements. Wikipedia is just wrong. <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=5" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/kepler-22-b/424221/103">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/kepler-22-b/424221/103</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 11 Dec 2011 03:04:26 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-424221-103</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/kepler-22-b/424221.rss">Kepler 22-b</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Kepler 22-b</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@MistaBigBoss MistaBigBoss]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/mistabigboss">@MistaBigBoss</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“The Wanderer, post:101, topic:424221”][quote author=The Outsider link=topic=526878.msg3843443#msg3843443 date=1323446312]<br>
Brian Cox defines it as 92 natural occurring chemical elements and insists they are all that be. I don’t know about artificial ones but I assume that’s where people get different numbers from.<br>
[/quote]<br>
I read that too. I was like huh. How can there be 90 non-synthetic materials, yet there’s 92 that are in nature. Contradiction much? I was reading in my human anatomy book and it said there are 92 natural occurring elements, and the rest of the elements are synthetic. Yet at the same time, the periodic table in the back of the book had only 90 as non-synthetic. Going to ask my chemistry teacher that. <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=5" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"> Unless anyone else can explain.[/quote]As of November 2011, 118 elements have been identified, the latest being ununoctium in 2002.[2] Of the 118 known elements, <span class="bbcode-b">only the first 94 are known to occur naturally on Earth</span> (88 in non-trace amounts). Of these, 80 are stable or essentially so, while the others are radioactive, decaying into lighter elements over various timescales from fractions of a second to billions of years. Additional elements, of higher atomic numbers than those naturally occurring, have been produced artificially as the synthetic products of man-made nuclear reactions.</p>
<p>Source: wikipedia</p>
<p>I suppose to really know the elements we need to study biology instead of searching how many elements there are in the universe.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/kepler-22-b/424221/102">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/kepler-22-b/424221/102</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 11 Dec 2011 02:59:39 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-424221-102</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/kepler-22-b/424221.rss">Kepler 22-b</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Kepler 22-b</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@the_wanderer The Wanderer]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/the_wanderer">@the_wanderer</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote quote-modified" data-post="82" data-topic="424221">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 The Outsider:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Brian Cox defines it as 92 natural occurring chemical elements and insists they are all that be. I don’t know about artificial ones but I assume that’s where people get different numbers from.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I read that too. I was like huh. How can there be 90 non-synthetic materials, yet there’s 92 that are in nature. Contradiction much? I was reading in my human anatomy book and it said there are 92 natural occurring elements, and the rest of the elements are synthetic. Yet at the same time, the periodic table in the back of the book had only 90 as non-synthetic. Going to ask my chemistry teacher that. <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=5" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"> Unless anyone else can explain.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/kepler-22-b/424221/101">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/kepler-22-b/424221/101</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 11 Dec 2011 02:53:02 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-424221-101</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/kepler-22-b/424221.rss">Kepler 22-b</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Kepler 22-b</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Frell Frell]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/frell">@Frell</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>meh language is language. I prefer the ones where you roll your tongue excessively or speak in small movements, however if you use phlegm alot nty.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/kepler-22-b/424221/100">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/kepler-22-b/424221/100</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 11 Dec 2011 01:17:58 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-424221-100</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/kepler-22-b/424221.rss">Kepler 22-b</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
