<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>First Github Project - Twitch Plays Bot - Open Source</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/first-github-project-twitch-plays-bot-open-source/542169</link>
    <description>For my first project, I will be working on my TwitchPlays bot. This will be open source, so when functioning, anyone will be able to use it. This will simulate the Twitch Plays style of gaming that has risen in popularity recently. Instructions will be given when the project is complete, and feel free to contribute if you would like! This is coded in Java and will work with any Emulator (and actually works for other applications if you configure it properly). Rather than being a boring command prompt dialogue like my previous Twitch Plays program written in Python, this one will have beautiful GUI&#39;s, saving of settings, different game modes (Anarchy and Democracy), ease of access, brining the best experience for Twitch streamers. This project has started today, and please contact me if you are interested in participating in my first Github project!

https://github.com/mablack01/TwitchPlays</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 14 Apr 2014 22:34:53 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>General Programming</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/first-github-project-twitch-plays-bot-open-source/542169.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>First Github Project - Twitch Plays Bot - Open Source</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@hottys2good4 hottys2good4]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/hottys2good4">@hottys2good4</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>For my first project, I will be working on my TwitchPlays bot. This will be open source, so when functioning, anyone will be able to use it. This will simulate the Twitch Plays style of gaming that has risen in popularity recently. Instructions will be given when the project is complete, and feel free to contribute if you would like! This is coded in Java and will work with any Emulator (and actually works for other applications if you configure it properly). Rather than being a boring command prompt dialogue like my previous Twitch Plays program written in Python, this one will have beautiful GUI’s, saving of settings, different game modes (Anarchy and Democracy), ease of access, brining the best experience for Twitch streamers. This project has started today, and please contact me if you are interested in participating in my first Github project!</p>
<p><a href="https://github.com/mablack01/TwitchPlays" class="onebox" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">https://github.com/mablack01/TwitchPlays</a></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/first-github-project-twitch-plays-bot-open-source/542169/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/first-github-project-twitch-plays-bot-open-source/542169/1</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 14 Apr 2014 22:34:53 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-542169-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/first-github-project-twitch-plays-bot-open-source/542169.rss">First Github Project - Twitch Plays Bot - Open Source</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
