<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>[server help] Can&#39;t Get server Online(more inside)</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/server-help-cant-get-server-online-more-inside/406468</link>
    <description>Hello everyone I made this 317 simple client for me and some friends to mess around on and for me mainly to get use to the coding and what not, The only trouble now is getting the server online. I&#39;ve seen numerous tutorials and I have set up no-ip, I&#39;ve even allowexd it through the fire wall, andportforwarded and have the server running and the No-ip DUC running and working. The only problem is I&#39;m not sure if I have to go into the source folder and put in my server address that I made with no-ip. Because when my friends try to join it says error connecting to server but I&#39;m playing.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 26 Jul 2011 05:11:31 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/server-help-cant-get-server-online-more-inside/406468.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>[server help] Can&#39;t Get server Online(more inside)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Billy_Mays Billy Mays]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/billy_mays">@Billy_Mays</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Hello everyone I made this 317 simple client for me and some friends to mess around on and for me mainly to get use to the coding and what not, The only trouble now is getting the server online. I’ve seen numerous tutorials and I have set up no-ip, I’ve even allowexd it through the fire wall, andportforwarded and have the server running and the No-ip DUC running and working. The only problem is I’m not sure if I have to go into the source folder and put in my server address that I made with no-ip. Because when my friends try to join it says error connecting to server but I’m playing.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/server-help-cant-get-server-online-more-inside/406468/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/server-help-cant-get-server-online-more-inside/406468/1</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 26 Jul 2011 05:11:31 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-406468-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/server-help-cant-get-server-online-more-inside/406468.rss">[server help] Can&#39;t Get server Online(more inside)</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
