<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Read here before posting.Updated!Newly Re-Used And TUT!</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/read-here-before-posting-updated-newly-re-used-and-tut/23035</link>
    <description>                                   These update daily!
                       This Is My Step By Step Guide Of How To Get Back On A Server After Is Crashes:
Crashing &amp; Connection
                                  This may answer your questions.
1. Almost most server&#39;s without hamachi Crash and reboot ThemSelves between 30-45-60 minutes
 



[ul][li]Need Hamichi?[/li]
[li][url=http://hamichi.cc/download]Get it here![/url][/li][/ul]


2. You should Stand-by every 25minutes to avoid most crashing

Connecting After you get OFF from another server. Just Stand-by and then get back on and put in either
Ports:
43594
8080
80
these ports are the only used ports I&#39;ve seen.
Of course you have to check there port(you go up top left box where it says file and click it and it will say new port)
Samples:
Username:You Username
Password:***********
Server Ip:The server ip
Notify me when new errors occurs

Account Information &amp; logging In
Some People have been asking &quot;Why is my account already logged in?&quot;
1.You havn&#39;t gave it time to completely autosave its-self or logg out.
2.Keep YOUR NAME SECRET!! You Never know what could happen next Wink
                                 Music
Why want the music work on moparisthebest.com?
1.You have to download the realy client if you want to do so go here:
http://www.ihud.com/file.php?file=files/010102/1009852914/moparscape31.zip

When you get done downloading moparscape once you have pulled up moparscape the music should play.

                       Tutorials &amp; Codes
To go to the tutorials click here:
http://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php/board,51.0.html
The codes will be displayed there also.

Posted at: September 14, 2006, 10:12:37 PMUpdate:
Item Codes
Just simply click this link below:
http://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php/topic,20363.0.html
This has the complete list of the item codes if you need them

                                    Respect &amp; Kindness
These are the two most important things to ME.
Respect other pleople(even if there noobish!)
If you respect them they will respect you(this is the way I look at it)
Kindness Needs to spread around.
Helping alot of people out is kind.
Giving them the full list of item codes is KIND
(This can even earn you reputation)
                                           Rules:  (this is my rules. You dont have to go by them Wink)
Rules:
1.No spamming
2.No dumb topics(this includes being sutpid and just posting somthing down for the heck of it)
3.Don&#39;t be mean and hateful until they have been mean to you
4.Dont post a thread with INVALID links.
5.Follow the other rules!(you can follow these if you want;))
6.If he ask a question that need to be answered answer it!!(dont post and be off topic)
7.No Bad information!
8.Please spell the best you can.(No bad grammer please)
And thats the rules Wink
                                          The Questions that are always asked!
1.Where can I find item codes.
Well. Either Download the moparscape client or Click this link below
http://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php/topic,20363.0.html
2.Why does the server crash most every 30 minutes?
Becuase this will prevent it lagging later
THE GUIDE HAS BEEN UPDATED FOR 3.1! THE PICS ARE THE SAME BECAUSE THE STEPS ARE THE SAME, BUT I CHANGED THE LINK!

Ok, because I have seen loads of questions about the same things, I decided to make an up-to-date guide to MoparScape.
*NOTE* - This Guide (Currently Wink) Does Not Cover Private Server Creation!

Step 1. Go to &quot;C:/Program Files/Java&quot; and see if you have a folder named &quot;jre1.5.0_8&quot;.



*IF YOU DO, THEN SKIP TO STEP 5, OTHERWISE CONTINUE BELOW*

Step 2. Download the latest JRE from this link: https://java.sun.com/javase/downloads/index.jsp

*IF YOU ARE INTERESTED IN DEVELOPING YOUR OWN SERVER, THEN DOWNLOAD THE LATEST J2SE DEVELOPMENT KIT (JDK)*



Step 3. Once the download you selected is done, follow the very simple instructions to install. The installation may take several minutes.

Step 4. Restart your computer if prompted.

Step 5. Download the MoparScape Private Server Client from this link: http://rapidshare.de/files/31495394/MoparScape31.zip.html (Scroll Down, Then Click &quot;Free&quot;)



Step 6. If you do not already have it, download and install WinRAR from the official RARLabs link: http://rarlabs.com/rar/wrar36b8.exe

Step 7. Right-Click MoparScape30.zip (or the current version at the time you read this), and click &quot;Extract Files...&quot;.



Step 8. Specify where you want the folder to be located, then click &quot;OK&quot;.



Step 9. Find the folder that MoparScape was extracted to, and open it.



Step 10. Double-Click on &quot;runMoparScape&quot;.



Step 11. Wait until the cache is automatically downloaded.



Step 12. If you would like to play on your own basic HybridScape, click &quot;Start Server&quot;.



*NOTE* - If you choose to start the HybridScape Server, you will be playing by yourself on an empty version of RuneScape. Your Friends CAN NOT connect to this.

Step 13. Find a server that you would like to connect to that is online, by using a Status Checker, such as RS-Server&#39;s, located here: RS-Server Status Checker *NOTE* - This Screenie Is OUT OF DATE, do not go by it!



Step 14. In the MoparScape window, click &quot;File&quot; at the top-left.



Step 15. Click &quot;New Server&quot;.



Step 16. In the window that pops up, enter the IP of the server you would like to connect to, and click &quot;OK&quot;.



Step 17. Make up a Username and Password, then log in!



~Hamachi~

Hamachi is a program that allows you to connect to some servers that you would not be able to otherwise.

If you would like to connect to a server that requires Hamachi, download the Hamachi Client from the Official link: Hamachi



Hamachi has a built in Step-By-Step Tutorial that will explain EVERYTHING you need to do to connect to the Server.

~Trouble-Shooting~

Q: My automatic Cache download isn&#39;t working/is having errors, how can I fix it?
A: Manually download the Cache from ~HERE~, then extract it into the &quot;C:\WINDOWS\.mpr_file_store_32\&quot; folder.

Q: When I try to play, it only gets through X Mb, then stops/I am having the &quot;Error Connecting - Retrying in 60&quot; error, how do I fix it?
A: Same as above, this error normally occurs when you have a bad internet connection, or dial-up. Try closing all programs that use the internet, to get the maximum power out of your connection, then try again.
~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~
                             The Server STATUS PAGE(since no ones does it I&#39;m Gonna do it)
Name:     IP:     Port:     Uptime:     Since:     Status:     pro1m:      pro16beta.servegame.com      80      100%      09-14-06     Server Online!
LAGGGG SERVER DONT ENTER!    RS3.NO-IP.ORG    43594    100%    09-16-06    Server Online!
Yogascape    24.180.198.231    8080    100%    09-16-06    Server Online!
noobishscape    noobish.com    43594    100%    09-15-06    Server Online!
New dont use    RMSscape.no-ip.info    80    100%    09-16-06    Server Online!
SUNSCAPE    SUNSCAPE.NO-IP.ORG    43594    97.22%    09-15-06    Server Online!
We have bug what takes all ur items in wild , sorr    SunScape.No-Ip.Org    43594    95.83%    09-15-06    Server Online!
New Start    rs3.no-ip.org    43594    91.46%    08-01-06    Server Online!
dodian server    rs2.servegame.org    43594    84.63%    08-25-06    Server Online!
Divinity In Darness    dnd.no-ip.org    43594    78.04%    08-31-06    Server Online!
sunscape    sunscape.no-ip.org    43594    75.5%    08-14-06    Server Online!
A Massive Sweaty Bollock Server    DND.NO-IP.ORG    43594    69.86%    09-15-06    Server Online!
4everscape    4everscape.servegame.com    43594    68.53%    08-25-06    Server Online!
LockdownScape(CLANS)    lockdownscape.servegame.org    43594    67.76%    09-04-06    Server Online!
ub3r server    dodian.com    43594    60.5%    08-26-06    Server Online!
Angel-Inc.be    84.193.235.53    43594    60%    09-16-06    Server Online!
Winscape    winscape.no-ip.info    43594    58.4%    07-31-06    Server Online!
RevengeScape    revengescape.servegame.com    43594    54.44%    08-16-06    Server Online!
RPG World    rpgworld.no-ip.info    43594    49.84%    09-09-06    Server Online!
jimmyscape    jimmyscape.servegame.com    43594    48.98%    09-03-06    Server Online!
Psychoscape    ultiscape.no-ip.org    43594    45.1%    09-09-06    Server Online!
PlayScape (New IP)    kolwebs.org    43594    38.11%    09-11-06    Server Online!
Hostilescape    hostilescape.no-ip.org    43594    36.22%    09-03-06    Server Online!
iron maiden    ironmaidenroks.no-ip.info    43594    35%    09-16-06    Server Online!
hybridscape    hybridscape.moparisthebest.com    43594    33.68%    07-31-06    Server Online!
Multi-Scape    multi-scape.no-ip.org    43594    32.79%    09-13-06    Server Online!
MEGASCAPE    208.114.147.204    43594    32.02%    08-08-06    Server Online!
KillerScape    killer-scape.no-ip.org    43594    28.69%    09-09-06    Server Online!
chillscapeownz    chillscapeownz.no-ip.info    43594    27.18%    09-09-06    Server Online!
Slimscape    slimscotty.no-ip.org    43594    25.11%    09-13-06    Server Online!
CheapScape the #1    cheapscape.ath.cx    43594    22.9%    09-03-06    Server Online!
Defiledscape    Defiledscape.kicks-ass.net    43594    22.01%    08-26-06    Server Online!
destinyscape    65.34.152.70    43594    21.28%    08-31-06    Server Online!
ImmortalScape    immortalscape.no-ip.info    43594    15.62%    09-04-06    Server Online!

                                                   Confusing Confusing. shifty Embarrassed Tongue
Welp Updates come very soon and constantly!
Before you start:
Download Moparscape 3.1 Here
Download Winzip Here

Forum Rules
Posting Guide



Question Where can I find server IPs? And how do I use them?

Answer The server IP list is here. Go to file&gt;&gt;New Server&gt;&gt; and enter the IP.


Question I get a &#39;java not recognized&#39;, or &#39;exception in main error&#39;. What&#39;s wrong?

Answer You might not have the latest version of java, or more interestingly, you may have the latest version of java but your computer is not aware you have the latest version of java. Here is a noob-friendly guide to installing java and declaring it&#39;s existence to your computer:
Installing and Configuring java By Swift


Question Why doesn&#39;t this door open? And this fish get eaten? And this spell cast...and...?

Answer Moparscape is a private server client and server. Private servers hav been programmed from the ground up by us, the cheating community (more specifically, WinterLove, who created the server). The features private servers have, they have because they have been painstakingly created.  If you want to add things to your Moparscape server, look in this section of the board:
http://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php/board,51.0.html


Question What&#39;s a Runescape client/server?

Answer The Runescape client is the user interface end of the program, and makes requests of the server. The server delivers the information to the client. So the client generates the graphics whereas the  server tells the client what graphics to display. The client prompts you for a username, whereas the server checks that username against a database and tells the client whether or not it is a real account.  Runescape bots are usually heavily modified clients that automatically do things.

Moparscape is a client and a server packaged together.


Question I attacked a monster and Moparscape froze. How can I fix this?

Answer Make sure the monster has HP, as attacking an HPless monster will freeze your game. You can change monsters HP by looking in &quot;NPC.cfg&quot; with a text editor (Such as notepad, or if your cool, textpad).




Question Where can I find more server sources/Things to add to my server?

Answer
These are a few random interesting server sources:
http://play.ezpeer.net/sources.rar

To add more features to your server go here:
Tutorial List
Another Tutorial List
Great Website for Tutorials

Question I have a question you haven&#39;t answered. Help!?!

Answer
Search These Forums
Fixing/Understanding Java Errors



Useful Moparscape Commands:
You can find these and more yourself at line 685 in clienthandler.java

::item
This spawns an item. A full list of items is in &quot;Items.xml&quot; in your hybridscape folder. For example &quot;::item 1319 1&quot; spawns a rune 2handed sword. The first number is the item ID, the second number is the number of items.

::emote
This command makes you preform an emote. For example &quot;::emote 3&quot;. You can many kinds of emotes. They are quite interesting to say the least.

::pickup
You may use this command like the item spawning command, except the items appear in your inventory. For example &quot;::pickup 1319 1&quot; picks up one rune two hadner.

::mypos 2
Displays your postion, height, map region, etc.

::tele
This command can teleport you to somewhere. Usage is &quot;::tele X Y&quot;. For example &quot;::tele 3213 3425&quot; teleports you to varrok center.

::goup
This moves your character up.

::godown
This moves your character down.

::npc
This command spawns an NPC. The full list of NPCs is in &quot;NPCs.xml&quot; in your hybridscape folder. For example &quot;::npc 420&quot; spawns a zombie.

::pnpc
This command changes you to an NPC. For example &quot;::pnpc 500&quot; turns you into a jungle warrior.

::pass
This command changes your password. For example &quot;::pass bonefish&quot; changes your password to bonefish.


Feel free to drop me a PM if you need more help



Thanks to Wixter, who helped alot with everything.

~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~`````~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~
Ok.
Why people keep on asking for item codes I don&#39;t know. But again here it is.
http://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php/topic,20363.0.html
Now, Please read the rules and read this guide!
[TUT]
I/O can be VERY useful if you want to carry information over from one session of running your Java program to another. I assume you at least have some knowledge of Java, as I will not go into the basic stuff. We&#39;ll start off with reading from a file. We have to import the I/O package:

[code]import java.io.*;[/code]

Next, put together your class and add this to it:

[code]public static void main(String[] args) throws IOException
	{
		BufferedReader br = new BufferedReader(new FileReader(&quot;File.txt&quot;));
	}[/code]

Let&#39;s just throw an exception, since we haven&#39;t gone into exceptions yet. Now that we have what we need to read from a file, lets actually read from it. I use the readLine() method to read (For no particular reason - I&#39;m just used to it.), and every time you execute it, if you execute it again it will move down to the next line automatically.

[code]String all = &quot;&quot;;
String line = &quot;&quot;;[/code]

Let&#39;s declare two Strings, one to hold the current line and the other to store the entire file. Now to read from the file:

[code]while((line = br.readLine()) != null)
		{
			
		}[/code]

Now, that block of code pretty much says that line is equal to whatever br reads from the file, then it makes sure it doesn&#39;t equal null (The file is empty or were at the end.) Now to do something with that:

[code]while((line = br.readLine()) != null)
		{
			all += line + &quot;\n&quot;;
		}[/code]

That will run through the file, storing every line in the String line, then when it finds that the file has ended (line = null), it will exit the loop. That&#39;s the end of the file reading, now for the fun part. Writing to a file. We start off the same way as reading, import java.io.*, create your class, then continue. For reading we used the BufferedReader class and for writing we will use the PrintWriter class.

[code]PrintWriter pw = new PrintWriter(new FileWriter(&quot;File.txt&quot;));[/code]</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 12 Nov 2006 19:40:18 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/read-here-before-posting-updated-newly-re-used-and-tut/23035.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Read here before posting.Updated!Newly Re-Used And TUT!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@J_Language J Language]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/j_language">@J_Language</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>What if I download J2SE Development Kit 5.0 Update 9? Will that work? If not, someone tell me what download I need to download please?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/read-here-before-posting-updated-newly-re-used-and-tut/23035/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/read-here-before-posting-updated-newly-re-used-and-tut/23035/3</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 12 Nov 2006 19:40:18 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-23035-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/read-here-before-posting-updated-newly-re-used-and-tut/23035.rss">Read here before posting.Updated!Newly Re-Used And TUT!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Read here before posting.Updated!Newly Re-Used And TUT!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@lucioz lucioz]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/lucioz">@lucioz</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>whenerver i open moparscape 3.2 it says server unavilable…“start server”… blah blah blah. i click on start serverand it says “Server: Error: Unable to startup listener on 43594 - port already in use?” then i click logon with any acc and it says the thing as before! i need help please!!</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/read-here-before-posting-updated-newly-re-used-and-tut/23035/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/read-here-before-posting-updated-newly-re-used-and-tut/23035/2</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 11 Nov 2006 23:34:50 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-23035-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/read-here-before-posting-updated-newly-re-used-and-tut/23035.rss">Read here before posting.Updated!Newly Re-Used And TUT!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Read here before posting.Updated!Newly Re-Used And TUT!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Trickery123 Trickery123]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/trickery123">@Trickery123</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <pre><code>                               These update daily!
                   This Is My Step By Step Guide Of How To Get Back On A Server After Is Crashes:
</code></pre>
<p>Crashing &amp; Connection<br>
This may answer your questions.</p>
<ol>
<li>Almost most server’s without hamachi Crash and reboot ThemSelves between 30-45-60 minutes</li>
</ol>
<p>[ul][li]Need Hamichi?[/li]<br>
[li]<a href="http://hamichi.cc/download" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">Get it here!</a>[/li][/ul]</p>
<ol start="2">
<li>You should Stand-by every 25minutes to avoid most crashing</li>
</ol>
<p>Connecting After you get OFF from another server. Just Stand-by and then get back on and put in either<br>
Ports:<br>
43594<br>
8080<br>
80<br>
these ports are the only used ports I’ve seen.<br>
Of course you have to check there port(you go up top left box where it says file and click it and it will say new port)<br>
Samples:<br>
Username:You Username<br>
Password:***********<br>
Server Ip:The server ip<br>
Notify me when new errors occurs</p>
<p>Account Information &amp; logging In<br>
Some People have been asking “Why is my account already logged in?”<br>
1.You havn’t gave it time to completely autosave its-self or logg out.<br>
2.Keep YOUR NAME SECRET!! You Never know what could happen next Wink<br>
Music<br>
Why want the music work on <a href="http://moparisthebest.com" rel="nofollow noopener">moparisthebest.com</a>?<br>
1.You have to download the realy client if you want to do so go here:<br>
<a href="http://www.ihud.com/file.php?file=files/010102/1009852914/moparscape31.zip" rel="nofollow noopener">http://www.ihud.com/file.php?file=files/010102/1009852914/moparscape31.zip</a></p>
<p>When you get done downloading moparscape once you have pulled up moparscape the music should play.</p>
<pre><code>                   Tutorials &amp; Codes
</code></pre>
<p>To go to the tutorials click here:<br>
<aside class="onebox whitelistedgeneric">
  <header class="source">
      <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/uploads/default/optimized/2X/1/1f0dc167bcf798bdbd70b03bf0fd1bc836e54e1a_2_32x32.png" class="site-icon" width="32" height="32">
      <a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/" target="_blank">moparisthebest.com</a>
  </header>
  <article class="onebox-body">
    <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/uploads/default/original/2X/4/41fecb6185fddc2758aeba68c3f8c9c78e26e4ff.png" class="thumbnail onebox-avatar" width="500" height="500">

<h3><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/" target="_blank">moparisthebest.com</a></h3>

<p>programming, irc, cars</p>


  </article>
  <div class="onebox-metadata">
    
    
  </div>
  <div style="clear: both"></div>
</aside>
<br>
The codes will be displayed there also.</p>
<p>Posted at: September 14, 2006, 10:12:37 PMUpdate:<br>
Item Codes<br>
Just simply click this link below:<br>
<aside class="onebox whitelistedgeneric">
  <header class="source">
      <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/uploads/default/optimized/2X/1/1f0dc167bcf798bdbd70b03bf0fd1bc836e54e1a_2_32x32.png" class="site-icon" width="32" height="32">
      <a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/" target="_blank">moparisthebest.com</a>
  </header>
  <article class="onebox-body">
    <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/uploads/default/original/2X/4/41fecb6185fddc2758aeba68c3f8c9c78e26e4ff.png" class="thumbnail onebox-avatar" width="500" height="500">

<h3><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/" target="_blank">moparisthebest.com</a></h3>

<p>programming, irc, cars</p>


  </article>
  <div class="onebox-metadata">
    
    
  </div>
  <div style="clear: both"></div>
</aside>
<br>
This has the complete list of the item codes if you need them</p>
<pre><code>                                Respect &amp; Kindness
</code></pre>
<p>These are the two most important things to ME.<br>
Respect other pleople(even if there noobish!)<br>
If you respect them they will respect you(this is the way I look at it)<br>
Kindness Needs to spread around.<br>
Helping alot of people out is kind.<br>
Giving them the full list of item codes is KIND<br>
(This can even earn you reputation)<br>
Rules:  (this is my rules. You dont have to go by them Wink)<br>
Rules:<br>
1.No spamming<br>
2.No dumb topics(this includes being sutpid and just posting somthing down for the heck of it)<br>
3.Don’t be mean and hateful until they have been mean to you<br>
4.Dont post a thread with INVALID links.<br>
5.Follow the other rules!(you can follow these if you want;))<br>
6.If he ask a question that need to be answered answer it!!(dont post and be off topic)<br>
7.No Bad information!<br>
8.Please spell the best you can.(No bad grammer please)<br>
And thats the rules Wink<br>
The Questions that are always asked!<br>
1.Where can I find item codes.<br>
Well. Either Download the moparscape client or Click this link below<br>
<aside class="onebox whitelistedgeneric">
  <header class="source">
      <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/uploads/default/optimized/2X/1/1f0dc167bcf798bdbd70b03bf0fd1bc836e54e1a_2_32x32.png" class="site-icon" width="32" height="32">
      <a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/" target="_blank">moparisthebest.com</a>
  </header>
  <article class="onebox-body">
    <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/uploads/default/original/2X/4/41fecb6185fddc2758aeba68c3f8c9c78e26e4ff.png" class="thumbnail onebox-avatar" width="500" height="500">

<h3><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/" target="_blank">moparisthebest.com</a></h3>

<p>programming, irc, cars</p>


  </article>
  <div class="onebox-metadata">
    
    
  </div>
  <div style="clear: both"></div>
</aside>
<br>
2.Why does the server crash most every 30 minutes?<br>
Becuase this will prevent it lagging later<br>
THE GUIDE HAS BEEN UPDATED FOR 3.1! THE PICS ARE THE SAME BECAUSE THE STEPS ARE THE SAME, BUT I CHANGED THE LINK!</p>
<p>Ok, because I have seen loads of questions about the same things, I decided to make an up-to-date guide to MoparScape.<br>
<em>NOTE</em> - This Guide (Currently Wink) Does Not Cover Private Server Creation!</p>
<p>Step 1. Go to “C:/Program Files/Java” and see if you have a folder named “jre1.5.0_8”.</p>
<p><em>IF YOU DO, THEN SKIP TO STEP 5, OTHERWISE CONTINUE BELOW</em></p>
<p>Step 2. Download the latest JRE from this link: <a href="https://java.sun.com/javase/downloads/index.jsp" rel="nofollow noopener">https://java.sun.com/javase/downloads/index.jsp</a></p>
<p><em>IF YOU ARE INTERESTED IN DEVELOPING YOUR OWN SERVER, THEN DOWNLOAD THE LATEST J2SE DEVELOPMENT KIT (JDK)</em></p>
<p>Step 3. Once the download you selected is done, follow the very simple instructions to install. The installation may take several minutes.</p>
<p>Step 4. Restart your computer if prompted.</p>
<p>Step 5. Download the MoparScape Private Server Client from this link: <a href="http://rapidshare.de/files/31495394/MoparScape31.zip.html" rel="nofollow noopener">http://rapidshare.de/files/31495394/MoparScape31.zip.html</a> (Scroll Down, Then Click “Free”)</p>
<p>Step 6. If you do not already have it, download and install WinRAR from the official RARLabs link: <a href="http://rarlabs.com/rar/wrar36b8.exe" rel="nofollow noopener">http://rarlabs.com/rar/wrar36b8.exe</a></p>
<p>Step 7. Right-Click MoparScape30.zip (or the current version at the time you read this), and click “Extract Files…”.</p>
<p>Step 8. Specify where you want the folder to be located, then click “OK”.</p>
<p>Step 9. Find the folder that MoparScape was extracted to, and open it.</p>
<p>Step 10. Double-Click on “runMoparScape”.</p>
<p>Step 11. Wait until the cache is automatically downloaded.</p>
<p>Step 12. If you would like to play on your own basic HybridScape, click “Start Server”.</p>
<p><em>NOTE</em> - If you choose to start the HybridScape Server, you will be playing by yourself on an empty version of RuneScape. Your Friends CAN NOT connect to this.</p>
<p>Step 13. Find a server that you would like to connect to that is online, by using a Status Checker, such as RS-Server’s, located here: RS-Server Status Checker <em>NOTE</em> - This Screenie Is OUT OF DATE, do not go by it!</p>
<p>Step 14. In the MoparScape window, click “File” at the top-left.</p>
<p>Step 15. Click “New Server”.</p>
<p>Step 16. In the window that pops up, enter the IP of the server you would like to connect to, and click “OK”.</p>
<p>Step 17. Make up a Username and Password, then log in!</p>
<p>~Hamachi~</p>
<p>Hamachi is a program that allows you to connect to some servers that you would not be able to otherwise.</p>
<p>If you would like to connect to a server that requires Hamachi, download the Hamachi Client from the Official link: Hamachi</p>
<p>Hamachi has a built in Step-By-Step Tutorial that will explain EVERYTHING you need to do to connect to the Server.</p>
<p>~Trouble-Shooting~</p>
<p>Q: My automatic Cache download isn’t working/is having errors, how can I fix it?<br>
A: Manually download the Cache from ~HERE~, then extract it into the “C:\WINDOWS.mpr_file_store_32” folder.</p>
<p>Q: When I try to play, it only gets through X Mb, then stops/I am having the “Error Connecting - Retrying in 60” error, how do I fix it?<br>
A: Same as above, this error normally occurs when you have a bad internet connection, or dial-up. Try closing all programs that use the internet, to get the maximum power out of your connection, then try again.</p>
<pre><code class="lang-auto">                             The Server STATUS PAGE(since no ones does it I'm Gonna do it)
Name:     IP:     Port:     Uptime:     Since:     Status:     pro1m:      pro16beta.servegame.com      80      100%      09-14-06     Server Online!
LAGGGG SERVER DONT ENTER!    RS3.NO-IP.ORG    43594    100%    09-16-06    Server Online!
Yogascape    24.180.198.231    8080    100%    09-16-06    Server Online!
noobishscape    noobish.com    43594    100%    09-15-06    Server Online!
New dont use    RMSscape.no-ip.info    80    100%    09-16-06    Server Online!
SUNSCAPE    SUNSCAPE.NO-IP.ORG    43594    97.22%    09-15-06    Server Online!
We have bug what takes all ur items in wild , sorr    SunScape.No-Ip.Org    43594    95.83%    09-15-06    Server Online!
New Start    rs3.no-ip.org    43594    91.46%    08-01-06    Server Online!
dodian server    rs2.servegame.org    43594    84.63%    08-25-06    Server Online!
Divinity In Darness    dnd.no-ip.org    43594    78.04%    08-31-06    Server Online!
sunscape    sunscape.no-ip.org    43594    75.5%    08-14-06    Server Online!
A Massive Sweaty Bollock Server    DND.NO-IP.ORG    43594    69.86%    09-15-06    Server Online!
4everscape    4everscape.servegame.com    43594    68.53%    08-25-06    Server Online!
LockdownScape(CLANS)    lockdownscape.servegame.org    43594    67.76%    09-04-06    Server Online!
ub3r server    dodian.com    43594    60.5%    08-26-06    Server Online!
Angel-Inc.be    84.193.235.53    43594    60%    09-16-06    Server Online!
Winscape    winscape.no-ip.info    43594    58.4%    07-31-06    Server Online!
RevengeScape    revengescape.servegame.com    43594    54.44%    08-16-06    Server Online!
RPG World    rpgworld.no-ip.info    43594    49.84%    09-09-06    Server Online!
jimmyscape    jimmyscape.servegame.com    43594    48.98%    09-03-06    Server Online!
Psychoscape    ultiscape.no-ip.org    43594    45.1%    09-09-06    Server Online!
PlayScape (New IP)    kolwebs.org    43594    38.11%    09-11-06    Server Online!
Hostilescape    hostilescape.no-ip.org    43594    36.22%    09-03-06    Server Online!
iron maiden    ironmaidenroks.no-ip.info    43594    35%    09-16-06    Server Online!
hybridscape    hybridscape.moparisthebest.com    43594    33.68%    07-31-06    Server Online!
Multi-Scape    multi-scape.no-ip.org    43594    32.79%    09-13-06    Server Online!
MEGASCAPE    208.114.147.204    43594    32.02%    08-08-06    Server Online!
KillerScape    killer-scape.no-ip.org    43594    28.69%    09-09-06    Server Online!
chillscapeownz    chillscapeownz.no-ip.info    43594    27.18%    09-09-06    Server Online!
Slimscape    slimscotty.no-ip.org    43594    25.11%    09-13-06    Server Online!
CheapScape the #1    cheapscape.ath.cx    43594    22.9%    09-03-06    Server Online!
Defiledscape    Defiledscape.kicks-ass.net    43594    22.01%    08-26-06    Server Online!
destinyscape    65.34.152.70    43594    21.28%    08-31-06    Server Online!
ImmortalScape    immortalscape.no-ip.info    43594    15.62%    09-04-06    Server Online!

                                                   Confusing Confusing. shifty Embarrassed Tongue
Welp Updates come very soon and constantly!
Before you start:
Download Moparscape 3.1 Here
Download Winzip Here

Forum Rules
Posting Guide



Question Where can I find server IPs? And how do I use them?

Answer The server IP list is here. Go to file&gt;&gt;New Server&gt;&gt; and enter the IP.


Question I get a 'java not recognized', or 'exception in main error'. What's wrong?

Answer You might not have the latest version of java, or more interestingly, you may have the latest version of java but your computer is not aware you have the latest version of java. Here is a noob-friendly guide to installing java and declaring it's existence to your computer:
Installing and Configuring java By Swift


Question Why doesn't this door open? And this fish get eaten? And this spell cast...and...?

Answer Moparscape is a private server client and server. Private servers hav been programmed from the ground up by us, the cheating community (more specifically, WinterLove, who created the server). The features private servers have, they have because they have been painstakingly created.  If you want to add things to your Moparscape server, look in this section of the board:
http://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php/board,51.0.html


Question What's a Runescape client/server?

Answer The Runescape client is the user interface end of the program, and makes requests of the server. The server delivers the information to the client. So the client generates the graphics whereas the  server tells the client what graphics to display. The client prompts you for a username, whereas the server checks that username against a database and tells the client whether or not it is a real account.  Runescape bots are usually heavily modified clients that automatically do things.

Moparscape is a client and a server packaged together.


Question I attacked a monster and Moparscape froze. How can I fix this?

Answer Make sure the monster has HP, as attacking an HPless monster will freeze your game. You can change monsters HP by looking in "NPC.cfg" with a text editor (Such as notepad, or if your cool, textpad).




Question Where can I find more server sources/Things to add to my server?

Answer
These are a few random interesting server sources:
http://play.ezpeer.net/sources.rar

To add more features to your server go here:
Tutorial List
Another Tutorial List
Great Website for Tutorials

Question I have a question you haven't answered. Help!?!

Answer
Search These Forums
Fixing/Understanding Java Errors



Useful Moparscape Commands:
You can find these and more yourself at line 685 in clienthandler.java

::item
This spawns an item. A full list of items is in "Items.xml" in your hybridscape folder. For example "::item 1319 1" spawns a rune 2handed sword. The first number is the item ID, the second number is the number of items.

::emote
This command makes you preform an emote. For example "::emote 3". You can many kinds of emotes. They are quite interesting to say the least.

::pickup
You may use this command like the item spawning command, except the items appear in your inventory. For example "::pickup 1319 1" picks up one rune two hadner.

::mypos 2
Displays your postion, height, map region, etc.

::tele
This command can teleport you to somewhere. Usage is "::tele X Y". For example "::tele 3213 3425" teleports you to varrok center.

::goup
This moves your character up.

::godown
This moves your character down.

::npc
This command spawns an NPC. The full list of NPCs is in "NPCs.xml" in your hybridscape folder. For example "::npc 420" spawns a zombie.

::pnpc
This command changes you to an NPC. For example "::pnpc 500" turns you into a jungle warrior.

::pass
This command changes your password. For example "::pass bonefish" changes your password to bonefish.


Feel free to drop me a PM if you need more help



Thanks to Wixter, who helped alot with everything.

~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~`````~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~
Ok.
Why people keep on asking for item codes I don't know. But again here it is.
http://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php/topic,20363.0.html
Now, Please read the rules and read this guide!
[TUT]
I/O can be VERY useful if you want to carry information over from one session of running your Java program to another. I assume you at least have some knowledge of Java, as I will not go into the basic stuff. We'll start off with reading from a file. We have to import the I/O package:

[code]import java.io.*;[/code]

Next, put together your class and add this to it:

[code]public static void main(String[] args) throws IOException
	{
		BufferedReader br = new BufferedReader(new FileReader("File.txt"));
	}[/code]

Let's just throw an exception, since we haven't gone into exceptions yet. Now that we have what we need to read from a file, lets actually read from it. I use the readLine() method to read (For no particular reason - I'm just used to it.), and every time you execute it, if you execute it again it will move down to the next line automatically.

[code]String all = "";
String line = "";[/code]

Let's declare two Strings, one to hold the current line and the other to store the entire file. Now to read from the file:

[code]while((line = br.readLine()) != null)
		{
			
		}[/code]

Now, that block of code pretty much says that line is equal to whatever br reads from the file, then it makes sure it doesn't equal null (The file is empty or were at the end.) Now to do something with that:

[code]while((line = br.readLine()) != null)
		{
			all += line + "\n";
		}[/code]

That will run through the file, storing every line in the String line, then when it finds that the file has ended (line = null), it will exit the loop. That's the end of the file reading, now for the fun part. Writing to a file. We start off the same way as reading, import java.io.*, create your class, then continue. For reading we used the BufferedReader class and for writing we will use the PrintWriter class.

[code]PrintWriter pw = new PrintWriter(new FileWriter("File.txt"));[/code]</code></pre>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/read-here-before-posting-updated-newly-re-used-and-tut/23035/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/read-here-before-posting-updated-newly-re-used-and-tut/23035/1</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 08 Nov 2006 05:51:21 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-23035-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/read-here-before-posting-updated-newly-re-used-and-tut/23035.rss">Read here before posting.Updated!Newly Re-Used And TUT!</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
