<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Moparscape Tutorial Board</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/moparscape-tutorial-board/362241</link>
    <description>Please make new threads in the [url=http://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php/board,51.0.html]Server Tutorials[/url] board hidden until a moderator approves them.  :cool:</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 01 Oct 2010 09:36:13 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Community Suggestions</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/moparscape-tutorial-board/362241.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Moparscape Tutorial Board</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@lothy Lothy]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/lothy">@lothy</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Obviously I wasn’t clear enough above.</p>
<p>No, it’s not going to be filtered again.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/moparscape-tutorial-board/362241/10">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/moparscape-tutorial-board/362241/10</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Oct 2010 09:36:13 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-362241-10</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/moparscape-tutorial-board/362241.rss">Moparscape Tutorial Board</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Moparscape Tutorial Board</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Rixxx Rix_]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/rixxx">@Rixxx</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <blockquote>Chances are, that won't work very well, either. Specifically on moderators, the amount of effort needed to review a tutorial is far from trivial. The person critiquing them needs to have a strong and recent background in servers (which I don't believe any of the staff can qualify for anymore), an accurate understanding of the Java language (or any other language the tutorial targets), and a very thorough understanding of the rules outlined which the tutorial must follow. They need to have common knowledge of the section, so they can be preventative of duplicate tutorials, unless one outdoes another. And, being the least used of all, such a moderator would need to be willing to offer constructive criticism on every single tutorial, whether it be denied or not. In the old system, we would send private messages to users whose tutorials got denied, explaining to them what they need to improve for it to be accepted later on.</blockquote>
There is a chance for it to work well too. Wouldn't a moderator have a very thorough understanding of the outlined tutorial rules considering he is part of the staff team? The way you mention about staff members supposed to understand Java makes it sound like a majority of Moparscapers are any better. Of course they're not thus their tutorials wouldn't be so advanced. There's also a list of existing tutorials in the board therefore the moderator can always refer to it if need be. Isn't the way of moderators locking topics in the tutorial board "for being snippets", "common sense" etc the same as PMing users the reason for their tutorials getting denied.
<blockquote>Some of these rules are impossible to enforce (such as determining if the work is genuinely anyones, determining if explanations are "detailed" enough, determining of titles are "clear" and "accurate" enough, etc). Others are far too restrictive (you must explain your code, you must follow an outline, titles need to be clear and concise). There's no breathing room in a system like that.</blockquote>
If a tutorial is leeched, that's where other users can play a part. The users here aren't just registered on Moparscape, they use Rune–Server as well and are able to report tutorials that are basically copied.
<p>A tutorial, as defined by <a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Tutorial" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">Wikipedia</a> (let’s not argue about how articles on Wikipedia can be edited easily), is: one method of transferring knowledge and may be used as a part of learning … seeks to teach by example and supply the information to complete a certain task. It is only common sense for a tutorial to be of knowledge thus if codes aren’t explained, they aren’t worthy of being accepted.</p>
<blockquote>The filter only drove more people away and added another number to the moderators' workloads.</blockquote>
It is only common sense for a tutorial to be of knowledge thus if codes in a tutorial aren't explained, the tutorial isn't worthy of being accepted.
<p>This is the best for the site. <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/smiley.png?v=5" title=":smiley:" class="emoji" alt=":smiley:"></p>
<aside class="quote no-group quote-modified" data-post="8" data-topic="362241">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 the bank:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Delete the site…</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Tell Moparisthebest that!</p>
<p>One long post. :rolleyes:</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/moparscape-tutorial-board/362241/9">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/moparscape-tutorial-board/362241/9</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Oct 2010 09:20:14 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-362241-9</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/moparscape-tutorial-board/362241.rss">Moparscape Tutorial Board</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Moparscape Tutorial Board</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@the_bank the bank]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/the_bank">@the_bank</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Delete the site…</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/moparscape-tutorial-board/362241/8">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/moparscape-tutorial-board/362241/8</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 30 Sep 2010 23:09:10 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-362241-8</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/moparscape-tutorial-board/362241.rss">Moparscape Tutorial Board</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Moparscape Tutorial Board</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@mod_taharok Taharok]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/mod_taharok">@mod_taharok</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“Rixxx, post:6, topic:362241”][quote author=Lothy link=topic=458526.msg3355861#msg3355861 date=1285853774]<br>
In a word, no.</p>
<p>We aren’t reverting back to filtering out topics. It was a thorn in the side of regular users, and a pain in the arse for the moderator team.<br>
[/quote]<br>
Let someone be a section moderator of that board then.[/quote]</p>
<p>Chances are, that won’t work very well, either. Specifically on moderators, the amount of effort needed to review a tutorial is far from trivial. The person critiquing them needs to have a strong and recent background in servers (which I don’t believe any of the staff can qualify for anymore), an accurate understanding of the Java language (or any other language the tutorial targets), and a very thorough understanding of the rules outlined which the tutorial must follow. They need to have common knowledge of the section, so they can be preventative of duplicate tutorials, unless one outdoes another. And, being the least used of all, such a moderator would need to be willing to offer constructive criticism on every single tutorial, whether it be denied or not. In the old system, we would send private messages to users whose tutorials got denied, explaining to them what they need to improve for it to be accepted later on.</p>
<p>Conversely on the members side, a restrictive system requires very detailed and sometimes verbose rules which the tutorial must follow. A few of the rules we’ve used in the past include:</p>
<p>[ul][li]post your work only[/li][li]provide detailed explanations to any and all code snippets provided (no “copy and paste” tutorials)[/li][li]tutorials must follow an outline…[/li][li]titles need to be clear and accurate[/li][/ul]</p>
<p>Some of these rules are impossible to enforce (such as determining if the work is genuinely anyones, determining if explanations are “detailed” enough, determining of titles are “clear” and “accurate” enough, etc). Others are far too restrictive (you <span class="bbcode-b">must</span> explain your code, you <span class="bbcode-b">must</span> follow an outline, titles <span class="bbcode-b">need</span> to be clear and concise). There’s no breathing room in a system like that.</p>
<p>The tutorials section started off as a place where any and all developments were posted, sometimes in an effort to actually help people, but probably more often in an effort to gain respect, popularity, and karma points. The section began to transform into what many would call a “shithole,” as it was full of people attacking each other, spamming nonstop, and hardly any worthwhile tutorials (worthwhile being anything a user could find informative and educational, relevant to RSPS). The staff eventually took control of the section, but immediately things got out of hand in the opposite extreme. Entire pages were locked, rules of control were created, and no user member input was considered. These harsh actions only continued to grow steadily worse over the year following.</p>
<p>Afterwards, the moderators seemed to grow more lenient in the section (meaning they still handed out the same harsh punishments and enforced the same rules, but at a far less rate). After more transformations of rules, harsh punishments, driving people out of the section, etc, the filter was added. I think the general thought behind the filter was to allow moderators to enforce the strict rules easier. The thought was good, but the setting was terrible. The filter only drove more people away and added another number to the moderators’ workloads.</p>
<p>I may have went a bit out of context in order to try and explain my own point of view here. We have made too many mistakes in the past regarding that section. To be completely honest, it should never have become this complex in the first place. Since it has, however, there are far too many mixed opinions on how it should be run. It seems the MoparScape community is almost bent between whether the filter should be there, many of them not even being here before the filter was put in place, or even back when all the strict rules were started.</p>
<p>The only scenario which has yet to be tested in that section, or even on the site as a whole, is one where we build up guidelines to counter only what is a nuisance, rather than trying to be preventative of scenarios which likely no longer exist, or never will. I have spent too much time theorizing what our actions could do on the site, and too little time actually trying the way where users get the most benefits possible, even if it means an extra workload for the moderators. I no longer want to do what I think is best for the site, but rather find out what is best.</p>
<p>Another long post. :rolleyes:</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/moparscape-tutorial-board/362241/7">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/moparscape-tutorial-board/362241/7</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 30 Sep 2010 21:32:26 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-362241-7</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/moparscape-tutorial-board/362241.rss">Moparscape Tutorial Board</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Moparscape Tutorial Board</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Rixxx Rix_]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/rixxx">@Rixxx</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“Lothy, post:5, topic:362241”]In a word, no.</p>
<p>We aren’t reverting back to filtering out topics. It was a thorn in the side of regular users, and a pain in the arse for the moderator team.[/quote]<br>
Let someone be a section moderator of that board then.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/moparscape-tutorial-board/362241/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/moparscape-tutorial-board/362241/6</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 30 Sep 2010 13:40:51 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-362241-6</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/moparscape-tutorial-board/362241.rss">Moparscape Tutorial Board</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Moparscape Tutorial Board</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@lothy Lothy]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/lothy">@lothy</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>In a word, no.</p>
<p>We aren’t reverting back to filtering out topics. It was a thorn in the side of regular users, and a pain in the arse for the moderator team.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/moparscape-tutorial-board/362241/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/moparscape-tutorial-board/362241/5</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 30 Sep 2010 13:36:14 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-362241-5</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/moparscape-tutorial-board/362241.rss">Moparscape Tutorial Board</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Moparscape Tutorial Board</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@mod_taharok Taharok]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/mod_taharok">@mod_taharok</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“Rixxx, post:3, topic:362241”][quote author=Taharok link=topic=458526.msg3355425#msg3355425 date=1285788996]<br>
It’s been generally agreed upon that we aren’t filtering tutorials anymore. We do see a lot of issues in the board and are finding less restrictive ways of fixing them. Filtering tutorials is just too censoring to ever work correctly. <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/expressionless.png?v=5" title=":expressionless:" class="emoji" alt=":expressionless:"><br>
[/quote]<br>
The board already has requirements of tutorials to be posted. If a user does not follow the requirements, the tutorial will be rejected. Therefore filtering is still the best idea, no?[/quote]</p>
<p>The board has requirements right now. That’s to say, it may not later on. We are assessing every single board on the site, and the tutorials board is one the main ones I focused on. Redoing the requirements and ensuring no filter is readded are the main steps being taken to reform the section. I would recommend waiting a few weeks to see what the changes bring, then critique them and offer more helpful suggestions. <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=5" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/moparscape-tutorial-board/362241/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/moparscape-tutorial-board/362241/4</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 30 Sep 2010 11:39:14 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-362241-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/moparscape-tutorial-board/362241.rss">Moparscape Tutorial Board</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Moparscape Tutorial Board</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Rixxx Rix_]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/rixxx">@Rixxx</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote no-group quote-modified" data-post="2" data-topic="362241">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 Taharok:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>It’s been generally agreed upon that we aren’t filtering tutorials anymore. We do see a lot of issues in the board and are finding less restrictive ways of fixing them. Filtering tutorials is just too censoring to ever work correctly. <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/expressionless.png?v=5" title=":expressionless:" class="emoji" alt=":expressionless:"></p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>The board already has requirements of tutorials to be posted. If a user does not follow the requirements, the tutorial will be rejected. Therefore filtering is still the best idea, no?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/moparscape-tutorial-board/362241/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/moparscape-tutorial-board/362241/3</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 30 Sep 2010 07:56:07 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-362241-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/moparscape-tutorial-board/362241.rss">Moparscape Tutorial Board</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Moparscape Tutorial Board</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@mod_taharok Taharok]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/mod_taharok">@mod_taharok</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>It’s been generally agreed upon that we aren’t filtering tutorials anymore. We do see a lot of issues in the board and are finding less restrictive ways of fixing them. Filtering tutorials is just too censoring to ever work correctly. <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/expressionless.png?v=5" title=":expressionless:" class="emoji" alt=":expressionless:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/moparscape-tutorial-board/362241/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/moparscape-tutorial-board/362241/2</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 29 Sep 2010 19:36:36 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-362241-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/moparscape-tutorial-board/362241.rss">Moparscape Tutorial Board</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Moparscape Tutorial Board</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Rixxx Rix_]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/rixxx">@Rixxx</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Please make new threads in the <a href="http://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php/board,51.0.html" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">Server Tutorials</a> board hidden until a moderator approves them.  <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/cool.png?v=5" title=":cool:" class="emoji" alt=":cool:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/moparscape-tutorial-board/362241/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/moparscape-tutorial-board/362241/1</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 29 Sep 2010 13:23:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-362241-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/moparscape-tutorial-board/362241.rss">Moparscape Tutorial Board</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
