<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Cache Grabbing?</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/cache-grabbing/332639</link>
    <description>I apologise if this is in the wrong section, I did try and weigh up which category it would fit in best. I&#39;m here to talk about something which affects me and many others and stops us from playing the official &#39;Runescape&#39; game, that is: mobile broadband. Please no &#39;g3t r33l br0adband n00b&#39;, keep the flame to a minimum. I&#39;m quite impressed with my mobile broadband service and happily game on Xbox Live with optimum ping.

Anyway the problem is, mobile broadband hates loading the cache. Whether it be maps or interfaces, it usually decides to just...die due to the way the modem handles packets, so I&#39;m led to believe. So is there anyway to grab the current cache (and always grab the &#39;current&#39; cache), all maps, interfaces etc. as a whole nice little package which can be dumped into the .jagex_cache_32 folder and therefore all users like me would never have to face this problem again, we&#39;d just have to download the cache everytime there&#39;s an update rather than get it automatically updated on client load.

Once again, I apologise if this is not the correct place. But more and more people are ditching their phone lines everyday, for the simplicity and ease of mobile broadband...which is improving every year. Maybe it&#39;s a UK thing? but meh. It&#39;d be nice if we could find a fix.

EDIT: God damn: &quot;Request topics do not belong here; if you&#39;re looking for help then please use the Client Help section.&quot; *sigh*</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 13 Mar 2010 21:24:09 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Game Development</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/cache-grabbing/332639.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Cache Grabbing?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Lin Lin]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/lin">@Lin</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I’m not sure what exactly you’re talking about, but I’ve found SEVERAL videos on YouTube of people playing RuneScape on their iPhones/iPods. If this IS what you’re talking about, there’s certain things you have to do in order to make it work. Here’s one of the videos I found that covers both: <a href="http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=H-HgTDZQ_i8" rel="nofollow noopener">http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=H-HgTDZQ_i8</a></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/cache-grabbing/332639/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/cache-grabbing/332639/3</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 13 Mar 2010 21:24:09 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-332639-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/cache-grabbing/332639.rss">Cache Grabbing?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Cache Grabbing?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@spy_man47 spy man47]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/spy_man47">@spy_man47</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Go put this in Client help!</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/cache-grabbing/332639/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/cache-grabbing/332639/2</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 13 Mar 2010 13:43:17 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-332639-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/cache-grabbing/332639.rss">Cache Grabbing?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Cache Grabbing?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@bburton31 bburton31]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/bburton31">@bburton31</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I apologise if this is in the wrong section, I did try and weigh up which category it would fit in best. I’m here to talk about something which affects me and many others and stops us from playing the official ‘Runescape’ game, that is: mobile broadband. Please no ‘g3t r33l br0adband n00b’, keep the flame to a minimum. I’m quite impressed with my mobile broadband service and happily game on Xbox Live with optimum ping.</p>
<p>Anyway the problem is, mobile broadband hates loading the cache. Whether it be maps or interfaces, it usually decides to just…die due to the way the modem handles packets, so I’m led to believe. So is there anyway to grab the current cache (and always grab the ‘current’ cache), all maps, interfaces etc. as a whole nice little package which can be dumped into the .jagex_cache_32 folder and therefore all users like me would never have to face this problem again, we’d just have to download the cache everytime there’s an update rather than get it automatically updated on client load.</p>
<p>Once again, I apologise if this is not the correct place. But more and more people are ditching their phone lines everyday, for the simplicity and ease of mobile broadband…which is improving every year. Maybe it’s a UK thing? but meh. It’d be nice if we could find a fix.</p>
<p>EDIT: God damn: “Request topics do not belong here; if you’re looking for help then please use the Client Help section.” <em>sigh</em></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/cache-grabbing/332639/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/cache-grabbing/332639/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 13 Mar 2010 10:57:16 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-332639-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/cache-grabbing/332639.rss">Cache Grabbing?</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
