<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Unable to find the model..?</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/unable-to-find-the-model/527565</link>
    <description>Okay so my client has the new whip model and i&#39;m trying to get the old whip model. In the beginning I just tried to delete the whip ints from class 8.java and I deleted 5409 and 5412 from the models, compiled, and ran.. but the new whip model was still there.. so i searched around and i heard it could be gzipped so I maybe had to put a new model or something.. So I downloaded the old whip model (2 dat files, 5409 and 5412) and i got the ints.. i copied/pasted the ints into class 8.java and i copied/pasted the 2 dat files into my Models folder in the client.. compiled, ran.. and when i log into my server and try to add the models &quot;Add model 5409&quot; or &quot;Add model 5412&quot;.. I get the message saying &quot;Unable to find the model. 5409&quot;.. I have no idea why it says its unable to find the model when its sitting right there in my models folder..?</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2013 08:04:53 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Game Development</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/unable-to-find-the-model/527565.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Unable to find the model..?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@tanner1234 tanner1234]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/tanner1234">@tanner1234</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Okay so my client has the new whip model and i’m trying to get the old whip model. In the beginning I just tried to delete the whip ints from class 8.java and I deleted 5409 and 5412 from the models, compiled, and ran… but the new whip model was still there… so i searched around and i heard it could be gzipped so I maybe had to put a new model or something… So I downloaded the old whip model (2 dat files, 5409 and 5412) and i got the ints… i copied/pasted the ints into class 8.java and i copied/pasted the 2 dat files into my Models folder in the client… compiled, ran… and when i log into my server and try to add the models “Add model 5409” or “Add model 5412”… I get the message saying “Unable to find the model. 5409”… I have no idea why it says its unable to find the model when its sitting right there in my models folder…?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/unable-to-find-the-model/527565/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/unable-to-find-the-model/527565/1</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2013 08:04:53 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-527565-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/unable-to-find-the-model/527565.rss">Unable to find the model..?</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
