<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Help to get the music and sound effects on MoparScape 3.4 .zip version</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/help-to-get-the-music-and-sound-effects-on-moparscape-3-4-zip-version/540589</link>
    <description>Hi! :)
I was playing Moparscape recently, and noticed the harp in the down right corner. I clicked it and saw that I needed to use the high-detail version of the game in order to hear the songs and the sound effects. At that time i thought that the developer ment that I had to change from &quot;low memorie&quot; to &quot;high memorie&quot; in the batch file. I tested it, but no. It didn&#39;t work. 

So now I wonder, can I only hear the sounds and music on the web version? Or is there a version that isn&#39;t released yet, or simply just a file I can&#39;t find? It would be great to be able to hear the sound effects and the music in-game! I know about the sound and music files that lies in the folder &quot;.mpr_file_store_32&quot;, so maybe they can be of use?


Thanks for answers! :D</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2014 22:29:49 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/help-to-get-the-music-and-sound-effects-on-moparscape-3-4-zip-version/540589.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Help to get the music and sound effects on MoparScape 3.4 .zip version</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Ebbe Ebbe]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/ebbe">@Ebbe</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Hi! <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=5" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"><br>
I was playing Moparscape recently, and noticed the harp in the down right corner. I clicked it and saw that I needed to use the high-detail version of the game in order to hear the songs and the sound effects. At that time i thought that the developer ment that I had to change from “low memorie” to “high memorie” in the batch file. I tested it, but no. It didn’t work.</p>
<p>So now I wonder, can I only hear the sounds and music on the web version? Or is there a version that isn’t released yet, or simply just a file I can’t find? It would be great to be able to hear the sound effects and the music in-game! I know about the sound and music files that lies in the folder “.mpr_file_store_32”, so maybe they can be of use?</p>
<p>Thanks for answers! <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/smiley.png?v=5" title=":smiley:" class="emoji" alt=":smiley:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/help-to-get-the-music-and-sound-effects-on-moparscape-3-4-zip-version/540589/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/help-to-get-the-music-and-sound-effects-on-moparscape-3-4-zip-version/540589/1</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2014 22:29:49 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-540589-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/help-to-get-the-music-and-sound-effects-on-moparscape-3-4-zip-version/540589.rss">Help to get the music and sound effects on MoparScape 3.4 .zip version</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
