<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>GoodOl&#39;Scape ~ Nothing Like The Good Ol&#39; Days!</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/goodolscape-nothing-like-the-good-ol-days/449988</link>
    <description>GoodOl&#39;Scape ~ Nothing Like The Good Ol&#39; Days!

http://goodoldays.ulmb.com/index.php 
                 or 
http://www.goodolscape.co.nr/ (This one doesn&#39;t work yet but it will be active within the next 24 hours)

I am currently making a new server, so far only have a website. I am making it like how RuneScape was before the Grand Exchange came in. We all love those days! xD I do have a working forums and stuff. You can apply to be a mod and what not for when the server goes live within the next month. I would like to have people tell me what they want in it and give me suggestions so I can add it to the server. I will be editing the website too so if you have suggestions for that, please also post in the suggestion forum. I&#39;d like to have people stick around and post on the forums until I get the server up and those same people can play and see what they have been waiting for and tell me about bugs and glitches. Hopefully I will be seeing some of you soon!
Thanks,
Johnny.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 17 Jul 2012 16:57:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/goodolscape-nothing-like-the-good-ol-days/449988.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>GoodOl&#39;Scape ~ Nothing Like The Good Ol&#39; Days!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@GoodOlScape GoodOlScape]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/goodolscape">@GoodOlScape</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>GoodOl’Scape ~ Nothing Like The Good Ol’ Days!</p>
<p><a href="http://goodoldays.ulmb.com/index.php" class="onebox" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">http://goodoldays.ulmb.com/index.php</a><br>
or<br>
<a href="http://www.goodolscape.co.nr/" rel="nofollow noopener">http://www.goodolscape.co.nr/</a> (This one doesn’t work yet but it will be active within the next 24 hours)</p>
<p>I am currently making a new server, so far only have a website. I am making it like how RuneScape was before the Grand Exchange came in. We all love those days! xD I do have a working forums and stuff. You can apply to be a mod and what not for when the server goes live within the next month. I would like to have people tell me what they want in it and give me suggestions so I can add it to the server. I will be editing the website too so if you have suggestions for that, please also post in the suggestion forum. I’d like to have people stick around and post on the forums until I get the server up and those same people can play and see what they have been waiting for and tell me about bugs and glitches. Hopefully I will be seeing some of you soon!<br>
Thanks,<br>
Johnny.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/goodolscape-nothing-like-the-good-ol-days/449988/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/goodolscape-nothing-like-the-good-ol-days/449988/1</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jul 2012 16:57:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-449988-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/goodolscape-nothing-like-the-good-ol-days/449988.rss">GoodOl&#39;Scape ~ Nothing Like The Good Ol&#39; Days!</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
