<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Help portforwarding</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/help-portforwarding/452844</link>
    <description>ok its virtually impossible for me to portforward my rsps... im hoping one of you is kind enough to give me 10 minutes of their time while they tv me and portforward my rsps... i have the pages up that will help you (no-ip) (default gateway page). now my server and client is untouched as i deleted it and then redownloaded it. so please dont say i didn&#39;t do anything as ive been trying all summer. SOMEONE PLEASE HELP ME. I DONT KNOW HOW ILL GET THE TEAMVIEW INFORMATION TO YOU BUT I WILL! HELP ME! I forgot to mention that if u portforward my rsps and it works in a webclient ill give you admin on server and, i dont know if i can reward u, but 5mrsgp</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 04 Aug 2012 18:30:50 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/help-portforwarding/452844.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Help portforwarding</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@yojayojay yojayojay]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/yojayojay">@yojayojay</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>ok its virtually impossible for me to portforward my rsps… im hoping one of you is kind enough to give me 10 minutes of their time while they tv me and portforward my rsps… i have the pages up that will help you (no-ip) (default gateway page). now my server and client is untouched as i deleted it and then redownloaded it. so please dont say i didn’t do anything as ive been trying all summer. SOMEONE PLEASE HELP ME. I DONT KNOW HOW ILL GET THE TEAMVIEW INFORMATION TO YOU BUT I WILL! HELP ME! I forgot to mention that if u portforward my rsps and it works in a webclient ill give you admin on server and, i dont know if i can reward u, but 5mrsgp</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/help-portforwarding/452844/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/help-portforwarding/452844/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 04 Aug 2012 18:30:50 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-452844-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/help-portforwarding/452844.rss">Help portforwarding</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
