<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>PI need help (challenging)</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/pi-need-help-challenging/447874</link>
    <description>Hey guys, i need help.. this isn&#39;t challenging but, it&#39;s confusing to explain... ok. This involves combat assistant.. ok, i want to change the time someone gets attacked.. so usually when you hit a player it hits them at the right time. for example when a whip swings right when it swings at the players body, it hits them. i have that currently, i want to change it to this video below. the player gets hit right when the player swings the whip (beginning of the swing) the hp comes up right when the swing coems up first thing. heres the video, 


http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=A6zo1nkus_w&amp;feature=context-vrec

Remember, look at when the player gets hit and when the whip swings.

ESPECIALLY when the dds specs right in the beginning... instead at the right time. Also, i think it is in attack like speed or something. please help

HITTING EARLIER THEN USUALL..</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 02 Jul 2012 21:45:47 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/pi-need-help-challenging/447874.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>PI need help (challenging)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@shank_beast shank beast]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/shank_beast">@shank_beast</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Hey guys, i need help… this isn’t challenging but, it’s confusing to explain… ok. This involves combat assistant… ok, i want to change the time someone gets attacked… so usually when you hit a player it hits them at the right time. for example when a whip swings right when it swings at the players body, it hits them. i have that currently, i want to change it to this video below. the player gets hit right when the player swings the whip (beginning of the swing) the hp comes up right when the swing coems up first thing. heres the video,</p>
<div class="lazyYT" data-youtube-id="A6zo1nkus_w" data-youtube-title="Runescape's Best Pker  (Original)" data-width="480" data-height="270" data-parameters="feature=oembed&amp;wmode=opaque"></div>
<p>Remember, look at when the player gets hit and when the whip swings.</p>
<p>ESPECIALLY when the dds specs right in the beginning… instead at the right time. Also, i think it is in attack like speed or something. please help</p>
<p>HITTING EARLIER THEN USUALL…</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/pi-need-help-challenging/447874/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/pi-need-help-challenging/447874/1</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 02 Jul 2012 21:45:47 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-447874-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/pi-need-help-challenging/447874.rss">PI need help (challenging)</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
