<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>RSR Has Re-Opened Applications. Read for info ;)</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rsr-has-re-opened-applications-read-for-info/6724</link>
    <description>Hiya, first off, yes I have got permission to advertise- I got it from Mopar some weeks ago but I&#39;m sure he doesn&#39;t mind me only just posting now.

RS-Resources.com is reopening applications for new members, the site run by the lovely Taios whom I am sure you all know:D. She previously closed the registrations in order for the new Java runtime bot not to be leaked, leeched etc. The new bot &#39;ARGA&#39; is a java bot which will be running in runtime, the Macrosoft team have been working hard the last few months and it certainly is something not to be missed as the bot itself never needs updating except when new features/bug fixes are added.

We are an anti-leech community and therefore do not accept just anyone, people with any type of programming experience stand a great chance of getting it and that can be anything from PHP to JAVA to VB (Anything, but not basic- that sucks ;) lol j/k) However active and helpful members are accepted aswell!

If you want to join we really are looking for active member, go to the site click on forums and you&#39;ll see applications. I advise you to read the stickies and put me as your refferer, I&#39;m a moderator so I will also be having a say in who gets in  :cool:

The site is also undergoing many things ATM, including new skins, and mods- we will be adding a shop mod and various others, also a Market place is possibly going to be opened for very trusted members only.


Good Luck on the applications, hope to see you all there,

Greeny</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 29 Jul 2006 08:15:56 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>General Discussion</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rsr-has-re-opened-applications-read-for-info/6724.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>RSR Has Re-Opened Applications. Read for info ;)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Greeny Greeny]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/greeny">@Greeny</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Hiya, first off, yes I have got permission to advertise- I got it from Mopar some weeks ago but I’m sure he doesn’t mind me only just posting now.</p>
<p><a href="http://RS-Resources.com" rel="nofollow noopener">RS-Resources.com</a> is reopening applications for new members, the site run by the lovely Taios whom I am sure you all know:D. She previously closed the registrations in order for the new Java runtime bot not to be leaked, leeched etc. The new bot ‘ARGA’ is a java bot which will be running in runtime, the Macrosoft team have been working hard the last few months and it certainly is something not to be missed as the bot itself never needs updating except when new features/bug fixes are added.</p>
<p>We are an anti-leech community and therefore do not accept just anyone, people with any type of programming experience stand a great chance of getting it and that can be anything from PHP to JAVA to VB (Anything, but not basic- that sucks <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/wink.png?v=9" title=":wink:" class="emoji" alt=":wink:"> lol j/k) However active and helpful members are accepted aswell!</p>
<p>If you want to join we really are looking for active member, go to the site click on forums and you’ll see applications. I advise you to read the stickies and put me as your refferer, I’m a moderator so I will also be having a say in who gets in  <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/cool.png?v=9" title=":cool:" class="emoji" alt=":cool:"></p>
<p>The site is also undergoing many things ATM, including new skins, and mods- we will be adding a shop mod and various others, also a Market place is possibly going to be opened for very trusted members only.</p>
<p>Good Luck on the applications, hope to see you all there,</p>
<p>Greeny</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rsr-has-re-opened-applications-read-for-info/6724/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rsr-has-re-opened-applications-read-for-info/6724/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 29 Jul 2006 08:15:56 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-6724-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rsr-has-re-opened-applications-read-for-info/6724.rss">RSR Has Re-Opened Applications. Read for info ;)</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
