<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Interfaces? PI</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/interfaces-pi/405186</link>
    <description>I saw this on a previous server I had which i deleted and didn&#39;t get to see the code.. could anyone tell me how i could make something like this:
When i click object 4388 interface 18681 is displayed then i get teleported to pos 3100,3481 and while i&#39;m there a smoky screen interface id 16152 is displayed WHILE i&#39;m there? so like when i walk around that smoky screen interface is always on screen while i&#39;m there.. i will be extremely extreeeemly thankful if anyone could tell me if this is possible and how to do it, i would be very pleased if anyone could give me this code. i know it goes in uh clickingobjects.java or something.

Thank you
~Atro</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 19 Jul 2011 23:39:05 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/interfaces-pi/405186.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Interfaces? PI</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@lifezjoke lifezjoke]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/lifezjoke">@lifezjoke</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I saw this on a previous server I had which i deleted and didn’t get to see the code… could anyone tell me how i could make something like this:<br>
When i click object 4388 interface 18681 is displayed then i get teleported to pos 3100,3481 and while i’m there a smoky screen interface id 16152 is displayed WHILE i’m there? so like when i walk around that smoky screen interface is always on screen while i’m there… i will be extremely extreeeemly thankful if anyone could tell me if this is possible and how to do it, i would be very pleased if anyone could give me this code. i know it goes in uh clickingobjects.java or something.</p>
<p>Thank you<br>
~Atro</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/interfaces-pi/405186/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/interfaces-pi/405186/1</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 19 Jul 2011 23:39:05 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-405186-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/interfaces-pi/405186.rss">Interfaces? PI</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
