<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Change of plan maybe</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/change-of-plan-maybe/552138</link>
    <description>Ok so not knowing what to do with the failed compile attempt, out of interest, I went back to the beginning, only trying the [u]EasyRsc[/u] source this time, using the machine with java 6v35 (last time I tried EasyRsc was with java 8, and nothing happened).

So the sever and client of EasyRsc loaded up fine, even though I hadn&#39;t made any edits to make the Java path in the bat files right, for some reason it just loaded up anyway.  I went ahead and edited the menu.java file to change the colours of the boxes, just as a test.  It worked (screenshot).  So now I&#39;m a little perplexed and confused as to what to do.  I&#39;m really tempted to just forget the Noobscape thing and modify the Easyscape back to a normal RSC experience, but some things first: (the list returns)

a) in Noobscape, if I tried to talk to say a guard, it would say he wasn&#39;t interested in talking.  In Easy, nothing happens!
b) in Noobscape, if I talk to a banker, he&#39;ll ask if I want to access my bank and I have options etc.  In Easy, sure he&#39;ll ask about the bank, [u]but[/u] I might not be facing him and/or standing one space away from him when that happens.  Maybe we&#39;re not facing each other and maybe the distance is not fixed at one space. This annoys me.  I kind of expect that when I interact with an npc the distance is fixed and the direction is the same.  So when this doesn&#39;t happen the game feels broken.
c) in Noobscape, when I talk to that wizard in the centre of a town who teleports you places (the guy I plan to delete), well, at least in Noobscape he responds when you click him.  In Easy, nothing happens at all which makes me wonder if there&#39;s other guys out there who just can&#39;t do anything when you click them.   

So my question is this: these three above queries I have with Easy, are they actually fixable?  If you guys think they are fixable then I will just start work on Easy and that&#39;ll be that.  If it&#39;s the case that they are fixable but it&#39;ll take time to manually key in words and numbers in java/xml files, then seriously that&#39;s not an issue for me.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 24 Jun 2015 17:32:08 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/change-of-plan-maybe/552138.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Change of plan maybe</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@mft004 mft004]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/mft004">@mft004</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Updated?</p>
<p>But when I compile Noobscape, nothing happens and the client won’t start again.</p>
<p>When I compile EasyRsc, something happens and the edited client will start.</p>
<p>But I admit I’m the least knowledgeable here.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/change-of-plan-maybe/552138/9">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/change-of-plan-maybe/552138/9</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jun 2015 17:32:08 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-552138-9</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/change-of-plan-maybe/552138.rss">Change of plan maybe</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Change of plan maybe</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@hyperkilljoy hyperkilljoy]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/hyperkilljoy">@hyperkilljoy</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>noobscape is an updated version of easyrsc</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/change-of-plan-maybe/552138/8">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/change-of-plan-maybe/552138/8</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jun 2015 05:49:20 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-552138-8</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/change-of-plan-maybe/552138.rss">Change of plan maybe</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Change of plan maybe</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@RSC_Jerry_2001 RSC Jerry 2001]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/rsc_jerry_2001">@RSC_Jerry_2001</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote" data-post="6" data-topic="552138">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 object:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>mft004: First of all, when it comes to programming, practically anything is possible. You just have to be creative. If you don’t know Java, let alone how to program, you need to learn that first, before you delve into projects as big as this one. Sure, you can still do things related to RSC private servers, but don’t expect too much.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>yep.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/change-of-plan-maybe/552138/7">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/change-of-plan-maybe/552138/7</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jun 2015 23:11:44 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-552138-7</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/change-of-plan-maybe/552138.rss">Change of plan maybe</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Change of plan maybe</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Protosstribe object]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/protosstribe">@Protosstribe</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>mft004: First of all, when it comes to programming, practically anything is possible. You just have to be creative. If you don’t know Java, let alone how to program, you need to learn that first, before you delve into projects as big as this one. Sure, you can still do things related to RSC private servers, but don’t expect too much.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/change-of-plan-maybe/552138/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/change-of-plan-maybe/552138/6</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jun 2015 21:45:04 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-552138-6</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/change-of-plan-maybe/552138.rss">Change of plan maybe</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Change of plan maybe</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@mft004 mft004]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/mft004">@mft004</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Right in that case, no more Noobscape, I’ll get busy with EasyRsc.  I was just encouraged when I made a change to a .java file, compiled and then saw the right result when I loaded client/server up.  If I can edit not just .xml and .rscd but also .java, it seems I’ve got a better chance at an overall good outcome.</p>
<p>When I get to that point you mentioned, I’ll pop back and past code.</p>
<p>Thanks again</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/change-of-plan-maybe/552138/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/change-of-plan-maybe/552138/5</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jun 2015 21:29:05 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-552138-5</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/change-of-plan-maybe/552138.rss">Change of plan maybe</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Change of plan maybe</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Rodgerwilco Rodgerwilco]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/rodgerwilco">@Rodgerwilco</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Well yea, you’re going to want to familiarize yourself with the source. The least you could do is get to the point where you find the code block that deals with your issue and post the code here so we can look at it. Rather than not knowing where it is at.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/change-of-plan-maybe/552138/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/change-of-plan-maybe/552138/4</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jun 2015 21:21:27 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-552138-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/change-of-plan-maybe/552138.rss">Change of plan maybe</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Change of plan maybe</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@mft004 mft004]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/mft004">@mft004</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Alright, so would you say then that the things you mentioned I should learn could fix the three queries I had with EasyRsc?  e.g. when you interact with an npc you’re at a fixed distance and face each other?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/change-of-plan-maybe/552138/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/change-of-plan-maybe/552138/3</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jun 2015 21:14:45 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-552138-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/change-of-plan-maybe/552138.rss">Change of plan maybe</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Change of plan maybe</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Rodgerwilco Rodgerwilco]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/rodgerwilco">@Rodgerwilco</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I would suggest just learning what is in your source directory and what each file contains.</p>
<p>Player.java will relate to Player specific variables<br>
MiscPacketBuilder relates to various packets sent from the server to client.</p>
<p>You will eventually find the NPCHandler(s), each NPC is given its own file and the logic of that npc is in that class. So you will need to learn what your npcs do and how they do it.</p>
<p>You should also read up on basic java fundamentals. There are various websites and books you can read up on (if you have access to a local library or buy one on amazon?)</p>
<p><a href="https://docs.oracle.com/javase/tutorial/java/nutsandbolts/" class="onebox" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">https://docs.oracle.com/javase/tutorial/java/nutsandbolts/</a><br>
<aside class="onebox whitelistedgeneric">
  <header class="source">
      <a href="http://javabeginnerstutorial.com/core-java/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Java Beginners Tutorial</a>
  </header>
  <article class="onebox-body">
    <img src="http://ad.linksynergy.com/fs-bin/show?id=hOzXY7hET9c&amp;bids=323058.533682&amp;type=2&amp;subid=0" class="thumbnail onebox-avatar" width="1" height="1">

<h3><a href="http://javabeginnerstutorial.com/core-java/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Core Java Tutorial | Learn By Example Core Java | Cheat Sheet for Core Java</a></h3>

<p>This Java tutorial is basically for Beginners who wants to learn java from basics. Here you learn everything from installing JDK to Variable to operator to Access modifier.</p>


  </article>
  <div class="onebox-metadata">
    
    
  </div>
  <div style="clear: both"></div>
</aside>
</p>
<p>Using an IDE like eclipse is going to cut down your development time so defiantly download the latest version of eclipse and import your project.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/change-of-plan-maybe/552138/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/change-of-plan-maybe/552138/2</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jun 2015 21:09:35 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-552138-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/change-of-plan-maybe/552138.rss">Change of plan maybe</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Change of plan maybe</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@mft004 mft004]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/mft004">@mft004</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Ok so not knowing what to do with the failed compile attempt, out of interest, I went back to the beginning, only trying the <span class="bbcode-u">EasyRsc</span> source this time, using the machine with java 6v35 (last time I tried EasyRsc was with java 8, and nothing happened).</p>
<p>So the sever and client of EasyRsc loaded up fine, even though I hadn’t made any edits to make the Java path in the bat files right, for some reason it just loaded up anyway.  I went ahead and edited the menu.java file to change the colours of the boxes, just as a test.  It worked (screenshot).  So now I’m a little perplexed and confused as to what to do.  I’m really tempted to just forget the Noobscape thing and modify the Easyscape back to a normal RSC experience, but some things first: (the list returns)</p>
<p>a) in Noobscape, if I tried to talk to say a guard, it would say he wasn’t interested in talking.  In Easy, nothing happens!<br>
b) in Noobscape, if I talk to a banker, he’ll ask if I want to access my bank and I have options etc.  In Easy, sure he’ll ask about the bank, <span class="bbcode-u">but</span> I might not be facing him and/or standing one space away from him when that happens.  Maybe we’re not facing each other and maybe the distance is not fixed at one space. This annoys me.  I kind of expect that when I interact with an npc the distance is fixed and the direction is the same.  So when this doesn’t happen the game feels broken.<br>
c) in Noobscape, when I talk to that wizard in the centre of a town who teleports you places (the guy I plan to delete), well, at least in Noobscape he responds when you click him.  In Easy, nothing happens at all which makes me wonder if there’s other guys out there who just can’t do anything when you click them.</p>
<p>So my question is this: these three above queries I have with Easy, are they actually fixable?  If you guys think they are fixable then I will just start work on Easy and that’ll be that.  If it’s the case that they are fixable but it’ll take time to manually key in words and numbers in java/xml files, then seriously that’s not an issue for me.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/change-of-plan-maybe/552138/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/change-of-plan-maybe/552138/1</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jun 2015 21:01:53 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-552138-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/change-of-plan-maybe/552138.rss">Change of plan maybe</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
