<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Vulkan - New Graphics API by Khronos Group</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/vulkan-new-graphics-api-by-khronos-group/554774</link>
    <description>A few days ago Khronos Group launched the initial release of Vulkan, a new graphics API. It may not entirely replace OpenGL, but it&#39;s a combination of OpenGL and OpenCL, streamlined for many platforms, including PCs, consoles and phones.

So if anyone here is interested in learning about OpenGL, I suggest you learn Vulkan instead. As well as their binary intermediate language SPIR-V.

Have anyone else here heard anything about this? Or maybe even tested it?</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 19 Feb 2016 01:38:33 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>General Programming</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/vulkan-new-graphics-api-by-khronos-group/554774.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Vulkan - New Graphics API by Khronos Group</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Tree Tree]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/tree">@Tree</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <blockquote>So if anyone here is interested in learning about OpenGL, I suggest you learn Vulkan instead.</blockquote>
<p>I agree with everything but this. I think OpenGL is still fine for someone entering graphics programming. That way they start to understand what limitations Vulkan eases. The verbosity of Vulkan would overwhelm a beginner programmer (eg. 700ish lines to show a triangle (<a href="https://github.com/SaschaWillems/Vulkan/blob/master/triangle/triangle.cpp" rel="nofollow noopener">https://github.com/SaschaWillems/Vulkan/blob/master/triangle/triangle.cpp</a>). Support for OpenGL isn’t going anywhere soon and I don’t think anyone should worry that they’re learning outdated skills. However if you’re familiar with graphics, then I do agree that they should start picking it up.</p>
<p>It will be interesting to see how long the support lasts as we start to add more and more abstraction to the mix. That’s when I can see the usefulness of OpenGL decreasing. Let’s not forget that there’s always going to be code already written that uses OpenGL, so it will not be an overnight transition.</p>
<p>For anyone reading (not directed at Object), think of Vulkan as something like Apple’s Metal. You’re dealing with a lower level, allowing more room to breathe. Due to it being closer to the hardware level, you’re able to squeeze a lot more performance. It also comes with a cost of learning, due to the abstractions something higher level provides not being there.</p>
<p>Here’s a fairly loose example. Imagine a self-driving car and you can put a destination in and the car will drive there. Sure, it will all work out of the box but it may not take the fastest route (it may go the long way or circle a round-a-bout three times). That’s OpenGL, where you have limited control over the finer things. So for the longest of times, graphics programmers tried to make the best of it. Due to the limitations, you may add blockages to these routes that cause the long drives. It’s hackish but it works sometimes. This is also what graphics programmers did, using workarounds or complex solutions. The car manufacturer sees a problem and adds extra buttons to the car, none of which give complete control but allow for further workarounds. Eventually the car has too many buttons and becomes way too messy. Then one day they say, “screw it, let’s build something with that finer level of control.”. Problem is, you now have to specify every little part. How the car drives, the speed and the destination. I mean, it’s great for those car enthusiasts  but it’s initially complex for a teenager with their first car.</p>
<p>Edit: Some additional resources for anyone who wants to give it a shot:</p>
<p><a href="https://github.com/SaschaWillems/Vulkan" rel="nofollow noopener">https://github.com/SaschaWillems/Vulkan</a> - Examples.<br>
<a href="https://developer.nvidia.com/open-source-vulkan-c-api" rel="nofollow noopener">https://developer.nvidia.com/open-source-vulkan-c-api</a> - Recommendation.</p>
<p>Video to watch doing a comparison.</p>
<div class="lazyYT" data-youtube-id="P_I8an8jXuM" data-youtube-title="PowerVR Rogue GPUs running Gnome Horde demo (Vulkan prototype)" data-width="480" data-height="270" data-parameters="feature=oembed&amp;wmode=opaque"></div>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/vulkan-new-graphics-api-by-khronos-group/554774/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/vulkan-new-graphics-api-by-khronos-group/554774/2</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 19 Feb 2016 01:38:33 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-554774-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/vulkan-new-graphics-api-by-khronos-group/554774.rss">Vulkan - New Graphics API by Khronos Group</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Vulkan - New Graphics API by Khronos Group</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Protosstribe object]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/protosstribe">@Protosstribe</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>A few days ago Khronos Group launched the initial release of Vulkan, a new graphics API. It may not entirely replace OpenGL, but it’s a combination of OpenGL and OpenCL, streamlined for many platforms, including PCs, consoles and phones.</p>
<p>So if anyone here is interested in learning about OpenGL, I suggest you learn Vulkan instead. As well as their binary intermediate language SPIR-V.</p>
<p>Have anyone else here heard anything about this? Or maybe even tested it?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/vulkan-new-graphics-api-by-khronos-group/554774/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/vulkan-new-graphics-api-by-khronos-group/554774/1</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 18 Feb 2016 19:50:59 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-554774-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/vulkan-new-graphics-api-by-khronos-group/554774.rss">Vulkan - New Graphics API by Khronos Group</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
