<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>[PI] How do I make an area multi-combat?</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/pi-how-do-i-make-an-area-multi-combat/372979</link>
    <description>I have godwars on my server. The one thing several users have complained about though is that some of the areas aren&#39;t multi-comat, which makes it extremely difficult to win, unless you have a team, in which at least four people are there keeping the other NPC&#39;s from attacking you, that way you can actually attack the boss. How do I make an area multi-combat? I&#39;d really appreciate any help.

Edit: Since I haven&#39;t received a response yet, I did some searching and found a potential solution in NPC.java.

I added the coords of the areas I wanted to make multi, and restarted the server, but it still didn&#39;t work.

Please help!</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 12 Dec 2010 16:16:46 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/pi-how-do-i-make-an-area-multi-combat/372979.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>[PI] How do I make an area multi-combat?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Amayzing Amayzing]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/amayzing">@Amayzing</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I have godwars on my server. The one thing several users have complained about though is that some of the areas aren’t multi-comat, which makes it extremely difficult to win, unless you have a team, in which at least four people are there keeping the other NPC’s from attacking you, that way you can actually attack the boss. How do I make an area multi-combat? I’d really appreciate any help.</p>
<p>Edit: Since I haven’t received a response yet, I did some searching and found a potential solution in NPC.java.</p>
<p>I added the coords of the areas I wanted to make multi, and restarted the server, but it still didn’t work.</p>
<p>Please help!</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/pi-how-do-i-make-an-area-multi-combat/372979/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/pi-how-do-i-make-an-area-multi-combat/372979/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 12 Dec 2010 16:16:46 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-372979-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/pi-how-do-i-make-an-area-multi-combat/372979.rss">[PI] How do I make an area multi-combat?</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
