<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Getting no-ip to work behind a router</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/getting-no-ip-to-work-behind-a-router/10019</link>
    <description>i look and observed other people making servers, read tuts for about a week, didint ask questions but 1 or 2, and now i have a decent server up and running. BUT IT REQUIRES HAMACHI!  and this is annoying because not all people have hamachi, so i wanted to get a no-ip. so you say *no-ip would be my answer to this* right? well i cant get no-ip to work. i halfway know the problem. ok i am behind a router. i removed the router for 10 min and asked my friend to try the ip adress now. it worked. but when i have toe router connected, it doesnt work *and my moms bf says i need to keep the router up* so he can get on *dur*. i fowarded the ports on my router settings, and on my firewall. i even completely disabled my firewall in hopes of getting my no-ip to work. but still no hopw. anyone know the problem? if so can you please give me some advise? thanks.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2006 20:03:52 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>General Discussion</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/getting-no-ip-to-work-behind-a-router/10019.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Getting no-ip to work behind a router</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@pur3_d3ath pur3 d3ath]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/pur3_d3ath">@pur3_d3ath</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>hamachi is in no way annoying, id rather be in a server with hamachi then without, hamachi servers tend to lag less and be better…you should use hamachi…</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/getting-no-ip-to-work-behind-a-router/10019/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/getting-no-ip-to-work-behind-a-router/10019/2</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2006 20:03:52 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-10019-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/getting-no-ip-to-work-behind-a-router/10019.rss">Getting no-ip to work behind a router</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Getting no-ip to work behind a router</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@killemquick0 killemquick0]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/killemquick0">@killemquick0</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>i look and observed other people making servers, read tuts for about a week, didint ask questions but 1 or 2, and now i have a decent server up and running. BUT IT REQUIRES HAMACHI!  and this is annoying because not all people have hamachi, so i wanted to get a no-ip. so you say <em>no-ip would be my answer to this</em> right? well i cant get no-ip to work. i halfway know the problem. ok i am behind a router. i removed the router for 10 min and asked my friend to try the ip adress now. it worked. but when i have toe router connected, it doesnt work <em>and my moms bf says i need to keep the router up</em> so he can get on <em>dur</em>. i fowarded the ports on my router settings, and on my firewall. i even completely disabled my firewall in hopes of getting my no-ip to work. but still no hopw. anyone know the problem? if so can you please give me some advise? thanks.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/getting-no-ip-to-work-behind-a-router/10019/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/getting-no-ip-to-work-behind-a-router/10019/1</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2006 18:57:09 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-10019-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/getting-no-ip-to-work-behind-a-router/10019.rss">Getting no-ip to work behind a router</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
