<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Windows xp recovery console</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/windows-xp-recovery-console/418216</link>
    <description>I need a really quick reply--within the next hour. I have a windows xp pro 64 bit install cd. My question is can I use that cd to use the recovery console and repair my friends system. I&#39;m thinking I&#39;m going to have to download the 32 bit version of xp pro. Also does the edition of xp matter with repairing windows xp of a corrupt system file?

A quick response would be very appriciated b/c I plan to be heading to her place within this hour. If I can&#39;t fix it tonight I&#39;m going to let her use one of my computers over the weekend so I can download the iso.

Edit: problem solved the cd won&#39;t even boot. It says the arcitecture isn&#39;t compatible

Thank you</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 15 Oct 2011 01:07:33 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>General Discussion</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/windows-xp-recovery-console/418216.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Windows xp recovery console</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@xryz xryz]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/xryz">@xryz</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I need a really quick reply–within the next hour. I have a windows xp pro 64 bit install cd. My question is can I use that cd to use the recovery console and repair my friends system. I’m thinking I’m going to have to download the 32 bit version of xp pro. Also does the edition of xp matter with repairing windows xp of a corrupt system file?</p>
<p>A quick response would be very appriciated b/c I plan to be heading to her place within this hour. If I can’t fix it tonight I’m going to let her use one of my computers over the weekend so I can download the iso.</p>
<p>Edit: problem solved the cd won’t even boot. It says the arcitecture isn’t compatible</p>
<p>Thank you</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/windows-xp-recovery-console/418216/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/windows-xp-recovery-console/418216/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 15 Oct 2011 01:07:33 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-418216-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/windows-xp-recovery-console/418216.rss">Windows xp recovery console</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
