<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>My chiledhood eckspeeriienses</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-chiledhood-eckspeeriienses/545284</link>
    <description>When I was 12 I had my first sexual experience. At the time, I lived in a little suburb outside of Cleveland and anyway, the girl next door and I were really good friends. Our parents were both gone for the day and she was over playing Transformers with me. So anyway, we kinda got.. Bored I guess? And we started playing truth or dare, which turned into ‘you show me yours, I’ll show you mine&quot;. So anyway there I Was, 12 years old, heart pounding, blood rushing in my ears, and the chick (who was a year older than me actually) takes off her panties and hikes her little skirt up. so What did I do, you ask? I whistled for a cab, and when it came near, the license plate said “fresh” and there were dice in the mirror. If anything I could say that this cab was rare, but I thought “naw forget it, yo home to bel-air!” I pulled up to the house about seven or eight and I yelled to the cabbie “yo homes smell ya later!” Looked at my kingdom, I was finally there. To settle my throne as the prince of bel-air.

After arriving in bel-air I took a few minutes to contemplate how my new life will turn out and then this whiff of pizza smothered me - it tickled and teased my appetite a little so I thought I might order one myself. I picked up the phone, it arrived rather fast. It was pepperoni; I loved it.

I am very secure about my pizza. You have obviously never tasted pizza if you think mine look bad, and that is very sad for you. You should get a pizza right away so you will have some knowledge of pizza and not sound like a fool when you speak. Again, I would ask you to prove your own pizza making skills if you think you are capable of judging others so harshly. But that would require something well beyond your capabilities. You really should try pizza, it is quite delicious and you won&#39;t sound so stupid when you comment. That is incredibly important considering I am a heron. I have a long neck and I pick fish out of the water with my beak. If you don&#39;t repost this comment on 10 other pages, I will fly into your kitchen tonight and make a mess of your pots and pans.

And after you have commented/reposted you should wipe that smug smirk off your face because I have this feeling that you are going to comment &quot;meow&quot;, ok for one, &quot;meow&quot; is literally my catphrase (see what i did there?) whenever someone says &quot;meow&quot; on fb or something, i respond &quot;HEY! that&#39;s MY catphrase&quot; thing 2... i was so depressed at one point in my life that i tried to put myself into a coma by drinking too much water. it involved me watching too much robot chicken, and drinking from 3 full big glasses of water over and over without hardly stopping. i dont think it worked though because i urinated too much. good source of water though! ;D


I prefer vodka to water, but I wouldn&#39;t drink 3 full big glases of vodka because drunk me gets into fights... This one time I was in the tyne and wear pub and this rite ol geezer came up to me n smacked his can of special brew ova. i swear it was an accident and then he was like: &quot;Wot the fok did ye just say 2 me m8? i dropped out of newcastle primary skool im the sickest bloke ull ever meet &amp; ive nicked ova 300 chocolate globbernaughts frum tha corner shop. im trained in street fitin&#39; &amp; im the strongest foker in tha entire newcastle gym. yer nothin to me but a cheeky lil bellend w/ a fit mum &amp; fakebling. ill waste u and smash a fokin bottle oer yer head bruv, i swer. ya think u can fokin run ya gabber at me whilst sittin on yer arse behind a lil screen? think again wanka. im callin me homeboys rite now preparin for a proper scrap. A roomble thatll make ur nan sore jus hearin about it. yer a waste bruv. me crew be all over tha place &amp; ill beat ya to a proper fokin pulp with me fists wanka. if i aint satisfied w/ that ill borrow me m8s cricket paddle &amp; see if that gets u the fok out o&#39; newcastle ya daft kunt. if ye had seen this bloody fokin mess commin ye might a&#39; kept ya gabber from runnin. but it seems yea stupid lil twat, innit? ima shite fury &amp; ull drown in it m8. ur ina proper mess knob.&quot;

so i was like &quot;u are 1 fucking cheeky kunt mate i swear i am goin 2 wreck u i swear on my mums life and i no u are scared lil bitch gettin your mates to send me messages saying dont meet up coz u r sum big bastard with muscles lol fuckin sad mate really sad jus shows what a scared lil gay boy u are and whats all this crap ur mates sendin me about sum bodybuildin website that 1 of your faverite places to look at men u lil fuckin gay boy fone me if u got da balls cheeky prick see if u can step up lil queer&quot; and smacked him till he no see.&quot;

then this cheeky merican cunt m9 hit me out of nowhere and told me: &quot;What the fuck did you just fucking say about me, you little bitch? I’ll have you know I graduated top of my class in the Navy Seals, and I’ve been involved in numerous secret raids on Al-Quaeda, and I have over 300 confirmed kills. I am trained in gorilla warfare and I’m the top sniper in the entire US armed forces. You are nothing to me but just another target. I will wipe you the fuck out with precision the likes of which has never been seen before on this Earth, mark my fucking words. You think you can get away with saying that shit to me over the Internet? Think again, fucker. As we speak I am contacting my secret network of spies across the USA and your IP is being traced right now so you better prepare for the storm, maggot. The storm that wipes out the pathetic little thing you call your life. You’re fucking dead, kid. I can be anywhere, anytime, and I can kill you in over seven hundred ways, and that’s just with my bare hands. Not only am I extensively trained in unarmed combat, but I have access to the entire arsenal of the United States Marine Corps and I will use it to its full extent to wipe your miserable ass off the face of the continent, you little shit. If only you could have known what unholy retribution your little “clever” comment was about to bring down upon you, maybe you would have held your fucking tongue. But you couldn’t, you didn’t, and now you’re paying the price, you goddamn idiot. I will shit fury all over you and you will drown in it. You’re fucking dead, kiddo.&quot;

wat a fookin dikhed

Anyways I went home and guys, you&#39;ll never believe what just happened no less than 999999 minutes ago. so my sister and her boyfriend came home while i was watching TV and they went into the kitchen to get some drinks. while in the kitchen they were doing their whole lovey dovey thing and kissing and playing grab-ass and what not, and it was unappealing to me, so i went up to my room. a few minutes later, i heard them enter into my sister&#39;s room and then some rustling occurred. i thought nothing of it, they were probably just making out again on her bed. then i heard her scream and i got worried so i ran over to her room, and opened the door, got on the floor, everybody walk the dinosaur! open to door, get on the floor, everybody walk the dinosaur! BOOM BOOM ACKLAKKALAKKA BOOM BOOM BOOM ACKLAKKALAKKA BOOM!

after the dinosaurs dignity was violated, my nan told me that I is 14 years old, and I have boobs. One day I was asleep in my bed, than I wolk up to a very surprising treat, I had boobs. I felt very astonished. Why would the good lawrd jebus give poor old Zurela boobs? My first instinct was to call my boyfriend and tell him, so I did. I knew we would abuse my love for my &quot;Chesticles&quot; but I didn&#39;t mind. So later on in the day he came over, and he was astonished too. My mother had not yet noticed, but my father had to check for breast cancer, thankfully he did, he checked for 7 and a half hours and found nothing, he said he needs to check everyday because my mom had it once and he didn&#39;t want to loose me like he lost my mom, cause she died. Anyways so my Boyfriend came over and he checked too, apparently Breast cancer is a very serious disease, but I didn&#39;t tell him about dada because I know he just wanted to be sure because he loved me. So after about a hour or two of that we played WoW and we lvled up, he told me I gave him an &quot;erevecton&quot; you know, that thing when it forces you outta the house, but I just ignored the comment because I am not his landlord, I just think he was being silly. He went home, and dad told me the power of boobs, and he told be if I have to be under heavy surveillance in the shower because if I don&#39;t scrub my &quot;boobs&#39; enough a demon will come out and kill us all. This is how mom died, so he says. So I washed this thoroughly and he made sure they are clean Enough. I really love how my boobs made everyone care about me more, and ladies I had no idea the upkeep of these things, so if there is any more tips I need, please tell me!

I stepped out the shower and went out outside because  I had to take care of my uncle&#39;s dog for a while. He was a big Golden Retriever and his name was Sasu. After about 3 days, I was extremely turned on and without a boyfriend, so this dog in my pussy seemed like a pretty good idea. One day, I decided to go for a walk and take the dog with me. I was conveniently wearing a skirt and once we reached a pretty secluded street, I pulled up my skirt and got on all fours. At first the dog just sniffed my butt around but once he got the idea, he got on top of me and started humping my butt through my panties. He kept banging against my clit and my juices were flowing to pretty much everywhere. I didn&#39;t let him inside me yet because I was too afraid. I mean, think about it. That&#39;s pretty fucking gross. But anyways. Whenever I got back home, I sat on the front porch. My uncle had come back and was ready to pick up the dog but he was inside talking to my sister. My uncle told me to stay outside with Sasu for a while, so I did. While we were out there, I was sitting on a bench with my legs spread open and Sasu kept trying to stick his nose in my crotch. Usually, I&#39;d push his face away and close my legs, but I was extremely wet and was dripping everywhere. So I let Sasu lick it up. Since I had never been eaten out before, I really didn&#39;t know that what I was doing was sexual in the least, but I realized that it felt really good and was only making me wetter. Even after I came Sasu was still licking it all up and the front of my skirt was soaked in a combination of my pussy juice and Sasu&#39;s saliva. Once I had to go back inside, I just twisted my skirt to the side and went to my room to change.

i came out the room and still felt horny so i switched on the tv looking for something good and this really interesting report came up, it was as follows:

when Jewish population remains under 5,000 of any given country they will be regarded as a peace-loving minority and not as a threat to anyone: Estonia -- 1,800 Jews Bulgaria -- 2,300 Jews Costa Rica -- 2,400 Jews Peru -- 2,800 Jews Slovakia -- 3,000 Jews Kazakhstan -- 4,100 Jews

At 5,000 to 10,000 they begin to separate from other ethnic minorities and disaffected groups: Morocco -- 5,200 Jews Greece -- 5,300 Jews Denmark -- 7,000 Jews Austria -- 8,100 Jews Latvia -- OVER 9000 JEWS

From 10,000 on they exercise an inordinate influence in proportion to their percentage of the population.They will push for the introduction of kosher (clean by Jewish standards) food, thereby securing food preparation jobs for Jews. They will increase pressure on supermarket chains to feature it on their shelves - along with threats for failure to comply. At this point, they will work to get the ruling government to allow them to rule themselves under Pentateuch, the Hebrew Law. Panama -- 10,000 Jews Switzerland -- 14,000 Jews Turkey -- 17,000 Jews Poland -- 25,000 Jews Italy -- 30,000 Jews

When Jews reach over 50,000 of the population, they will bail out funds managers as a means of complaint about their conditions (Ben Bernanke -- Fed chairman) . Any non-Jewish action that offends Judaism will result in stock fluctuations and foreclosures (United States -- Housing market). Belgium -- 51,000 Jews Mexico -- 53,000 Jews Belarus -- 72,000 Jews

After reaching 100,000 expect hair-trigger market crashes, Neo-Nazi group formations, sporadic killings and synagogue burning: Australia -- 120,000 Jews Ukraine -- 142,000 Jews

At 200,000 you will find widespread hatred of Jews, chronic terror attacks and ongoing anti-Jew warfare: Germany -- 220,000 Jews Argentina -- 250,000 Jews United Kingdom -- 350,000 Jews Canada -- 390,000 Jews

From 500,000 you may expect unfettered persecution by non-believers and other religions, sporadic establishments of Holocaust museums, use of Pentateuch as a weapon and loan interest, the tax placed on Gentiles: France -- 600,000 Jews Russia -- 800,000 Jews

3,000,000+ will usher in the establishment of a permanent Jewish state-- Hollywood-- where there&#39;s supposed to be peace because everybody is a Jew: Israel -- 5,600,000 Jews United States -- 6,150,000 Jews

thanks for reading

rep++</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2014 21:39:29 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>General Discussion</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-chiledhood-eckspeeriienses/545284.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>My chiledhood eckspeeriienses</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@strucker Strucker]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/strucker">@strucker</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“hydreigon_, post:14, topic:545284”]I would like to take a moment to share one of my past experiences:</p>
<p>When I was 17 my girlfriend at the time was finally ready to have sex. I, as one might expect of a 17 year old, was excited. Neither hell nor high water was going to stand between me and my final destination.</p>
<p>I get ready for the night, trim everything up, shower extra well. Unfortunately there was also an issue. I have a digestional disorder that sometimes cause my sh!t to become large and quite solid while still inside me. I wasn’t aware it was a treatable problem and, in fact, just thought everyone had to deal with the equivalent of anal kidney stones. I bring this up because I had a mighty one which had been loaded into the gun for several days.</p>
<p>Let me set the scene. Her parents are away. We have her house to ourselves. She was always a little kinky so she demands we do it in her parents bed.</p>
<p>I walk in to a candle holocaust. She’s been working on this all day apparently, and its as bright as high noon in there with the lights off. Which is good, because she proceeds to do a sweet, sexy little dance for me. At 16, she was AMAZING. For those of you who never experienced a female at that age, I pity the fool.</p>
<p>Now I’m sitting on the bed, watching this dance. I smile and tell her how good she looks. Unfortunately, most of my attention is focused on the dull throbbing from my sphincter and the large amount of intestinal discomfort associated with not dropping duce in days. But somehow I still get hard and we go to town.</p>
<p>She starts out on top, then we switch. I bend her over the bed, and I even smack her a$$ (a ballsy move at the time, but she loved it). Due to my built up distraction, I last for what seems like FOREVER. She can’t stop moaning and telling me how good it feels, and then she says what every man wants to hear “I want to make you go in my mouth.” I **** love women.</p>
<p>So she goes down on me. She was always average at best in the head department but at least she tried. She pops my **** out of her mouth long enough to look up at me and say “tell me if you like this”. Then I feel it.</p>
<p>She stuck her finger up my a$$.</p>
<p>My brain hits the panic switch and every muscle in my entire body locks up tighter than a three year old virgin. But its too late. I take a massive, PAINFUL, PAINFUL sh!t, all over her parents comforter.<br>
No, you aren’t understanding. I mean large. Huge. IMMENSE. Take your largest sh!t and multiple it by forty-two and you’ll have an idea of what flew out of me. And gents, when I say flew, I don’t mean “I pooped.” I mean “projectile”. I mean “hurricane force winds hitting an umbrella stand”. And due to my condition, it comes out as a large, dark brown, smelly harpoon.</p>
<p>I know it hit her. I didn’t see it. She ran screaming “OH MY GOD OHMYGODOHMYGODEEEEEWWWWWWWW” but I always imagined that, due to her position, it hit her right in the chin. Or at least the tits.</p>
<p>I would like to say I got up to go after her. But I heard the bathroom door shut and I just lied there. The smell hit me after a few seconds. It smelled like someone rolled a cat in sh!t and threw it into a tire fire. I looked down and saw, to date, the largest bowel movement I’ve ever heard of laying on the bed. Then I noticed the blood, and when I did, I noticed the pain.</p>
<p>Apparently the fact that it was so large caused it to rip my a$$ a little bit (thought I was bleeding from the inside. This little doctors trip the next day is what taught me of my condition). There was a small pool of blood where my a$$ had been. A final reminder of the exact place and moment I lost my virginity. I will treasure this memory for all my days.</p>
<p>I grab my sh!t with my hands and go to the downstairs bathroom. I throw around 1/3 into the toilet and flush, fearing any more will clog it and only add to my already significant woes.</p>
<p>I stand there, holding 2/3’s of my biggest sh!t of all time, feeling a trickle of blood flow down my leg, trying to ignore the sharp pain stabbing my rectum. I find myself wishing I had a photo of this.</p>
<p>Anyway, I finish flushing my baby, clean off my hands, jam toilet paper between my cheeks (I skipped the bandaid) and went upstairs. I could hear my girlfriend sobbing from behind the bathroom door. I decided not to say anything to her and just keep moving. The smell in her parents room was abysmal. Its like when you take a sh!t and walk out of the bathroom you think “hey not so bad today,” but then you walk back in to grab your magazine and go “HOLY SH!T!”. It was one of those moments.</p>
<p>The scene is burned behind my eyelids for all time. My life. My shame. My very first time smelled like a pile of dead babies. I quickly got dressed since the heat from ten thousand candles was making the room feel more like a port-a-potty. I was aware enough to grab the comforter on my way out and drag it downstairs to their washer. Also the top and bottom sheets since the blood had leaked on through all the way to mattress. Still no sign of the GF but at this point I considered it a blessing.</p>
<p>I jammed in the washer with 3 loads worth of detergent and set it on spin, knowing that not even the hand of God would save these linens, let alone Tide and Snuggles.</p>
<p>Then I left. I avoided my GF’s calls for days until she came to my house. We had a long talk about what happened. Talk being synonymous with “breaking up with me because I **** on her”. And it was all over. She promised not to tell a soul and I don’t THINK she ever did. She was probably as ashamed as I was about the whole deed. But I will always remember this ‘happening’ as the most embarrassing thing that has ever happened to me.[/quote]lmao 10/10 would read again</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-chiledhood-eckspeeriienses/545284/15">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-chiledhood-eckspeeriienses/545284/15</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2014 21:39:29 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-545284-15</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-chiledhood-eckspeeriienses/545284.rss">My chiledhood eckspeeriienses</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>My chiledhood eckspeeriienses</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@hydreigon hydreigon_]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/hydreigon">@hydreigon</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I would like to take a moment to share one of my past experiences:</p>
<p>When I was 17 my girlfriend at the time was finally ready to have sex. I, as one might expect of a 17 year old, was excited. Neither hell nor high water was going to stand between me and my final destination.</p>
<p>I get ready for the night, trim everything up, shower extra well. Unfortunately there was also an issue. I have a digestional disorder that sometimes cause my sh!t to become large and quite solid while still inside me. I wasn’t aware it was a treatable problem and, in fact, just thought everyone had to deal with the equivalent of anal kidney stones. I bring this up because I had a mighty one which had been loaded into the gun for several days.</p>
<p>Let me set the scene. Her parents are away. We have her house to ourselves. She was always a little kinky so she demands we do it in her parents bed.</p>
<p>I walk in to a candle holocaust. She’s been working on this all day apparently, and its as bright as high noon in there with the lights off. Which is good, because she proceeds to do a sweet, sexy little dance for me. At 16, she was AMAZING. For those of you who never experienced a female at that age, I pity the fool.</p>
<p>Now I’m sitting on the bed, watching this dance. I smile and tell her how good she looks. Unfortunately, most of my attention is focused on the dull throbbing from my sphincter and the large amount of intestinal discomfort associated with not dropping duce in days. But somehow I still get hard and we go to town.</p>
<p>She starts out on top, then we switch. I bend her over the bed, and I even smack her a$$ (a ballsy move at the time, but she loved it). Due to my built up distraction, I last for what seems like FOREVER. She can’t stop moaning and telling me how good it feels, and then she says what every man wants to hear “I want to make you go in my mouth.” I **** love women.</p>
<p>So she goes down on me. She was always average at best in the head department but at least she tried. She pops my **** out of her mouth long enough to look up at me and say “tell me if you like this”. Then I feel it.</p>
<p>She stuck her finger up my a$$.</p>
<p>My brain hits the panic switch and every muscle in my entire body locks up tighter than a three year old virgin. But its too late. I take a massive, PAINFUL, PAINFUL sh!t, all over her parents comforter.<br>
No, you aren’t understanding. I mean large. Huge. IMMENSE. Take your largest sh!t and multiple it by forty-two and you’ll have an idea of what flew out of me. And gents, when I say flew, I don’t mean “I pooped.” I mean “projectile”. I mean “hurricane force winds hitting an umbrella stand”. And due to my condition, it comes out as a large, dark brown, smelly harpoon.</p>
<p>I know it hit her. I didn’t see it. She ran screaming “OH MY GOD OHMYGODOHMYGODEEEEEWWWWWWWW” but I always imagined that, due to her position, it hit her right in the chin. Or at least the tits.</p>
<p>I would like to say I got up to go after her. But I heard the bathroom door shut and I just lied there. The smell hit me after a few seconds. It smelled like someone rolled a cat in sh!t and threw it into a tire fire. I looked down and saw, to date, the largest bowel movement I’ve ever heard of laying on the bed. Then I noticed the blood, and when I did, I noticed the pain.</p>
<p>Apparently the fact that it was so large caused it to rip my a$$ a little bit (thought I was bleeding from the inside. This little doctors trip the next day is what taught me of my condition). There was a small pool of blood where my a$$ had been. A final reminder of the exact place and moment I lost my virginity. I will treasure this memory for all my days.</p>
<p>I grab my sh!t with my hands and go to the downstairs bathroom. I throw around 1/3 into the toilet and flush, fearing any more will clog it and only add to my already significant woes.</p>
<p>I stand there, holding 2/3’s of my biggest sh!t of all time, feeling a trickle of blood flow down my leg, trying to ignore the sharp pain stabbing my rectum. I find myself wishing I had a photo of this.</p>
<p>Anyway, I finish flushing my baby, clean off my hands, jam toilet paper between my cheeks (I skipped the bandaid) and went upstairs. I could hear my girlfriend sobbing from behind the bathroom door. I decided not to say anything to her and just keep moving. The smell in her parents room was abysmal. Its like when you take a sh!t and walk out of the bathroom you think “hey not so bad today,” but then you walk back in to grab your magazine and go “HOLY SH!T!”. It was one of those moments.</p>
<p>The scene is burned behind my eyelids for all time. My life. My shame. My very first time smelled like a pile of dead babies. I quickly got dressed since the heat from ten thousand candles was making the room feel more like a port-a-potty. I was aware enough to grab the comforter on my way out and drag it downstairs to their washer. Also the top and bottom sheets since the blood had leaked on through all the way to mattress. Still no sign of the GF but at this point I considered it a blessing.</p>
<p>I jammed in the washer with 3 loads worth of detergent and set it on spin, knowing that not even the hand of God would save these linens, let alone Tide and Snuggles.</p>
<p>Then I left. I avoided my GF’s calls for days until she came to my house. We had a long talk about what happened. Talk being synonymous with “breaking up with me because I **** on her”. And it was all over. She promised not to tell a soul and I don’t THINK she ever did. She was probably as ashamed as I was about the whole deed. But I will always remember this ‘happening’ as the most embarrassing thing that has ever happened to me.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-chiledhood-eckspeeriienses/545284/14">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-chiledhood-eckspeeriienses/545284/14</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 26 Jul 2014 05:42:46 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-545284-14</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-chiledhood-eckspeeriienses/545284.rss">My chiledhood eckspeeriienses</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>My chiledhood eckspeeriienses</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@gothic_queen casey.]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/gothic_queen">@gothic_queen</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I was at the bar last night for my buddies 21st birthday party, and needless to say it didn’t end to well. We got a $30 drink special which included domestics, bombs, and mixed drinks for 4 hours, it was pretty much worth it since beers were about $2, bombs are about $3-$4 and mixed are about $4-$5… So as were getting our drinks the bartender made a couple comments about us not tipping, and honestly we probably gave her about $3 the whole time we were there. She was pretty heavyset and we were all pretty drunk after awhile, so after she made a second comment about us not tipping her I told her to shut her fat ****ing mouth and to do her job. She brings over the manager, he asks me what the problem is, and obviously belligerant I told him that his fat ass waitress was asking for tips, which is something you aren’t supposed to do anyways as a bartender/sever.</p>
<p>SO anywho, she gets mad, I tell the manager his bar is a dump and I wanted my money back for the poor service. We start arguing, a bouncer comes over, and puts his hands on my wrist, so I punched him in the face and there was a fight with like 3 of us and a couple of the bouncers. The Cops come and ask me what happened, I told him the bouncer put his hands on me and I punched him for touching me. He put me in cuffs and ask me where I was from, so I told him West Philadelphia born and raised on the playground where I spent most of my days chilling out, maxing and relaxing all cool and all shooting some b-ball<br>
outside of school when a couple of guys they were up to no good started making trouble in our neighborhood I got in one little fight and my mom got scared she said your moving in with your auntie and uncle in Bel-Air.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-chiledhood-eckspeeriienses/545284/13">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-chiledhood-eckspeeriienses/545284/13</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2014 02:21:24 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-545284-13</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-chiledhood-eckspeeriienses/545284.rss">My chiledhood eckspeeriienses</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>My chiledhood eckspeeriienses</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@asyo4 asyo4]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/asyo4">@asyo4</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[youtube]<a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=RubBzkZzpUA%5B/youtube%5D" rel="nofollow noopener">https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=RubBzkZzpUA[/youtube]</a></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-chiledhood-eckspeeriienses/545284/12">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-chiledhood-eckspeeriienses/545284/12</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2014 01:46:02 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-545284-12</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-chiledhood-eckspeeriienses/545284.rss">My chiledhood eckspeeriienses</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>My chiledhood eckspeeriienses</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@drubrkletern drubrkletern]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/drubrkletern">@drubrkletern</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Some background on me, I was born in the remote village of habibi in the outskirts of djibouti to an albanian prostitute where i was raised by an ascetic monk in the azerbaijan mountains before moving to croatia at the age of 5. at the age of 15 I was conscripted into the croatian military where I served as a janitorial technician in iran. After moving to florida at 19, I followed my mothers footsteps and roamed the streets as a prostitute, selling blowjobs for 5 bucks.After a brief stint in rehab, i turned my life around and became a personal trainer. In the past several years I’ve hunted with the indigenous tribes of sri lanka, found 3 previously unknown star clusters with nothing more than my grandmothers magnifying glass, some ducktape and tinfoil and and have had a statue erected in honor of me in Uzbekistan for peace negotiatians with the native titthibhalad tribe.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-chiledhood-eckspeeriienses/545284/11">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-chiledhood-eckspeeriienses/545284/11</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2014 01:06:32 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-545284-11</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-chiledhood-eckspeeriienses/545284.rss">My chiledhood eckspeeriienses</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>My chiledhood eckspeeriienses</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@whackatre Whackatre]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/whackatre">@whackatre</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>This didn’t happen today, but I had just come to terms with it because of how mortified I have been in front of my mom since it has happened.</p>
<p>This happened when I was 12 and I (female) had just figured out what masturbating was and how good it felt just touching it. It hadn’t quite registered to me yet that masturbation is an activity that you don’t do with other people in the room. Yeah, I was one of those kind of people.</p>
<p>One day, when my mom and I were watching TV together, I went to go grab a blanket because it was starting to get cold. As I put it on over my legs, I thought to myself “right now seems like a good time to start touching myself”. So as my mom and I are watching TV, I start going at it. It is quite obvious what is going on, as the blanket that is covering me looks as though it is being ravaged by a crazy animal.</p>
<p>My mom quickly realized what was going on and just stared at me with wide-eyes and grabbed my arm and jerked it up. After I stared at her, not realizing that masturbating while sitting next to my mom is not the best thing to do, she calls my dad in the room so she can tell me that it’s normal to do, but not with her there.</p>
<p>My face turned as red as Flamin’ Hot Cheetos fingers and I ran to my room and wasn’t able to make eye contact with her for about a year afterwards. I have managed to keep it repressed up until recently, where I still cringe every time.</p>
<p>TL;DR: started stabbing the cat with my mom in the room</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-chiledhood-eckspeeriienses/545284/10">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-chiledhood-eckspeeriienses/545284/10</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2014 01:02:59 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-545284-10</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-chiledhood-eckspeeriienses/545284.rss">My chiledhood eckspeeriienses</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>My chiledhood eckspeeriienses</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@tL tL]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/tl">@tL</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>When I was about 10 or 11 years old I was an oversexed little girl. My bedroom was in the mezzanine of our family apartment, and you had to climb a little set of stairs to get to a partial wall.</p>
<p>That means whoever’s on the other side can hear everything that’s going on in the bedroom extremely clearly.</p>
<p>My dad quietly walked up the stairs to wish me a good night right as I was enacting out loud both sides of a scenario where a man was taking my virginity, and I was protesting because it hurt too much. It was very overblown and dramatic, and I repeated it several times before I realized my dad was frozen on the other side of the door.</p>
<p>He quietly backed down the stairs while I fell silent. We never mentioned it.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-chiledhood-eckspeeriienses/545284/9">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-chiledhood-eckspeeriienses/545284/9</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2014 23:36:12 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-545284-9</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-chiledhood-eckspeeriienses/545284.rss">My chiledhood eckspeeriienses</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>My chiledhood eckspeeriienses</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@asshole_rule asshole_rule]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/asshole_rule">@asshole_rule</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>i was very entertained for the first 3 1/2 lines</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-chiledhood-eckspeeriienses/545284/8">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-chiledhood-eckspeeriienses/545284/8</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2014 22:57:56 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-545284-8</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-chiledhood-eckspeeriienses/545284.rss">My chiledhood eckspeeriienses</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>My chiledhood eckspeeriienses</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@whackatre Whackatre]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/whackatre">@whackatre</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>That’s cool, OP, because when I was 12 I had my first sexual experience. At the time, I lived in a little suburb outside of Cleveland and anyway, the girl next door and I were really good friends. Our parents were both gone for the day and she was over playing Transformers with me. So anyway, we kinda got… Bored I guess? And we started playing truth or dare, which turned into ‘you show me yours, I’ll show you mine". So anyway there I Was, 12 years old, heart pounding, blood rushing in my ears, and the chick (who was a year older than me actually) takes off her panties and hikes her little skirt up. so What did I do, you ask? I whistled for a cab, and when it came near, the license plate said “fresh” and there were dice in the mirror. If anything I could say that this cab was rare, but I thought “naw forget it, yo home to bel-air!” I pulled up to the house about seven or eight and I yelled to the cabbie “yo homes smell ya later!” Looked at my kingdom, I was finally there. To settle my throne as the prince of bel-air.</p>
<p>After arriving in bel-air I took a few minutes to contemplate how my new life will turn out and then this whiff of pizza smothered me - it tickled and teased my appetite a little so I thought I might order one myself. I picked up the phone, it arrived rather fast. It was pepperoni; I loved it.</p>
<p>I am very secure about my pizza. You have obviously never tasted pizza if you think mine look bad, and that is very sad for you. You should get a pizza right away so you will have some knowledge of pizza and not sound like a fool when you speak. Again, I would ask you to prove your own pizza making skills if you think you are capable of judging others so harshly. But that would require something well beyond your capabilities. You really should try pizza, it is quite delicious and you won’t sound so stupid when you comment. That is incredibly important considering I am a heron. I have a long neck and I pick fish out of the water with my beak. If you don’t repost this comment on 10 other pages, I will fly into your kitchen tonight and make a mess of your pots and pans.</p>
<p>And after you have commented/reposted you should wipe that smug smirk off your face because I have this feeling that you are going to comment “meow”, ok for one, “meow” is literally my catphrase (see what i did there?) whenever someone says “meow” on fb or something, i respond “HEY! that’s MY catphrase” thing 2… i was so depressed at one point in my life that i tried to put myself into a coma by drinking too much water. it involved me watching too much robot chicken, and drinking from 3 full big glasses of water over and over without hardly stopping. i dont think it worked though because i urinated too much. good source of water though! ;D</p>
<p>I prefer vodka to water, but I wouldn’t drink 3 full big glases of vodka because drunk me gets into fights… This one time I was in the tyne and wear pub and this rite ol geezer came up to me n smacked his can of special brew ova. i swear it was an accident and then he was like: “Wot the fok did ye just say 2 me m8? i dropped out of newcastle primary skool im the sickest bloke ull ever meet &amp; ive nicked ova 300 chocolate globbernaughts frum tha corner shop. im trained in street fitin’ &amp; im the strongest foker in tha entire newcastle gym. yer nothin to me but a cheeky lil bellend w/ a fit mum &amp; fakebling. ill waste u and smash a fokin bottle oer yer head bruv, i swer. ya think u can fokin run ya gabber at me whilst sittin on yer arse behind a lil screen? think again wanka. im callin me homeboys rite now preparin for a proper scrap. A roomble thatll make ur nan sore jus hearin about it. yer a waste bruv. me crew be all over tha place &amp; ill beat ya to a proper fokin pulp with me fists wanka. if i aint satisfied w/ that ill borrow me m8s cricket paddle &amp; see if that gets u the fok out o’ newcastle ya daft kunt. if ye had seen this bloody fokin mess commin ye might a’ kept ya gabber from runnin. but it seems yea stupid lil twat, innit? ima shite fury &amp; ull drown in it m8. ur ina proper mess knob.”</p>
<p>so i was like “u are 1 fudgeing cheeky kunt mate i swear i am goin 2 wreck u i swear on my mums life and i no u are scared lil bitch gettin your mates to send me messages saying dont meet up coz u r sum big bastard with muscles lol fudgein sad mate really sad jus shows what a scared lil gay boy u are and whats all this crap ur mates sendin me about sum bodybuildin website that 1 of your faverite places to look at men u lil fudgein gay boy fone me if u got da balls cheeky prick see if u can step up lil queer” and smacked him till he no see."</p>
<p>then this cheeky merican runt m9 hit me out of nowhere and told me: “What the fudge did you just fudgeing say about me, you little bitch? I’ll have you know I graduated top of my class in the Navy Seals, and I’ve been involved in numerous secret raids on Al-Quaeda, and I have over 300 confirmed kills. I am trained in gorilla warfare and I’m the top sniper in the entire US armed forces. You are nothing to me but just another target. I will wipe you the fudge out with precision the likes of which has never been seen before on this Earth, mark my fudgeing words. You think you can get away with saying that shit to me over the Internet? Think again, fudgeer. As we speak I am contacting my secret network of spies across the USA and your IP is being traced right now so you better prepare for the storm, maggot. The storm that wipes out the pathetic little thing you call your life. You’re fudgeing dead, kid. I can be anywhere, anytime, and I can kill you in over seven hundred ways, and that’s just with my bare hands. Not only am I extensively trained in unarmed combat, but I have access to the entire arsenal of the United States Marine Corps and I will use it to its full extent to wipe your miserable ass off the face of the continent, you little shit. If only you could have known what unholy retribution your little “clever” comment was about to bring down upon you, maybe you would have held your fudgeing tongue. But you couldn’t, you didn’t, and now you’re paying the price, you goddamn idiot. I will shit fury all over you and you will drown in it. You’re fudgeing dead, kiddo.”</p>
<p>wat a fookin dikhed</p>
<p>Anyways I went home and guys, you’ll never believe what just happened no less than 999999 minutes ago. so my sister and her boyfriend came home while i was watching TV and they went into the kitchen to get some drinks. while in the kitchen they were doing their whole lovey dovey thing and kissing and playing grab-ass and what not, and it was unappealing to me, so i went up to my room. a few minutes later, i heard them enter into my sister’s room and then some rustling occurred. i thought nothing of it, they were probably just making out again on her bed. then i heard her scream and i got worried so i ran over to her room, and opened the door, got on the floor, everybody walk the dinosaur! open to door, get on the floor, everybody walk the dinosaur! BOOM BOOM ACKLAKKALAKKA BOOM BOOM BOOM ACKLAKKALAKKA BOOM!</p>
<p>after the dinosaurs dignity was violated, my nan told me that I is 14 years old, and I have boobs. One day I was asleep in my bed, than I wolk up to a very surprising treat, I had boobs. I felt very astonished. Why would the good lawrd jebus give poor old Zurela boobs? My first instinct was to call my boyfriend and tell him, so I did. I knew we would abuse my love for my “Chesticles” but I didn’t mind. So later on in the day he came over, and he was astonished too. My mother had not yet noticed, but my father had to check for breast cancer, thankfully he did, he checked for 7 and a half hours and found nothing, he said he needs to check everyday because my mom had it once and he didn’t want to loose me like he lost my mom, cause she died. Anyways so my Boyfriend came over and he checked too, apparently Breast cancer is a very serious disease, but I didn’t tell him about dada because I know he just wanted to be sure because he loved me. So after about a hour or two of that we played WoW and we lvled up, he told me I gave him an “erevecton” you know, that thing when it forces you outta the house, but I just ignored the comment because I am not his landlord, I just think he was being silly. He went home, and dad told me the power of boobs, and he told be if I have to be under heavy surveillance in the shower because if I don’t scrub my "boobs’ enough a demon will come out and kill us all. This is how mom died, so he says. So I washed this thoroughly and he made sure they are clean Enough. I really love how my boobs made everyone care about me more, and ladies I had no idea the upkeep of these things, so if there is any more tips I need, please tell me!</p>
<p>I stepped out the shower and went out outside because  I had to take care of my uncle’s dog for a while. He was a big Golden Retriever and his name was Sasu. After about 3 days, I was extremely turned on and without a boyfriend, so this dog in my pussy seemed like a pretty good idea. One day, I decided to go for a walk and take the dog with me. I was conveniently wearing a skirt and once we reached a pretty secluded street, I pulled up my skirt and got on all fours. At first the dog just sniffed my butt around but once he got the idea, he got on top of me and started humping my butt through my panties. He kept banging against my clit and my juices were flowing to pretty much everywhere. I didn’t let him inside me yet because I was too afraid. I mean, think about it. That’s pretty fudgeing gross. But anyways. Whenever I got back home, I sat on the front porch. My uncle had come back and was ready to pick up the dog but he was inside talking to my sister. My uncle told me to stay outside with Sasu for a while, so I did. While we were out there, I was sitting on a bench with my legs spread open and Sasu kept trying to stick his nose in my crotch. Usually, I’d push his face away and close my legs, but I was extremely wet and was dripping everywhere. So I let Sasu lick it up. Since I had never been eaten out before, I really didn’t know that what I was doing was sexual in the least, but I realized that it felt really good and was only making me wetter. Even after I came Sasu was still licking it all up and the front of my skirt was soaked in a combination of my pussy juice and Sasu’s saliva. Once I had to go back inside, I just twisted my skirt to the side and went to my room to change.</p>
<p>i came out the room and still felt horny so i switched on the tv looking for something good and this really interesting report came up, it was as follows:</p>
<p>when Jewish population remains under 5,000 of any given country they will be regarded as a peace-loving minority and not as a threat to anyone: Estonia – 1,800 Jews Bulgaria – 2,300 Jews Costa Rica – 2,400 Jews Peru – 2,800 Jews Slovakia – 3,000 Jews Kazakhstan – 4,100 Jews</p>
<p>At 5,000 to 10,000 they begin to separate from other ethnic minorities and disaffected groups: Morocco – 5,200 Jews Greece – 5,300 Jews Denmark – 7,000 Jews Austria – 8,100 Jews Latvia – OVER 9000 JEWS</p>
<p>From 10,000 on they exercise an inordinate influence in proportion to their percentage of the population.They will push for the introduction of kosher (clean by Jewish standards) food, thereby securing food preparation jobs for Jews. They will increase pressure on supermarket chains to feature it on their shelves - along with threats for failure to comply. At this point, they will work to get the ruling government to allow them to rule themselves under Pentateuch, the Hebrew Law. Panama – 10,000 Jews Switzerland – 14,000 Jews Turkey – 17,000 Jews Poland – 25,000 Jews Italy – 30,000 Jews</p>
<p>When Jews reach over 50,000 of the population, they will bail out funds managers as a means of complaint about their conditions (Ben Bernanke – Fed chairman) . Any non-Jewish action that offends Judaism will result in stock fluctuations and foreclosures (United States – Housing market). Belgium – 51,000 Jews Mexico – 53,000 Jews Belarus – 72,000 Jews</p>
<p>After reaching 100,000 expect hair-trigger market crashes, Neo-Nazi group formations, sporadic killings and synagogue burning: Australia – 120,000 Jews Ukraine – 142,000 Jews</p>
<p>At 200,000 you will find widespread hatred of Jews, chronic terror attacks and ongoing anti-Jew warfare: Germany – 220,000 Jews Argentina – 250,000 Jews United Kingdom – 350,000 Jews Canada – 390,000 Jews</p>
<p>From 500,000 you may expect unfettered persecution by non-believers and other religions, sporadic establishments of Holocaust museums, use of Pentateuch as a weapon and loan interest, the tax placed on Gentiles: France – 600,000 Jews Russia – 800,000 Jews</p>
<p>3,000,000+ will usher in the establishment of a permanent Jewish state-- Hollywood-- where there’s supposed to be peace because everybody is a Jew: Israel – 5,600,000 Jews United States – 6,150,000 Jews</p>
<p>thanks for reading</p>
<p>rep++</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-chiledhood-eckspeeriienses/545284/7">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-chiledhood-eckspeeriienses/545284/7</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2014 22:49:31 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-545284-7</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-chiledhood-eckspeeriienses/545284.rss">My chiledhood eckspeeriienses</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>My chiledhood eckspeeriienses</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Phillipe Phillipé]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/phillipe">@Phillipe</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>do not know what read I just. inspired piece, deserve award.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-chiledhood-eckspeeriienses/545284/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-chiledhood-eckspeeriienses/545284/6</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2014 20:39:26 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-545284-6</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-chiledhood-eckspeeriienses/545284.rss">My chiledhood eckspeeriienses</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>My chiledhood eckspeeriienses</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@pure2ownage Pure_]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/pure2ownage">@pure2ownage</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>irc sqwad checkin in</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-chiledhood-eckspeeriienses/545284/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-chiledhood-eckspeeriienses/545284/5</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2014 20:39:14 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-545284-5</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-chiledhood-eckspeeriienses/545284.rss">My chiledhood eckspeeriienses</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>My chiledhood eckspeeriienses</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@bootnecklad bootnecklad]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/bootnecklad">@bootnecklad</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>damned polski jew you fc.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-chiledhood-eckspeeriienses/545284/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-chiledhood-eckspeeriienses/545284/4</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2014 20:34:25 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-545284-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-chiledhood-eckspeeriienses/545284.rss">My chiledhood eckspeeriienses</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>My chiledhood eckspeeriienses</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Ashi Ashi]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/ashi">@Ashi</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>tl;dr you’ve been a horn dog since you where 12 and Jewish? Your fav pizza is pepperoni?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-chiledhood-eckspeeriienses/545284/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-chiledhood-eckspeeriienses/545284/3</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2014 20:34:16 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-545284-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-chiledhood-eckspeeriienses/545284.rss">My chiledhood eckspeeriienses</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>My chiledhood eckspeeriienses</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@The_Un-Named The Un-Named]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/the_un-named">@The_Un-Named</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>wat a fookin dikhed! Lol! A+ post.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-chiledhood-eckspeeriienses/545284/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-chiledhood-eckspeeriienses/545284/2</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2014 20:33:43 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-545284-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-chiledhood-eckspeeriienses/545284.rss">My chiledhood eckspeeriienses</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>My chiledhood eckspeeriienses</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Fat_Cookies Fat Cookies]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/fat_cookies">@Fat_Cookies</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>When I was 12 I had my first sexual experience. At the time, I lived in a little suburb outside of Cleveland and anyway, the girl next door and I were really good friends. Our parents were both gone for the day and she was over playing Transformers with me. So anyway, we kinda got… Bored I guess? And we started playing truth or dare, which turned into ‘you show me yours, I’ll show you mine". So anyway there I Was, 12 years old, heart pounding, blood rushing in my ears, and the chick (who was a year older than me actually) takes off her panties and hikes her little skirt up. so What did I do, you ask? I whistled for a cab, and when it came near, the license plate said “fresh” and there were dice in the mirror. If anything I could say that this cab was rare, but I thought “naw forget it, yo home to bel-air!” I pulled up to the house about seven or eight and I yelled to the cabbie “yo homes smell ya later!” Looked at my kingdom, I was finally there. To settle my throne as the prince of bel-air.</p>
<p>After arriving in bel-air I took a few minutes to contemplate how my new life will turn out and then this whiff of pizza smothered me - it tickled and teased my appetite a little so I thought I might order one myself. I picked up the phone, it arrived rather fast. It was pepperoni; I loved it.</p>
<p>I am very secure about my pizza. You have obviously never tasted pizza if you think mine look bad, and that is very sad for you. You should get a pizza right away so you will have some knowledge of pizza and not sound like a fool when you speak. Again, I would ask you to prove your own pizza making skills if you think you are capable of judging others so harshly. But that would require something well beyond your capabilities. You really should try pizza, it is quite delicious and you won’t sound so stupid when you comment. That is incredibly important considering I am a heron. I have a long neck and I pick fish out of the water with my beak. If you don’t repost this comment on 10 other pages, I will fly into your kitchen tonight and make a mess of your pots and pans.</p>
<p>And after you have commented/reposted you should wipe that smug smirk off your face because I have this feeling that you are going to comment “meow”, ok for one, “meow” is literally my catphrase (see what i did there?) whenever someone says “meow” on fb or something, i respond “HEY! that’s MY catphrase” thing 2… i was so depressed at one point in my life that i tried to put myself into a coma by drinking too much water. it involved me watching too much robot chicken, and drinking from 3 full big glasses of water over and over without hardly stopping. i dont think it worked though because i urinated too much. good source of water though! ;D</p>
<p>I prefer vodka to water, but I wouldn’t drink 3 full big glases of vodka because drunk me gets into fights… This one time I was in the tyne and wear pub and this rite ol geezer came up to me n smacked his can of special brew ova. i swear it was an accident and then he was like: “Wot the fok did ye just say 2 me m8? i dropped out of newcastle primary skool im the sickest bloke ull ever meet &amp; ive nicked ova 300 chocolate globbernaughts frum tha corner shop. im trained in street fitin’ &amp; im the strongest foker in tha entire newcastle gym. yer nothin to me but a cheeky lil bellend w/ a fit mum &amp; fakebling. ill waste u and smash a fokin bottle oer yer head bruv, i swer. ya think u can fokin run ya gabber at me whilst sittin on yer arse behind a lil screen? think again wanka. im callin me homeboys rite now preparin for a proper scrap. A roomble thatll make ur nan sore jus hearin about it. yer a waste bruv. me crew be all over tha place &amp; ill beat ya to a proper fokin pulp with me fists wanka. if i aint satisfied w/ that ill borrow me m8s cricket paddle &amp; see if that gets u the fok out o’ newcastle ya daft kunt. if ye had seen this bloody fokin mess commin ye might a’ kept ya gabber from runnin. but it seems yea stupid lil twat, innit? ima shite fury &amp; ull drown in it m8. ur ina proper mess knob.”</p>
<p>so i was like “u are 1 fucking cheeky kunt mate i swear i am goin 2 wreck u i swear on my mums life and i no u are scared lil bitch gettin your mates to send me messages saying dont meet up coz u r sum big bastard with muscles lol fuckin sad mate really sad jus shows what a scared lil gay boy u are and whats all this crap ur mates sendin me about sum bodybuildin website that 1 of your faverite places to look at men u lil fuckin gay boy fone me if u got da balls cheeky prick see if u can step up lil queer” and smacked him till he no see."</p>
<p>then this cheeky merican cunt m9 hit me out of nowhere and told me: “What the fuck did you just fucking say about me, you little bitch? I’ll have you know I graduated top of my class in the Navy Seals, and I’ve been involved in numerous secret raids on Al-Quaeda, and I have over 300 confirmed kills. I am trained in gorilla warfare and I’m the top sniper in the entire US armed forces. You are nothing to me but just another target. I will wipe you the fuck out with precision the likes of which has never been seen before on this Earth, mark my fucking words. You think you can get away with saying that shit to me over the Internet? Think again, fucker. As we speak I am contacting my secret network of spies across the USA and your IP is being traced right now so you better prepare for the storm, maggot. The storm that wipes out the pathetic little thing you call your life. You’re fucking dead, kid. I can be anywhere, anytime, and I can kill you in over seven hundred ways, and that’s just with my bare hands. Not only am I extensively trained in unarmed combat, but I have access to the entire arsenal of the United States Marine Corps and I will use it to its full extent to wipe your miserable ass off the face of the continent, you little shit. If only you could have known what unholy retribution your little “clever” comment was about to bring down upon you, maybe you would have held your fucking tongue. But you couldn’t, you didn’t, and now you’re paying the price, you goddamn idiot. I will shit fury all over you and you will drown in it. You’re fucking dead, kiddo.”</p>
<p>wat a fookin dikhed</p>
<p>Anyways I went home and guys, you’ll never believe what just happened no less than 999999 minutes ago. so my sister and her boyfriend came home while i was watching TV and they went into the kitchen to get some drinks. while in the kitchen they were doing their whole lovey dovey thing and kissing and playing grab-ass and what not, and it was unappealing to me, so i went up to my room. a few minutes later, i heard them enter into my sister’s room and then some rustling occurred. i thought nothing of it, they were probably just making out again on her bed. then i heard her scream and i got worried so i ran over to her room, and opened the door, got on the floor, everybody walk the dinosaur! open to door, get on the floor, everybody walk the dinosaur! BOOM BOOM ACKLAKKALAKKA BOOM BOOM BOOM ACKLAKKALAKKA BOOM!</p>
<p>after the dinosaurs dignity was violated, my nan told me that I is 14 years old, and I have boobs. One day I was asleep in my bed, than I wolk up to a very surprising treat, I had boobs. I felt very astonished. Why would the good lawrd jebus give poor old Zurela boobs? My first instinct was to call my boyfriend and tell him, so I did. I knew we would abuse my love for my “Chesticles” but I didn’t mind. So later on in the day he came over, and he was astonished too. My mother had not yet noticed, but my father had to check for breast cancer, thankfully he did, he checked for 7 and a half hours and found nothing, he said he needs to check everyday because my mom had it once and he didn’t want to loose me like he lost my mom, cause she died. Anyways so my Boyfriend came over and he checked too, apparently Breast cancer is a very serious disease, but I didn’t tell him about dada because I know he just wanted to be sure because he loved me. So after about a hour or two of that we played WoW and we lvled up, he told me I gave him an “erevecton” you know, that thing when it forces you outta the house, but I just ignored the comment because I am not his landlord, I just think he was being silly. He went home, and dad told me the power of boobs, and he told be if I have to be under heavy surveillance in the shower because if I don’t scrub my "boobs’ enough a demon will come out and kill us all. This is how mom died, so he says. So I washed this thoroughly and he made sure they are clean Enough. I really love how my boobs made everyone care about me more, and ladies I had no idea the upkeep of these things, so if there is any more tips I need, please tell me!</p>
<p>I stepped out the shower and went out outside because  I had to take care of my uncle’s dog for a while. He was a big Golden Retriever and his name was Sasu. After about 3 days, I was extremely turned on and without a boyfriend, so this dog in my pussy seemed like a pretty good idea. One day, I decided to go for a walk and take the dog with me. I was conveniently wearing a skirt and once we reached a pretty secluded street, I pulled up my skirt and got on all fours. At first the dog just sniffed my butt around but once he got the idea, he got on top of me and started humping my butt through my panties. He kept banging against my clit and my juices were flowing to pretty much everywhere. I didn’t let him inside me yet because I was too afraid. I mean, think about it. That’s pretty fucking gross. But anyways. Whenever I got back home, I sat on the front porch. My uncle had come back and was ready to pick up the dog but he was inside talking to my sister. My uncle told me to stay outside with Sasu for a while, so I did. While we were out there, I was sitting on a bench with my legs spread open and Sasu kept trying to stick his nose in my crotch. Usually, I’d push his face away and close my legs, but I was extremely wet and was dripping everywhere. So I let Sasu lick it up. Since I had never been eaten out before, I really didn’t know that what I was doing was sexual in the least, but I realized that it felt really good and was only making me wetter. Even after I came Sasu was still licking it all up and the front of my skirt was soaked in a combination of my pussy juice and Sasu’s saliva. Once I had to go back inside, I just twisted my skirt to the side and went to my room to change.</p>
<p>i came out the room and still felt horny so i switched on the tv looking for something good and this really interesting report came up, it was as follows:</p>
<p>when Jewish population remains under 5,000 of any given country they will be regarded as a peace-loving minority and not as a threat to anyone: Estonia – 1,800 Jews Bulgaria – 2,300 Jews Costa Rica – 2,400 Jews Peru – 2,800 Jews Slovakia – 3,000 Jews Kazakhstan – 4,100 Jews</p>
<p>At 5,000 to 10,000 they begin to separate from other ethnic minorities and disaffected groups: Morocco – 5,200 Jews Greece – 5,300 Jews Denmark – 7,000 Jews Austria – 8,100 Jews Latvia – OVER 9000 JEWS</p>
<p>From 10,000 on they exercise an inordinate influence in proportion to their percentage of the population.They will push for the introduction of kosher (clean by Jewish standards) food, thereby securing food preparation jobs for Jews. They will increase pressure on supermarket chains to feature it on their shelves - along with threats for failure to comply. At this point, they will work to get the ruling government to allow them to rule themselves under Pentateuch, the Hebrew Law. Panama – 10,000 Jews Switzerland – 14,000 Jews Turkey – 17,000 Jews Poland – 25,000 Jews Italy – 30,000 Jews</p>
<p>When Jews reach over 50,000 of the population, they will bail out funds managers as a means of complaint about their conditions (Ben Bernanke – Fed chairman) . Any non-Jewish action that offends Judaism will result in stock fluctuations and foreclosures (United States – Housing market). Belgium – 51,000 Jews Mexico – 53,000 Jews Belarus – 72,000 Jews</p>
<p>After reaching 100,000 expect hair-trigger market crashes, Neo-Nazi group formations, sporadic killings and synagogue burning: Australia – 120,000 Jews Ukraine – 142,000 Jews</p>
<p>At 200,000 you will find widespread hatred of Jews, chronic terror attacks and ongoing anti-Jew warfare: Germany – 220,000 Jews Argentina – 250,000 Jews United Kingdom – 350,000 Jews Canada – 390,000 Jews</p>
<p>From 500,000 you may expect unfettered persecution by non-believers and other religions, sporadic establishments of Holocaust museums, use of Pentateuch as a weapon and loan interest, the tax placed on Gentiles: France – 600,000 Jews Russia – 800,000 Jews</p>
<p>3,000,000+ will usher in the establishment of a permanent Jewish state-- Hollywood-- where there’s supposed to be peace because everybody is a Jew: Israel – 5,600,000 Jews United States – 6,150,000 Jews</p>
<p>thanks for reading</p>
<p>rep++</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-chiledhood-eckspeeriienses/545284/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-chiledhood-eckspeeriienses/545284/1</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2014 20:30:46 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-545284-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-chiledhood-eckspeeriienses/545284.rss">My chiledhood eckspeeriienses</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
