<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Opinions on mechanics</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/opinions-on-mechanics/434300</link>
    <description>Hi guys, I need opinions on some mechanics that I have in mind.


Imagine an online role playing game, played in first person. A game, where there are rooms (or servers), hosted by players. Those rooms can take from 2 to 64 players. In that game, there is a smart human-like alien race trying to eliminate all humans and conquer the earth. The earth, as a reaction has formed a United Army with soldiers from many different nations.


The players take the role of one of those soldiers. All aliens in the game are computer-controlled. Meaning that this will be an online game where people have to team up to fight against aliens (controlled by computers).


There will basically be no PVP at all. When entering one of those rooms (or servers), you will not be brought straight in the action. You will be taken to a city that is safe (alien-free). There you can start a talk with other people, buy/sell goods, train your skills,... But you are one step away from entering the battlefield and fighting for your planet.


This is what I have in mind. I need opinions on these mechanics, because I would like a game like this, but I don&#39;t know if other people would too.
And this would be a very time consuming project so I don&#39;t want to waste time on something that will not be played in the end.


Why do I let people host servers, simple, because I don&#39;t have the resources to host massive servers myself. So I let the players host small servers. That is also the cause of a brain cracking problem. Since this is a role playing game, player stats are saved in a database. And servers hosted on 3rd party computers access my database containing info about all players in order to be able to read and save stats.


By letting players host servers, I enable a lot of security risks.



Here are my 2 solutions, but I don&#39;t know how secure they actually are:


I&#39;m thinking of letting the master server (hosted by me) send data about how to access the database to those servers once they get started and are verified by the master server as being the latest (and being a legit) version (through an MD5 check sum).
This way, they would not be able to decompile the server and fetch info about the database.


Then there is memory editing stuff in the server by the hosters which would eventually result in manipulated stats being saved to the database. I will solve that problem by using an anti-cheat method I developed for a flash game.


Also, only verified servers get added to the list of servers in the master server. This would eliminate all modified and outdated servers.

Anyhow, that&#39;s about it. What do you guys think? Would you play something like this? Do you know any games similar to this?


[b][size=20pt]UPDATE:[/size][/b]


[b]Stormynature from gamedev.net responded to my topic with:[/b]

[i][font=trebuchet ms]Okay what I have from this is you are simply at an idea stage. You don&#39;t necessarily go into that much detail or specifics. For example is each room a literal clone of another room i.e. the same city or does each room represent a different city on the world and the data you collect back shows the overall success of the war etc. Do you plan to have resources transferrable through different rooms i.e. war supplies in excess at one room could be smuggled traded to another room to help with their battle. I guess what I am looking for is more detail as to how your game is designed in terms of the game itself not just the physical setup.[/font][/i]

[b]I responded to him with:[/b]

[i][font=trebuchet ms]
Thank you for your response. I&#39;ll go into more detail.


In this game, there will be 2 - 3 cities, for the first playable version.


Meaning that when hosting a server or room for the game, the hoster has to choose which city it wants to host for.
Then, when a player wants to play a game, it has to choose a room/server with the player&#39;s preferred city.


Simply put, there will be a bunch of servers/rooms and every one of them will be hosting for one of the available cities.


Why am I saying hosting FOR a city? Because those rooms/servers are part of something bigger. All crucial data regarding player stats, money, items,... will be calculated by those rooms/servers, but eventually saved to a database managed by me. Whenever a player logs into a room/server (hosted by someone that is not me), that server will fetch that particular player&#39;s data (his items, money, stats,...) from the global game database (managed by me).


So yes, you can transfer goods from one room to another. [/font][/i]</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 25 Mar 2012 03:32:52 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Game Development</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/opinions-on-mechanics/434300.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Opinions on mechanics</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@MistaBigBoss MistaBigBoss]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/mistabigboss">@MistaBigBoss</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“veer, post:2, topic:434300”]For someone who is prematurely overplanning you sure do a poor job of it. Why would an MD5 sum prevent the server from serving up falsified stats and compromising the integrity of your master databases?[/quote]To make the servers provide compromised data you have two options:</p>
<p>Reverse-engineering and memory editing.</p>
<p>Reverse-engineering can be fought with that MD5 sum. On initialization, just before the server has started, where it’s in a state that it’s completely identical on any computer, it will generate a MD5 sum of its total size in bytes. Every time a server tries to save stats to the master database, it will have to contact the master server for information on how to access the master database. The master server will provide a particular server with that database information IF that server has a legit checksum. If that server is verified, it will receive the database information from the master server, save the stats, close the connection and forget that information. Every time it wants to submit stats, it will have to ask the master server, I don’t want my db information to be saved in the memory of a 3rd party computer for more than 10 seconds. That database information will be encrypted when sent over to a server. Only the server will be able to decrypt that information and it can only do that if it gets it in the first place.</p>
<p>Of course, this will not be enough but this is where my limit is. Hackers could for instance sniff that db info, decrypt it through examining a server and then fuck up my db, but I’ll have to crack my brain over that problem later.</p>
<p>Then we have memory editing. Changing values (money, stats,…) in-game with e.g. cheat engine (memory editing software) will not be possible because there will always be control values running in the background (this is an anti-cheat method I designed). The only way to bypass this is by first being able to go faster than my server can think, this can be achieved by debugging and using break points. Then by finding a random generated number that is used to encrypt values like money and stats into new values that are being used as control values. And last but not least, being able to figure out my anti-cheat system, making your own control values with that number you found earlier, and then being able to manipulate the current control values with your new control values that correspond to your modified values (money, stats,…) before the server manages to run another check to see if the money and stats flowing around are legit.</p>
<p>My job is to make it as secure as possible, without using to much processing power. If it comes to a point where my game is being compromised by hackers, I would probably have made enough cash to buy dedicated servers and eliminate ALL security risks.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/opinions-on-mechanics/434300/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/opinions-on-mechanics/434300/3</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 25 Mar 2012 03:32:52 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-434300-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/opinions-on-mechanics/434300.rss">Opinions on mechanics</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Opinions on mechanics</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@slavemaster veer]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/slavemaster">@slavemaster</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>For someone who is prematurely overplanning you sure do a poor job of it. Why would an MD5 sum prevent the server from serving up falsified stats and compromising the integrity of your master databases?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/opinions-on-mechanics/434300/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/opinions-on-mechanics/434300/2</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 24 Mar 2012 23:34:08 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-434300-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/opinions-on-mechanics/434300.rss">Opinions on mechanics</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Opinions on mechanics</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@MistaBigBoss MistaBigBoss]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/mistabigboss">@MistaBigBoss</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Hi guys, I need opinions on some mechanics that I have in mind.</p>
<p>Imagine an online role playing game, played in first person. A game, where there are rooms (or servers), hosted by players. Those rooms can take from 2 to 64 players. In that game, there is a smart human-like alien race trying to eliminate all humans and conquer the earth. The earth, as a reaction has formed a United Army with soldiers from many different nations.</p>
<p>The players take the role of one of those soldiers. All aliens in the game are computer-controlled. Meaning that this will be an online game where people have to team up to fight against aliens (controlled by computers).</p>
<p>There will basically be no PVP at all. When entering one of those rooms (or servers), you will not be brought straight in the action. You will be taken to a city that is safe (alien-free). There you can start a talk with other people, buy/sell goods, train your skills,… But you are one step away from entering the battlefield and fighting for your planet.</p>
<p>This is what I have in mind. I need opinions on these mechanics, because I would like a game like this, but I don’t know if other people would too.<br>
And this would be a very time consuming project so I don’t want to waste time on something that will not be played in the end.</p>
<p>Why do I let people host servers, simple, because I don’t have the resources to host massive servers myself. So I let the players host small servers. That is also the cause of a brain cracking problem. Since this is a role playing game, player stats are saved in a database. And servers hosted on 3rd party computers access my database containing info about all players in order to be able to read and save stats.</p>
<p>By letting players host servers, I enable a lot of security risks.</p>
<p>Here are my 2 solutions, but I don’t know how secure they actually are:</p>
<p>I’m thinking of letting the master server (hosted by me) send data about how to access the database to those servers once they get started and are verified by the master server as being the latest (and being a legit) version (through an MD5 check sum).<br>
This way, they would not be able to decompile the server and fetch info about the database.</p>
<p>Then there is memory editing stuff in the server by the hosters which would eventually result in manipulated stats being saved to the database. I will solve that problem by using an anti-cheat method I developed for a flash game.</p>
<p>Also, only verified servers get added to the list of servers in the master server. This would eliminate all modified and outdated servers.</p>
<p>Anyhow, that’s about it. What do you guys think? Would you play something like this? Do you know any games similar to this?</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">[size=20pt]UPDATE:[/size]</span></p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Stormynature from <a href="http://gamedev.net" rel="nofollow noopener">gamedev.net</a> responded to my topic with:</span></p>
<p><span class="bbcode-i">[font=trebuchet ms]Okay what I have from this is you are simply at an idea stage. You don’t necessarily go into that much detail or specifics. For example is each room a literal clone of another room i.e. the same city or does each room represent a different city on the world and the data you collect back shows the overall success of the war etc. Do you plan to have resources transferrable through different rooms i.e. war supplies in excess at one room could be smuggled traded to another room to help with their battle. I guess what I am looking for is more detail as to how your game is designed in terms of the game itself not just the physical setup.[/font]</span></p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">I responded to him with:</span></p>
<p>[i][font=trebuchet ms]<br>
Thank you for your response. I’ll go into more detail.</p>
<p>In this game, there will be 2 - 3 cities, for the first playable version.</p>
<p>Meaning that when hosting a server or room for the game, the hoster has to choose which city it wants to host for.<br>
Then, when a player wants to play a game, it has to choose a room/server with the player’s preferred city.</p>
<p>Simply put, there will be a bunch of servers/rooms and every one of them will be hosting for one of the available cities.</p>
<p>Why am I saying hosting FOR a city? Because those rooms/servers are part of something bigger. All crucial data regarding player stats, money, items,… will be calculated by those rooms/servers, but eventually saved to a database managed by me. Whenever a player logs into a room/server (hosted by someone that is not me), that server will fetch that particular player’s data (his items, money, stats,…) from the global game database (managed by me).</p>
<p>So yes, you can transfer goods from one room to another. [/font][/i]</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/opinions-on-mechanics/434300/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/opinions-on-mechanics/434300/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 26 Feb 2012 14:55:20 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-434300-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/opinions-on-mechanics/434300.rss">Opinions on mechanics</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
