<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Offering help with programming</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/offering-help-with-programming/259080</link>
    <description>I&#39;m doing an education which has a part of java programming. Now I&#39;d like to practice my java programming and thought someone here might need my help.

I&#39;m not new to programming private servers of runescape, I did it a few years back and was having my own private server. It was actually a success but I was running on a crap pc and then it&#39;s no wonder that i had lots of lag.

I&#39;m searching for someone which already has a server running because I won&#39;t help with hamachi or no-ip crap. I&#39;m willing to code difficult things, but not things like placing a thousand npc&#39;s which is very easy and just a lot of work.

I&#39;ve posted before and it got locked. Maybe because I was confused with someone who wants to steal files... 
To clear that up, I don&#39;t need any of your private server files. But it would be useful to know what source u used.

So... again, anyone interested?[br][br][size=1]Posted on: January 29, 2009, 04:59:38 am[/size][hr]ah, shiit.. moving to the right section, sorry, lock it :rolleyes:</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2009 10:48:56 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/offering-help-with-programming/259080.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Offering help with programming</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@b0unty b0unty]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/b0unty">@b0unty</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I’m doing an education which has a part of java programming. Now I’d like to practice my java programming and thought someone here might need my help.</p>
<p>I’m not new to programming private servers of runescape, I did it a few years back and was having my own private server. It was actually a success but I was running on a crap pc and then it’s no wonder that i had lots of lag.</p>
<p>I’m searching for someone which already has a server running because I won’t help with hamachi or no-ip crap. I’m willing to code difficult things, but not things like placing a thousand npc’s which is very easy and just a lot of work.</p>
<p>I’ve posted before and it got locked. Maybe because I was confused with someone who wants to steal files…<br>
To clear that up, I don’t need any of your private server files. But it would be useful to know what source u used.</p>
<p>So… again, anyone interested?[br][br][size=1]Posted on: January 29, 2009, 04:59:38 am[/size][hr]ah, shiit… moving to the right section, sorry, lock it :rolleyes:</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/offering-help-with-programming/259080/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/offering-help-with-programming/259080/1</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2009 10:48:56 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-259080-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/offering-help-with-programming/259080.rss">Offering help with programming</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
