<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Refreshing Appearences</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/refreshing-appearences/171526</link>
    <description>Yeah yeah yeah &quot;YOU SUCK AT CODING&quot;... No....

I&#39;ve tried everything I can think of. I cannot seem to get my server to auto refresh someone some like in my members area when they walk in they get teled out about 2 squares away from the entrance. It dose not show other pwople that. It shows them right at the entrance. When they do it again it makes them look like they are inside the members castle. Then they get far enough and walk through walls. but once you tele away or log out and in then it refreshes them.


I have added everything I can think of.... I added update apearance there and to boolean process... I even made a void with that inside of it and added the void to boolean process.

I do not know what to do. If anyone could help me out that would be good.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 07 Jan 2008 00:50:59 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/refreshing-appearences/171526.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Refreshing Appearences</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@jungledude jungledude]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/jungledude">@jungledude</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Yeah yeah yeah “YOU SUCK AT CODING”… No…</p>
<p>I’ve tried everything I can think of. I cannot seem to get my server to auto refresh someone some like in my members area when they walk in they get teled out about 2 squares away from the entrance. It dose not show other pwople that. It shows them right at the entrance. When they do it again it makes them look like they are inside the members castle. Then they get far enough and walk through walls. but once you tele away or log out and in then it refreshes them.</p>
<p>I have added everything I can think of… I added update apearance there and to boolean process… I even made a void with that inside of it and added the void to boolean process.</p>
<p>I do not know what to do. If anyone could help me out that would be good.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/refreshing-appearences/171526/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/refreshing-appearences/171526/1</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 07 Jan 2008 00:50:59 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-171526-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/refreshing-appearences/171526.rss">Refreshing Appearences</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
