<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>RPGMVX School Lesson 1: Design Documents</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rpgmvx-school-lesson-1-design-documents/401931</link>
    <description>[b]Note: Please do not flame this topic it is here upon request. As much as this is not a RPG Maker site, I have gotten 5 pm&#39;s asking me to make tutorials ever since I posted RPG Maker VX online engine last night. If you have nothing good to say, dont say anything. Just go on your way to another topic please. I am asking nicely and I have not once disrespected anybody else so I am asking please respect me.[/b]

[b]Lesson 1[/b]: Design Documents

Welcome to RPG Maker VX School. Here you will learn how to create professional, quiality games using RPG Maker VX, Ruby, and RGSS2.
Eventually we will move onto Online games. In RPG Maker XP this was impossible, but with RPGMVX and the new
scripting language RGSS2 this is very simple to do. In order to be able to follow these lessons you will 
have to have the full version of RPG Maker VX which you can download here free of charge: http://up.ht/isq5q9

[b]Chapter 1[/b]: The Beginning

Design Documents ,or &quot;The Double D&#39;s&quot; as most programmers call it, is one of the most important parts of creating
a successful game. What a design document is, is a document that is basically the outline of your entire
game. This includes credits, sprites, music, quests, and all the basics of a typical RPG. Most DD&#39;s take weeks
or even months to write. Usually DD&#39;s change over time as the developers work on the game. Adding or taking 
away as they please.

[b]Practice 1-1: Complete the Practice[/b]

Write a short Design Document consisting of:

1. Title of the game (This usually comes to you last)
2. Credits (Mappers, Composers, Scripters ect...)
3. Quest Name
4. Quest Layout (Who to talk to, what to do, and a reward at the end.)

Here is an example of one that I made:

[b]1. Rune Lords
2. GML Programmer (All)
3. Unstable Foundations
4. Description: [/b]

Welcome to Rune Lords! Sir Vant, a White Knight, needs your help: he has found a dragon underneath Lumbridge! Unfortunately, he has not had time to prepare for it, and he needs your help!

[b]Difficulty:[/b] Novice

[b]Length:[/b] Short

[b]Quest Requirements:[/b] None

[b]Skill/Other Requirements:[/b] None

[b]Items Needed to Complete Quest:[/b] None

[b]Items Acquired During Quest:[/b] Bronze platebody, Bronze sword, Bronze sq shield, Drugged meat.

[b]Reward:[/b] Level up to 4, and 150gp

[b]Start Point:[/b] You will start this quest after creating a new Rune Lords account.

[b]To Start:[/b] Speak to Sir Vant.

[b]Instructions:[/b]
Walk north after creating your character and speak to Sir Vant by using spacebar on him. 
A chat box will appear. Click the spacebar to continue. Afterwards, you will see a cutescene 
where a fearsome dragon appears and kills Sir Vant&#39;s squire. A goblin sneaks in while this is going on, and starts stealing the items in Sir Vant&#39;s bag. Now talk again to Sir Vant and he will ask you to deal with the goblin for him. Take the bronze armor that the squire dropped when he was killed by pressing spacebar or enter while standing next to it. Press the Esc key to go into the player menu. Select equip and equip the newly aquired items. Then click spacebar on the goblin to attack it. When it&#39;s dead, talk again to Sir Vant to discover his plan to kill the dragon. Click space on Sir Vant&#39;s bag, which is right next to him, to retrieve a piece of Drugged meat. Next to the bag, once you have the meat click on the wooden gate to enter it. Run to the north by holding shift and then go west. You will find yourself in the section with the wooden pillars. 
Once there another cutscene will happen in which you place the meat in the dragons food bowel. Now run back, go through the gate again, and speak to Sir Vant. He will ask you if you put the meat in the bowl, select &quot;Yes I&#39;ve done it&quot;. You will see a cutescene where the dragon eats the meat and falls asleep. Now talk to Sir Vant again. Search Sir Vant&#39;s bag to find the supplies you will need to complete his plan. You will see a cutscene of you catching the wooden pillars on fire and the roof caves killing the dragon. After the dragon is dead, you will see a new person, Roddeck. Talk to him. Roddeck will thank you and give you 150gp. Sir Vant will want his Squire&#39;s possessions back. Talk to him and he will take them. He will thank you and you will level up to level 4. Next he will tell you to walk north and then east til you find a ladder. Climb the ladder and escape to Lumbridge. You are now level 4 and have 150gp.
Congratulations! Tutorial Completed! 

This looks about right. We’ve got a clear idea of what will happen from beginning to end.  
It can be tempting to think that, “Oh, I’ve got a pretty good idea of what to do in my head, so no worries!” However, when it comes to actually creating the story, ideas get mixed up and even forgotten. To keep things fresh, it’s best to record all your ideas on paper for future reference.

Additionally, if you can come up with ideas for items, magic, names and traits of monsters, etc., it will be easier to create a solid game. Finally, write down any other ideas you may have, even if they are not directly related to the story. They can be a source of creativity and inspiration later on. Congratulations on completing Lesson 1! In Lesson 2, we will get our hands dirty working with RPG Maker.

[b]There will be a new tutorial every 3 days.[/b]</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 02 Jul 2011 21:51:29 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>General Discussion</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rpgmvx-school-lesson-1-design-documents/401931.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>RPGMVX School Lesson 1: Design Documents</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@GML_Programmer GML Programmer]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/gml_programmer">@GML_Programmer</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>The graphics are better but XP does not support online, and the scripting language is out dated. The new RGSS2 language is much more efficient and powerful. Graphics are not everything and besides I can always import my own graphics.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rpgmvx-school-lesson-1-design-documents/401931/9">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rpgmvx-school-lesson-1-design-documents/401931/9</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 02 Jul 2011 21:51:29 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-401931-9</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rpgmvx-school-lesson-1-design-documents/401931.rss">RPGMVX School Lesson 1: Design Documents</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>RPGMVX School Lesson 1: Design Documents</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@someone2 someone2]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/someone2">@someone2</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>If you’re gonna use a stupid maker program, use RPG Maker XP, not VX. XP has better 2D graphics.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rpgmvx-school-lesson-1-design-documents/401931/8">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rpgmvx-school-lesson-1-design-documents/401931/8</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 02 Jul 2011 17:24:17 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-401931-8</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rpgmvx-school-lesson-1-design-documents/401931.rss">RPGMVX School Lesson 1: Design Documents</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>RPGMVX School Lesson 1: Design Documents</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@MistaBigBoss MistaBigBoss]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/mistabigboss">@MistaBigBoss</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“GML Programmer, post:6, topic:401931”][quote author=I Vain I link=topic=498984.msg3648976#msg3648976 date=1309584648]<br>
The general programming rules say no tutorials.<br>
[/quote]So I guess I chose the right place lol[/quote]I’m not going to make this but I am looking forward to reading the tutorials, nice job.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rpgmvx-school-lesson-1-design-documents/401931/7">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rpgmvx-school-lesson-1-design-documents/401931/7</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 02 Jul 2011 11:38:20 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-401931-7</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rpgmvx-school-lesson-1-design-documents/401931.rss">RPGMVX School Lesson 1: Design Documents</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>RPGMVX School Lesson 1: Design Documents</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@GML_Programmer GML Programmer]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/gml_programmer">@GML_Programmer</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“I Vain I”]The general programming rules say no tutorials.[/quote]So I guess I chose the right place lol</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rpgmvx-school-lesson-1-design-documents/401931/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rpgmvx-school-lesson-1-design-documents/401931/6</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 02 Jul 2011 05:39:22 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-401931-6</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rpgmvx-school-lesson-1-design-documents/401931.rss">RPGMVX School Lesson 1: Design Documents</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>RPGMVX School Lesson 1: Design Documents</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@GML_Programmer GML Programmer]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/gml_programmer">@GML_Programmer</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“marcbob, post:4, topic:401931”]General programming?[/quote]Ok Ill move it there and tell a staff to delete this one<br>
Edit: Never mind no tuts allowed there.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rpgmvx-school-lesson-1-design-documents/401931/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rpgmvx-school-lesson-1-design-documents/401931/5</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 02 Jul 2011 05:30:21 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-401931-5</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rpgmvx-school-lesson-1-design-documents/401931.rss">RPGMVX School Lesson 1: Design Documents</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>RPGMVX School Lesson 1: Design Documents</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@marcbob marcbob]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/marcbob">@marcbob</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>General programming?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rpgmvx-school-lesson-1-design-documents/401931/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rpgmvx-school-lesson-1-design-documents/401931/4</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 02 Jul 2011 05:28:07 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-401931-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rpgmvx-school-lesson-1-design-documents/401931.rss">RPGMVX School Lesson 1: Design Documents</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>RPGMVX School Lesson 1: Design Documents</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@GML_Programmer GML Programmer]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/gml_programmer">@GML_Programmer</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“Slave Scyth, post:2, topic:401931”]I like the effort, but I don’t think General Discussion could possibly be the right section for this.[/quote]Thanks, I wasn’t very sure where to put this. General was the only place I could think of.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rpgmvx-school-lesson-1-design-documents/401931/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rpgmvx-school-lesson-1-design-documents/401931/3</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 02 Jul 2011 05:20:07 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-401931-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rpgmvx-school-lesson-1-design-documents/401931.rss">RPGMVX School Lesson 1: Design Documents</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>RPGMVX School Lesson 1: Design Documents</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Slave_Scyth Slave Scyth]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/slave_scyth">@Slave_Scyth</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I like the effort, but I don’t think General Discussion could possibly be the right section for this.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rpgmvx-school-lesson-1-design-documents/401931/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rpgmvx-school-lesson-1-design-documents/401931/2</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 02 Jul 2011 05:17:57 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-401931-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rpgmvx-school-lesson-1-design-documents/401931.rss">RPGMVX School Lesson 1: Design Documents</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>RPGMVX School Lesson 1: Design Documents</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@GML_Programmer GML Programmer]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/gml_programmer">@GML_Programmer</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p><span class="bbcode-b">Note: Please do not flame this topic it is here upon request. As much as this is not a RPG Maker site, I have gotten 5 pm’s asking me to make tutorials ever since I posted RPG Maker VX online engine last night. If you have nothing good to say, dont say anything. Just go on your way to another topic please. I am asking nicely and I have not once disrespected anybody else so I am asking please respect me.</span></p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Lesson 1</span>: Design Documents</p>
<p>Welcome to RPG Maker VX School. Here you will learn how to create professional, quiality games using RPG Maker VX, Ruby, and RGSS2.<br>
Eventually we will move onto Online games. In RPG Maker XP this was impossible, but with RPGMVX and the new<br>
scripting language RGSS2 this is very simple to do. In order to be able to follow these lessons you will<br>
have to have the full version of RPG Maker VX which you can download here free of charge: <a href="http://up.ht/isq5q9" rel="nofollow noopener">http://up.ht/isq5q9</a></p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Chapter 1</span>: The Beginning</p>
<p>Design Documents ,or “The Double D’s” as most programmers call it, is one of the most important parts of creating<br>
a successful game. What a design document is, is a document that is basically the outline of your entire<br>
game. This includes credits, sprites, music, quests, and all the basics of a typical RPG. Most DD’s take weeks<br>
or even months to write. Usually DD’s change over time as the developers work on the game. Adding or taking<br>
away as they please.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Practice 1-1: Complete the Practice</span></p>
<p>Write a short Design Document consisting of:</p>
<ol>
<li>Title of the game (This usually comes to you last)</li>
<li>Credits (Mappers, Composers, Scripters ect…)</li>
<li>Quest Name</li>
<li>Quest Layout (Who to talk to, what to do, and a reward at the end.)</li>
</ol>
<p>Here is an example of one that I made:</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">1. Rune Lords<br>
2. GML Programmer (All)<br>
3. Unstable Foundations<br>
4. Description: </span></p>
<p>Welcome to Rune Lords! Sir Vant, a White Knight, needs your help: he has found a dragon underneath Lumbridge! Unfortunately, he has not had time to prepare for it, and he needs your help!</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Difficulty:</span> Novice</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Length:</span> Short</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Quest Requirements:</span> None</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Skill/Other Requirements:</span> None</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Items Needed to Complete Quest:</span> None</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Items Acquired During Quest:</span> Bronze platebody, Bronze sword, Bronze sq shield, Drugged meat.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Reward:</span> Level up to 4, and 150gp</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Start Point:</span> You will start this quest after creating a new Rune Lords account.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">To Start:</span> Speak to Sir Vant.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Instructions:</span><br>
Walk north after creating your character and speak to Sir Vant by using spacebar on him.<br>
A chat box will appear. Click the spacebar to continue. Afterwards, you will see a cutescene<br>
where a fearsome dragon appears and kills Sir Vant’s squire. A goblin sneaks in while this is going on, and starts stealing the items in Sir Vant’s bag. Now talk again to Sir Vant and he will ask you to deal with the goblin for him. Take the bronze armor that the squire dropped when he was killed by pressing spacebar or enter while standing next to it. Press the Esc key to go into the player menu. Select equip and equip the newly aquired items. Then click spacebar on the goblin to attack it. When it’s dead, talk again to Sir Vant to discover his plan to kill the dragon. Click space on Sir Vant’s bag, which is right next to him, to retrieve a piece of Drugged meat. Next to the bag, once you have the meat click on the wooden gate to enter it. Run to the north by holding shift and then go west. You will find yourself in the section with the wooden pillars.<br>
Once there another cutscene will happen in which you place the meat in the dragons food bowel. Now run back, go through the gate again, and speak to Sir Vant. He will ask you if you put the meat in the bowl, select “Yes I’ve done it”. You will see a cutescene where the dragon eats the meat and falls asleep. Now talk to Sir Vant again. Search Sir Vant’s bag to find the supplies you will need to complete his plan. You will see a cutscene of you catching the wooden pillars on fire and the roof caves killing the dragon. After the dragon is dead, you will see a new person, Roddeck. Talk to him. Roddeck will thank you and give you 150gp. Sir Vant will want his Squire’s possessions back. Talk to him and he will take them. He will thank you and you will level up to level 4. Next he will tell you to walk north and then east til you find a ladder. Climb the ladder and escape to Lumbridge. You are now level 4 and have 150gp.<br>
Congratulations! Tutorial Completed!</p>
<p>This looks about right. We’ve got a clear idea of what will happen from beginning to end.<br>
It can be tempting to think that, “Oh, I’ve got a pretty good idea of what to do in my head, so no worries!” However, when it comes to actually creating the story, ideas get mixed up and even forgotten. To keep things fresh, it’s best to record all your ideas on paper for future reference.</p>
<p>Additionally, if you can come up with ideas for items, magic, names and traits of monsters, etc., it will be easier to create a solid game. Finally, write down any other ideas you may have, even if they are not directly related to the story. They can be a source of creativity and inspiration later on. Congratulations on completing Lesson 1! In Lesson 2, we will get our hands dirty working with RPG Maker.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">There will be a new tutorial every 3 days.</span></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rpgmvx-school-lesson-1-design-documents/401931/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rpgmvx-school-lesson-1-design-documents/401931/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 02 Jul 2011 05:02:14 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-401931-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rpgmvx-school-lesson-1-design-documents/401931.rss">RPGMVX School Lesson 1: Design Documents</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
