<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Need help with people connecting to server!</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/need-help-with-people-connecting-to-server/320257</link>
    <description>Hello All,  i am used to private servers, i have run my own private server awhile ago, about a year ago i would say. I recently put xp on my computer and took out vista. I decided to run a private server again. I got uTorrent, and server base, a client and a no-ip account. I made a No-IP account and ip, got my uTorrent port to 43594, im trying to get my cousin to connect with the IP i made with the No-IP account. I downloaded the No-Ip duc thing that show&#39;s up in the task bar.

If anyone could help i&#39;d apprechiate it very much, i have msn also and Teamviewer (Remote Control Desktop Sharing)

   Please &amp; Thankyou,
      -Spyder.[br][br][size=1]Posted on: December 17, 2009, 09:12:01 pm[/size][hr]Anyone?[br][br][size=1]Posted on: December 18, 2009, 10:42:30 am[/size][hr]Anyone?</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 18 Dec 2009 02:34:36 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/need-help-with-people-connecting-to-server/320257.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Need help with people connecting to server!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Owner_Spyder Owner Spyder]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/owner_spyder">@Owner_Spyder</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Hello All,  i am used to private servers, i have run my own private server awhile ago, about a year ago i would say. I recently put xp on my computer and took out vista. I decided to run a private server again. I got uTorrent, and server base, a client and a no-ip account. I made a No-IP account and ip, got my uTorrent port to 43594, im trying to get my cousin to connect with the IP i made with the No-IP account. I downloaded the No-Ip duc thing that show’s up in the task bar.</p>
<p>If anyone could help i’d apprechiate it very much, i have msn also and Teamviewer (Remote Control Desktop Sharing)</p>
<p>Please &amp; Thankyou,<br>
-Spyder.[br][br][size=1]Posted on: December 17, 2009, 09:12:01 pm[/size][hr]Anyone?[br][br][size=1]Posted on: December 18, 2009, 10:42:30 am[/size][hr]Anyone?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/need-help-with-people-connecting-to-server/320257/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/need-help-with-people-connecting-to-server/320257/1</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 18 Dec 2009 02:34:36 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-320257-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/need-help-with-people-connecting-to-server/320257.rss">Need help with people connecting to server!</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
