<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Caterpillars Trigger Emergency in Liberia</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/caterpillars-trigger-emergency-in-liberia/259005</link>
    <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;MONROVIA, Liberia (Jan. 27) — Liberia&#39;s president declared a state of emergency over an invasion of crop-eating caterpillars that has affected 350,000 people in the West African country.
President Ellen Johnson Sirleaf told lawmakers Monday night that the pests &quot;have invaded our country with the potential to set back our progress in the production of food and export crops.&quot;
This is indeed a crisis and I hereby declare a state of national emergency with particular emphasis on the existing and potentially affected counties,&quot; she said.
The inch-long pests, which have been identified as army worms — the caterpillar stage of a moth — are clogging wells and waterways with excrement and devouring vital crops including banana, plantain, coffee and cocoa.
The outbreak in Liberia, which is still recovering from years of civil war, has been blamed on last year&#39;s unusually long rainy season. The pests have also entered neighboring Guinea, according to the U.N. Food and Agriculture Organization.
Sirleaf said the government has set up a task force to deal with the situation and has started spraying in the affected areas. She also said water and food were being supplied to people displaced by the pest invasion.
But she warned that more effort and more resources are required &quot;if we are to be successful in containing this problem.&quot; She ordered the Minister of Finance to identify budgetary resources &quot;from any source possible that can be used to meet the needs that are required.&quot;
An Agriculture Ministry-led command post, manned by fewer than 100 pest control workers, has been set up near the central provincial town of Gbarnga in a bid to contain the invading caterpillars that number in the tens of millions.
The last time Liberia experienced such an invasion of pests was 30 years ago, but officials then were able to prevent its spread.
The West African nation was ravaged by civil wars for years until 2003. The drawn-out conflict that began in 1989 left about 200,000 people dead and displaced half the country&#39;s population of 3 million.&lt;/blockquote&gt;

Sauce: [url=http://news.aol.com/article/caterpillar-infestation-in-liberia/317187]http://news.aol.com/article/caterpillar-infestation-in-liberia/317187[/url]


Those things are giant o.O</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2009 22:09:20 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>General Discussion</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/caterpillars-trigger-emergency-in-liberia/259005.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Caterpillars Trigger Emergency in Liberia</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@chassy13 Chassy13]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/chassy13">@chassy13</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <blockquote>MONROVIA, Liberia (Jan. 27) — Liberia's president declared a state of emergency over an invasion of crop-eating caterpillars that has affected 350,000 people in the West African country.
President Ellen Johnson Sirleaf told lawmakers Monday night that the pests "have invaded our country with the potential to set back our progress in the production of food and export crops."
This is indeed a crisis and I hereby declare a state of national emergency with particular emphasis on the existing and potentially affected counties," she said.
The inch-long pests, which have been identified as army worms — the caterpillar stage of a moth — are clogging wells and waterways with excrement and devouring vital crops including banana, plantain, coffee and cocoa.
The outbreak in Liberia, which is still recovering from years of civil war, has been blamed on last year's unusually long rainy season. The pests have also entered neighboring Guinea, according to the U.N. Food and Agriculture Organization.
Sirleaf said the government has set up a task force to deal with the situation and has started spraying in the affected areas. She also said water and food were being supplied to people displaced by the pest invasion.
But she warned that more effort and more resources are required "if we are to be successful in containing this problem." She ordered the Minister of Finance to identify budgetary resources "from any source possible that can be used to meet the needs that are required."
An Agriculture Ministry-led command post, manned by fewer than 100 pest control workers, has been set up near the central provincial town of Gbarnga in a bid to contain the invading caterpillars that number in the tens of millions.
The last time Liberia experienced such an invasion of pests was 30 years ago, but officials then were able to prevent its spread.
The West African nation was ravaged by civil wars for years until 2003. The drawn-out conflict that began in 1989 left about 200,000 people dead and displaced half the country's population of 3 million.</blockquote>
<p>Sauce: <a href="http://news.aol.com/article/caterpillar-infestation-in-liberia/317187" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">http://news.aol.com/article/caterpillar-infestation-in-liberia/317187</a></p>
<p>Those things are giant o.O</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/caterpillars-trigger-emergency-in-liberia/259005/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/caterpillars-trigger-emergency-in-liberia/259005/1</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2009 22:09:20 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-259005-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/caterpillars-trigger-emergency-in-liberia/259005.rss">Caterpillars Trigger Emergency in Liberia</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
