<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Divinex, The Great Reborn</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/divinex-the-great-reborn/546770</link>
    <description>Hello everyone, 

To cut to the chase and keep this short &amp; sweet, I have been searching for a good server for a while now. One that focused on gameplay and the community, over donations, votes, loyalty, ect. After searching for over a YEAR, with no success. So instead, i&#39;ve created my own.

What makes me better than most servers? Well, with my server i will NOT ask for donations. There is no donation shop, no vote shop, pk point shop, none of that nonsense. Everything is hosted and supported out of my pocket for your entertainment. I believe what makes an RSPS fun is not having to worry about anything, and just having fun. Working together to go item hunting, bossing, ect is what all private servers should be about. Not donations and votes. That&#39;s my goal. To bring together a great community, where everyone is friends. Not a bunch of players who spend money to buy all of the best items and then sit AFK at home. I do not see the fun in that.

My server is a 317, using kirithiums base almost completely redone. We have the standard features like nex, corp, poly, jadinko, revs, ect. All skills work, vanguard, battlemage, ect work. Also, I enjoy keeping things fresh, so i&#39;ve edited LOTS of underpowered items (Like barrows) to make them formidable and worth getting. Most people aim to get torva, and items like that. Well now, ALL of the items will hold some value. Barrows will be worth the trip. There are lots of things that i have added to make my server a little more unique. like full Dharok has a 6% chance of a 1 hit K.O, ignoring prayer, item protection, ect. D claws have a &quot;bleeding&quot; after effect similar to poison. D chain negates vengeance, and much more! endless combinations for you to try. Nothing is overpowered, nothing is underpowered.  I have spent a lot of time customizing item stats to make for a unique experiences.  

I also pay my staff REAL money, bi weekly. I am currently looking for staff, as i have none. 

I&#39;d appreciate if you gave me a try!

https://www.dropbox.com/s/rm06b3cf7biczdf/RebornX%20Client.jar?dl=0

thank you.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 17 Sep 2014 18:01:13 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/divinex-the-great-reborn/546770.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Divinex, The Great Reborn</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@beemer beemer]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/beemer">@beemer</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I can pull this off because unlike a lot of server hosters, I have a VERY well paying job. I can comfortably host my server and pay my staff out of pocket.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/divinex-the-great-reborn/546770/7">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/divinex-the-great-reborn/546770/7</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 17 Sep 2014 18:01:13 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-546770-7</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/divinex-the-great-reborn/546770.rss">Divinex, The Great Reborn</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Divinex, The Great Reborn</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@I_Am_Second I Am Second]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/i_am_second">@I_Am_Second</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I’ll be completely honest… I have no freaking clue how you expect this to work for you.  :palm:</p>
<p>No revenue, but you’re going to pay staff. No votes, but you expect to grow. I like how it’s different, but you may need to restructure your core.</p>
<p>How much are you paying staff?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/divinex-the-great-reborn/546770/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/divinex-the-great-reborn/546770/6</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2014 17:04:14 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-546770-6</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/divinex-the-great-reborn/546770.rss">Divinex, The Great Reborn</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Divinex, The Great Reborn</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Little_G Little G]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/little_g">@Little_G</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Very nice community as well! I think everyone should check this out <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=5" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/divinex-the-great-reborn/546770/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/divinex-the-great-reborn/546770/5</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2014 16:30:59 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-546770-5</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/divinex-the-great-reborn/546770.rss">Divinex, The Great Reborn</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Divinex, The Great Reborn</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@beemer beemer]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/beemer">@beemer</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>thanks guys! really appreciate it.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/divinex-the-great-reborn/546770/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/divinex-the-great-reborn/546770/4</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2014 18:21:18 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-546770-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/divinex-the-great-reborn/546770.rss">Divinex, The Great Reborn</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Divinex, The Great Reborn</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Little_G Little G]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/little_g">@Little_G</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>What I look for in a server is just what this is! No need to spend tons of money to get the best items, it all comes through hard work!</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/divinex-the-great-reborn/546770/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/divinex-the-great-reborn/546770/3</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2014 18:13:59 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-546770-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/divinex-the-great-reborn/546770.rss">Divinex, The Great Reborn</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Divinex, The Great Reborn</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Ykcud Ykcud]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/ykcud">@Ykcud</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I LOVE this philosophy for a server. Every player is on equal grounds. I have been waiting for a server like this for a very long time. You should add pictures of course, and perhaps list the features and all around “fancy up” your ad. Its well written otherwise and gets he point across. I recommend every give this server a try and especially if you want to play on a server where no one gets bs extra experience or items because they “donated” (seriously, that is not what a donation means) or were forced to vote, you owe it to yourself to give this one a look.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/divinex-the-great-reborn/546770/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/divinex-the-great-reborn/546770/2</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2014 17:37:44 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-546770-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/divinex-the-great-reborn/546770.rss">Divinex, The Great Reborn</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Divinex, The Great Reborn</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@beemer beemer]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/beemer">@beemer</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Hello everyone,</p>
<p>To cut to the chase and keep this short &amp; sweet, I have been searching for a good server for a while now. One that focused on gameplay and the community, over donations, votes, loyalty, ect. After searching for over a YEAR, with no success. So instead, i’ve created my own.</p>
<p>What makes me better than most servers? Well, with my server i will NOT ask for donations. There is no donation shop, no vote shop, pk point shop, none of that nonsense. Everything is hosted and supported out of my pocket for your entertainment. I believe what makes an RSPS fun is not having to worry about anything, and just having fun. Working together to go item hunting, bossing, ect is what all private servers should be about. Not donations and votes. That’s my goal. To bring together a great community, where everyone is friends. Not a bunch of players who spend money to buy all of the best items and then sit AFK at home. I do not see the fun in that.</p>
<p>My server is a 317, using kirithiums base almost completely redone. We have the standard features like nex, corp, poly, jadinko, revs, ect. All skills work, vanguard, battlemage, ect work. Also, I enjoy keeping things fresh, so i’ve edited LOTS of underpowered items (Like barrows) to make them formidable and worth getting. Most people aim to get torva, and items like that. Well now, ALL of the items will hold some value. Barrows will be worth the trip. There are lots of things that i have added to make my server a little more unique. like full Dharok has a 6% chance of a 1 hit K.O, ignoring prayer, item protection, ect. D claws have a “bleeding” after effect similar to poison. D chain negates vengeance, and much more! endless combinations for you to try. Nothing is overpowered, nothing is underpowered.  I have spent a lot of time customizing item stats to make for a unique experiences.</p>
<p>I also pay my staff REAL money, bi weekly. I am currently looking for staff, as i have none.</p>
<p>I’d appreciate if you gave me a try!</p>
<p><a href="https://www.dropbox.com/s/rm06b3cf7biczdf/RebornX%20Client.jar?dl=0" class="onebox" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">https://www.dropbox.com/s/rm06b3cf7biczdf/RebornX%20Client.jar?dl=0</a></p>
<p>thank you.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/divinex-the-great-reborn/546770/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/divinex-the-great-reborn/546770/1</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2014 12:33:17 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-546770-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/divinex-the-great-reborn/546770.rss">Divinex, The Great Reborn</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
