<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>True Blood [TV Series]</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/true-blood-tv-series/531854</link>
    <description>So I just got done watching the last episode of True Blood season 6 and I must say that despite being a fudgeed up version of twilight I can actually come to appreciate most things. First thing I noticed when I started this series was the horrible accent which did get better over time or maybe I just adjusted but either way the accents are horrible. The first few series start off rocky and some parts don&#39;t make sense and when they finish with it, they literally finish with it, everything is thrown out and a new idea comes in. 

I couldn&#39;t help but notice that every single female character had to have a naked scene, whether this was a thing that the director suggested or if it actually meant something, though there was literally sex in every episode so it may have been a urge for the script writer, the director or even the book writer if there is one. I also couldn&#39;t get over the fact that one of the characters just seems to want to fudge every guy she comes in contact with and it kind of pissed me off because she wouldn&#39;t pick the one guy everyone wanted her to go with. It was frustrating seeing this character develop from a shy virgin to a raging slut monster, throughout these scenes I couldn&#39;t help but picture Mario eating a magic mushroom only to start rampaging through his pipes raping every single goomba he came in contact with, and that is her character development explained.

Overall it is quite a good series to get into if you ignore the twilight bits. Though towards the end someone gets massive amounts of power and all you want is for them to keep it but once again HBO do everything the opposite of what you want and take it all way.

So if you&#39;ve seen the series comment below, let me know (one liner stolen) But overall I would rate this series a 7.5 out of 10 tabbies, good job HBO.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 22 Sep 2013 10:50:05 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>General Discussion</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/true-blood-tv-series/531854.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>True Blood [TV Series]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@TabbyKiller TabbyKiller]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/tabbykiller">@TabbyKiller</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>So I just got done watching the last episode of True Blood season 6 and I must say that despite being a fudgeed up version of twilight I can actually come to appreciate most things. First thing I noticed when I started this series was the horrible accent which did get better over time or maybe I just adjusted but either way the accents are horrible. The first few series start off rocky and some parts don’t make sense and when they finish with it, they literally finish with it, everything is thrown out and a new idea comes in.</p>
<p>I couldn’t help but notice that every single female character had to have a naked scene, whether this was a thing that the director suggested or if it actually meant something, though there was literally sex in every episode so it may have been a urge for the script writer, the director or even the book writer if there is one. I also couldn’t get over the fact that one of the characters just seems to want to fudge every guy she comes in contact with and it kind of pissed me off because she wouldn’t pick the one guy everyone wanted her to go with. It was frustrating seeing this character develop from a shy virgin to a raging slut monster, throughout these scenes I couldn’t help but picture Mario eating a magic mushroom only to start rampaging through his pipes raping every single goomba he came in contact with, and that is her character development explained.</p>
<p>Overall it is quite a good series to get into if you ignore the twilight bits. Though towards the end someone gets massive amounts of power and all you want is for them to keep it but once again HBO do everything the opposite of what you want and take it all way.</p>
<p>So if you’ve seen the series comment below, let me know (one liner stolen) But overall I would rate this series a 7.5 out of 10 tabbies, good job HBO.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/true-blood-tv-series/531854/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/true-blood-tv-series/531854/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 22 Sep 2013 10:50:05 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-531854-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/true-blood-tv-series/531854.rss">True Blood [TV Series]</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
