<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>My inactivity</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-inactivity/404763</link>
    <description>So I went on vacation forth of July weekend and came back home and my router and integrated lan on my motherboard was fried. So I was like whatever i&#39;ll buy a network adapter for my spare pci slot and a new router. So on monday (yesterday) my new network adapter comes in the mail and when I get home my computer is showing a blue screen error (not being new to me as it happens periodically) I just restart the box and then I find out my harddrive is no longer being detected. So on the day I get my new network adapter my harddrive disk fails. So now I&#39;m ordering a exact copy of my hdd, took awhile to find because its a OEM part only. I&#39;m going to try and replace the circuit board and see if that works. It&#39;s long distance shipping so it will take around another month or so. If it does work I 
might buy another disk and make use of RAID.

tl;dr Backups of backups of backups and god hates me</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 20 Jul 2011 22:15:33 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Games</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-inactivity/404763.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>My inactivity</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@moparisthebest Moparisthebest]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/moparisthebest">@moparisthebest</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Whether you can recover your hard drive or not doesn’t depend on the next kind that you buy, you can still buy any type.  But yes, backing up is essential, personally I recommend SpiderOak for that, too late this time though.</p>
<p>It’s certainly possible it came in through the DSL line, it happens all the time.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-inactivity/404763/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-inactivity/404763/4</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 20 Jul 2011 22:15:33 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-404763-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-inactivity/404763.rss">My inactivity</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>My inactivity</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@zuppers zuppers]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/zuppers">@zuppers</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“Moparisthebest, post:2, topic:404763”]Sounds like your house got hit by lightning, it’s happened to me before, even with a surge protector it came in through the cable line and fried my modem and 2 ports on my router.</p>
<p>Anyway, why can’t you just buy any old hard drive?  You shouldn’t need the specific one that came out of your computer.[/quote]I’m trying to recover what’s on my hdd. Because it’s like losing a finger or something.</p>
<p>And yeah there was a storm but everything is on surge protectors. I thought maybe it came in via the dsl line and fried everything but I wasn’t sure if that was possible.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-inactivity/404763/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-inactivity/404763/3</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 20 Jul 2011 15:36:08 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-404763-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-inactivity/404763.rss">My inactivity</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>My inactivity</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@moparisthebest Moparisthebest]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/moparisthebest">@moparisthebest</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Sounds like your house got hit by lightning, it’s happened to me before, even with a surge protector it came in through the cable line and fried my modem and 2 ports on my router.</p>
<p>Anyway, why can’t you just buy any old hard drive?  You shouldn’t need the specific one that came out of your computer.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-inactivity/404763/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-inactivity/404763/2</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 19 Jul 2011 02:13:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-404763-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-inactivity/404763.rss">My inactivity</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>My inactivity</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@zuppers zuppers]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/zuppers">@zuppers</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>So I went on vacation forth of July weekend and came back home and my router and integrated lan on my motherboard was fried. So I was like whatever i’ll buy a network adapter for my spare pci slot and a new router. So on monday (yesterday) my new network adapter comes in the mail and when I get home my computer is showing a blue screen error (not being new to me as it happens periodically) I just restart the box and then I find out my harddrive is no longer being detected. So on the day I get my new network adapter my harddrive disk fails. So now I’m ordering a exact copy of my hdd, took awhile to find because its a OEM part only. I’m going to try and replace the circuit board and see if that works. It’s long distance shipping so it will take around another month or so. If it does work I<br>
might buy another disk and make use of RAID.</p>
<p>tl;dr Backups of backups of backups and god hates me</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-inactivity/404763/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-inactivity/404763/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 17 Jul 2011 19:35:20 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-404763-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-inactivity/404763.rss">My inactivity</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
