<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Well what do you think about this?</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/well-what-do-you-think-about-this/245827</link>
    <description>What do you think of this? 

*Read it all, to get it. It&#39;s a story.


Let&#39;s say you and a bunch of your friends always go to the bar for a drink after work. Some of your friends pitch in for the drinks.(Your the rich guy).


1-4 of your friends don&#39;t pay at all, because they can&#39;t afford it.

5th Friend pays $1
6th Friend pays $3
7th Friend pays $7
8th Friend pays $12
9th Friend pays $18
10th Friend(You) pays $59
---------------------------
Total $100


Now the owner of the bar is so grateful that you guys are loyal customers, because you guys come everyday and provide him a steady income of cash, that he will give you a 20% discount.

You guys are &quot;Wow ,that&#39;s great&quot;. You guys then think of way to split the extra $20 dollars. One of the options you think is, give $2 dollars to every person, but that isn&#39;t fair, because 1-4 people aren&#39;t paying at all! So then the owner comes and says, well the 5th person who pays a $1 goes in the list that doesn&#39;t pay anything at all, and the rest of you pay lower than what you pay now.(represented by the table below.)

1-5 of your friends don&#39;t pay at all.
6th Friend pays $2 (That&#39;s a 33% savings)
7th Friend pays $5 (That&#39;s a 28% savings)
8th Friend pays $9 (That&#39;s a 25% savings)
9th Friend pays $14 (That&#39;s a 22% savings)
10th Friend(You) Pays $49 (That&#39;s a 16% savings)
---------------------------------------------
Total: $80


So then, your all: &quot;That sounds good!&quot;. So your leaving the bar with your friends, your walking and the 6th friend says, &quot;It&#39;s not fair!, I only saved $1 and you saved $10, why do you get more of the discount!&quot;, then the 7th friend jumps in and says the same thing, &quot;I only saved $2 dollars but you saved $10!&quot;, and then the NERVE of the 5th guy who got off with a freebie, saying he didn&#39;t get any of the discount, and wanted some of it. So you get beat up.

To anyone with common sense you see it&#39;s not right to give people who pay LESS than you to receive an amount of money that is close to yours or higher. They had the more savings as you saw by the percents when you only had a 16% savings.

So then the next day, your friends go to the bar, but this time your not there. They say, &quot;Ah it&#39;s ok, we don&#39;t need him&quot;. So they drink their beers, and when the bill comes, they see that they don&#39;t even have HALF of the money to pay the bill, because you paid more than half of the bill.

Here&#39;s the punch line.

The first table represents how the taxing system WAS before, 10% to 40% of the people didn&#39;t pay taxes because they were too poor. The rich people(Being you) didn&#39;t mind picking up their &quot;tab&quot;. You guys paid more of the taxes.

Now the second table represents the taxing system NOW,(well until it is changed), It was from Bush&#39;s tax cuts.
10% to 50% of the people didn&#39;t pay taxes.
The rich people again picked up their tab. But this time, you guys aren&#39;t showing up as much. As shown by the economic fall in the country, the rich people aren&#39;t picking up the tabs of the much poorer people in the country. And it has been going on for a year now. The poor people are complaining because they are only receiving $1000 checks and they want more! When they are not EVEN PAYING taxes. Just goes to show you that rich people aren&#39;t always going to be there for you, and that things look really bad for the economy. Well until the new administration hopefully changes it all.

I found this really interesting, just thought I&#39;d share it with you guys. Post of what you guys think about this.

I didn&#39;t make this.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 22 Nov 2008 17:20:34 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>General Discussion</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/well-what-do-you-think-about-this/245827.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Well what do you think about this?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@R.I.P_RSC R.I.P RSC]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/r.i.p_rsc">@R.I.P_RSC</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Poor people shouldn’t nag, they didn’t put in any effort in school etc…</p>
<p>On-Topic: I doubt the new administration will do much better then the current one.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/well-what-do-you-think-about-this/245827/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/well-what-do-you-think-about-this/245827/2</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 22 Nov 2008 17:20:34 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-245827-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/well-what-do-you-think-about-this/245827.rss">Well what do you think about this?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Well what do you think about this?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Java_Is_My_Bitch Java Is My Bitch™]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/java_is_my_bitch">@Java_Is_My_Bitch</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>What do you think of this?</p>
<p>*Read it all, to get it. It’s a story.</p>
<p>Let’s say you and a bunch of your friends always go to the bar for a drink after work. Some of your friends pitch in for the drinks.(Your the rich guy).</p>
<p>1-4 of your friends don’t pay at all, because they can’t afford it.</p>
<h2>5th Friend pays $1<br>
6th Friend pays $3<br>
7th Friend pays $7<br>
8th Friend pays $12<br>
9th Friend pays $18<br>
10th Friend(You) pays $59</h2>
<p>Total $100</p>
<p>Now the owner of the bar is so grateful that you guys are loyal customers, because you guys come everyday and provide him a steady income of cash, that he will give you a 20% discount.</p>
<p>You guys are “Wow ,that’s great”. You guys then think of way to split the extra $20 dollars. One of the options you think is, give $2 dollars to every person, but that isn’t fair, because 1-4 people aren’t paying at all! So then the owner comes and says, well the 5th person who pays a $1 goes in the list that doesn’t pay anything at all, and the rest of you pay lower than what you pay now.(represented by the table below.)</p>
<h2>1-5 of your friends don’t pay at all.<br>
6th Friend pays $2 (That’s a 33% savings)<br>
7th Friend pays $5 (That’s a 28% savings)<br>
8th Friend pays $9 (That’s a 25% savings)<br>
9th Friend pays $14 (That’s a 22% savings)<br>
10th Friend(You) Pays $49 (That’s a 16% savings)</h2>
<p>Total: $80</p>
<p>So then, your all: “That sounds good!”. So your leaving the bar with your friends, your walking and the 6th friend says, “It’s not fair!, I only saved $1 and you saved $10, why do you get more of the discount!”, then the 7th friend jumps in and says the same thing, “I only saved $2 dollars but you saved $10!”, and then the NERVE of the 5th guy who got off with a freebie, saying he didn’t get any of the discount, and wanted some of it. So you get beat up.</p>
<p>To anyone with common sense you see it’s not right to give people who pay LESS than you to receive an amount of money that is close to yours or higher. They had the more savings as you saw by the percents when you only had a 16% savings.</p>
<p>So then the next day, your friends go to the bar, but this time your not there. They say, “Ah it’s ok, we don’t need him”. So they drink their beers, and when the bill comes, they see that they don’t even have HALF of the money to pay the bill, because you paid more than half of the bill.</p>
<p>Here’s the punch line.</p>
<p>The first table represents how the taxing system WAS before, 10% to 40% of the people didn’t pay taxes because they were too poor. The rich people(Being you) didn’t mind picking up their “tab”. You guys paid more of the taxes.</p>
<p>Now the second table represents the taxing system NOW,(well until it is changed), It was from Bush’s tax cuts.<br>
10% to 50% of the people didn’t pay taxes.<br>
The rich people again picked up their tab. But this time, you guys aren’t showing up as much. As shown by the economic fall in the country, the rich people aren’t picking up the tabs of the much poorer people in the country. And it has been going on for a year now. The poor people are complaining because they are only receiving $1000 checks and they want more! When they are not EVEN PAYING taxes. Just goes to show you that rich people aren’t always going to be there for you, and that things look really bad for the economy. Well until the new administration hopefully changes it all.</p>
<p>I found this really interesting, just thought I’d share it with you guys. Post of what you guys think about this.</p>
<p>I didn’t make this.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/well-what-do-you-think-about-this/245827/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/well-what-do-you-think-about-this/245827/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 22 Nov 2008 17:13:49 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-245827-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/well-what-do-you-think-about-this/245827.rss">Well what do you think about this?</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
