<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Abyss - A work in progress</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/abyss-a-work-in-progress/521886</link>
    <description>[CENTER][IMG]http://abyss-rsps.com/forums/digitalvb/morbid/misc/vbulletin4_logo.png[/img]


[CENTER][URL=http://&quot;http://abyss-rsps.com/webclient.html&quot;]Play Now[/URL] | [URL=http://&quot;http://abyss-rsps.com/client.jar&quot;]Download Client[/URL] | [URL=http://&quot;http://abyss-rsps.com/forums/&quot;]Forum[/URL] |  [URL=http://&quot;http://abyss-rsps.com/donate.php&quot;]Donate[/URL] [/CENTER]


[SIZE=4][B]Abyss-RSPS Advertisement thread[/B][/SIZE]


Why Join us:
No matter what the suggestion is, we at-least listen to what the community wants. The community decides how we run the server and how we update the server. We want the community to be a big part on server decisions so everyone can have a say in how the server runs. That being said, our developer team is working around the clock trying to provide for the needs of the server. We have our website developer, Paiman, whom works with site/forum updates and security so that the forums can&#39;t be hijacked or anything of the sort. Our server developers, Denis and Hank, work side by side fixing bugs that need fixed, making content that is enjoyable, and working until the aspirin doesn&#39;t really help to much. The rest of the staff team works with handling all player-based issues that occur on the server. We are proud to say that we have a lot of unique features available for everyone to partake in and even more if you&#39;re a donator.



Developer Team:
[B][url=http://www.rune-server.org/members/blackout/]Blackout[/url][/B] - Server Developer/Abyss Founder
[B]Paiman[/B] - Website Developer



Updates:

[B]2013-06-23[/B]
Added bank @ magic trees
Fixed Shops
Added Rune ore rocks to mining area.
Fixed Gem prices. ( 300 coin profit for dragon stones, 260 for diamond, 200 under diamond )
Fixed Ganodermic Poncho placement.
Fixed effigies.
Nurfed ganodermic Armour drops. Buffed polypore drop.
Fixed Saradomin god-sword special attack. 
Fixed Drop dupe.
Fixed NPC respawn times.
Fixed 4th floor of Dungeoneering.
Fixed Claw spec damage.

[B]2013-06-25[/B]
Fixed Goblin Salute emote sprite not showing up in the emote interface ²
Fixed Earth Battlestaves showing up as stackable items
Fixed Armadyl Runes showing up as non-stackable items
Fixed administrator commands and logs
Added Developer ranks for clear hierarchy
Fixed Yell colors and display for super donator ranked players
Fixed connection delay timeout for slower computers not connecting straight away
Fixed the bankers at the firemaking teleport (Varrock west bank): they stand behind the booths now -- keeping the hilarious examine message however.
Fixed the bank booths not opening the bank interface
Added banker at the home teleport area. No more running a marathon
Moved Bartak (the lottery NPC) to the well-area of home
Added lunar altar at home
Added chaos altar for curses at home (not yet coded, will take a while)
Moved prayer altar to symmetrically align with chaos altar
Removed the chairs and tables at home blocking easy access of the altars
Added praying animation to all three altars
Rotated the prayer altar correctly

[B]2013-06-26[/B]
Leather Recipe for Disaster gloves are no longer tradeable and sellable
All Recipe for Disaster gloves have correct bonusses (leather, bronze, iron, steel, black, mithril, adamant, rune, dragon, barrows)
Administrator commands fixed -- no more memory leaks
Administrator commands edited to aid in moderation of server
::players command edited to provide an accurate description of player&#39;s role (owner, admin, developer, donator, player, ...)
Fixed commands that were inaccessible by various staff members
Reduced teleport block spell duration from 8 to 5 minutes (like RuneScape)
Added confirmation dialogue handling to Ancient Magics teleports leading to the wilderness without notification
Added dialogue option handling to teleports leading to wilderness
Added actionhandling to confirmation options when teleporting to the wilderness.
Added fully working magic potions (extreme magic was already added)
Muted players are now refrained from using the ::yell command. Their yells are silent to others..
Fixed bug where player was required to have 10 defence to equip Black Elegant.

[B]2013-06-27[/B]
Added torstol drops to ~ 20 high levelled monsters and bosses
Chaos druids drop a wide variety of different levelled herb seeds.
Added low levelled seed drops to men and women (suggest other npcs)
Added mid-levelled seed drops to Renegade knights (suggest other npcs)
Added high-levelled seed drops (not including torstol) to all dragons (suggest other npcs)
Fixed teleport to brimhaven dungeon to go to brimhaven dungeon
Removed the seed box from the skiller shop to strengthen economy by trading with other players
Catching raw cod and raw bass now uses the correct big-fishing-net-animation.
bronze, iron and steel dragons have larger and correct drops
Added big fishing net to the skilling shop
Bass and cod now require big fishing nets instead of small
Slight tweak of fishing equipment prices in the shop - nothing too big..
Added Tome Of Frost effect: unlimited water runes serverside
Fixed server memory leaking from playersaves - fixed and added schedule to ensure player saves &amp; save handling requests
Added Event hooking to playersaves to keep backups
Fixed prices of dragon sq shield en shield right half in the shop to more realistic prices
Frost dragons now have reduced drop rate percentages and several other high levelled monsters drop herbs aswell!
Appended crowns to new playerRights such as server developer, owner and website developer ²
further increased banlist and mutelist handling to increase stability when checking them
Fixed blowkiss emote: now using proper animation and gfx
Fixed rare occasion where one would get an unexpected double drop from Frost Dragons
Engine shutdown hook when updating and restarting the server is improved
Grappling hook has been disabled for entering the Armadyl boss area in the God Wars Dungeon
Castle wars ( Lobby loading started. Zammy portal works. Sara portal works. Guthix = not started yet.)

[B]2013-06-28[/B]
Temporarily disabled Zammy boss in Gwd to prevent a memory leak
Added most of the animations for curses - finishing up :D
Added most of the gfx for curses!
Soulsplit is nearly done, NPC part is completely done, just player left
Zaryte bow now requires 80 Ranged instead of 50
Zaryte bow is now a twohanded weapon
Bolts have been reduced in base damage output, making them less overpowered but still a great, viable ammo for training ranged and bossing, ...
Polished drops for several high level bosses. Still adding more
Reworked the range max hit formula a bit (slight nerf)
Increased Zaryte bow base damage to make it more inline with other high-level bows
fixed some ranged gfx and animations when using throwables such as darts
Added extended model &amp; NPC dumping for Developers ²
Reworked the melee max hit calculation formula to deal with granite maul (partially)
Added melee max hit calculation formula variables for leech &amp; curse prayers.

[B]2013-06-29[/B]
All dungeoneering rewards now have proper equipment bonusses
Geyser Titan now uses a new projectile function for rendering gfx &amp; animations (I will extend this too all summoning familiars)
Spirit Tz-Kih updates: correct animations and gfx -- proper effects when using spirit cape
Spirit cape now reduces 20% of special attack points required to cast a familiar&#39;s special move
Castle wars ( Stepping stones done. Exploding potion done. Catapult done. )
Server now running on the VPS. 
Donation page now linked with Pay-Pal.

[B]2013-06-30[/B]
Fixed Dark Beast drop ratio - still improving.
Reworked the resetCurses(). and resetPrayers(). methods
Fixed playerHandler memory leaks when using save timers from the Gregorian Calendar
Fixed summoning familiars animations and gfx
added headicon matching for curses
Fixed major summoning bug exploited by several players
Fixed Nex: Cruor now spawns instead of the zombie.
Removed GWD bosses prayer handling to fix choking (temp fix)
added better command handling and getRights checks
Changed the Curses dialogue when praying at Chaos altar a bit. Should be bug free
Working on curse_icon_glows, nearly done
Fixed a bug allowing both curse and regular prayers to be used simultaneously.
Updated playerHandling to allow for prayer swapping and
Fixed prayer draining when swapping prayer types
Re-added the Zamorak boss to Gwd
Fixed another bug with stackable item IDs corrupting when saving charfile.
Fixed memory leaks from a loop caused by a bad method in the Shop Handler
Added sap, leech and deflect curses to the melee, range and magic maxhitformula.
Fixed a bug that created an infinite amount of entities in some of the logs -- causing huge memory leaks in the long run.

[B]2013-07-01[/B]
Fixed crowns on the client ²
Fixed background sprite rendering on client ²
Lowered loginbox to show the Abyss logo completely ²
Fixed yells for some people
Abyssal vine whip has correct bonusses.
Dungeoneering has a bug fixed
Removed rocktails and monkfish from shop to endorse fishing
Removed saradomin brews from shop to endorse herblore/farming
Fixed animations for cooking on a fire
Fixed animations for offering bones at an altar
Claws are two-handed
Fixed summoning familiar timer
Fixed server update timer
Fixed prayer draining partially
Fixed small bugs with curses
Reduced Nex HP and increased her accuracy and max hit.

[B]2013-07-02[/B]
Fixed Abyssal vine whip requirements. (75 attack &amp; 80 slayer)
Reworked the timestamp generation to Gregorian Calender API for time and date calculation
Renewed the ::players command to a more professional look.
Dragonfire Shields can be smithed on an anvil with 90 smithing and the required items.
Beginner guide dialogue is fixed
Bones-on-altar are improved
Cooking on a fire has correct animation




Media:


Login:
[IMG]http://i42.tinypic.com/2qdsgu1.png[/img]

Growing forums:
[IMG]http://i.imgur.com/yXrIIti.png[/img]

Clan Setups:
[IMG]http://img33.imageshack.us/img33/9616/ajs.png[/img]

Woodcutting:
[IMG]http://i.imgur.com/DSTZGjk.png[/img]

Duel Arena Staking works:
[IMG]http://i.imgur.com/bSZZ3uX.png[/img]

Fishing:
[IMG]http://img21.imageshack.us/img21/7433/7nb.png[/img] [IMG]http://img29.imageshack.us/img29/5262/jjn.png[/img]

Agility:
Gnome Course:
[IMG]http://img832.imageshack.us/img832/865/c3v5.png[/img]
 [IMG]http://i.imgur.com/UshwmTX.png[/img]

Barbarian Course:
[IMG]http://img577.imageshack.us/img577/1786/qil.png[/img] 
[IMG]http://img22.imageshack.us/img22/9719/o9k2.png[/img]

Wilderness Course: ( 80% - Will be completed 7-3-13 / 7-5-13 )
[IMG]http://img28.imageshack.us/img28/8796/n7t.png[/img]

Fletching:
[IMG]http://i.imgur.com/WIBtyrH.png[/img] [IMG]http://i.imgur.com/G4aMSUH.png[/img]

Herblore:
[IMG]http://i.imgur.com/xNkr8f1.png[/img] [IMG]http://img542.imageshack.us/img542/1204/tlpz.png[/img]

ETC:
[IMG]http://i.imgur.com/TcjRGGX.png[/img] [IMG]http://i.imgur.com/wFnFiRs.png[/img] [IMG]http://i.imgur.com/VRvZ0Ok.png[/img]
[IMG]http://img15.imageshack.us/img15/4863/bm7.png[/img] [IMG]http://i.imgur.com/0VbMUvo.png[/img]




Credits:
Graphics: Landon and John.
Base: Netty PI 
Client features: Infexis
Forums System: vBulletin 4.2.0
VPS: Trentahost
More Credits: phl0w/poesy700/10534/Tim/Scott/Harlan/Josh
Others whom have helped, we thank you as-well.



If you&#39;d like to show your support of the server, feel free to use the following image as your signature!

[IMG]http://abyss-rsps.com/Abyss2_zps7f681518.png[/img]

[/CENTER]</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 20 Jul 2013 18:42:32 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/abyss-a-work-in-progress/521886.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Abyss - A work in progress</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@birdhouse919 birdhouse919]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/birdhouse919">@birdhouse919</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Bump. <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/smiley.png?v=5" title=":smiley:" class="emoji" alt=":smiley:"></p>
<p>A ton of updates happening in-game / forums.<br>
Come Check it out.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/abyss-a-work-in-progress/521886/17">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/abyss-a-work-in-progress/521886/17</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 20 Jul 2013 18:42:32 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-521886-17</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/abyss-a-work-in-progress/521886.rss">Abyss - A work in progress</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Abyss - A work in progress</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Fiveriverflow Fiveriverflow]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/fiveriverflow">@Fiveriverflow</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Bump.</p>
<p>Updates:<br>
Bank tabs now in-game.<br>
Brewing drinks (cooking)<br>
Colored fires/Firelighters (fire-making)<br>
Started Skullbull course <em>Agility</em><br>
Snakeskin armor (crafting)<br>
Fixed dungeoneering complexity 3 on floor 5.<br>
Hiscores now 100% working.<br>
Dominion Tower.<br>
Beginner clue scrolls done.</p>
<p>A lot more updates on the way.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/abyss-a-work-in-progress/521886/16">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/abyss-a-work-in-progress/521886/16</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 13 Jul 2013 23:45:04 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-521886-16</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/abyss-a-work-in-progress/521886.rss">Abyss - A work in progress</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Abyss - A work in progress</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@birdhouse919 birdhouse919]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/birdhouse919">@birdhouse919</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Bump.</p>
<p>Last three days of updates added.</p>
<p>[code]2013-06-30<br>
Fixed Dark Beast drop ratio - still improving.<br>
Reworked the resetCurses(). and resetPrayers(). methods<br>
Fixed playerHandler memory leaks when using save timers from the Gregorian Calendar<br>
Fixed summoning familiars animations and gfx<br>
added headicon matching for curses<br>
Fixed major summoning bug exploited by several players<br>
Fixed Nex: Cruor now spawns instead of the zombie.<br>
Removed GWD bosses prayer handling to fix choking (temp fix)<br>
added better command handling and getRights checks<br>
Changed the Curses dialogue when praying at Chaos altar a bit. Should be bug free<br>
Working on curse_icon_glows, nearly done<br>
Fixed a bug allowing both curse and regular prayers to be used simultaneously.<br>
Updated playerHandling to allow for prayer swapping and<br>
Fixed prayer draining when swapping prayer types<br>
Re-added the Zamorak boss to Gwd<br>
Fixed another bug with stackable item IDs corrupting when saving charfile.<br>
Fixed memory leaks from a loop caused by a bad method in the Shop Handler<br>
Added sap, leech and deflect curses to the melee, range and magic maxhitformula.<br>
Fixed a bug that created an infinite amount of entities in some of the logs – causing huge memory leaks in the long run.</p>
<p>2013-07-01<br>
Fixed crowns on the client ²<br>
Fixed background sprite rendering on client ²<br>
Lowered loginbox to show the Abyss logo completely ²<br>
Fixed yells for some people<br>
Abyssal vine whip has correct bonusses.<br>
Dungeoneering has a bug fixed<br>
Removed rocktails and monkfish from shop to endorse fishing<br>
Removed saradomin brews from shop to endorse herblore/farming<br>
Fixed animations for cooking on a fire<br>
Fixed animations for offering bones at an altar<br>
Claws are two-handed<br>
Fixed summoning familiar timer<br>
Fixed server update timer<br>
Fixed prayer draining partially<br>
Fixed small bugs with curses<br>
Reduced Nex HP and increased her accuracy and max hit.</p>
<p>2013-07-02<br>
Fixed Abyssal vine whip requirements. (75 attack &amp; 80 slayer)<br>
Reworked the timestamp generation to Gregorian Calender API for time and date calculation<br>
Renewed the ::players command to a more professional look.<br>
Dragonfire Shields can be smithed on an anvil with 90 smithing and the required items.<br>
Beginner guide dialogue is fixed<br>
Bones-on-altar are improved<br>
Cooking on a fire has correct animation[/code]</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/abyss-a-work-in-progress/521886/15">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/abyss-a-work-in-progress/521886/15</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2013 13:56:13 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-521886-15</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/abyss-a-work-in-progress/521886.rss">Abyss - A work in progress</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Abyss - A work in progress</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Host_Gushers Host Gushers]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/host_gushers">@Host_Gushers</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Gl with this bro, looks like you have some potential <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/smiley.png?v=5" title=":smiley:" class="emoji" alt=":smiley:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/abyss-a-work-in-progress/521886/14">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/abyss-a-work-in-progress/521886/14</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2013 03:23:57 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-521886-14</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/abyss-a-work-in-progress/521886.rss">Abyss - A work in progress</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Abyss - A work in progress</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Cycnyg Cycnyg]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/cycnyg">@Cycnyg</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Bumped this thread. AMAZING SERVER. LOVE IT</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/abyss-a-work-in-progress/521886/13">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/abyss-a-work-in-progress/521886/13</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 30 Jun 2013 23:33:43 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-521886-13</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/abyss-a-work-in-progress/521886.rss">Abyss - A work in progress</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Abyss - A work in progress</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@birdhouse919 birdhouse919]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/birdhouse919">@birdhouse919</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote quote-modified" data-post="11" data-topic="521886">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/loveandpower/40/5_e05bb34c421432ee4d40de30c10af3e5.png" class="avatar"> Loveandpower:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>you need to to give credit to Galkon as we all know that’s his clan chat</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I thought I listed Josh in the credits before, meant no disrespect.<br>
Updated thread layout and added him in the credits.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/abyss-a-work-in-progress/521886/12">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/abyss-a-work-in-progress/521886/12</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 30 Jun 2013 04:19:42 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-521886-12</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/abyss-a-work-in-progress/521886.rss">Abyss - A work in progress</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Abyss - A work in progress</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Loveandpower Loveandpower]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/loveandpower">@Loveandpower</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>you need to to give credit to Galkon as we all know that’s his clan chat</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/abyss-a-work-in-progress/521886/11">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/abyss-a-work-in-progress/521886/11</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2013 12:40:43 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-521886-11</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/abyss-a-work-in-progress/521886.rss">Abyss - A work in progress</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Abyss - A work in progress</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@arham_4 arham 4]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/arham_4">@arham_4</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Pretty nice.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/abyss-a-work-in-progress/521886/10">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/abyss-a-work-in-progress/521886/10</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2013 04:20:19 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-521886-10</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/abyss-a-work-in-progress/521886.rss">Abyss - A work in progress</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Abyss - A work in progress</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@birdhouse919 birdhouse919]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/birdhouse919">@birdhouse919</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Bought a VPS with DDOS protection.<br>
Will be switching over soon, with a client update as-well.</p>
<p>Server will be down for a short amount of time.</p>
<p>Two New Developers added to the team:</p>
<p>Ua|Eight - Site Developer<br>
Denis - Server Developer</p>
<p>Recent Updates:</p>
<blockquote>Fixed Goblin Salute emote sprite not showing up in the emote interface ²
Fixed Earth Battle-staves showing up as stack-able items
Fixed Armadyl Runes showing up as non-stack-able items
Fixed administrator commands and logs
Added Developer ranks for clear hierarchy
Fixed Yell colors and display for super donator ranked players
Fixed connection delay timeout for slower computers not connecting straight away
Fixed the bankers at the fire-making teleport (Varrock west bank): they stand behind the booths now -- keeping the hilarious examine message however.
Fixed the bank booths not opening the bank interface
Added banker at the home teleport area. No more running a marathon
Moved Bartak (the lottery NPC) to the well-area of home
Added lunar altar at home
Added chaos altar for curses at home (not yet coded, will take a while)
Moved prayer altar to symmetrically align with chaos altar
Removed the chairs and tables at home blocking easy access of the altars
Added praying animation to all three altars
Rotated the prayer altar correctly
Leather Recipe for Disaster gloves are no longer trade-able and sell-able
All Recipe for Disaster gloves have correct bonuses (leather, bronze, iron, steel, black, mithril, adamant, rune, dragon, barrows)
Administrator commands fixed -- no more memory leaks
Administrator commands edited to aid in moderation of server
::players command edited to provide an accurate description of player's role (owner, admin, developer, donator, player, ...)
Fixed commands that were inaccessible by various staff members
Reduced teleport block spell duration from 8 to 5 minutes (like RuneScape)
Added confirmation dialogue handling to Ancient Magics teleports leading to the wilderness without notification
Added dialogue option handling to teleports leading to wilderness
Added actionhandling to confirmation options when teleporting to the wilderness.
Added fully working magic potions (extreme magic was already added)
Muted players are now refrained from using the ::yell command. Their yells are silent to others..
Fixed bug where player was required to have 10 defence to equip Black Elegant.
Added bank @ magic trees
Fixed Shops
Added Rune ore rocks to mining area.
Fixed Gem prices. ( 300 coin profit for dragon stones, 260 for diamond, 200 under diamond )
Fixed Ganodermic Poncho placement.
Fixed effigies.
Nurfed ganodermic Armour drops. Buffed poly-pore drop.
Disabled current 11698 glitch. ( Spec broken. )
Fixed Drop dupe.
Fixed NPC respawn times.
Fixed 4th floor of Dungeoneering.
Fixed Claw spec damage.</blockquote>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/abyss-a-work-in-progress/521886/9">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/abyss-a-work-in-progress/521886/9</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2013 01:45:28 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-521886-9</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/abyss-a-work-in-progress/521886.rss">Abyss - A work in progress</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Abyss - A work in progress</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@3lv3n_snip3r 3lv3n snip3r]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/3lv3n_snip3r">@3lv3n_snip3r</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I see you ripped RevolutionXPK’s site before they shut down.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/abyss-a-work-in-progress/521886/8">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/abyss-a-work-in-progress/521886/8</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 21 Jun 2013 06:10:08 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-521886-8</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/abyss-a-work-in-progress/521886.rss">Abyss - A work in progress</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Abyss - A work in progress</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@birdhouse919 birdhouse919]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/birdhouse919">@birdhouse919</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Thread updated!</p>
<p>Huge update happened today, read over the features and look at the new pictures to see.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/abyss-a-work-in-progress/521886/7">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/abyss-a-work-in-progress/521886/7</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 21 Jun 2013 03:39:52 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-521886-7</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/abyss-a-work-in-progress/521886.rss">Abyss - A work in progress</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Abyss - A work in progress</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Loveandpower Loveandpower]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/loveandpower">@Loveandpower</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>You are trying keep up the work!</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/abyss-a-work-in-progress/521886/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/abyss-a-work-in-progress/521886/6</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 19 Jun 2013 12:02:47 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-521886-6</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/abyss-a-work-in-progress/521886.rss">Abyss - A work in progress</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Abyss - A work in progress</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@DevilXsummoner DevilXsummoner]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/devilxsummoner">@DevilXsummoner</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Good Luck Bro…</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/abyss-a-work-in-progress/521886/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/abyss-a-work-in-progress/521886/5</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 19 Jun 2013 03:07:09 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-521886-5</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/abyss-a-work-in-progress/521886.rss">Abyss - A work in progress</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Abyss - A work in progress</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Flame3 John]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/flame3">@Flame3</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>That’s fine. I’ve also removed your donation link. If you would like to see why, please refer to this section’s <a href="https://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php/topic,640022.0.html" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">Rules and Guidelines</a>.<br>
Good luck.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/abyss-a-work-in-progress/521886/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/abyss-a-work-in-progress/521886/4</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 16 Jun 2013 19:51:10 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-521886-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/abyss-a-work-in-progress/521886.rss">Abyss - A work in progress</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Abyss - A work in progress</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@birdhouse919 birdhouse919]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/birdhouse919">@birdhouse919</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“Flame_, post:2, topic:521886”]Please provide links, otherwise I will lock this thread within 1 hour of this post.<br>
Thanks.[/quote]</p>
<p>Fixed, sorry about that. They were there when I looked, but apparently, I’m seeing things. haha</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/abyss-a-work-in-progress/521886/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/abyss-a-work-in-progress/521886/3</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 16 Jun 2013 19:48:15 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-521886-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/abyss-a-work-in-progress/521886.rss">Abyss - A work in progress</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Abyss - A work in progress</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Flame3 John]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/flame3">@Flame3</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Please provide links, otherwise I will lock this thread within 1 hour of this post.<br>
Thanks.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/abyss-a-work-in-progress/521886/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/abyss-a-work-in-progress/521886/2</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 16 Jun 2013 19:31:25 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-521886-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/abyss-a-work-in-progress/521886.rss">Abyss - A work in progress</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Abyss - A work in progress</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@birdhouse919 birdhouse919]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/birdhouse919">@birdhouse919</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[CENTER]<img src="http://abyss-rsps.com/forums/digitalvb/morbid/misc/vbulletin4_logo.png" alt width="" height=""></p>
<p>[CENTER]<a data-bbcode="true">Play Now</a> | <a data-bbcode="true">Download Client</a> | <a data-bbcode="true">Forum</a> |  <a data-bbcode="true">Donate</a> [/CENTER]</p>
<p>[SIZE=4]<span class="bbcode-b">Abyss-RSPS Advertisement thread</span>[/SIZE]</p>
<p>Why Join us:<br>
No matter what the suggestion is, we at-least listen to what the community wants. The community decides how we run the server and how we update the server. We want the community to be a big part on server decisions so everyone can have a say in how the server runs. That being said, our developer team is working around the clock trying to provide for the needs of the server. We have our website developer, Paiman, whom works with site/forum updates and security so that the forums can’t be hijacked or anything of the sort. Our server developers, Denis and Hank, work side by side fixing bugs that need fixed, making content that is enjoyable, and working until the aspirin doesn’t really help to much. The rest of the staff team works with handling all player-based issues that occur on the server. We are proud to say that we have a lot of unique features available for everyone to partake in and even more if you’re a donator.</p>
<p>Developer Team:<br>
<span class="bbcode-b"><a href="http://www.rune-server.org/members/blackout/" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">Blackout</a></span> - Server Developer/Abyss Founder<br>
<span class="bbcode-b">Paiman</span> - Website Developer</p>
<p>Updates:</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">2013-06-23</span><br>
Added bank @ magic trees<br>
Fixed Shops<br>
Added Rune ore rocks to mining area.<br>
Fixed Gem prices. ( 300 coin profit for dragon stones, 260 for diamond, 200 under diamond )<br>
Fixed Ganodermic Poncho placement.<br>
Fixed effigies.<br>
Nurfed ganodermic Armour drops. Buffed polypore drop.<br>
Fixed Saradomin god-sword special attack.<br>
Fixed Drop dupe.<br>
Fixed NPC respawn times.<br>
Fixed 4th floor of Dungeoneering.<br>
Fixed Claw spec damage.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">2013-06-25</span><br>
Fixed Goblin Salute emote sprite not showing up in the emote interface ²<br>
Fixed Earth Battlestaves showing up as stackable items<br>
Fixed Armadyl Runes showing up as non-stackable items<br>
Fixed administrator commands and logs<br>
Added Developer ranks for clear hierarchy<br>
Fixed Yell colors and display for super donator ranked players<br>
Fixed connection delay timeout for slower computers not connecting straight away<br>
Fixed the bankers at the firemaking teleport (Varrock west bank): they stand behind the booths now – keeping the hilarious examine message however.<br>
Fixed the bank booths not opening the bank interface<br>
Added banker at the home teleport area. No more running a marathon<br>
Moved Bartak (the lottery NPC) to the well-area of home<br>
Added lunar altar at home<br>
Added chaos altar for curses at home (not yet coded, will take a while)<br>
Moved prayer altar to symmetrically align with chaos altar<br>
Removed the chairs and tables at home blocking easy access of the altars<br>
Added praying animation to all three altars<br>
Rotated the prayer altar correctly</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">2013-06-26</span><br>
Leather Recipe for Disaster gloves are no longer tradeable and sellable<br>
All Recipe for Disaster gloves have correct bonusses (leather, bronze, iron, steel, black, mithril, adamant, rune, dragon, barrows)<br>
Administrator commands fixed – no more memory leaks<br>
Administrator commands edited to aid in moderation of server<br>
::players command edited to provide an accurate description of player’s role (owner, admin, developer, donator, player, …)<br>
Fixed commands that were inaccessible by various staff members<br>
Reduced teleport block spell duration from 8 to 5 minutes (like RuneScape)<br>
Added confirmation dialogue handling to Ancient Magics teleports leading to the wilderness without notification<br>
Added dialogue option handling to teleports leading to wilderness<br>
Added actionhandling to confirmation options when teleporting to the wilderness.<br>
Added fully working magic potions (extreme magic was already added)<br>
Muted players are now refrained from using the ::yell command. Their yells are silent to others…<br>
Fixed bug where player was required to have 10 defence to equip Black Elegant.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">2013-06-27</span><br>
Added torstol drops to ~ 20 high levelled monsters and bosses<br>
Chaos druids drop a wide variety of different levelled herb seeds.<br>
Added low levelled seed drops to men and women (suggest other npcs)<br>
Added mid-levelled seed drops to Renegade knights (suggest other npcs)<br>
Added high-levelled seed drops (not including torstol) to all dragons (suggest other npcs)<br>
Fixed teleport to brimhaven dungeon to go to brimhaven dungeon<br>
Removed the seed box from the skiller shop to strengthen economy by trading with other players<br>
Catching raw cod and raw bass now uses the correct big-fishing-net-animation.<br>
bronze, iron and steel dragons have larger and correct drops<br>
Added big fishing net to the skilling shop<br>
Bass and cod now require big fishing nets instead of small<br>
Slight tweak of fishing equipment prices in the shop - nothing too big…<br>
Added Tome Of Frost effect: unlimited water runes serverside<br>
Fixed server memory leaking from playersaves - fixed and added schedule to ensure player saves &amp; save handling requests<br>
Added Event hooking to playersaves to keep backups<br>
Fixed prices of dragon sq shield en shield right half in the shop to more realistic prices<br>
Frost dragons now have reduced drop rate percentages and several other high levelled monsters drop herbs aswell!<br>
Appended crowns to new playerRights such as server developer, owner and website developer ²<br>
further increased banlist and mutelist handling to increase stability when checking them<br>
Fixed blowkiss emote: now using proper animation and gfx<br>
Fixed rare occasion where one would get an unexpected double drop from Frost Dragons<br>
Engine shutdown hook when updating and restarting the server is improved<br>
Grappling hook has been disabled for entering the Armadyl boss area in the God Wars Dungeon<br>
Castle wars ( Lobby loading started. Zammy portal works. Sara portal works. Guthix = not started yet.)</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">2013-06-28</span><br>
Temporarily disabled Zammy boss in Gwd to prevent a memory leak<br>
Added most of the animations for curses - finishing up <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/smiley.png?v=9" title=":smiley:" class="emoji" alt=":smiley:"><br>
Added most of the gfx for curses!<br>
Soulsplit is nearly done, NPC part is completely done, just player left<br>
Zaryte bow now requires 80 Ranged instead of 50<br>
Zaryte bow is now a twohanded weapon<br>
Bolts have been reduced in base damage output, making them less overpowered but still a great, viable ammo for training ranged and bossing, …<br>
Polished drops for several high level bosses. Still adding more<br>
Reworked the range max hit formula a bit (slight nerf)<br>
Increased Zaryte bow base damage to make it more inline with other high-level bows<br>
fixed some ranged gfx and animations when using throwables such as darts<br>
Added extended model &amp; NPC dumping for Developers ²<br>
Reworked the melee max hit calculation formula to deal with granite maul (partially)<br>
Added melee max hit calculation formula variables for leech &amp; curse prayers.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">2013-06-29</span><br>
All dungeoneering rewards now have proper equipment bonusses<br>
Geyser Titan now uses a new projectile function for rendering gfx &amp; animations (I will extend this too all summoning familiars)<br>
Spirit Tz-Kih updates: correct animations and gfx – proper effects when using spirit cape<br>
Spirit cape now reduces 20% of special attack points required to cast a familiar’s special move<br>
Castle wars ( Stepping stones done. Exploding potion done. Catapult done. )<br>
Server now running on the VPS.<br>
Donation page now linked with Pay-Pal.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">2013-06-30</span><br>
Fixed Dark Beast drop ratio - still improving.<br>
Reworked the resetCurses(). and resetPrayers(). methods<br>
Fixed playerHandler memory leaks when using save timers from the Gregorian Calendar<br>
Fixed summoning familiars animations and gfx<br>
added headicon matching for curses<br>
Fixed major summoning bug exploited by several players<br>
Fixed Nex: Cruor now spawns instead of the zombie.<br>
Removed GWD bosses prayer handling to fix choking (temp fix)<br>
added better command handling and getRights checks<br>
Changed the Curses dialogue when praying at Chaos altar a bit. Should be bug free<br>
Working on curse_icon_glows, nearly done<br>
Fixed a bug allowing both curse and regular prayers to be used simultaneously.<br>
Updated playerHandling to allow for prayer swapping and<br>
Fixed prayer draining when swapping prayer types<br>
Re-added the Zamorak boss to Gwd<br>
Fixed another bug with stackable item IDs corrupting when saving charfile.<br>
Fixed memory leaks from a loop caused by a bad method in the Shop Handler<br>
Added sap, leech and deflect curses to the melee, range and magic maxhitformula.<br>
Fixed a bug that created an infinite amount of entities in some of the logs – causing huge memory leaks in the long run.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">2013-07-01</span><br>
Fixed crowns on the client ²<br>
Fixed background sprite rendering on client ²<br>
Lowered loginbox to show the Abyss logo completely ²<br>
Fixed yells for some people<br>
Abyssal vine whip has correct bonusses.<br>
Dungeoneering has a bug fixed<br>
Removed rocktails and monkfish from shop to endorse fishing<br>
Removed saradomin brews from shop to endorse herblore/farming<br>
Fixed animations for cooking on a fire<br>
Fixed animations for offering bones at an altar<br>
Claws are two-handed<br>
Fixed summoning familiar timer<br>
Fixed server update timer<br>
Fixed prayer draining partially<br>
Fixed small bugs with curses<br>
Reduced Nex HP and increased her accuracy and max hit.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">2013-07-02</span><br>
Fixed Abyssal vine whip requirements. (75 attack &amp; 80 slayer)<br>
Reworked the timestamp generation to Gregorian Calender API for time and date calculation<br>
Renewed the ::players command to a more professional look.<br>
Dragonfire Shields can be smithed on an anvil with 90 smithing and the required items.<br>
Beginner guide dialogue is fixed<br>
Bones-on-altar are improved<br>
Cooking on a fire has correct animation</p>
<p>Media:</p>
<p>Login:<br>
<div class="lightbox-wrapper"><a class="lightbox" href="http://i42.tinypic.com/2qdsgu1.png" title="2qdsgu1.png" rel="nofollow noopener"><img src="http://i42.tinypic.com/2qdsgu1.png" alt width="690" height="452"><div class="meta">
<svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-far-image svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#far-image"></use></svg><span class="filename">2qdsgu1.png</span><span class="informations">766×502</span><svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-discourse-expand svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#discourse-expand"></use></svg>
</div></a></div></p>
<p>Growing forums:<br>
<img src="http://i.imgur.com/yXrIIti.png" alt width="161" height="81"></p>
<p>Clan Setups:<br>
<img src="http://img33.imageshack.us/img33/9616/ajs.png" alt width="" height=""></p>
<p>Woodcutting:<br>
<img src="http://i.imgur.com/DSTZGjk.png" alt width="349" height="291"></p>
<p>Duel Arena Staking works:<br>
<img src="http://i.imgur.com/bSZZ3uX.png" alt width="161" height="81"></p>
<p>Fishing:<br>
<img src="http://img21.imageshack.us/img21/7433/7nb.png" alt width="" height=""> <img src="http://img29.imageshack.us/img29/5262/jjn.png" alt width="" height=""></p>
<p>Agility:<br>
Gnome Course:<br>
<img src="http://img832.imageshack.us/img832/865/c3v5.png" alt width="" height=""><br>
<img src="http://i.imgur.com/UshwmTX.png" alt width="161" height="81"></p>
<p>Barbarian Course:<br>
<img src="http://img577.imageshack.us/img577/1786/qil.png" alt width="" height=""><br>
<img src="http://img22.imageshack.us/img22/9719/o9k2.png" alt width="" height=""></p>
<p>Wilderness Course: ( 80% - Will be completed 7-3-13 / 7-5-13 )<br>
<img src="http://img28.imageshack.us/img28/8796/n7t.png" alt width="" height=""></p>
<p>Fletching:<br>
<img src="http://i.imgur.com/WIBtyrH.png" alt width="138" height="121"> <img src="http://i.imgur.com/G4aMSUH.png" alt width="112" height="123"></p>
<p>Herblore:<br>
<img src="http://i.imgur.com/xNkr8f1.png" alt width="105" height="184"> <img src="http://img542.imageshack.us/img542/1204/tlpz.png" alt width="" height=""></p>
<p>ETC:<br>
<img src="http://i.imgur.com/TcjRGGX.png" alt width="179" height="266"> <img src="http://i.imgur.com/wFnFiRs.png" alt width="188" height="260"> <img src="http://i.imgur.com/VRvZ0Ok.png" alt width="157" height="161"><br>
<img src="http://img15.imageshack.us/img15/4863/bm7.png" alt width="" height=""> <img src="http://i.imgur.com/0VbMUvo.png" alt width="160" height="162"></p>
<p>Credits:<br>
Graphics: Landon and John.<br>
Base: Netty PI<br>
Client features: Infexis<br>
Forums System: vBulletin 4.2.0<br>
VPS: Trentahost<br>
More Credits: phl0w/poesy700/10534/Tim/Scott/Harlan/Josh<br>
Others whom have helped, we thank you as-well.</p>
<p>If you’d like to show your support of the server, feel free to use the following image as your signature!</p>
<p><img src="http://abyss-rsps.com/Abyss2_zps7f681518.png" alt width="" height=""></p>
<p>[/CENTER]</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/abyss-a-work-in-progress/521886/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/abyss-a-work-in-progress/521886/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 16 Jun 2013 19:27:36 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-521886-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/abyss-a-work-in-progress/521886.rss">Abyss - A work in progress</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
