<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>How to report/spot malicious content [READ THIS UPDATED SSP + FORUMS!]</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-report-spot-malicious-content-read-this-updated-ssp-forums/397689</link>
    <description>
[ul][center][size=18pt]Stopping computer threats[/size][/center]

Alright, so with the increase of threats on the status page and on the forums it&#39;s probably a good idea that everyone gets a basic education on how to deal with them and recognize them. This thread is in response also to the growing number of threads asking about viruses and how they should be removed. So if anyone posts such a thread you should kindly point them in the correct direction (here). 

Now without further delay let us begin. I&#39;m going to create an easy to follow layout which can be quickly referenced to based on the situation you&#39;re in. 
[hr]
[b][u]Contents[/u][/b]

[iurl=#one]1) Recognizing that your system is infected (+ reporting) [/iurl]
[iurl=#two]2) Identifying infected pages (SSP/Forum + more)[/iurl]
[left] 
        [iurl=#three]3) RAT[/iurl]
        [iurl=#four]4) Keylogger[/iurl]
        [iurl=#five]5) Trojan[/iurl]
        [iurl=#six]6) Reporting[/iurl]
        [/left]
[hr]
[anchor=one]
[center][size=14pt]1) Recognizing that your system is infected (+ reporting)[/size][/center]

In order to remove an infected file you must first be aware that you have one. I&#39;m going to create a list of the main give aways for your computer being infected. I&#39;ll number them so that they&#39;re easy to follow. [b]If a scan doesn&#39;t pick up anything, you can tell by the below.[/b]

[list type=decimal]
[li]You notice a considerable decrease in your computers performance, this is a tell tale sign as these files are very draining on your computers resources.[/li]
[li]You notice that your computer is taking a while to startup, the infected file has to startup also, it could also make modifications to your system (which also need to startup).[/li]
[li]You notice UAC has been disabled, this is a key trick a lot of people use to limit your control over administrative tasks on your PC[/li]
[li]You notice that you cannot access task manager, this again is always used, this way you cannot end the process, or remove the file.[/li]
[/list]

These are just a few I thought are the most common nowadays, though there are more. Check out the links below for a compilation of other signs.

http://www.computer-realm.net/signs-virus-spyware/
http://www.onlinesecurityauthority.com/home-pc-security/10-ways-to-know-if-your-pc-has-virus/
http://www.technology-geek.com/10-signs-you-have-a-computer-virus/

I think that about covers it for this section, if you&#39;re unsure of any words used please use googles define feature.

define:word
[hr]
[anchor=two]
[center][size=14pt]2) Identifying infected pages (SSP/Forum + more)[/size][/center]

If you can identify the page which is infected before you get infected then you&#39;ll be saving yourself a lot of hassle. Most people who attempt to store infected files on your computer are lazy and lack genuine knowledge which would be required to be a &#39;good hacker&#39;.

[b]SSP:[/b]
[list type=decimal]
[li]You notice a lack of effort in the advertising of the page, things like &#39;jsdfjsgg&#39;. This is a tiny give away but not always true. It shows the person has no interest to advertise the server, only to infect you.[/li]
[li]You notice repeats with the same images/information. In 99% of cases this will be somebody attempting to mass infect users. [/li]
[/list]

On the SSP, if unsure you should always use a link scanner, these will scan potentially malicious links and give you information on them. If a link is found out to be malicious you should report it immediately. Here are some usefull tools to use while browsing the SSP.

[list type=decimal]
[li]Link scanner - This scans links to ensure they&#39;re safe. Good examples of link scanners include:  http://linkscanner.avg.com/   and http://linkscanner.explabs.com/linkscanner/default.aspx - be sure to always use a few link scanners as one of them may be incorrect, I&#39;ll be posting some more at the end of this post.[/li][/list]
[li]Source code check - This is vital when playing on a webclient, most tactics used on the SSP are Java drive bys (http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Drive-by_download). Checking the source code can almost complete eliminate this threat. A normal applet will look like this (Differs obviously):

[/li][/ul]
[code]
&lt;applet name=&quot;Webclient_Name&quot; width=&quot;765&quot; height=&quot;503&quot; archive=&quot;client.jar&quot; code=&quot;client.class&quot;&gt;
&lt;param name=&quot;java_arguments&quot; value=&quot;-Xmx1024m&quot;&gt;&lt;/applet&gt;
[/code]
[ul]Where as that only downloads client.jar, a drive by would redirect you to another index (index2.html in most cases) so doesn&#39;t have the applet code in it&#39;s main index. So, it wouldn&#39;t have the code above, just a code to fake what it would look like until it can redirect you to the page which downloads the infected file. (if that makes sense).  
[list][li]You notice that the webclient page looks like this: http://imageshack.us/photo/my-images/268/jdblooklike.jpg/  That is what most java drive bys will look like, if it looks like that you need to check it out and be careful about it.[/li]
[/list]

Take note that all SSP related ones count on the forum also. 

[b]Forums:[/b]
[list type=decimal]
[li]You notice the link has been spammed across all sections, this is against the rules anyhow so report it virus or not. [/li]
[li]You notice people in the comments are making posts about it being infected, surprisingly most people just ignore this. Don&#39;t.[/li]
[li]Virus scan - This is the most common sense thing, ever, you can use an online scanner or your own personal scanner it really doesn&#39;t matter. I&#39;ll be adding some online scanners at the end of the post.
[hr]
Now I&#39;m going to go over a few examples, and general names of things so people who aren&#39;t very good in this field can identify what malware they have. 
[hr]
[anchor=three]
[center][size=14pt]RAT[/size][/center]

RAT stands for remote administration tool, it goes by its name. It can control your computer and has an array of built in functions to make your life generally problematic. This can range from crashers, to messing with webcams and your computers sound system. I&#39;m going to go over what I myself would do if I had a RAT.

[list type=decimal]
[li]Cover all webcams, and disconnect sound/pen drives. This means the person is limited to how he can affect you/ see you physically. [/li]
[li]Clear all private data (passwords etc) from all programs and your browser, this means the person cannot grab them and use them. [/li]
[li]Download an anti virus, then boot into safe mode and scan. This way the RAT won&#39;t be able to harm you. You could also try to look for unusual processes, end them and then delete the file.[/li]
[/list]

RATs will slow down your system immensely because they come with a huge amount of monitoring. If you&#39;re confident, you can find the file, end the process and remove it yourself but I don&#39;t recommend that. 
[hr]
[anchor=four]
[center][size=14pt]keylogger[/size][/center]

It goes by its name, it logs keys, this is mainly used for stealing passwords and your personal data, this one cannot control your PC and the logs of what you&#39;ve typed are usually sent to an email. 

[list type=decimal]
[li]Use onscreen keyboard, if you really HAVE to do something use the onscreen keyboard. It will not log what you type there. [/li]
[li]Check for unusual processes, as always, this can be a good way to remove something.[/li]
[li]Download an anti virus, then boot into safe mode and scan. This way the RAT won&#39;t be able to harm you. You could also try to look for unusual processes, end them and then delete the file.[/li]
[/list]
[hr]
[anchor=five]
[center][size=14pt]Trojan[/size][/center]

This pretends to be something it&#39;s not, it derives its name from the old trojan horse story. It can take the shape of an anti-virus program, or a windows application, anything. The window which it appears in will be distorted, and it will over exaggerate a lot. (e.g you have 6000000000000 viruses, buy now or ur gonna die)

[list type=decimal]
[li]There isn&#39;t really a need to protect yourself much here, but it will create a lot of lagg so be prepared. [/li]
[li]Never trust it, no matter how legit it seems, just don&#39;t follow it. [/li]
[li]Download an anti-virus and scan, you will ALWAYS be able to notice the virus process in this case because they are so obvious (size wise compared to other processes).[/li]
[/list]
So that&#39;s it for my 3 examples.
[hr]
[anchor=six]
[center][size=14pt]Found one?[/size][/center]

If you&#39;ve found a server/post on Moparscape, or anything to do with mopar you should report it immediately (Can include moparisthebest, moparcraft). If it is a post click &#39;report to a moderator&#39;

If you&#39;re really struggling to find it, it looks like this:

http://imageshack.us/photo/my-images/849/reporttomod.jpg/

If it is on the status page, take note of the server you believe to be infected (with possible proof) and PM it to a member of staff. 
[hr]
[b]Usefull programs:[/b]

Computer scanners:
http://goo.gl/LQaT7
Link scanners:
http://goo.gl/Gc8wl
Information:
http://goo.gl/aj5wA
File searcher:
http://www.mediafire.com/?a1h473hd321aazk
[hr]
Quick tips:

[list]
[li]Run a scan
Reformat
System restore[/li]
[li][/li]
[/list]
[hr]
[i]This guide is not advanced in any way, shape, or form. It is designed to be basic and easy to understand for everyone on the community, so please do not post advanced methods which mock this guide as we don&#39;t wish to make reporting viruses confusing. If you really can&#39;t find proof and are sure the file has damaged your PC, PM myself, or another moderator and I&#39;m sure we will gladly look for you. Any reports that are on moparisthebest should be reported to a global moderator NOT a moparscape moderator or a moparcraft moderator. This is as short as I could get this guide, please take your time to read it all. Old sticky can be found at: http://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php/topic,479189.0.html[/i]

Feel free to post [i]basic[/i] ways you remove/notice malware, and it may be added. Please point out any errors in the post, thanks. [/list][/ul]</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 01 Jul 2011 06:30:56 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>General Discussion</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-report-spot-malicious-content-read-this-updated-ssp-forums/397689.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>How to report/spot malicious content [READ THIS UPDATED SSP + FORUMS!]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Tom Tom]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/tom">@Tom</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote quote-modified" data-post="12" data-topic="397689">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/fridder/40/5_e05bb34c421432ee4d40de30c10af3e5.png" class="avatar"> Fridder:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>I might be wrong, but I’ve been keylogged before and that person had the ability to close anything I opened, was I a RAT victim? This was about 14 months ago. AVG deleted it, so is it possible any passwords I’ve entered were logged for the past 14 months? Malwarebytes’ hasn’t found anything in the past 14 months, along with Norton.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>RATs can have keyloggers built in, and a list of other trouble causing tools. A basic keylogger should only log key strokes, nothing else. If the actual malware has been removed it shouldn’t be logging anything anymore.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-report-spot-malicious-content-read-this-updated-ssp-forums/397689/13">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-report-spot-malicious-content-read-this-updated-ssp-forums/397689/13</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jul 2011 06:30:56 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-397689-13</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-report-spot-malicious-content-read-this-updated-ssp-forums/397689.rss">How to report/spot malicious content [READ THIS UPDATED SSP + FORUMS!]</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>How to report/spot malicious content [READ THIS UPDATED SSP + FORUMS!]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Fridder Fridder]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/fridder">@Fridder</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I might be wrong, but I’ve been keylogged before and that person had the ability to close anything I opened, was I a RAT victim? This was about 14 months ago. AVG deleted it, so is it possible any passwords I’ve entered were logged for the past 14 months? Malwarebytes’ hasn’t found anything in the past 14 months, along with Norton.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-report-spot-malicious-content-read-this-updated-ssp-forums/397689/12">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-report-spot-malicious-content-read-this-updated-ssp-forums/397689/12</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jul 2011 03:40:42 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-397689-12</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-report-spot-malicious-content-read-this-updated-ssp-forums/397689.rss">How to report/spot malicious content [READ THIS UPDATED SSP + FORUMS!]</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>How to report/spot malicious content [READ THIS UPDATED SSP + FORUMS!]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Meeper98 Meeper98]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/meeper98">@Meeper98</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Was just stating what it would do, if you didn’t run virus scan. <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/wink.png?v=5" title=":wink:" class="emoji" alt=":wink:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-report-spot-malicious-content-read-this-updated-ssp-forums/397689/11">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-report-spot-malicious-content-read-this-updated-ssp-forums/397689/11</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jun 2011 02:39:37 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-397689-11</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-report-spot-malicious-content-read-this-updated-ssp-forums/397689.rss">How to report/spot malicious content [READ THIS UPDATED SSP + FORUMS!]</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>How to report/spot malicious content [READ THIS UPDATED SSP + FORUMS!]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Tom Tom]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/tom">@Tom</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote quote-modified" data-post="9" data-topic="397689">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/meeper98/40/5_e05bb34c421432ee4d40de30c10af3e5.png" class="avatar"> Meeper98:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Disconnecting wouldn’t take you off. It would just make it show as your computer was off to the person who has ratted you. Once you connect again all the logs are sent, as for Keyloggers; All logs are piled up so they’re sent right when you get connected to, at least for some of the programs i have used.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Well yes, but when the Internet is disconnected the person cannot operate your PC therefore you’re safe, trying to make a connection to a PC with no connection isn’t going to work. As I stated above the logs are piled up but by the time you’ve disconnected and done a virus scan the initial virus itself will be gone thus there will be nothing to send the logs.</p>
<p>Logs don’t send themselves.</p>
<p>inb4somesmartcommentfromsynchronized_</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-report-spot-malicious-content-read-this-updated-ssp-forums/397689/10">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-report-spot-malicious-content-read-this-updated-ssp-forums/397689/10</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 27 Jun 2011 15:19:16 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-397689-10</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-report-spot-malicious-content-read-this-updated-ssp-forums/397689.rss">How to report/spot malicious content [READ THIS UPDATED SSP + FORUMS!]</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>How to report/spot malicious content [READ THIS UPDATED SSP + FORUMS!]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Meeper98 Meeper98]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/meeper98">@Meeper98</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Disconnecting wouldn’t take you off. It would just make it show as your computer was off to the person who has ratted you. Once you connect again all the logs are sent, as for Keyloggers; All logs are piled up so they’re sent right when you get connected to, at least for some of the programs i have used.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-report-spot-malicious-content-read-this-updated-ssp-forums/397689/9">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-report-spot-malicious-content-read-this-updated-ssp-forums/397689/9</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 27 Jun 2011 10:08:37 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-397689-9</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-report-spot-malicious-content-read-this-updated-ssp-forums/397689.rss">How to report/spot malicious content [READ THIS UPDATED SSP + FORUMS!]</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>How to report/spot malicious content [READ THIS UPDATED SSP + FORUMS!]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@davidi2 Davidi2]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/davidi2">@davidi2</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Tom beta needs a BBC tag tutorial <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=5" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-report-spot-malicious-content-read-this-updated-ssp-forums/397689/8">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-report-spot-malicious-content-read-this-updated-ssp-forums/397689/8</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jun 2011 05:34:29 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-397689-8</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-report-spot-malicious-content-read-this-updated-ssp-forums/397689.rss">How to report/spot malicious content [READ THIS UPDATED SSP + FORUMS!]</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>How to report/spot malicious content [READ THIS UPDATED SSP + FORUMS!]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Svitkona Svitkona]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/svitkona">@Svitkona</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>The tags are somewhat messed up but otherwise nice guide. I see you’re going to suggest a list of anti viruses too, so this should end up as a good reference for most of the people on this site.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-report-spot-malicious-content-read-this-updated-ssp-forums/397689/7">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-report-spot-malicious-content-read-this-updated-ssp-forums/397689/7</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jun 2011 05:33:03 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-397689-7</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-report-spot-malicious-content-read-this-updated-ssp-forums/397689.rss">How to report/spot malicious content [READ THIS UPDATED SSP + FORUMS!]</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>How to report/spot malicious content [READ THIS UPDATED SSP + FORUMS!]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Tom Tom]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/tom">@Tom</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“rip4d, post:5, topic:397689”]Thanks for this, should help the community immensely.</p>
<p>And for RATs and Keyloggers… couldn’t you disconnect from the internet if you are on a desktop by unplugging the wireless adapter/Ethernet cable and be safe until you remove it?[/quote]</p>
<p>You could but as far as I’m aware some log strokes in a file which is then sent to an email/server. You can but it really depends on what situation you’re in.  For example, the file stored everything you’ve typed for 30 minutes and is then sent to the person who runs the malware.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-report-spot-malicious-content-read-this-updated-ssp-forums/397689/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-report-spot-malicious-content-read-this-updated-ssp-forums/397689/6</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 04 Jun 2011 20:20:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-397689-6</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-report-spot-malicious-content-read-this-updated-ssp-forums/397689.rss">How to report/spot malicious content [READ THIS UPDATED SSP + FORUMS!]</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>How to report/spot malicious content [READ THIS UPDATED SSP + FORUMS!]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@rip4d rip4d]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/rip4d">@rip4d</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Thanks for this, should help the community immensely.</p>
<p>And for RATs and Keyloggers… couldn’t you disconnect from the internet if you are on a desktop by unplugging the wireless adapter/Ethernet cable and be safe until you remove it?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-report-spot-malicious-content-read-this-updated-ssp-forums/397689/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-report-spot-malicious-content-read-this-updated-ssp-forums/397689/5</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 03 Jun 2011 19:17:37 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-397689-5</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-report-spot-malicious-content-read-this-updated-ssp-forums/397689.rss">How to report/spot malicious content [READ THIS UPDATED SSP + FORUMS!]</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>How to report/spot malicious content [READ THIS UPDATED SSP + FORUMS!]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Andrew_Ferguson The317Guy]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/andrew_ferguson">@Andrew_Ferguson</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Very nice, will help the newbies bone up on safety.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-report-spot-malicious-content-read-this-updated-ssp-forums/397689/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-report-spot-malicious-content-read-this-updated-ssp-forums/397689/4</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 03 Jun 2011 19:06:51 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-397689-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-report-spot-malicious-content-read-this-updated-ssp-forums/397689.rss">How to report/spot malicious content [READ THIS UPDATED SSP + FORUMS!]</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>How to report/spot malicious content [READ THIS UPDATED SSP + FORUMS!]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@krackkid Krackkid]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/krackkid">@krackkid</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Nice tagging skills ;D</p>
<p>Also good post I guess, mite help out.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-report-spot-malicious-content-read-this-updated-ssp-forums/397689/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-report-spot-malicious-content-read-this-updated-ssp-forums/397689/3</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 03 Jun 2011 18:51:45 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-397689-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-report-spot-malicious-content-read-this-updated-ssp-forums/397689.rss">How to report/spot malicious content [READ THIS UPDATED SSP + FORUMS!]</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>How to report/spot malicious content [READ THIS UPDATED SSP + FORUMS!]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Marine5287 Marine5287]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/marine5287">@Marine5287</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Thanks for this, it was very much needed. Hopefully will start taking action on reporting these.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-report-spot-malicious-content-read-this-updated-ssp-forums/397689/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-report-spot-malicious-content-read-this-updated-ssp-forums/397689/2</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 03 Jun 2011 18:42:30 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-397689-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-report-spot-malicious-content-read-this-updated-ssp-forums/397689.rss">How to report/spot malicious content [READ THIS UPDATED SSP + FORUMS!]</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>How to report/spot malicious content [READ THIS UPDATED SSP + FORUMS!]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Tom Tom]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/tom">@Tom</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[ul][center][size=18pt]Stopping computer threats[/size][/center]</p>
<p>Alright, so with the increase of threats on the status page and on the forums it’s probably a good idea that everyone gets a basic education on how to deal with them and recognize them. This thread is in response also to the growing number of threads asking about viruses and how they should be removed. So if anyone posts such a thread you should kindly point them in the correct direction (here).</p>
<p>Now without further delay let us begin. I’m going to create an easy to follow layout which can be quickly referenced to based on the situation you’re in.<br>
[hr]<br>
<span class="bbcode-b"><span class="bbcode-u">Contents</span></span></p>
<p>[iurl=#one]1) Recognizing that your system is infected (+ reporting) [/iurl]<br>
[iurl=#two]2) Identifying infected pages (SSP/Forum + more)[/iurl]<br>
[left]<br>
[iurl=#three]3) RAT[/iurl]<br>
[iurl=#four]4) Keylogger[/iurl]<br>
[iurl=#five]5) Trojan[/iurl]<br>
[iurl=#six]6) Reporting[/iurl]<br>
[/left]<br>
[hr]<br>
[anchor=one]<br>
[center][size=14pt]1) Recognizing that your system is infected (+ reporting)[/size][/center]</p>
<p>In order to remove an infected file you must first be aware that you have one. I’m going to create a list of the main give aways for your computer being infected. I’ll number them so that they’re easy to follow. <span class="bbcode-b">If a scan doesn’t pick up anything, you can tell by the below.</span></p>
<p>[list type=decimal]<br>
[li]You notice a considerable decrease in your computers performance, this is a tell tale sign as these files are very draining on your computers resources.[/li]<br>
[li]You notice that your computer is taking a while to startup, the infected file has to startup also, it could also make modifications to your system (which also need to startup).[/li]<br>
[li]You notice UAC has been disabled, this is a key trick a lot of people use to limit your control over administrative tasks on your PC[/li]<br>
[li]You notice that you cannot access task manager, this again is always used, this way you cannot end the process, or remove the file.[/li]<br>
[/list]</p>
<p>These are just a few I thought are the most common nowadays, though there are more. Check out the links below for a compilation of other signs.</p>
<p><aside class="onebox whitelistedgeneric">
  <header class="source">
      <img src="http://www.computer-realm.net/wp-content/uploads/post-images/2016/10/favicon.png" class="site-icon" width="42" height="44">
      <a href="http://www.computer-realm.net/signs-virus-spyware/" target="_blank" title="11:25PM - 07 July 2009" rel="nofollow noopener">Computer Realm – 7 Jul 09</a>
  </header>
  <article class="onebox-body">
    <img src="http://www.computer-realm.net/wp-content/uploads/post-images/2009/07/virus-spyware.jpg" class="thumbnail onebox-avatar" width="300" height="300">

<h3><a href="http://www.computer-realm.net/signs-virus-spyware/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Top 10 Signs, You Have Viruses or Spyware - Computer Realm</a></h3>

<p>Viruses and Spyware are pretty much the worst hassles to deal with when it comes to computers. A small price, for revolutionizing every aspect of our lives, businesses and day to day tasks making things a lot more efficient and productive. However,...</p>


  </article>
  <div class="onebox-metadata">
    
    
  </div>
  <div style="clear: both"></div>
</aside>
<br>
<a href="http://www.onlinesecurityauthority.com/home-pc-security/10-ways-to-know-if-your-pc-has-virus/" class="onebox" target="_blank">http://www.onlinesecurityauthority.com/home-pc-security/10-ways-to-know-if-your-pc-has-virus/</a><br>
<a href="http://www.technology-geek.com/10-signs-you-have-a-computer-virus/" class="onebox" target="_blank">http://www.technology-geek.com/10-signs-you-have-a-computer-virus/</a></p>
<p>I think that about covers it for this section, if you’re unsure of any words used please use googles define feature.</p>
<p>define:word<br>
[hr]<br>
[anchor=two]<br>
[center][size=14pt]2) Identifying infected pages (SSP/Forum + more)[/size][/center]</p>
<p>If you can identify the page which is infected before you get infected then you’ll be saving yourself a lot of hassle. Most people who attempt to store infected files on your computer are lazy and lack genuine knowledge which would be required to be a ‘good hacker’.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">SSP:</span><br>
[list type=decimal]<br>
[li]You notice a lack of effort in the advertising of the page, things like ‘jsdfjsgg’. This is a tiny give away but not always true. It shows the person has no interest to advertise the server, only to infect you.[/li]<br>
[li]You notice repeats with the same images/information. In 99% of cases this will be somebody attempting to mass infect users. [/li]<br>
[/list]</p>
<p>On the SSP, if unsure you should always use a link scanner, these will scan potentially malicious links and give you information on them. If a link is found out to be malicious you should report it immediately. Here are some usefull tools to use while browsing the SSP.</p>
<p>[list type=decimal]<br>
[li]Link scanner - This scans links to ensure they’re safe. Good examples of link scanners include:  <a href="http://linkscanner.avg.com/">http://linkscanner.avg.com/</a>   and <a href="http://linkscanner.explabs.com/linkscanner/default.aspx">http://linkscanner.explabs.com/linkscanner/default.aspx</a> - be sure to always use a few link scanners as one of them may be incorrect, I’ll be posting some more at the end of this post.[/li][/list]<br>
[li]Source code check - This is vital when playing on a webclient, most tactics used on the SSP are Java drive bys (<a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Drive-by_download">http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Drive-by_download</a>). Checking the source code can almost complete eliminate this threat. A normal applet will look like this (Differs obviously):</p>
<p>[/li][/ul]</p>
<pre><code class="lang-auto">&lt;applet name="Webclient_Name" width="765" height="503" archive="client.jar" code="client.class"&gt;
&lt;param name="java_arguments" value="-Xmx1024m"&gt;&lt;/applet&gt;</code></pre>
<p>[ul]Where as that only downloads client.jar, a drive by would redirect you to another index (index2.html in most cases) so doesn’t have the applet code in it’s main index. So, it wouldn’t have the code above, just a code to fake what it would look like until it can redirect you to the page which downloads the infected file. (if that makes sense).<br>
[list][li]You notice that the webclient page looks like this: <a href="http://imageshack.us/photo/my-images/268/jdblooklike.jpg/">http://imageshack.us/photo/my-images/268/jdblooklike.jpg/</a>  That is what most java drive bys will look like, if it looks like that you need to check it out and be careful about it.[/li]<br>
[/list]</p>
<p>Take note that all SSP related ones count on the forum also.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Forums:</span><br>
[list type=decimal]<br>
[li]You notice the link has been spammed across all sections, this is against the rules anyhow so report it virus or not. [/li]<br>
[li]You notice people in the comments are making posts about it being infected, surprisingly most people just ignore this. Don’t.[/li]<br>
[li]Virus scan - This is the most common sense thing, ever, you can use an online scanner or your own personal scanner it really doesn’t matter. I’ll be adding some online scanners at the end of the post.<br>
[hr]<br>
Now I’m going to go over a few examples, and general names of things so people who aren’t very good in this field can identify what malware they have.<br>
[hr]<br>
[anchor=three]<br>
[center][size=14pt]RAT[/size][/center]</p>
<p>RAT stands for remote administration tool, it goes by its name. It can control your computer and has an array of built in functions to make your life generally problematic. This can range from crashers, to messing with webcams and your computers sound system. I’m going to go over what I myself would do if I had a RAT.</p>
<p>[list type=decimal]<br>
[li]Cover all webcams, and disconnect sound/pen drives. This means the person is limited to how he can affect you/ see you physically. [/li]<br>
[li]Clear all private data (passwords etc) from all programs and your browser, this means the person cannot grab them and use them. [/li]<br>
[li]Download an anti virus, then boot into safe mode and scan. This way the RAT won’t be able to harm you. You could also try to look for unusual processes, end them and then delete the file.[/li]<br>
[/list]</p>
<p>RATs will slow down your system immensely because they come with a huge amount of monitoring. If you’re confident, you can find the file, end the process and remove it yourself but I don’t recommend that.<br>
[hr]<br>
[anchor=four]<br>
[center][size=14pt]keylogger[/size][/center]</p>
<p>It goes by its name, it logs keys, this is mainly used for stealing passwords and your personal data, this one cannot control your PC and the logs of what you’ve typed are usually sent to an email.</p>
<p>[list type=decimal]<br>
[li]Use onscreen keyboard, if you really HAVE to do something use the onscreen keyboard. It will not log what you type there. [/li]<br>
[li]Check for unusual processes, as always, this can be a good way to remove something.[/li]<br>
[li]Download an anti virus, then boot into safe mode and scan. This way the RAT won’t be able to harm you. You could also try to look for unusual processes, end them and then delete the file.[/li]<br>
[/list]<br>
[hr]<br>
[anchor=five]<br>
[center][size=14pt]Trojan[/size][/center]</p>
<p>This pretends to be something it’s not, it derives its name from the old trojan horse story. It can take the shape of an anti-virus program, or a windows application, anything. The window which it appears in will be distorted, and it will over exaggerate a lot. (e.g you have 6000000000000 viruses, buy now or ur gonna die)</p>
<p>[list type=decimal]<br>
[li]There isn’t really a need to protect yourself much here, but it will create a lot of lagg so be prepared. [/li]<br>
[li]Never trust it, no matter how legit it seems, just don’t follow it. [/li]<br>
[li]Download an anti-virus and scan, you will ALWAYS be able to notice the virus process in this case because they are so obvious (size wise compared to other processes).[/li]<br>
[/list]<br>
So that’s it for my 3 examples.<br>
[hr]<br>
[anchor=six]<br>
[center][size=14pt]Found one?[/size][/center]</p>
<p>If you’ve found a server/post on Moparscape, or anything to do with mopar you should report it immediately (Can include moparisthebest, moparcraft). If it is a post click ‘report to a moderator’</p>
<p>If you’re really struggling to find it, it looks like this:</p>
<p><a href="http://imageshack.us/photo/my-images/849/reporttomod.jpg/" class="onebox" target="_blank">http://imageshack.us/photo/my-images/849/reporttomod.jpg/</a></p>
<p>If it is on the status page, take note of the server you believe to be infected (with possible proof) and PM it to a member of staff.<br>
[hr]<br>
<span class="bbcode-b">Usefull programs:</span></p>
<p>Computer scanners:<br>
<a href="http://goo.gl/LQaT7" class="onebox" target="_blank">http://goo.gl/LQaT7</a><br>
Link scanners:<br>
<a href="http://goo.gl/Gc8wl" class="onebox" target="_blank">http://goo.gl/Gc8wl</a><br>
Information:<br>
<a href="http://goo.gl/aj5wA" class="onebox" target="_blank">http://goo.gl/aj5wA</a><br>
File searcher:<br>
<a href="http://www.mediafire.com/?a1h473hd321aazk" class="onebox" target="_blank">http://www.mediafire.com/?a1h473hd321aazk</a><br>
[hr]<br>
Quick tips:</p>
<p>[list]<br>
[li]Run a scan<br>
Reformat<br>
System restore[/li]<br>
[li][/li]<br>
[/list]<br>
[hr]<br>
<span class="bbcode-i">This guide is not advanced in any way, shape, or form. It is designed to be basic and easy to understand for everyone on the community, so please do not post advanced methods which mock this guide as we don’t wish to make reporting viruses confusing. If you really can’t find proof and are sure the file has damaged your PC, PM myself, or another moderator and I’m sure we will gladly look for you. Any reports that are on moparisthebest should be reported to a global moderator NOT a moparscape moderator or a moparcraft moderator. This is as short as I could get this guide, please take your time to read it all. Old sticky can be found at: <a href="http://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php/topic,479189.0.html">http://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php/topic,479189.0.html</a></span></p>
<p>Feel free to post <span class="bbcode-i">basic</span> ways you remove/notice malware, and it may be added. Please point out any errors in the post, thanks. [/list][/ul]</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-report-spot-malicious-content-read-this-updated-ssp-forums/397689/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-report-spot-malicious-content-read-this-updated-ssp-forums/397689/1</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 03 Jun 2011 18:40:27 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-397689-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-report-spot-malicious-content-read-this-updated-ssp-forums/397689.rss">How to report/spot malicious content [READ THIS UPDATED SSP + FORUMS!]</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
