<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>HELP With Custom Whip Models Please!</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/help-with-custom-whip-models-please/439572</link>
    <description>Ok so i recently realized i cannot recolour a whip to make lime.. lava.. ect. there is a code you can use for other servers such as modifiedColor = and originalColor = but my source doesnt have that. so i have resorted to custom making the models custom. my friend Sir Chase ( a beast at everything about RSPS&#39;s) has decided to help me with this if i pay. so i am going to. he has gotten very far. there are 2 things that need to be changed. The item in the inventory looks very awkward. and when you equip the whip, This random line of color is attatched from the characters hand to the bottom of the whip. i was wondering if any of you model experts out there know how to fix this! i bet chase can figure it out, but this could help a lot if one of you could give me some info. thanks! here is the pic of the problems. ( the line of color from the characters hand to the bottom of the whip, and wierd looking inventory of whips)

http://imageshack.us/photo/my-images/857/vlcsnap2012041322h01m40.png/</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 14 Apr 2012 02:27:56 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/help-with-custom-whip-models-please/439572.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>HELP With Custom Whip Models Please!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Fluffys Fluffys]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/fluffys">@Fluffys</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Ok so i recently realized i cannot recolour a whip to make lime… lava… ect. there is a code you can use for other servers such as modifiedColor = and originalColor = but my source doesnt have that. so i have resorted to custom making the models custom. my friend Sir Chase ( a beast at everything about RSPS’s) has decided to help me with this if i pay. so i am going to. he has gotten very far. there are 2 things that need to be changed. The item in the inventory looks very awkward. and when you equip the whip, This random line of color is attatched from the characters hand to the bottom of the whip. i was wondering if any of you model experts out there know how to fix this! i bet chase can figure it out, but this could help a lot if one of you could give me some info. thanks! here is the pic of the problems. ( the line of color from the characters hand to the bottom of the whip, and wierd looking inventory of whips)</p>
<aside class="onebox whitelistedgeneric">
  <header class="source">
      <img src="http://imageshack.com/favicon.ico" class="site-icon" width="16" height="16">
      <a href="http://imageshack.com/f/ntvlcsnap2012041322h01m40p" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">ImageShack</a>
  </header>
  <article class="onebox-body">
    <img src="http://imageshack.com/scaled/medium/857/vlcsnap2012041322h01m40.png" class="thumbnail" width="" height="">

<h3><a href="http://imageshack.com/f/ntvlcsnap2012041322h01m40p" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">vlcsnap2012041322h01m40.png - Click to see more photos</a></h3>

<p>Store and share all of your images @ IMAGESHACK.com</p>


  </article>
  <div class="onebox-metadata">
    
    
  </div>
  <div style="clear: both"></div>
</aside>

          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/help-with-custom-whip-models-please/439572/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/help-with-custom-whip-models-please/439572/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 14 Apr 2012 02:27:56 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-439572-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/help-with-custom-whip-models-please/439572.rss">HELP With Custom Whip Models Please!</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
