<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Pickpocketing help - Scar script</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/pickpocketing-help-scar-script/347900</link>
    <description>Well I thought this would work but apparently it&#39;s not.  I was trying to call 2 x,y axis locations in 1 time with mouse color but I think I&#39;m doing something wrong.

Here&#39;s what I got

[code]program Thiever;
{.include SRL/SRL.scar}

const
delay = 300;
NPC =  4821407;///NPC color

var
x,y : integer;

procedure thieve;
begin
  If(findcolor(x, y, NPC, 0, 0, 600, 600))then
  Mouse(x,y,2,2,false);
  wait(10);
  Mouse(x,(y-40),true);
end;

begin
  SetupSRL;
  repeat
    wait(delay+random(250));
    thieve;
  until(false)
end.[/code]

When I right click the &quot;man&quot; I was trying to get from that current location, -40 down the y axis of that current location to &quot;pickpocket&quot; which I thought would work.

It doesn&#39;t work the mouse goes straight to x,y top right screen and 40 down lol.

So I tried another method of bitmaps.  I selected the &quot;pickpocket&quot; text, and painted the background black and whatnot got it all setup, and after I added in a conditional statement to see if it&#39;d say if it found that image or not, it never found it.

So I read the help file in F1 and found another method of text searching, well I couldn&#39;t figure out how to get that to work to just search for the text &quot;pickpocket.&quot; And yeah.

Anyone have any solution to this? I wanna be able to click pickpocket. &gt;.&lt;</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 08 Jul 2010 07:20:39 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/pickpocketing-help-scar-script/347900.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Pickpocketing help - Scar script</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Innovation Innovation]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/innovation">@Innovation</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Well I thought this would work but apparently it’s not.  I was trying to call 2 x,y axis locations in 1 time with mouse color but I think I’m doing something wrong.</p>
<p>Here’s what I got</p>
<p>[code]program Thiever;<br>
{.include SRL/SRL.scar}</p>
<p>const<br>
delay = 300;<br>
NPC =  4821407;///NPC color</p>
<p>var<br>
x,y : integer;</p>
<p>procedure thieve;<br>
begin<br>
If(findcolor(x, y, NPC, 0, 0, 600, 600))then<br>
Mouse(x,y,2,2,false);<br>
wait(10);<br>
Mouse(x,(y-40),true);<br>
end;</p>
<p>begin<br>
SetupSRL;<br>
repeat<br>
wait(delay+random(250));<br>
thieve;<br>
until(false)<br>
end.[/code]</p>
<p>When I right click the “man” I was trying to get from that current location, -40 down the y axis of that current location to “pickpocket” which I thought would work.</p>
<p>It doesn’t work the mouse goes straight to x,y top right screen and 40 down lol.</p>
<p>So I tried another method of bitmaps.  I selected the “pickpocket” text, and painted the background black and whatnot got it all setup, and after I added in a conditional statement to see if it’d say if it found that image or not, it never found it.</p>
<p>So I read the help file in F1 and found another method of text searching, well I couldn’t figure out how to get that to work to just search for the text “pickpocket.” And yeah.</p>
<p>Anyone have any solution to this? I wanna be able to click pickpocket. &gt;.&lt;</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/pickpocketing-help-scar-script/347900/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/pickpocketing-help-scar-script/347900/1</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jul 2010 07:20:39 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-347900-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/pickpocketing-help-scar-script/347900.rss">Pickpocketing help - Scar script</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
