<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>[317] Need a tutorial on how to make... Just look [317]</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/317-need-a-tutorial-on-how-to-make-just-look-317/293105</link>
    <description>I am using Allstar V2 (i know, alot of people say it sucks... just using it for expirimenting) but i would like to add in a clan wars. A custom clan wars where you can fight the other clan (obviously) and not lose your items. And you know what clan you are on by obtaining a cape depending on the team you are on. and you get tickets if you win. and the tickets go for rewards. Please help =P

And I would like to know how to add in pk points when you kill someone. Please help with that... that one shouldn&#39;t be to hard.

And i would like to add a custom Bounty Hunter (like pk box, just you actually get a target) and they drop what they have unless they have an item... which they will need to buy with pk points. =] please help with all of these, will include you in creditz for showing me a tutorial or making the tutorial. =]</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 05 Aug 2009 17:09:22 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/317-need-a-tutorial-on-how-to-make-just-look-317/293105.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>[317] Need a tutorial on how to make... Just look [317]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@king_gauge king gauge]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/king_gauge">@king_gauge</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I am using Allstar V2 (i know, alot of people say it sucks… just using it for expirimenting) but i would like to add in a clan wars. A custom clan wars where you can fight the other clan (obviously) and not lose your items. And you know what clan you are on by obtaining a cape depending on the team you are on. and you get tickets if you win. and the tickets go for rewards. Please help =P</p>
<p>And I would like to know how to add in pk points when you kill someone. Please help with that… that one shouldn’t be to hard.</p>
<p>And i would like to add a custom Bounty Hunter (like pk box, just you actually get a target) and they drop what they have unless they have an item… which they will need to buy with pk points. =] please help with all of these, will include you in creditz for showing me a tutorial or making the tutorial. =]</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/317-need-a-tutorial-on-how-to-make-just-look-317/293105/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/317-need-a-tutorial-on-how-to-make-just-look-317/293105/1</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 05 Aug 2009 17:09:22 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-293105-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/317-need-a-tutorial-on-how-to-make-just-look-317/293105.rss">[317] Need a tutorial on how to make... Just look [317]</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
