<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>[1.8.1] Chunk64 Minecraft Survival (24/7) [Whitelist]</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/1-8-1-chunk64-minecraft-survival-24-7-whitelist/420025</link>
    <description>Server IP: 176.31.130.212

Introduction
Chunk64 is a new, whitelisted Minecraft Survival server. It has all the essential plugins to prevent and rollback griefing if needed to. We are currently building up a great community as we grow, and would like more regular and polite players to contribute to the server.

You can join the server to look around, but to have building privileges you must sign up here!

Server Information
As mentioned in the introduction, Chunk64 is a survival server - But we&#39;ve tried to incorporate the creative aspect of Minecraft into the server by adding in the ability to purchase materials (coloured wool, glowstone, grass blocks etc.) using an in-game currency plugin.

•We use iConomy (a currency system) which allows players to purchase unobtainable game items from shops, and trade with each other.
•We have disabled Creeper explosions and Endermen so they don&#39;t destroy your homes.
•Anti-griefing and rollback plugins are installed, just to destroy a griefer&#39;s hard work.
•We have admins and moderators on for most of the time, so you could always ask for help.
•The best part: A friendly community. Most of the players on our server are willing to help newcomers and each other - We kick/jail/ban naughty players and trolls.

Rules
♫ You know the rules, and so do I... ♫
[1] Speak normally, not like &quot;Can I haz fr33 di4m0ndz pl0x&quot;.
[2] No hacking or fly mods, we have plugins which detect cheating.
[3] Don&#39;t you dare steal! Admins and moderators can monitor chests and catch the thief.
[4] And obviously, don&#39;t grief. We all hate griefers, and you will get globally banned (MCbans).

Head to: http://bit.ly/thechunk64 for more info, screenshots and whitelist application!</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 30 Oct 2011 15:31:34 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Minecraft</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/1-8-1-chunk64-minecraft-survival-24-7-whitelist/420025.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>[1.8.1] Chunk64 Minecraft Survival (24/7) [Whitelist]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Chinwe Chinwe]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/chinwe">@Chinwe</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Server IP: 176.31.130.212</p>
<p>Introduction<br>
Chunk64 is a new, whitelisted Minecraft Survival server. It has all the essential plugins to prevent and rollback griefing if needed to. We are currently building up a great community as we grow, and would like more regular and polite players to contribute to the server.</p>
<p>You can join the server to look around, but to have building privileges you must sign up here!</p>
<p>Server Information<br>
As mentioned in the introduction, Chunk64 is a survival server - But we’ve tried to incorporate the creative aspect of Minecraft into the server by adding in the ability to purchase materials (coloured wool, glowstone, grass blocks etc.) using an in-game currency plugin.</p>
<p>•We use iConomy (a currency system) which allows players to purchase unobtainable game items from shops, and trade with each other.<br>
•We have disabled Creeper explosions and Endermen so they don’t destroy your homes.<br>
•Anti-griefing and rollback plugins are installed, just to destroy a griefer’s hard work.<br>
•We have admins and moderators on for most of the time, so you could always ask for help.<br>
•The best part: A friendly community. Most of the players on our server are willing to help newcomers and each other - We kick/jail/ban naughty players and trolls.</p>
<p>Rules<br>
♫ You know the rules, and so do I… ♫<br>
[1] Speak normally, not like “Can I haz fr33 di4m0ndz pl0x”.<br>
[2] No hacking or fly mods, we have plugins which detect cheating.<br>
[3] Don’t you dare steal! Admins and moderators can monitor chests and catch the thief.<br>
[4] And obviously, don’t grief. We all hate griefers, and you will get globally banned (MCbans).</p>
<p>Head to: <a href="http://bit.ly/thechunk64" rel="nofollow noopener">http://bit.ly/thechunk64</a> for more info, screenshots and whitelist application!</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/1-8-1-chunk64-minecraft-survival-24-7-whitelist/420025/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/1-8-1-chunk64-minecraft-survival-24-7-whitelist/420025/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 30 Oct 2011 15:31:34 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-420025-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/1-8-1-chunk64-minecraft-survival-24-7-whitelist/420025.rss">[1.8.1] Chunk64 Minecraft Survival (24/7) [Whitelist]</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
