<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>This is help for you to post pictures</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/this-is-help-for-you-to-post-pictures/167597</link>
    <description>Alright, I seen a few questions with people asking on how to put pictures on their post. So here is help on how to do that.

Difficulty-----3/10  (Depends on experience)

Needed Programs----- MS PAINT (Paint)

You will also need a photobucket account (IT IS FREE)



-First-
Take a picture of what you want from you&#39;re computer by hitting the &quot;pcs&quot; button or the &quot;PrtSc&quot; button.


-Second-
After you have done that, open up paint and hold &quot;Ctrl&quot; and hit &quot;v&quot; and you&#39;re image will appear. You may edit this image how ever you would like and if you make a mistake hold &quot;Ctrl&quot; and hit &quot;z&quot;


-Third-
Once the image is done being edited save it under the pictures folder (If you do not have a pictures folder I would recomend making one)


-Fourth-
If you&#39;re image is saved go to http://photobucket.com/ and sign up


-Fith-
Once you have signed up, make a new album and upload you&#39;re image you took a picture of. (The upload could take a while so be patient)


-Sixth-
After the photo has been uploaded view it and it will have a list around the bottom right that looks like this... 
[img]http://i254.photobucket.com/albums/hh85/dom_333/TUTforphoto1.jpg[/img]


-Seventh-
Use the one thats right above the &quot;New&quot; one for the forums, and yeah, so on...


-Last but not Least
Once you&#39;re finished and you get you&#39;re pictures or as people like to call them &quot;pics&quot; you can get something like this but with YOU&#39;RE picture...


[img]http://i254.photobucket.com/albums/hh85/dom_333/addictingscape2.jpg[/img]



I HOPE I REALLY HELPED! HAPPY POSTING TO ALL YOU PEOPLE! I HOPE YOU HAVE FUN WITH YOU&#39;RE PICTURES AND DON&#39;T BREAK RULES! (If you plan on flamming you CAN and WILL be reported.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 25 Dec 2007 04:19:22 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/this-is-help-for-you-to-post-pictures/167597.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>This is help for you to post pictures</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Bathus_Dio1 Bathus_Dio]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/bathus_dio1">@Bathus_Dio1</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Alright, I seen a few questions with people asking on how to put pictures on their post. So here is help on how to do that.</p>
<p>Difficulty-----3/10  (Depends on experience)</p>
<p>Needed Programs----- MS PAINT (Paint)</p>
<p>You will also need a photobucket account (IT IS FREE)</p>
<p>-First-<br>
Take a picture of what you want from you’re computer by hitting the “pcs” button or the “PrtSc” button.</p>
<p>-Second-<br>
After you have done that, open up paint and hold “Ctrl” and hit “v” and you’re image will appear. You may edit this image how ever you would like and if you make a mistake hold “Ctrl” and hit “z”</p>
<p>-Third-<br>
Once the image is done being edited save it under the pictures folder (If you do not have a pictures folder I would recomend making one)</p>
<p>-Fourth-<br>
If you’re image is saved go to <a href="http://photobucket.com/" rel="nofollow noopener">http://photobucket.com/</a> and sign up</p>
<p>-Fith-<br>
Once you have signed up, make a new album and upload you’re image you took a picture of. (The upload could take a while so be patient)</p>
<p>-Sixth-<br>
After the photo has been uploaded view it and it will have a list around the bottom right that looks like this…<br>
<img src="http://i254.photobucket.com/albums/hh85/dom_333/TUTforphoto1.jpg" alt width="" height=""></p>
<p>-Seventh-<br>
Use the one thats right above the “New” one for the forums, and yeah, so on…</p>
<p>-Last but not Least<br>
Once you’re finished and you get you’re pictures or as people like to call them “pics” you can get something like this but with YOU’RE picture…</p>
<p><img src="http://i254.photobucket.com/albums/hh85/dom_333/addictingscape2.jpg" alt width="" height=""></p>
<p>I HOPE I REALLY HELPED! HAPPY POSTING TO ALL YOU PEOPLE! I HOPE YOU HAVE FUN WITH YOU’RE PICTURES AND DON’T BREAK RULES! (If you plan on flamming you CAN and WILL be reported.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/this-is-help-for-you-to-post-pictures/167597/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/this-is-help-for-you-to-post-pictures/167597/1</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 25 Dec 2007 04:19:22 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-167597-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/this-is-help-for-you-to-post-pictures/167597.rss">This is help for you to post pictures</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
