<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>The team</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-team/411289</link>
    <description>This team is picked not only to moderate the site, but also to manage contributions for the site. We expect members of the team to post tutorials, answer questions, and contribute in any way possible. We expect members of the team to also post suggestions for new additions to the team, if they have any.

The team may start small, but we&#39;ll be sure to add members to balance out the workload we face. An idea I do have is to look for members that contribute outstandingly in particular sections, and making them a board moderator over those sections. If they do not falter in their contributions, and they prove a competent and able moderator, then they will be asked to join this team.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 21 Aug 2011 00:11:47 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Community Suggestions</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-team/411289.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>The team</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@mod_taharok Taharok]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/mod_taharok">@mod_taharok</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>This team is picked not only to moderate the site, but also to manage contributions for the site. We expect members of the team to post tutorials, answer questions, and contribute in any way possible. We expect members of the team to also post suggestions for new additions to the team, if they have any.</p>
<p>The team may start small, but we’ll be sure to add members to balance out the workload we face. An idea I do have is to look for members that contribute outstandingly in particular sections, and making them a board moderator over those sections. If they do not falter in their contributions, and they prove a competent and able moderator, then they will be asked to join this team.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-team/411289/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-team/411289/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 21 Aug 2011 00:11:47 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-411289-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-team/411289.rss">The team</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
