<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>[317] Requesting Host</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/317-requesting-host/524592</link>
    <description>Hello, my name is Bronson and I&#39;m looking for someone to host my server. I would do this myself but my main computer broke and I don&#39;t have the time or money to fix it. The server is a 317 PI that I&#39;ve just begun to code. I&#39;m open to a source switch if the host does not like the base that is being used or would just like to start fresh from another. This of course is only temporary until I get the money necessary to purchase a VPS. You will receive owner alongside myself and a set amount of the donation profit each month. Anyone who is interested can contact me through this site or send me a contact request on Skype stating why you are adding me, thank you.

Skype: bronson.bon</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2013 03:01:15 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/317-requesting-host/524592.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>[317] Requesting Host</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Bronson_Bon Bronson Bon]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/bronson_bon">@Bronson_Bon</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Hello, my name is Bronson and I’m looking for someone to host my server. I would do this myself but my main computer broke and I don’t have the time or money to fix it. The server is a 317 PI that I’ve just begun to code. I’m open to a source switch if the host does not like the base that is being used or would just like to start fresh from another. This of course is only temporary until I get the money necessary to purchase a VPS. You will receive owner alongside myself and a set amount of the donation profit each month. Anyone who is interested can contact me through this site or send me a contact request on Skype stating why you are adding me, thank you.</p>
<p>Skype: bronson.bon</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/317-requesting-host/524592/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/317-requesting-host/524592/1</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2013 03:01:15 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-524592-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/317-requesting-host/524592.rss">[317] Requesting Host</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
