<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Ambitious Project</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/ambitious-project/542684</link>
    <description>Hey guys, I hope you&#39;re all well.

I&#39;m currently working as an ESL teacher and some of my students will be going on to study Programming next year so I thought it&#39;d be an interesting idea to ask them to develop an RSC private server for experience. I want them to develop the server for one or two years and then maybe try to create their own game afterwards from scratch afterwards as I have some interesting ideas.

What I would like them to do is completely strip down RSC; redesign maps, npcs, characters and game play. How achievable is this? What is the best source to use etc.?

Secondly, if possible, could someone give me/the students some advice or point us in the right direction to find programs for redesigning npcs, animations and maps etc.

I&#39;d appreciate any general advice from those more experienced developers here.

Thanks.
Sal</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 09 May 2014 23:04:18 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/ambitious-project/542684.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Ambitious Project</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@SalRathor SalRathor]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/salrathor">@SalRathor</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Ideally both languages need to be supported simultaneously. Users should be able to type in both Arabic and English whereever they are whereas npcs and quests in their areas would be function in their languages.</p>
<p>I want to create a fun game with real world parallels and lessons where people can play yet also learn.</p>
<p>Regarding the students, makes sense. I may see if they’re interested in getting involved in basic tasks like modifying land etc. and try to find more advanced coders from the community like cleako to help out.</p>
<p>Thanks</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/ambitious-project/542684/15">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/ambitious-project/542684/15</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 May 2014 23:04:18 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-542684-15</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/ambitious-project/542684.rss">Ambitious Project</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Ambitious Project</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@nacional nacional]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/nacional">@nacional</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I agree completely with lothy. I think your heart is in the right place but it’s just going to be overwhelming.<br>
Take a look at <a href="http://alice.org" rel="nofollow noopener">alice.org</a>. Personally I find alice to be annoying, but it would cover concepts that will be useful<br>
and maybe then you can have them tackle something as ambitious as going to through dozens of classes with<br>
little documentation.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/ambitious-project/542684/14">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/ambitious-project/542684/14</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2014 02:40:10 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-542684-14</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/ambitious-project/542684.rss">Ambitious Project</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Ambitious Project</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Protosstribe object]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/protosstribe">@Protosstribe</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Or simply use the java.util.ResourceBundle class from the standard Java library. It’s used for internationalization (i18n) and localization (l10n). That is, language- and locale specific resources, such as text translations, images and any other Object type for that matter.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/ambitious-project/542684/13">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/ambitious-project/542684/13</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2014 07:47:38 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-542684-13</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/ambitious-project/542684.rss">Ambitious Project</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Ambitious Project</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Nothing1 -Nothing]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/nothing1">@Nothing1</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Or have a language configuration file which holds all the translations in them and depending on the language selection load the appropriate file. Then make the client send language type upon login to let server know which language client uses and switch the server to use the appropriate language configuration file for the client.</p>
<pre><code class="lang-auto">  &lt;LanguageDef&gt;
    &lt;text&gt;CANT_RETREAT&lt;/text&gt;
    &lt;translation&gt;&lt;/translation&gt;
  &lt;/LanguageDef&gt;</code></pre>
<p>This is the way most forums do their translations btw.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/ambitious-project/542684/12">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/ambitious-project/542684/12</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2014 06:16:32 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-542684-12</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/ambitious-project/542684.rss">Ambitious Project</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Ambitious Project</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@cleako cleako]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/cleako">@cleako</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Arguments against aside, a multi-language supporting game should be viable with duplicate talking NPCs, such as bankers that are separated by water through two islands with one island for English speaking NPCs and the other for Arabic speaking NPCs.</p>
<p>My thoughts on how to do a multi-language client would be to offer two client.jar files with one in English and the other in Arabic in the cache with a launcher GUI that first does a MD5 hash check for any client.jar updates and then display both game world and language selections. The world IP setting would be saved in the client.properties file in the cache folder for which IP to connect to and then the launcher would open the appropriate client.jar based on which language was selected in the launcher. Both clients would share the cache with the exception of Items.rscd, Npcs.rscd, Spells.rscd, and Prayers.rscd. Duplicates of the above mentioned .rscd cache files would be made and one set would be translated to Arabic. The Arabic client would then point to the differing Arabic cache files and various hard coded java game messages would be translated too for the Arabic client, such as game menu text. Each client would do it’s own MD5 hash check for updated cache files at launch so players wouldn’t have to wait for cache files of a language they don’t know to download.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/ambitious-project/542684/11">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/ambitious-project/542684/11</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2014 21:24:57 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-542684-11</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/ambitious-project/542684.rss">Ambitious Project</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Ambitious Project</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@lothy Lothy]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/lothy">@lothy</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Yeah, no. Do the right thing and teach them the things they’d learn in any other introduction to programming course. To do anything else is negligent, and will potentially turn them off the subject.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/ambitious-project/542684/10">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/ambitious-project/542684/10</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2014 23:19:17 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-542684-10</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/ambitious-project/542684.rss">Ambitious Project</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Ambitious Project</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@SalRathor SalRathor]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/salrathor">@SalRathor</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I’m not a computer science teacher, I’m an ESL teacher.</p>
<p>I’m not expecting them to build something amazing over night but it would give them something to focus on starting with small modifications and developing it further as they learn more. This would be in addition to their computer programming classes and something to focus on over their three month summer vacation.</p>
<p>It wouldn’t be a class project. It would be a project ran by one student in collaboration with other students who may be interested, and this of course, if he is interested.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/ambitious-project/542684/9">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/ambitious-project/542684/9</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2014 20:45:01 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-542684-9</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/ambitious-project/542684.rss">Ambitious Project</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Ambitious Project</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@lothy Lothy]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/lothy">@lothy</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Why on earth do you think this is a suitable project for a class of presumably new programmers?<br>
If you were a good teacher then you would be having them complete small, discrete, achievable tasks. Things like printing messages to the console, reversing arrays, calculating an average given an array, perhaps converting between Celsius and Fahrenheit. Certainly nothing more complex than something like an insertion sort algorithm.</p>
<p>Don’t be a shit instructor. Have them cover useful content.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/ambitious-project/542684/8">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/ambitious-project/542684/8</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2014 11:24:41 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-542684-8</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/ambitious-project/542684.rss">Ambitious Project</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Ambitious Project</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Zlacki Zlacki]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/zlacki">@Zlacki</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Smarter to design a better game engine using a different language, in my opinion.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/ambitious-project/542684/7">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/ambitious-project/542684/7</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2014 01:12:44 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-542684-7</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/ambitious-project/542684.rss">Ambitious Project</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Ambitious Project</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@SalRathor SalRathor]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/salrathor">@SalRathor</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Really? I didn’t know that…? Interesting.</p>
<p>I’ll look it up.</p>
<p>Thanks.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/ambitious-project/542684/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/ambitious-project/542684/6</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2014 20:02:54 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-542684-6</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/ambitious-project/542684.rss">Ambitious Project</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Ambitious Project</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Rodgerwilco Rodgerwilco]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/rodgerwilco">@Rodgerwilco</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>As a teacher you should know that you can use copyrighted material for educational purposes…</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/ambitious-project/542684/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/ambitious-project/542684/5</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2014 19:40:38 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-542684-5</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/ambitious-project/542684.rss">Ambitious Project</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Ambitious Project</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@cleako cleako]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/cleako">@cleako</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Jagex has not bothered with litigation against RSC private servers for intellectual property for years, if ever. If it were to become a project that would be sold, it would attract their attention. As long as it doesn’t become front page Reddit material, Jagex will not notice or care.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/ambitious-project/542684/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/ambitious-project/542684/4</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2014 18:46:41 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-542684-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/ambitious-project/542684.rss">Ambitious Project</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Ambitious Project</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@SalRathor SalRathor]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/salrathor">@SalRathor</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Thanks a lot Cleako, I really appreciate your help. I’ve added you to skype if that’s ok?</p>
<p>Your project sounds interesting.</p>
<p>My aim is to develop a game which also has language learning elements attached. I want people to feel like they’re playing with language being a natural byproduct.</p>
<p>I have a few interesting ideas i’d like to experiment with…</p>
<p>Oh, also, if we use the RSC game engine and strip the original content would jagex still have a problem with this?</p>
<p>Thanks again for your help.<br>
Sal</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/ambitious-project/542684/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/ambitious-project/542684/3</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2014 18:43:21 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-542684-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/ambitious-project/542684.rss">Ambitious Project</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Ambitious Project</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@cleako cleako]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/cleako">@cleako</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I am currently working on doing the exact same thing in terms of stripping all of the game assets and building a new game from scratch using the RSC game engine. Its not too terribly difficult to build new game assets but I hope to make things easier. My project is to create a zombie survival game, similar to DayZ using the RSC game engine. I am using Peeter’s DarkQuest source as my base which is based off the RSCA source which is based off of the RSCDaemon source. While Moparscape Classic is a well done project, it mixes in a lot of scala programming on top of the java and the added complexity is not personally my cup of tea right now. I have been fixing and improving several of the community tools and plan to create all of the necessary guides for how to use them (2D landscape editor, 3D landscape editor, sprite editor, map generator, etc).</p>
<p>The goal is to keep everything completely open source and available through GitHub. The programming IDE that I am using for the project is NetBeans which I have come to prefer over Eclipse. The RSC private server community on here used to be absolutely atrocious in terms of immaturity and uppity programmers but over the last few years, most have lost interest and left. Those who are here now have been great to work with from what I have experienced. I would suggest keeping what you develop running just within the classroom and not publicly playable as there remains at least one or two individuals that choose to launch daily DDoS attacks on various RSC private servers for different reasons.</p>
<p>MS paint works best for editing sprite PNG files. The rest of the RSC assets are proprietary and use the various RSC tools that the community has developed over the years. Most of it is XML based. The server uses MySQL for the database and the client cache is downloaded from a webserver. The webserver requirement for the cache can be removed - I just need to make some modifications to the client and tools that depend on it.</p>
<p>This is the project as well as various repositories for each part, including the tools that I am working with all inside GitHub: <a href="http://cleako.github.io" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">http://cleako.github.io</a></p>
<p>Would text-based instructions and video recorded demonstrations be the most useful for your students as non-native English speakers? Not sure what other methods for instruction would work well.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/ambitious-project/542684/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/ambitious-project/542684/2</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2014 16:26:01 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-542684-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/ambitious-project/542684.rss">Ambitious Project</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Ambitious Project</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@SalRathor SalRathor]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/salrathor">@SalRathor</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Hey guys, I hope you’re all well.</p>
<p>I’m currently working as an ESL teacher and some of my students will be going on to study Programming next year so I thought it’d be an interesting idea to ask them to develop an RSC private server for experience. I want them to develop the server for one or two years and then maybe try to create their own game afterwards from scratch afterwards as I have some interesting ideas.</p>
<p>What I would like them to do is completely strip down RSC; redesign maps, npcs, characters and game play. How achievable is this? What is the best source to use etc.?</p>
<p>Secondly, if possible, could someone give me/the students some advice or point us in the right direction to find programs for redesigning npcs, animations and maps etc.</p>
<p>I’d appreciate any general advice from those more experienced developers here.</p>
<p>Thanks.<br>
Sal</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/ambitious-project/542684/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/ambitious-project/542684/1</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2014 14:08:10 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-542684-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/ambitious-project/542684.rss">Ambitious Project</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
