<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>How to fix glitch in 508</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-fix-glitch-in-508/290461</link>
    <description>Hello, haxifix here with another question.

I have MithScape Source and I love it, but it has 1 glitch that apply&#39;s to alot of stuff that needs fixing.

When you are in a bank, or a trade screen, or a shop screen, basically any type of interface, and you don&#39;t click the close button, you just walk out of the screen, it still thinks that you are in that screen, like if you are in a trade, and you put up an item, then you walk out of the trade screen, your item is still in that screen, and if you click other items in your inventory they go into the trade screen which you can&#39;t see anymore, and the only way to fix this problem that I know of is to go into a different interface screen and then close that and you will be back to normal.

Like let&#39;s say the situation above just happened, to fix it, just go into your bank and just click close, you should have your items back, but that is a hassel and not everyone knows about that, so....is there any way to add some code that like if the players click out of an interface is executes the code of clicking the close button?

Thank you in advance.

- haxifix[br][br][size=1]Posted on: July 23, 2009, 03:55:25 pm[/size][hr]bump</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 23 Jul 2009 18:02:01 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-fix-glitch-in-508/290461.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>How to fix glitch in 508</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@haxifix haxifix]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/haxifix">@haxifix</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Hello, haxifix here with another question.</p>
<p>I have MithScape Source and I love it, but it has 1 glitch that apply’s to alot of stuff that needs fixing.</p>
<p>When you are in a bank, or a trade screen, or a shop screen, basically any type of interface, and you don’t click the close button, you just walk out of the screen, it still thinks that you are in that screen, like if you are in a trade, and you put up an item, then you walk out of the trade screen, your item is still in that screen, and if you click other items in your inventory they go into the trade screen which you can’t see anymore, and the only way to fix this problem that I know of is to go into a different interface screen and then close that and you will be back to normal.</p>
<p>Like let’s say the situation above just happened, to fix it, just go into your bank and just click close, you should have your items back, but that is a hassel and not everyone knows about that, so…is there any way to add some code that like if the players click out of an interface is executes the code of clicking the close button?</p>
<p>Thank you in advance.</p>
<ul>
<li>haxifix[br][br][size=1]Posted on: July 23, 2009, 03:55:25 pm[/size][hr]bump</li>
</ul>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-fix-glitch-in-508/290461/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-fix-glitch-in-508/290461/1</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jul 2009 18:02:01 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-290461-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-fix-glitch-in-508/290461.rss">How to fix glitch in 508</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
