<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Donations</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/donations/537272</link>
    <description>I want to talk about donations and what people think of them in RSPS&#39;s. I understand this is a controversial subject, but they are generally a necessity to maintain a server&#39;s online presence. 

I have had experience to say that servers that accept donations purely for the sake of funding the server do not work. There has to be more of an incentive other than a forum rank for people to donate. Where do you draw the line between giving incentive to donate, and giving an unfair advantage? What I&#39;d like to know your opinion on is:

[CODE]
[B]Do you believe donating is essential for a server to be successful?:[/B]
[B]Do you tend to donate for servers you play?:[/B]
[B]Do you agree with donating for items?:[/B]
[B]What do you consider a balance between perks for donating and an unfair advantage?:[/B]
[B]What else do you find acceptable/unacceptable?:[/B]
[/CODE]

Personally, I agree that &quot;donations&quot; (even though it defies the definition of what a donation is) are essential if you want to keep your game online for people to play, but at the same time if there was a way I could provide a server and fund it all myself, I would, and donating would not be an option.

Unfortunately, I&#39;d have to say 99.9% of all servers that have a .com domain and paid hosting are not ran by people who can comfortably afford to run it for free. I know a few people get hundreds or even thousands a month in donations, and barely invest the money back into the game (advertising, security, better hosting, paying developers etc.). So if you are getting more in donations than what it costs to run, what do you do with the rest of the money? Some keep it as a sort of payment for their hard work (which is acceptable). What about holding weekly competitions with monetary prizes as a sort of thanks to your players?

Please discuss the aspects of donations in RSPS&#39;s and what your opinions are on what works, what is right and what is wrong. I&#39;m interested in seeing other people&#39;s views on something that is quite a big part of private servers nowadays.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2014 15:15:17 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/donations/537272.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Donations</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Encryption Encryption]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/encryption">@Encryption</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[B]Do you believe donating is essential for a server to be successful?:[/B] Well yes for expenses towards the server alone, but most people want it for their pockets.<br>
[B]Do you tend to donate for servers you play?:[/B] Yes, I’ve donated to a PK Server, and the benefits are quite amazing. Although I don’t play anymore.<br>
[B]Do you agree with donating for items?:[/B] No, just for a status, and the ability to wield certain items like members on the official RuneScape server.<br>
[B]What do you consider a balance between perks for donating and an unfair advantage?:[/B] Hmm, not sure everyone has their view on this. I’m not an O.P kind of guy.<br>
[B]What else do you find acceptable/unacceptable?:[/B] They should switch “donations” for the server to buy player membership today.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/donations/537272/19">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/donations/537272/19</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2014 15:15:17 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-537272-19</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/donations/537272.rss">Donations</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Donations</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@mastertech0 mastertech0]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/mastertech0">@mastertech0</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote" data-post="2" data-topic="537272">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/zyle1992/40/5_e05bb34c421432ee4d40de30c10af3e5.png" class="avatar"> zyle1992:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>I have always been a firm believer that “donating” to get some sort of benefit in game (higher exp rate, items, etc) has always been a bit shady. I’ve always believed that donations should go solely to maintaining the server, and website if it has one. Not as a way to make a profit.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I personally believe that to be true. I mean you don’t even care that it’s helping the server your biggest factor is that you got a “membership” as Iare69 said it’s called donating not subscribing.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/donations/537272/18">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/donations/537272/18</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2014 14:31:19 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-537272-18</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/donations/537272.rss">Donations</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Donations</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Clawz_fury lare69]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/clawz_fury">@Clawz_fury</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[B]Do you believe donating is essential for a server to be successful?:[/B] Yes and no, I mean some people need them in order to pay for website and vps expenses.</p>
<p>[B]Do you tend to donate for servers you play?:[/B] lol no I would never waste my money on a private server</p>
<p>[B]Do you agree with donating for items?:[/B] No, that’s a great way to ruin an economy. The same thing is happening to runescape right now! They’re basically letting players buy their items and look where its gotten them?</p>
<p>[B]What do you consider a balance between perks for donating and an unfair advantage?:[/B] Balance would be giving donators yell privileges or a custom title, anything tangible or that gives them an advantage in game is unfair.</p>
<p>[B]What else do you find acceptable/unacceptable?:[/B] Donators shouldn’t even expect anything from donating. It’s called a <span class="bbcode-b">donation</span>, not a membership. <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=5" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/donations/537272/17">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/donations/537272/17</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2014 06:34:49 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-537272-17</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/donations/537272.rss">Donations</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Donations</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@arham_4 arham 4]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/arham_4">@arham_4</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[B]Do you believe donating is essential for a server to be successful?:[/B] Very, I speak from experience. I run entirely on donations.<br>
[B]Do you tend to donate for servers you play?:[/B] If it seems promising and if I have the money (which is usually the reason why I don’t, I didnt get a paypal until maybe 2 months ago, which was when I stopped playing RSPS (most of them atleast)).<br>
[B]Do you agree with donating for items?:[/B] No.<br>
[B]What do you consider a balance between perks for donating and an unfair advantage?:[/B] Add on to features, don’t bend them. What this means is that you don’t say,</p>
<blockquote>Dragon claws hit harder for donators!</blockquote>
Rather, you give them a new feature. Like:
[code]
- Auras
- Custom titles
- An extra training area? (no bosses)
- A special socializing area? (only if the community is large, don't split the community)
- Maybe a small EXP boost?
- Some 1 or 2 extra shops.
[/code]
In my eyes, I'd see that as a good reason to donate. I get features to add onto that are visible (auras, titles), a place to train my skills with a bit less time (extra training area), a place to just socialize with other guys who donated for the server I like (socializing area), a small extra kick in for something that happens to me with almost every action (EXP), and some extra equipment that still can be acquired in one place, but can be accessed quicker (the shops).
[B]What else do you find acceptable/unacceptable?:[/B] Don't give free times. I mean, don't give free tradeable items. Maybe like an EXP lamp is fine, but not like 5000 whips. I prefer to not make currency (donator points), but I see it necessary as they can stack and give you money in larger numbers (so you can keep the server longer).
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/donations/537272/16">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/donations/537272/16</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 26 Feb 2014 22:34:29 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-537272-16</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/donations/537272.rss">Donations</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Donations</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Uncalled Uncalled]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/uncalled">@Uncalled</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[B]Do you believe donating is essential for a server to be successful?:[/B] Yes.</p>
<p>[B]Do you tend to donate for servers you play?:[/B] I don’t play any servers.</p>
<p>[B]Do you agree with donating for items?:[/B] Only for items that are also obtainable in game as well. So it’s like a “get it fast and easy” sort of method, if you don’t want to spend hours of bossing for a set. Also cosmetics are agreeable items to donate for as they give no bonuses in game, other than making your character look ‘cool’.</p>
<p>[B]What do you consider a balance between perks for donating and an unfair advantage?:[/B] Better drop rates, faster experience, etc. Nothing like boosted statistics, longer lasting potions, or anything that will make your character just more powerful in general. I once had a server that let extreme donors (granted, you had to donate a fairly large sum of money for this rank) have unlimited prayer points, so they wouldn’t have to fill their inventory more with potions and etc. But giving them access to things such as a bank command, faster drop rates, simple things like that would be a great incentive for players to donate.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/donations/537272/15">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/donations/537272/15</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 26 Feb 2014 21:19:46 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-537272-15</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/donations/537272.rss">Donations</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Donations</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@TheOfficialSkittles TheOfficialSkittles]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/theofficialskittles">@TheOfficialSkittles</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Donating to a server makes sense;<br>
People are commenting on her about not donating because the server must shut-down soon;<br>
There’s reason you don’t donate to a server that’s been up for 3 days or 3 weeks<br>
You donate to a server that’s got a 15+ player base for the benifits and a good eco;<br>
If you have a server that doesn’t have that there’s honestly no point in donating nuffsaid;</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/donations/537272/14">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/donations/537272/14</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2014 14:16:14 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-537272-14</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/donations/537272.rss">Donations</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Donations</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@JavaTC JavaTC]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/javatc">@JavaTC</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“Zombie Juice, post:12, topic:537272”][quote author=JavaTC link=topic=656088.msg4391676#msg4391676 date=1387754521]<br>
[B]Do you believe donating is essential for a server to be successful?:[/B]<br>
Yes, since servers cost money.  Granted it isn’t much money, however if you want to make a content-packed, feature full, unique server, a $12 vps probably won’t do for very long.</p>
<p>[B]Do you tend to donate for servers you play?:[/B]<br>
If I like them enough and the owner and staff are actually knowledgeable as to what they’re doing then I put a few bucks forward.  I have no issues doing so considering it’s entertainment and community.  Granted it isn’t exactly a big $50 donation, I doubt a few dollars will ever be turned down.</p>
<p>[B]Do you agree with donating for items?:[/B]<br>
Sure, nothing wrong with it.  Really the items should be cosmetic or have a small vantage over other weapons, but not huge.  Just don’t offer rare monster drops or anything, preferably they should be earned.</p>
<p>[B]What do you consider a balance between perks for donating and an unfair advantage?:[/B]<br>
Depends, some say donating in and of itself is unfair since not everyone has money.  I don’t hold that stance.  If someone who doesn’t want to spend or just doesn’t have the time into the server, I have no issue with them dropping $50 or so to get a new set of armor and a shiny sword.  But anything offered should be <span class="bbcode-u">reasonably</span> obtainable in-game.  Reasonably meaning not voting every 12 hours for 2 months straight, or killing 10000 monsters for a single item.</p>
<p>[B]What else do you find acceptable/unacceptable?:[/B]<br>
No Rare materials (Barrows, whips, etc) in shops in the donator zone.  Stuff like dragon bones is fine, but they should have to work for things too, not just blow money out the ass to get whatever they want when they want it.<br>
[/quote]<br>
very good points. a lot of, if not all, people agree with cosmetics being the items that are donateable. i, however, really despise being able to donate on a spawn server for korasi, chaotics, vesta, statius etc. i get very frustrated trying to fight people who have the maximum op equipment, when i first start out only having a fighter torso and whip. i don’t feel like donating unless it’s a server i have been playing for a couple of months. most spawn servers are the same, spawn, pk safe for coins and pk risk. not much incentive to donate to all of them because those with a budget need to plan their donations carefully.[/quote]<br>
That also differs for me since I rarely do PvP, the pking community is absolutely terrible :p.  My own view is having a few kids with big wallets running around with their toys is much better than a server that has no VPS and few players because there’s no incentive to donate.  Even if you’re against it and justify your views in every way, the fact of the matter is that your competition offers good incentive while you don’t, and lazy people will naturally flock there.  So you can either retain some kind of self-awarded honor by not having it, or have it and run the server properly while hiring developers to make new content.  Your choice.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/donations/537272/13">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/donations/537272/13</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 23 Dec 2013 07:22:05 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-537272-13</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/donations/537272.rss">Donations</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Donations</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Zombie_Juice Zombie Juice]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/zombie_juice">@Zombie_Juice</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“JavaTC, post:11, topic:537272”][B]Do you believe donating is essential for a server to be successful?:[/B]<br>
Yes, since servers cost money.  Granted it isn’t much money, however if you want to make a content-packed, feature full, unique server, a $12 vps probably won’t do for very long.</p>
<p>[B]Do you tend to donate for servers you play?:[/B]<br>
If I like them enough and the owner and staff are actually knowledgeable as to what they’re doing then I put a few bucks forward.  I have no issues doing so considering it’s entertainment and community.  Granted it isn’t exactly a big $50 donation, I doubt a few dollars will ever be turned down.</p>
<p>[B]Do you agree with donating for items?:[/B]<br>
Sure, nothing wrong with it.  Really the items should be cosmetic or have a small vantage over other weapons, but not huge.  Just don’t offer rare monster drops or anything, preferably they should be earned.</p>
<p>[B]What do you consider a balance between perks for donating and an unfair advantage?:[/B]<br>
Depends, some say donating in and of itself is unfair since not everyone has money.  I don’t hold that stance.  If someone who doesn’t want to spend or just doesn’t have the time into the server, I have no issue with them dropping $50 or so to get a new set of armor and a shiny sword.  But anything offered should be <span class="bbcode-u">reasonably</span> obtainable in-game.  Reasonably meaning not voting every 12 hours for 2 months straight, or killing 10000 monsters for a single item.</p>
<p>[B]What else do you find acceptable/unacceptable?:[/B]<br>
No Rare materials (Barrows, whips, etc) in shops in the donator zone.  Stuff like dragon bones is fine, but they should have to work for things too, not just blow money out the ass to get whatever they want when they want it.[/quote]<br>
very good points. a lot of, if not all, people agree with cosmetics being the items that are donateable. i, however, really despise being able to donate on a spawn server for korasi, chaotics, vesta, statius etc. i get very frustrated trying to fight people who have the maximum op equipment, when i first start out only having a fighter torso and whip. i don’t feel like donating unless it’s a server i have been playing for a couple of months. most spawn servers are the same, spawn, pk safe for coins and pk risk. not much incentive to donate to all of them because those with a budget need to plan their donations carefully.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/donations/537272/12">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/donations/537272/12</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 23 Dec 2013 01:42:03 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-537272-12</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/donations/537272.rss">Donations</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Donations</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@JavaTC JavaTC]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/javatc">@JavaTC</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[B]Do you believe donating is essential for a server to be successful?:[/B]<br>
Yes, since servers cost money.  Granted it isn’t much money, however if you want to make a content-packed, feature full, unique server, a $12 vps probably won’t do for very long.</p>
<p>[B]Do you tend to donate for servers you play?:[/B]<br>
If I like them enough and the owner and staff are actually knowledgeable as to what they’re doing then I put a few bucks forward.  I have no issues doing so considering it’s entertainment and community.  Granted it isn’t exactly a big $50 donation, I doubt a few dollars will ever be turned down.</p>
<p>[B]Do you agree with donating for items?:[/B]<br>
Sure, nothing wrong with it.  Really the items should be cosmetic or have a small vantage over other weapons, but not huge.  Just don’t offer rare monster drops or anything, preferably they should be earned.</p>
<p>[B]What do you consider a balance between perks for donating and an unfair advantage?:[/B]<br>
Depends, some say donating in and of itself is unfair since not everyone has money.  I don’t hold that stance.  If someone who doesn’t want to spend or just doesn’t have the time into the server, I have no issue with them dropping $50 or so to get a new set of armor and a shiny sword.  But anything offered should be <span class="bbcode-u">reasonably</span> obtainable in-game.  Reasonably meaning not voting every 12 hours for 2 months straight, or killing 10000 monsters for a single item.</p>
<p>[B]What else do you find acceptable/unacceptable?:[/B]<br>
No Rare materials (Barrows, whips, etc) in shops in the donator zone.  Stuff like dragon bones is fine, but they should have to work for things too, not just blow money out the ass to get whatever they want when they want it.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/donations/537272/11">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/donations/537272/11</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 22 Dec 2013 23:22:01 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-537272-11</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/donations/537272.rss">Donations</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Donations</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Ashi Ashi]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/ashi">@Ashi</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I donated, got bored, disputed my money back.<br>
I personally could not care about a server that is only up for the money.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/donations/537272/10">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/donations/537272/10</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 21 Dec 2013 18:55:07 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-537272-10</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/donations/537272.rss">Donations</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Donations</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Zombie_Juice Zombie Juice]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/zombie_juice">@Zombie_Juice</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Thanks for the replies so far, also Ruby, that sounds really good.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/donations/537272/9">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/donations/537272/9</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 21 Dec 2013 18:43:28 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-537272-9</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/donations/537272.rss">Donations</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Donations</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Travas Travas]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/travas">@Travas</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“Ruby, post:7, topic:537272”][quote author=Travas link=topic=656088.msg4391359#msg4391359 date=1387642724]<br>
I’d never donate to a server.  Why waste money on something that’s going to shut down soon?<br>
[/quote]<br>
Direct counter to that would be to just mention SoulSplit.[/quote]The only reason SoulSplit is alive is because they pay Jagex to stay off their backs.  I’ve heard the owner, after paying off Jagex, still rakes in the cash.  I really don’t think donating to a server that doesn’t need money (or should I say deserve money) should get money handed to them.  I haven’t payed attention to private servers for years now so I might be wrong.</p>
<p>Again, why waste money on something that is going to shut down soon?  Maybe not soon, but SoulSplit cannot stay alive forever.  I just personally think buying virtual items on a game that is so unprofessional and ran by kiddies is just completely idiotic.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/donations/537272/8">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/donations/537272/8</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 21 Dec 2013 18:24:45 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-537272-8</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/donations/537272.rss">Donations</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Donations</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Ruby_Forums_Coder Ruby]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/ruby_forums_coder">@Ruby_Forums_Coder</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote" data-post="6" data-topic="537272">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/travas/40/5_e05bb34c421432ee4d40de30c10af3e5.png" class="avatar"> Travas:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>I’d never donate to a server.  Why waste money on something that’s going to shut down soon?</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Direct counter to that would be to just mention SoulSplit.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/donations/537272/7">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/donations/537272/7</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 21 Dec 2013 17:30:55 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-537272-7</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/donations/537272.rss">Donations</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Donations</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Travas Travas]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/travas">@Travas</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I’d never donate to a server.  Why waste money on something that’s going to shut down soon?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/donations/537272/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/donations/537272/6</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 21 Dec 2013 16:18:44 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-537272-6</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/donations/537272.rss">Donations</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Donations</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Ruby_Forums_Coder Ruby]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/ruby_forums_coder">@Ruby_Forums_Coder</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>The donation theory we’re sticking into Epicurus this time round is a pretty good one, it still gives a great incentive to donate but gives no advantages other than aesthetics in game. Basically the TL;DR version is that people can donate for the generic rare items on runescape, party hats, halloween masks, santa hats, even things like elegant clothing and flared trousers etc. The way it works is to have two models for each item in game, the donation model and the full ingame model. The donation model is untradeable therefore people can’t get any monetary gain from it. When they donate all they receive is a better looking character. The full in game items can still be won from events and what not in game held by staff for certain occasions or on a scheduled basis. One of the big downfalls of Epicurus on the original relaunch was that the economy went downhill and got very very bad. This should stop people with the irl big bucks bringing unnecessary amount of high priced items into circulation in the server, instead only the donor gets the benefits which are purely for looks.</p>
<p>I believe that if every server done this it’d solve a lot of the economy issues and still maintain an incentive to donate to keep the server running. It’s a win win for everyone.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/donations/537272/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/donations/537272/5</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 21 Dec 2013 16:01:27 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-537272-5</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/donations/537272.rss">Donations</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Donations</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@yoeril yoeril]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/yoeril">@yoeril</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>A main problem is that players expect a return for their donation because every server offers this.</p>
<p>If your going to accept donations without giving a reward you will have no chance against the big servers who make bank and invest it into advertising and all kinds of server upgrades.</p>
<p>This is sadly how the RsPs community is, but its human. Bound to happen even on RS with all the paid stuff they added.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/donations/537272/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/donations/537272/4</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2013 21:50:18 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-537272-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/donations/537272.rss">Donations</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Donations</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Zombie_Juice Zombie Juice]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/zombie_juice">@Zombie_Juice</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote" data-post="2" data-topic="537272">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/zyle1992/40/5_e05bb34c421432ee4d40de30c10af3e5.png" class="avatar"> zyle1992:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>I have always been a firm believer that “donating” to get some sort of benefit in game (higher exp rate, items, etc) has always been a bit shady. I’ve always believed that donations should go solely to maintaining the server, and website if it has one. Not as a way to make a profit.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Would you donate to a server that you liked for nothing in return? For example, $10.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/donations/537272/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/donations/537272/3</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2013 18:44:13 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-537272-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/donations/537272.rss">Donations</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Donations</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@zyle1992 Zymus]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/zyle1992">@zyle1992</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I have always been a firm believer that “donating” to get some sort of benefit in game (higher exp rate, items, etc) has always been a bit shady. I’ve always believed that donations should go solely to maintaining the server, and website if it has one. Not as a way to make a profit.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/donations/537272/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/donations/537272/2</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2013 18:39:41 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-537272-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/donations/537272.rss">Donations</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Donations</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Zombie_Juice Zombie Juice]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/zombie_juice">@Zombie_Juice</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I want to talk about donations and what people think of them in RSPS’s. I understand this is a controversial subject, but they are generally a necessity to maintain a server’s online presence.</p>
<p>I have had experience to say that servers that accept donations purely for the sake of funding the server do not work. There has to be more of an incentive other than a forum rank for people to donate. Where do you draw the line between giving incentive to donate, and giving an unfair advantage? What I’d like to know your opinion on is:</p>
<p><code>
[B]Do you believe donating is essential for a server to be successful?:[/B]
[B]Do you tend to donate for servers you play?:[/B]
[B]Do you agree with donating for items?:[/B]
[B]What do you consider a balance between perks for donating and an unfair advantage?:[/B]
[B]What else do you find acceptable/unacceptable?:[/B]
</code></p>
<p>Personally, I agree that “donations” (even though it defies the definition of what a donation is) are essential if you want to keep your game online for people to play, but at the same time if there was a way I could provide a server and fund it all myself, I would, and donating would not be an option.</p>
<p>Unfortunately, I’d have to say 99.9% of all servers that have a .com domain and paid hosting are not ran by people who can comfortably afford to run it for free. I know a few people get hundreds or even thousands a month in donations, and barely invest the money back into the game (advertising, security, better hosting, paying developers etc.). So if you are getting more in donations than what it costs to run, what do you do with the rest of the money? Some keep it as a sort of payment for their hard work (which is acceptable). What about holding weekly competitions with monetary prizes as a sort of thanks to your players?</p>
<p>Please discuss the aspects of donations in RSPS’s and what your opinions are on what works, what is right and what is wrong. I’m interested in seeing other people’s views on something that is quite a big part of private servers nowadays.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/donations/537272/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/donations/537272/1</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2013 18:15:12 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-537272-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/donations/537272.rss">Donations</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
