<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>[317] Action Interval problems</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/317-action-interval-problems/540003</link>
    <description>So I don&#39;t waste your time, long story shot. I&#39;ve been working on very nice mining methods for my 317. Everything in them works perfect and the way I want them to work. Except for one small thing. My action interval is set to 1500, meaning you need to wait 1.5 seconds before mining each ore/completing the actions declared in the case. The problem is, when you do the action so many times, eventually the interval adds up, and won&#39;t let you do the action anymore for an extended period of time.

My guess is that the problem is most likely somewhere in the process. In there something declared such as maybe,

[code]if (actionInterval &gt; # - SOMETHING[/code]

I&#39;ve searched and searched but can&#39;t find anything. In this source, the actionInterval is based on well, clicks..... I tried to find a way around this problem, implementing a basic random event. With every click, there is a chance of getting a screen that pops up, telling you to click a specific stat to continue playing. I tried to increase the rate of this random, hoping it would stop people from spam clicking.

The problem is, I feel as if your actions get throttled too quickly. My question is a) How can I truly prevent spam-clicking?/What can I do, to decrease the chance of people spam clicking? (I know it sounds stupid, you may think, well.... People will always spam click.) b) How can I fix up my mining methods, to make them more efficient, so I won&#39;t come across this problem. If the problem doesn&#39;t seem clear to anyone trying to help, I&#39;ll explain it in a different way so you can.

Here&#39;s the key codes for the problem, that I&#39;ve put into my mining method.....

[code]if (System.currentTimeMillis() - lastAction &gt; actionInterval) {[/code]

Comes after the playerLevel required, checking for the pickaxe, blah, blah, blah.....

Later in the method of course comes,

[code]		actionInterval = 1500;
			lastAction = System.currentTimeMillis();[/code]

Allowing you to only do the action every so often..... Can anyone tell me why the server doesn&#39;t allow me to continue doing the action? After clicking the rocks a certain amount of times?</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2014 05:52:47 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/317-action-interval-problems/540003.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>[317] Action Interval problems</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@MyNameIsDylan MyNameIsDylan]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/mynameisdylan">@MyNameIsDylan</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Doesn’t look like it.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/317-action-interval-problems/540003/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/317-action-interval-problems/540003/3</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2014 05:52:47 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-540003-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/317-action-interval-problems/540003.rss">[317] Action Interval problems</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[317] Action Interval problems</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Clawz_fury lare69]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/clawz_fury">@Clawz_fury</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>that seems odd. check if the actionInterval value is being increased anywhere</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/317-action-interval-problems/540003/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/317-action-interval-problems/540003/2</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2014 19:45:37 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-540003-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/317-action-interval-problems/540003.rss">[317] Action Interval problems</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[317] Action Interval problems</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@MyNameIsDylan MyNameIsDylan]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/mynameisdylan">@MyNameIsDylan</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>So I don’t waste your time, long story shot. I’ve been working on very nice mining methods for my 317. Everything in them works perfect and the way I want them to work. Except for one small thing. My action interval is set to 1500, meaning you need to wait 1.5 seconds before mining each ore/completing the actions declared in the case. The problem is, when you do the action so many times, eventually the interval adds up, and won’t let you do the action anymore for an extended period of time.</p>
<p>My guess is that the problem is most likely somewhere in the process. In there something declared such as maybe,</p>
<pre><code class="lang-auto"></code></pre>
<p>I’ve searched and searched but can’t find anything. In this source, the actionInterval is based on well, clicks… I tried to find a way around this problem, implementing a basic random event. With every click, there is a chance of getting a screen that pops up, telling you to click a specific stat to continue playing. I tried to increase the rate of this random, hoping it would stop people from spam clicking.</p>
<p>The problem is, I feel as if your actions get throttled too quickly. My question is a) How can I truly prevent spam-clicking?/What can I do, to decrease the chance of people spam clicking? (I know it sounds stupid, you may think, well… People will always spam click.) b) How can I fix up my mining methods, to make them more efficient, so I won’t come across this problem. If the problem doesn’t seem clear to anyone trying to help, I’ll explain it in a different way so you can.</p>
<p>Here’s the key codes for the problem, that I’ve put into my mining method…</p>
<pre><code class="lang-auto"></code></pre>
<p>Comes after the playerLevel required, checking for the pickaxe, blah, blah, blah…</p>
<p>Later in the method of course comes,</p>
<p><code>		actionInterval = 1500;
			lastAction = System.currentTimeMillis();</code></p>
<p>Allowing you to only do the action every so often… Can anyone tell me why the server doesn’t allow me to continue doing the action? After clicking the rocks a certain amount of times?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/317-action-interval-problems/540003/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/317-action-interval-problems/540003/1</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2014 17:21:36 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-540003-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/317-action-interval-problems/540003.rss">[317] Action Interval problems</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
