<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>How do i make server?</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-do-i-make-server/73406</link>
    <description>i want to but the tut is complicated i cant undersgtand much of it</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 02 Apr 2007 20:41:08 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-do-i-make-server/73406.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>How do i make server?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@P3rscape P3rscape]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/p3rscape">@P3rscape</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>i got a older one here:</p>
<p>[size=40pt]Setting up No-IP[/size]<br>
First off we need to get you a No-IP account so if you have a Dynamic or Static IP your ip to log into your server will always remain the same so Open your favorite web browser and navigate it to <a href="http://no-ip.com" rel="nofollow noopener">http://no-ip.com</a> or click this link when you get to this website Press the button “Sign Up Now” and register your account. Once your account is active log into it and click the “Add” button underneath Hosts/Redirects. As the HostName enter the name of your server For Example, my server name is HydroScape so i put hydroscape in the hostname box. Next as the part underneath HostName you will see a drop-down menu of domains you can use, you can select any of them you want for example my server IP is <a href="http://hydroscape.no-ip.org" rel="nofollow noopener">hydroscape.no-ip.org</a> so i selected <a href="http://no-ip.org" rel="nofollow noopener">no-ip.org</a>. Select your Host Name and scroll to the bottom leaving all the other settings Alone. now press “Create Host”. Now its time to download the No-IP DUC. Scroll to the top of the Page and select Download, Now select the operating system you are running (E.G. Windows XP would be Windows, Linux would be Linux, Machintosh would be Mac. once downloaded, open the file you downloaded and it will begin an install of the program, click next through the whole thing, now when its installed you should be asked for a Username and Password. type your username from No-Ip Which is the email you registered with. now enter your No-IP password. you will then see your HostName you created. now check the checkbox beside it and you should see a yellow smiley face. you have completed this version of the Tutorial. Next its getting the server functioning.<br>
[size=40pt]Setting up the Server[/size]<br>
First off we need to Download Java Development Kit(JDK) it can be found At this link: <a href="http://java.sun.com/j2ee/1.4/download.html" rel="nofollow noopener">http://java.sun.com/j2ee/1.4/download.html</a> Find JDK 5.0 on that page and press download then scroll down and press Accept then scroll down and Download the Offline Installer. Next, Run the offline installer. click next all through the installation. Now we have JDK installed so we need to move onto Downloading a server. In my previous tutorial revisions i have stuck with NixScape but i think it Might be time for a change as NixScape runs on VERY old coding and is VERY unstable So i would suggest downloading Project 16 which can be found at <a href="Http://p16.dodian.com" rel="nofollow noopener">Http://p16.dodian.com</a> and was coded by Wolf using WhiteScape. Ok we have a server, We have JDK, We have No-IP, now we need a client so if you already have a client your good to go. but if not you can get MoparScape V. 3.0 @ <a href="http://moparisthebest.com/moparscape.html" rel="nofollow noopener">http://moparisthebest.com/moparscape.html</a> Ok. that sums up this part of the tutorial next is [size=40pt]Setting up your Firewall.[/size]<br>
Setting Windows FireWall Exceptions<br>
In Windows XP Home Service Pack 2 or Windows XP Pro Service Pack 2 Go to Start -&gt; Control Panel and Open Security Center. Now Click Windows Firewall Which is at the bottom of the Security Center. Now you should See Enable. Enable Without Exceptions. and Disable. and the top Tags should say “General” “Exceptions” and “Advanced”. Click the Exceptions Tab. now you should see a list of programs classified to the Windows Firewall as “Exceptions” Click “Add Port” and Name the Port the same name as your server and put the port # as 43594. Then click Ok. You have Successfully setup your Windows Firewall to allow Traffic into your Computer using the port 43594 Which is the runescape private server Default port. That sums this section up.<br>
Port Forwarding (Used for routers to allow the traffic to port 43594<br>
Contact your Routers Manual for instructions on port forwarding because ever router is different.<br>
Fixing “Can Not Find Specified Location” and “Device is not ready”<br>
Right click on Run&amp;Compile and click edit<br>
delete all the code in it and replace with this:</p>
<hr>
<p>Code:</p>
<p><a class="mention" href="/u/echo">@echo</a> offCOLOR 08title YOURSERVERNAME Client"C:…Program Files…Java…jdk1.5.0_07…bin…javac.exe" -cp . *.java"C:…Program Files…Java…jre1.5.0_07…bin…java.exe" serverpause</p>
<hr>
<p>or if that one doesnt work try this one</p>
<hr>
<p>Code:</p>
<p><a class="mention" href="/u/echo">@echo</a> offCOLOR 08title YOURSERVERNAME Client"C:…Program Files…Java…jdk1.5.0_06…bin…javac.exe" -cp . *.java"C:…Program Files…Java…jdk1.5.0_06…bin…java.exe" serverpause</p>
<hr>
<p>That sums this tutorial up. Thanks for reading.<br>
P.S:<br>
If you dont get this, nothing you will get.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-do-i-make-server/73406/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-do-i-make-server/73406/5</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 02 Apr 2007 20:41:08 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-73406-5</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-do-i-make-server/73406.rss">How do i make server?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>How do i make server?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Eh_Pretty_Easy Eh Pretty Easy]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/eh_pretty_easy">@Eh_Pretty_Easy</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Lmao, like 70% of the people on the forums are like 8-11 year old who can’t read, and if they can read, they won’t understand a crap. It would be good if we had a ultimate server guide written in noob language. No-ip would be nouu-aip. xD <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/smiley.png?v=6" title=":smiley:" class="emoji" alt=":smiley:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-do-i-make-server/73406/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-do-i-make-server/73406/4</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 02 Apr 2007 20:23:32 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-73406-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-do-i-make-server/73406.rss">How do i make server?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>How do i make server?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Zenzie Zenzie]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/zenzie">@Zenzie</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Click here time to make a noob friendly tut?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-do-i-make-server/73406/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-do-i-make-server/73406/3</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 02 Apr 2007 20:13:01 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-73406-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-do-i-make-server/73406.rss">How do i make server?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>How do i make server?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Click_Here Click Here]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/click_here">@Click_Here</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>you dont understand mod taharoks ultimate server tut? just read it throught carefully and keep reading through it again and again</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-do-i-make-server/73406/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-do-i-make-server/73406/2</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 02 Apr 2007 20:10:06 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-73406-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-do-i-make-server/73406.rss">How do i make server?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>How do i make server?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@hayhay159 hayhay159]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/hayhay159">@hayhay159</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>i want to but the tut is complicated i cant undersgtand much of it</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-do-i-make-server/73406/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-do-i-make-server/73406/1</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 02 Apr 2007 20:07:45 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-73406-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-do-i-make-server/73406.rss">How do i make server?</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
