<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Lets have a &quot;story of the week&quot; competition?</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/lets-have-a-story-of-the-week-competition/15740</link>
    <description>hi guys,

            I was thinking since we have a signiture of the week competition why not a story of the week? I would be glad to put this together myself if mopar likes the idea. Ive put togther a few base line rules for now but first we must see if anyone would enter :).


RULES: 
- Words: Maximum 1000

- No smileys, no l33t, acronyms or other silly stuff 

- No vulgarity, keep it clean (PG13 like LOTR) 
 
- Only one entry per member, no more, and no changes or replacement entries 

- Don&#39;t steal other peoples work 

- No cheating!

- The judge have absolute power, so please don&#39;t complain. 


Perhaps we could put together a group of judges or perhaps they could be publicly rated. Stories should be rated in the following way -


Concept / idea - 4 points

punctuation - 3 points, good use of word

StoryLine -
0 points: minimun score, not good at all
1 points: 1/5 
2 points: 2/5 
3 points: 3/5 
4 points: 4/5 
5 points: Maximum score, very good

i will try and organise somwthing as a reward  for the winner but for now this is undecided atm, please take this as an oppertunity to express your creative side :)

thx for your input,

solemn wishes</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 29 Sep 2006 05:38:01 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>General Discussion</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/lets-have-a-story-of-the-week-competition/15740.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Lets have a &quot;story of the week&quot; competition?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@therealjdb JDB`]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/therealjdb">@therealjdb</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>we have a writing section now, kinda, its actually part of the review section all the way at the bottem of the forums</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/lets-have-a-story-of-the-week-competition/15740/58">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/lets-have-a-story-of-the-week-competition/15740/58</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 29 Sep 2006 05:38:01 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-15740-58</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/lets-have-a-story-of-the-week-competition/15740.rss">Lets have a &quot;story of the week&quot; competition?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Lets have a &quot;story of the week&quot; competition?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Akriam Akriam]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/akriam">@Akriam</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Alright chumps <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/wink.png?v=9" title=":wink:" class="emoji" alt=":wink:"> Time for my story about a little place called Elddem:</p>
<p>.::Elddem::.Storyline Beta<br>
My name is Ferge, and this is an account of the history of Elddem, from the man who saw it’s beginning, and will see it’s end…<br>
Elddem is not an ordinary place as you may imagine. It is filled with magic and wonder. Most children dream of a place such as this, that is, a place of such greatness you will never want to leave. But wherever there is such as nice place as this, there is someone trying to stop that peace.<br>
It all began a few thousand years back, when the world we now live in today became so overrun with anger and hatred that the gods threatened to destroy our world. One great man, Ferge pleaded with the gods to spare the world they had created. The gods listened and instead of destroying the world, made a new world, one you will know as Elddem. The gods brought Ferge to the new world and made him a mighty ruler. Ferge was very grateful, but he missed his family. Ferge wanted to be with his loved ones, so he created a portal to his world, Elddem, for his family to come through. When the rest of the world found out about this portal, a great war was waged, and many people from both sides were killed. The gods, sickened by the destruction of Elddem closed the portal and put a curse on Ferge and his family that he would never die, but still feel the pains of the world he once belonged to. Elddem was no longer perfect, so the gods had a meeting trying to decide what to do. They decided that they would send monsters into the world to keep the men inline. This brought forth different races such as elves and dwarves. The gods also sent their soldiers to be among the people so they would stay in line. No longer would the people become disruptive, or so the gods thought.</p>
<p>The people were obedient for many years, but eventually a Ferge could not take it any longer. He felt horrible and wanted to die. He recruited an army and tried to kill the gods.<br>
The gods thought it no longer fit to live among the people, so they destroyed every living thing in Elddem accept Ferge and his family, so the memory of the past would be forgotten. They then repopulated Elddem and created a small island for them to live on. This island is protected by thousands of curses and spells, and a human can only reach it’s lands by the gods request. Today Elddem is much like Earth; accept for the fact that is a magical place, one full of wonder. That might be the soul reason that the gods did not destroy Elddem, because they thought it could become a better place, a place unlike Earth, and they had hoped that one day, Elddem would be fit for the gods to live amongst the people once again.<br>
With the constant discovery of new creatures in Elddem, the people eventually started using the creatures as they used horses and ox back on Earth. It was inevitable that the humans eventually found the dragon. The people who found it knew how powerful this creature was just by looking at it, so they kept it a secret. They formed a tribe called the dragoons, and with every passing second they spent with the dragons, the magic from the dragons started to rub off on them. The dragoons had become so powerful that they could not continue to be a secret. The gods gave the dragoons great power and glory. The dragoons were peaceful, so the gods gave them the task of ruling over Elddem, and they did a great job of it. The whole world of Elddem seemed to be in a better mood. This age is referred to as the “Golden Age”. After about 600 years of this great period in Elddem, an army from and uncharted island in the east plotted to attack the dragoons so they could rule the Elddem.<br>
There was a great war, lasting 34 years. When it finally looked as if the army from the east, or as they preferred themselves to be called the Imperials, were about to lose, the Imperials knew they had to dishonor themselves if they whished to win the Great War. They poisoned the dragon’s water supply, so the dragons would catch diseases. The diseases eventually spread to the dragoons, and the Imperials had wiped the dragons and dragoons off the face of the Elddem, or so they had thought. The gods protected a small group of dragons and dragoons, knowing they were the purest race in all of Elddem. The dragoons appear around the world of Elddem every now and then, and if you are lucky enough to see one, you are extremely lucky. Today the dragoons help the gods keep everything under control. It is said that if you see one your luck is so great that you will become rich.<br>
It is not sure as to the exact time, but Elddem historians like to believe that between the 600th and 653rd year of the Imperials reign Ferge was brought to the gods, and had a great revelation. He saw that he was the cause of the pain, and started to run out the door to try and do something about it, when the gods removed the curse because they saw that he was once again a pure heart. He immediately turned to dust and died. His family had been returned the age they were before the curse was put on them. The gods sent a man to Ferge’s family, and when the doorknob turned, and the door opened, Ferge stepped through the door. He had been reborned as a man, an immortal man with such pure heart that the gods trusted him in leading an army to free the people from the Imperials tyranny.<br>
Who was Ferge’s army you say? The dragoons. They had repopulated among themselves, and had become even more powerful. Even though they had less numbers than the Imperials, they knew in their hearts they could destroy them.  Ferge’s army won the first battle of that war, with very few casualties. That victory was followed by many wins and loses, but they knew they could win, it just wouldn’t be easy.<br>
About two in a half years into the war the gods knew that Ferge, even though he was immortal, was tired and missing his family, so they let him go back (no one knows exactly where “back” is, but it is some remote location) to his family. The leader who took Ferge’s place is doing just fine, and Ferge will sometimes appear on the battlefield, although rarely.<br>
Now it is time to say a word about you, young one.  You were born in the 3rd year of this war and it is now the 21st year. Now that you are ready to leave your family and go out on your own, you must know some things and remember you can visit your family anytime you want. But the most important thing is BE CAREFUL IN THE IMPERIAL’S LAND!<br>
Copyright - © 2006 SoulGamerz/Elddem/Akriam</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/lets-have-a-story-of-the-week-competition/15740/57">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/lets-have-a-story-of-the-week-competition/15740/57</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 29 Sep 2006 05:26:55 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-15740-57</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/lets-have-a-story-of-the-week-competition/15740.rss">Lets have a &quot;story of the week&quot; competition?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Lets have a &quot;story of the week&quot; competition?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@extreme300 extreme300]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/extreme300">@extreme300</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Here is mine. I wrote it last night, it was for an english project that was due today…it sucks but here it is:</p>
<blockquote>[b]The River Cat[/b]
<p>“Paul! Where are you?” yelled Norman as he searched through along the river. He was searching for his brother who had been swept down the river.<br>
Earlier that day he, his father and his brother Paul were fly fishing in the river. He was having a great time. Him and his brother were catching the fish while their father was reading his Bible. After about five minutes of fishing he had already caught three fish. Paul, however, wasn’t as lucky. He hadn’t caught any fish and he was getting frustrated that his brother was catching fish and he hadn’t even had a bite.<br>
After a while Norman went to see how their father was doing. Paul was somewhat relieved that he had gone because now he could catch some fish, and Norman couldn’t hog them all. He spotted a large fish on the other side of the river. He casted out his line over to the fish and started to reeled in the line. It bit the hook! He pulled back quickly on the line and hooked the fish. It fought viciously. He reeled in  the line and let go so that the line wouldn’t break. The fish kept on fighting and fighting, it was leading him farther and farther down the river, and the water just kept getting deeper and deeper. Soon it was almost over his head. The water was also moving faster, slowly turning into rapids. Norman saw this and ran after his brother but Paul was going to fast for him to catch up.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-i">Where is he?</span> wondered Norman, sitting down on a log. He had gotten to a point in the river where the water was only about a foot high. <span class="bbcode-i">I’ve been searching for three hours already and there hasn’t been any sign of him or his fishing gear.</span><br>
He looked up and to his surprise saw a cat sitting about ten feet away. “Hey little cat, what are you doing out here?” he got up and slowly crept towards the cat. It was a large grey cat, with spots of white that gave it a smokey appearance. It had big brown eyes that looked up at him as if it understood what Norman was saying to it. He got about an arms reach away and started to move his hand closer and closer towards the cat. It moved forward and let him pet it. He petted the cat, it started to purr, “ Now what would a nice cat like you be doing out here in the woods? Oh well you seem to be just fine,” the cat looked up at him, he smiled. “Now if only I was able to find Paul. I suppose you don’t know where he is.” the cat stopped purring and looked down, Norman almost thought it looked as if it was trying to remember something. All of a sudden it turned around and started walking away. “Hey! Where are you going?” it stopped walking and looked back at him, then it turned its head and started to walk away again. <span class="bbcode-i">I wonder where it’ s going?</span> he thought.<br>
Norman walked back over to the log and once again sat down. <span class="bbcode-i">Now what am I going to do? I have no idea where Paul is. I’ve looked everywhere and I just can’t find him! Oh well I better start looking for him again.</span><br>
So he got up and started walking farther down the river.<br>
After a while of walking he came across a small clearing in the woods. To his surprise he saw the cat sitting in the middle of the clearing looking at him. It walked up to him, rubbed against his leg and then started walking towards the woods. “Now where are you going?” It looked back at him and then looked at the trees, then back at him again. <span class="bbcode-i">I think it wants me to follow it.</span> So he followed the cat into the woods. The cat kept a ten foot distance from him the entire time. When Norman stopped to rest the cat just stopped and waited for him to be rested. It led him through the woods until they came to another clearing. It was full of grass around four feet tall. The cat walked into the clearing and disappeared in the grass, Norman could only tell where that cat was from the movement of the grass. When it got to about the middle of the clearing it stopped, he could see a large indent in the grass. He walked over, and as he got closer he could see that there was a clothed figure laying on it’s side where the cat had stopped. “Paul!” he ran over to the body, “Paul, wakeup! Paul! Paul!. Paul let out a groan, rolled on to his back and opened his eyes. “Norman? Is that you?”<br>
“Yes it’s me.” he said kneeling by his brothers side.<br>
“Where am i? And what happened?”<br>
“You are in a clearing not far away from the river, as for what happened i was hoping you could tell me that.”<br>
Paul sat up, “Hmm, let me think…I had hooked a realy big fish, and it was strong, it started to pull me down the river.”<br>
“Why didn’t you let go?”<br>
“I didn’t want to lose it, but the water got deeper and faster until it started turning into rapids. I let go of my rod but it was too late. The water was moving too fast and I couldn’t get out. Then I hit my head on what I think was a rock, I blacked out and then the next thing I remember is that the water had slowed down and had gotten shallow. Something grabbed me by the back of the collar, I don’t know for sure but I think it was some large cat, because I could feel whiskers on the back of my neck. After that I blacked out again.” The cat began to purr, “What is that?” asked Paul.<br>
“It’s a cat that I found a while ago. It led me right to this spot where I found you.”<br>
“Really? Maybe it pulled me out.” Norman smiled.<br>
“Yeah, right. Now lets see if we can get you home.”<br>
So they walked back up and found their father who was still sitting there reading his Bible, “Well are you ready to go?”<br>
“Yup, lets go”<br>
So they went home and they lived happily ever after.</p>
<p>The End</p>
</blockquote>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/lets-have-a-story-of-the-week-competition/15740/56">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/lets-have-a-story-of-the-week-competition/15740/56</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 26 Sep 2006 07:01:51 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-15740-56</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/lets-have-a-story-of-the-week-competition/15740.rss">Lets have a &quot;story of the week&quot; competition?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Lets have a &quot;story of the week&quot; competition?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@wall_of_fir wall of fir]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/wall_of_fir">@wall_of_fir</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>How do joo like mine?[br][size=1]Posted at: September 24, 2006, 10:18:20 AM[/size][hr]Hello?how do you like mine???[br][size=1]Posted at: September 25, 2006, 04:28:48 PM[/size][hr]RRRGGGHH!!</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/lets-have-a-story-of-the-week-competition/15740/55">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/lets-have-a-story-of-the-week-competition/15740/55</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 26 Sep 2006 06:07:46 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-15740-55</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/lets-have-a-story-of-the-week-competition/15740.rss">Lets have a &quot;story of the week&quot; competition?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Lets have a &quot;story of the week&quot; competition?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Drunk_On_Java Drunk On Java]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/drunk_on_java">@Drunk_On_Java</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Oh my god xero. That’s disturbing. :eek:</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/lets-have-a-story-of-the-week-competition/15740/54">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/lets-have-a-story-of-the-week-competition/15740/54</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 24 Sep 2006 20:16:20 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-15740-54</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/lets-have-a-story-of-the-week-competition/15740.rss">Lets have a &quot;story of the week&quot; competition?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Lets have a &quot;story of the week&quot; competition?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@wall_of_fir wall of fir]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/wall_of_fir">@wall_of_fir</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Fine, noone will answer, so I’m making another story.</p>
<p>“Ahh…Autumn,” Skidd said with a deep breath, “a good time to just chill outside before Winter comes.”</p>
<p>“Indeed.” Robert clarified.</p>
<p>“So…what do you wanna do?” Skidd asked</p>
<p>“I know, lets work on our Rust collection!That things getting pretty big!” Robert exclaimed.</p>
<p>“Yeah!” Skidd said, walking to the rust collection with Robert.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b"><em>rustles</em></span></p>
<p>“What was that?” Skidd asked.</p>
<p>“Probably just a squirrel or something, c’mon.” Robert assured.</p>
<p>Later at their ‘rust collection’…</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b"><em>rustles</em></span></p>
<p>“WTF WAS THAT!” Skidd swore.</p>
<p>"Skidd!"Robert yelled.</p>
<p>“Sorry, but whats with that noise?I keep hearing it.” Skidd worried.</p>
<p>“Stop being such a baby, Skidd, and kelp me carry this stuff to the rust collection.” Robert exclaimed.</p>
<p>“Rrgh.Its kinda heavy,” <em>drops something</em> “and bulky.”</p>
<p>“Hello gentlemen.” A man said.</p>
<p>“Who’s he?and why does he have grass stains on his tux?” Skidd whispered.</p>
<p>“I dunno, its your house.” Robert said.</p>
<p>“Gentlemen?What are you whipering about?” The man asked.</p>
<ol start="2">
<li>
</li>
</ol>
<p>“Uh, nothing.Who are you?” Robert asked.</p>
<p>“Why, I’m an assasinator.” The main said bizzarily.</p>
<p>Right then, the boys dropped their rust and began SPRINTING towards the house, the man still back at the spot they dropped their stuff, grinning.</p>
<p><em>dials 9-1-1…</em></p>
<p>“Hello?Police?Yes, we’re on 3495 Maple Road Torrenstown. We’ve just met this man…he said he’s and assasinator.” Said Skidd.</p>
<p>“Alright, can you tell us where in your house he is?” The lady asked.</p>
<p>The two boys glanced at eachother, then glanced outside.He wasnt there.</p>
<p>“W-W-Why do you need to know where he is?” Skidd asked.</p>
<p>“To get to that part of the house quicker.” She said.</p>
<p>"Dam-er…I mean crap…we dont know.Can you please hurry u-<em>line breaks</em></p>
<p>( to be continued )</p>
<p>Those were first two chapters what do you think?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/lets-have-a-story-of-the-week-competition/15740/53">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/lets-have-a-story-of-the-week-competition/15740/53</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 24 Sep 2006 20:15:47 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-15740-53</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/lets-have-a-story-of-the-week-competition/15740.rss">Lets have a &quot;story of the week&quot; competition?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Lets have a &quot;story of the week&quot; competition?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@xerozcheez xerozcheez]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/xerozcheez">@xerozcheez</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Here’s a story I wrote about Fasga, this is the untrue one about his life, but I have written a true biography on him also, and I’ll be writing another story about two noobs who turn into successful pros</p>
<blockquote>Once upon a time there was a man named Fasga, he was a middle aged black man who lived with his Uncle and Aunt in a caravan. Fasga and his relatives were all gypsies, and had lots of fun travelling in their carvans, singing songs, telling stories, licking each other, and oooo! Although they were known as outcasts, freaks as you will, they were kind and generous people, who although were odd, they were still happy.
<p>Now, onto our adventure, Fasga hadn’t left the caravan for nearly 3 years, due to him recently becoming very shy. But then, one fine summers afternoon, he opened the caravan door, and took his first step into the real world for the first time in ages. While he had been inside all that time, Fasga had learned to code java, and also how to make love to his pet rabbit, we won’t talk about anything too unusual though, for now anyway, so let me tell you about his java life…</p>
<p>Fasga had learned many codes, and he loved coding, he soon went to join dodian, and through plagiarism, betrayal and deep hatred for Xerozcheez, he worked his way to administrator, he then moved onto rs-server, as he was never a big fan of mopar, due to him being homosexual and rejected, and then did the same as he did on dodian to get global moderator.</p>
<p>Anyway, as our story continues, Fasga had took his first step into the real world, and then fainted, in front of him he saw his Uncle and Aunt.</p>
<p>“I…I can’t do it!”, said Fasga.</p>
<p>“Can’t do what Fasga?”, asked his Aunt, looking into Fasga’s eyes with passion and love.</p>
<p>“I can’t make it in the real world! I…I just don’t believe in myself anymore, please, I can’t do this, I can’t go on!”, cried Fasga, like the pussy he was.</p>
<p>“You can do fine Fasga, why don’t you have sex with Mr Bunny?”, she replied.</p>
<p>“I don’t wanna have sex with Mr Bunny, I’m not in the mood!”, screamed Fasga.</p>
<p>“There there, don’t fret my dear.”</p>
<p>“What’s the point in living this life! I can’t go on! I’ve lost the edge!”, Fasga began to sob.</p>
<p>“Don’t do it my boy!”, said his Uncle.</p>
<p>“I have to, I just have to!”</p>
<p>“No you don’t, you can’t kill yourself now son, you’ve got so much ahead of you!”</p>
<p>“Kill myself? I thought you were trying to stop me from going back to my father for more pounding, but I guess you don’t know me, do you?! DO YOU?!?!”, shouted Fasga, in anger and tears.</p>
<p>“No! Me and your Aunt both know you very well, we just didn’t…”</p>
<p>“Don’t lie, you probably aren’t even related to me”, Fasga ran off into the distant sunset, crying.</p>
<p>“No!”, cried Fasga’s Aunt.</p>
<p>“Let him go my dear, let him go…”, said Fasga’s Uncle, in a soft clear voice.</p>
<p>Fasga then ran away back home, to recieve an ass pounding off his father, after weeks of begging, and long walking, Fasga finally made it to his hometown, and knocked softly on his parents front door… there was no reply, he then smashed open the door in depression and anger, and when he was inside, he found his parents there, lying dead on the floor. Fasga starred in horror, then to his left, saw a computer screen, on it was an IM saying, “o hay der u noobs, i hakked da adman n sed it waz u now he gunna ban u irl n mak u go 2 hell haha noob!!!”, the IM was from Slysoft, Fasga’s arch rival, who was also homosexual. Fasga fell on his knees, put his head into his hands, and started to spank that miniscule head like nothing before, until he stood up and squirtted into his fathers face. “There”, Fasga said, “That’s the cumshot part done, shame there was no pounding…”, then he fell on his knees again, put his head into his hands, his face that is, and began to cry. He sat there for hours upon hours, sobbing, but don’t think he’s crying about nothing, you’d cry if you were Fasga and came home to find your parents killed by your arch rival, and then no sex after travelling for weeks, right? So Fasga set off to hunt Slysoft…</p>
<p>Fasga stole his parents car, and headed north to go into Slysoft’s secret base located in the North Pole, the last time Fasga went there, it was just to ride the North Pole, this time, it was to ride the North Pole and then infiltrate Slysoft’s fortress, and uncover the evil plot to destroy human society, and bring justice so all of those weak. Fasga finally arrived at Slysoft’s base, which was a statue of Slysoft himself, he snipered the robotic guards, and then went through the back door, it would of been quicker to go through the foot, but Fasga prefers browner places. So Fasga crawled himself through all the shit he could handle, and then sneaked his way up to the brain, where Slysoft lived…</p>
<p>It was here, where he confronted Slysoft, then they both said “Damnit that’s a nice ass, if only you were gay like me!” in synchronization to one another, “Oh my god…” said Fasga, starring shocked at Slysoft. Then they both ran up to each other and started making love, and they lived happily ever after, the end!</p>
</blockquote>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/lets-have-a-story-of-the-week-competition/15740/52">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/lets-have-a-story-of-the-week-competition/15740/52</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 24 Sep 2006 20:05:50 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-15740-52</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/lets-have-a-story-of-the-week-competition/15740.rss">Lets have a &quot;story of the week&quot; competition?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Lets have a &quot;story of the week&quot; competition?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@wall_of_fir wall of fir]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/wall_of_fir">@wall_of_fir</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Hmm…Can I write another?Just for fun?[br][size=1]Posted at: September 24, 2006, 09:20:25 AM[/size][hr]Hello?Can I have an ANSWER please?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/lets-have-a-story-of-the-week-competition/15740/51">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/lets-have-a-story-of-the-week-competition/15740/51</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 24 Sep 2006 19:37:06 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-15740-51</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/lets-have-a-story-of-the-week-competition/15740.rss">Lets have a &quot;story of the week&quot; competition?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Lets have a &quot;story of the week&quot; competition?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Drunk_On_Java Drunk On Java]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/drunk_on_java">@Drunk_On_Java</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Nice story. Good grab.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/lets-have-a-story-of-the-week-competition/15740/50">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/lets-have-a-story-of-the-week-competition/15740/50</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 24 Sep 2006 19:19:16 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-15740-50</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/lets-have-a-story-of-the-week-competition/15740.rss">Lets have a &quot;story of the week&quot; competition?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Lets have a &quot;story of the week&quot; competition?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@wall_of_fir wall of fir]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/wall_of_fir">@wall_of_fir</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>lol looks like you took your time.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/lets-have-a-story-of-the-week-competition/15740/49">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/lets-have-a-story-of-the-week-competition/15740/49</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 24 Sep 2006 19:12:15 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-15740-49</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/lets-have-a-story-of-the-week-competition/15740.rss">Lets have a &quot;story of the week&quot; competition?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Lets have a &quot;story of the week&quot; competition?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@sppt sppt]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/sppt">@sppt</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>i like this idea, but more of this kind of style: <a href="http://wurmonline.com/forum/viewtopic.php?t=18" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">http://wurmonline.com/forum/viewtopic.php?t=18</a><br>
but then not in competition way</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/lets-have-a-story-of-the-week-competition/15740/48">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/lets-have-a-story-of-the-week-competition/15740/48</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 24 Sep 2006 16:36:36 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-15740-48</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/lets-have-a-story-of-the-week-competition/15740.rss">Lets have a &quot;story of the week&quot; competition?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Lets have a &quot;story of the week&quot; competition?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@pookey71 Pookey71]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/pookey71">@pookey71</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Lols sounds like flash and superman story O.o but i like it <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/smiley.png?v=9" title=":smiley:" class="emoji" alt=":smiley:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/lets-have-a-story-of-the-week-competition/15740/47">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/lets-have-a-story-of-the-week-competition/15740/47</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 24 Sep 2006 15:57:29 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-15740-47</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/lets-have-a-story-of-the-week-competition/15740.rss">Lets have a &quot;story of the week&quot; competition?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Lets have a &quot;story of the week&quot; competition?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Do0mz Do0mz]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/do0mz">@Do0mz</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Crickets, an occasional owl and the sound of the crackling fire broke the silence of the night only here and there. Two friends sat around a fire burning upon a concrete slab, bathing in its circle of warmth. Two age-old trees that grow so high as to form a natural roof above their heads covered them. The modest, redbrick house stood less than twenty meters away from the trees and only the lonely kitchen light could be seen all the way to the tree. The fresh air rejuvenated the two young men whom sat listening to the absence of civilization out here in the bush. A big dog yawned lazily as it lay sleeping next to the fire, its black coat covered in red dust. The entire yard, which included the two trees, the house and a backyard were fenced closed with barbed wire.</p>
<p>“Will?”</p>
<p>The young man with the powerful physique and the curly brown hair looked up. Across the fire sat his life-long friend and closest companion. Although both age about 20, they could not look further apart. He is a large, athletically built, almost chubby young man with a friendly face, while his friend is a short, thin man with messed up hair and a boyish face that shone with permanent cheek. He towered over his short friend by almost a head, if not more.</p>
<p>“Will!” his friend said again, only more loudly this time.</p>
<p>“Mavis!” he said back, equally suddenly. Although this is not his friend real name, he has called him by this nickname for many years now. His own nickname, Maxx, was also given to him a long time ago, but lately he has become accustomed to hearing this name in different circumstances than before. Circumstances his oldest friend does not even know about.</p>
<p>“Pass me another beer!” Mavis ordered. “Are you wimping out on me? You haven’t had four beers yet and already you look ready to pass out! We haven’t even begun!”</p>
<p>“Oh shut up, I’ll pass out when I want to,” Maxx said and leaned forward to grab another beer out of the cooler. His head was spinning already, but he would rather die than tell this to Mavis. He would never hear the end of it.</p>
<p>“No you won’t!” Mavis said cocky and grabbed the beer out of Maxx’s hand. “It was your idea to come to you grandfather’s farm for the weekend. You promised me a drinking session to end all others!”</p>
<p>“I’m not passed out yet!” Maxx said. In one fluent motion, he downed his beer in one gulp, threw the bottle onto the heap of discarded bottles and grabbed a new beer out of the cooler.</p>
<p>“Now that’s more like it!” Mavis said and did the same, gulping it down so fast that the beer foamed down the side of his face.</p>
<p>“How can someone so small pack in so much beer?” Maxx asked with a laugh and sunk back into his lawn chair.</p>
<p>“Years of practice!” Mavis answered and beckoned to Maxx to pass him yet another beer.</p>
<p>They sat quiet again for a few minutes, listening to the jackals howling up the mountains, allowing the serenity of their surroundings to add to their comfort. Maxx stared down at the beer in his hand. His head felt woozy and his eyes blurred. If he continues on at this pace he’ll be drunk before midnight, but he’ll be damned if Mavis isn’t going to join him.</p>
<p>“I still can’t believe you left your hi-fi at home!” Mavis said. “Now we have twenty CDs, but no music.”</p>
<p>“Well if you weren’t in such a hurry to leave, I would have remembered,” Maxx argued and grabbed a large bone left over on his plate and chucked it at the dog that eagerly awoke from his slumber when he smelled the food. “Now stop complaining and light us a cigarette.”</p>
<p>Mavis smiled and reached for his packet of cigarettes and his lighter. Soon the two friends sat smoking happily, while getting drunk and complaining about everything they could find fault with.</p>
<ol start="2">
<li>
</li>
</ol>
<p>“… so I lend her my car and when I got it back she had driven through a wooden fence!”</p>
<p>Maxx laughed; the joke seeming more funny than the first seven times he had heard it. He giggled, gave a sharp hiccup and reached for the cooler when the dog suddenly lifted its head. It gave a sharp growl and stood up. All the while growling, it sniffed the air.</p>
<p>“What’s he doing?” Mavis asked and quickly climbed up onto his chair, almost as if the dog would not be able to reach him. “Shut up dog!”</p>
<p>“Toska! Lie down!” Maxx reprimanded the dog. Suddenly the dog started barking and ran off into the dark. It continued barking and growling.</p>
<p>“Just ignore him! He probably saw a rabbit or something!” Maxx said, not feeling at all in the mood to go calm the dog. “You were saying about…”</p>
<p>Before he could finish his sentence, the dog gave a yelp of pain and went quiet. Both young men immediately sat up in their chairs, their ears cocked.</p>
<p>“What was that?” whispered Mavis.</p>
<p>“I don’t know,” Maxx whispered back. His heart was beating in his chest and he could scarcely hear anything above his own breathing.</p>
<p>“Should we go check?” Mavis whispered again. His usually mischievous face now looked scared.</p>
<p>“I think so,” Maxx answered again.</p>
<p>Both young men slowly stood up, but before they could start moving, a figure stepped out of the darkness. Maxx saw him first and a cold shiver shot through his body. The man looked angry and carried a huge gun, which he had swung across his shoulder. In his other hand he carried a bolt-cutter with which he had obviously gained entry through the fence. It took Mavis only a second to catch up and a quick whimper told Maxx that he had now seen the intruder as well.</p>
<p>The intruder rested his eyes on the two young men and, without saying a word, beckoned with his arm. Five more men stepped from the shadows, each with a big semi-automatic gun swung across his shoulders. They eyed the two young men without a word, but with eyes that dared them to do something.</p>
<p>“Against the tree!” the first one shouted and pointed his gun at them. Both of them immediately backed up till they stood against the tree. One of the others rushed forward and started patting them up and down, but soon realized that they had nothing with them but the clothes on their body. He quickly rejoined the others.</p>
<p>“Where is the safe?” the same guy said again.</p>
<p>“In…in the main bedroom down the hall!” Maxx said quickly, but immediately felt a little cowardly for talking so quickly. “But there is no money in there! This is only my grandfather’s f…”</p>
<p>“Quiet!” another guy said and Maxx noticed for the first time how nervous they all looked.</p>
<p>“We know there is no money, but your grandfather does have a lot of guns and hunting rifles!” and with those words he turned around and gave orders in a language that Maxx could not understand. A few seconds later, the leader and three others walked towards the house. Maxx’s mind quickly turned towards the telephone in the house. If only he could reach it, but his heart sank quickly. If they are any smarter than baboons, they would have cut the wires first thing. He shifted nervously.</p>
<p>“Stand still!” one of the remaining two men bellowed, he aimed with his gun at Maxx. “All I need is an excuse to fill you full of lead.”</p>
<p>“Why…?” Mavis tried to protest, but the other guy’s gun was already pointing in his direction. He quickly shut up! Both he and Maxx realized that these guys were nervous and ruthless. Killing two young people would not rate as important on their radar. Maxx shot Mavis a glance and both of them froze in place.</p>
<p>Maxx’s thoughts burned. He has to do something! He can see it in these people’s eyes. They do not care! They will kill them both as soon as they have everything they came for. But he would have to reveal his secret to others. His brother had warned him never to reveal his secret. Yet, saving his life and that of his friend seemed like a bigger priority at the moment. Slowly he started to stir the invisible ‘dynamo’ inside him. Immediately the hair on the back of his arms started to stand on end. He could feel the familiar trickle rising up inside his stomach, almost like the feeling you get when your foot is asleep.</p>
<p>“Whatever you do, don’t touch me,” Maxx whispered at his friend.</p>
<p>“What?” Mavis replied.</p>
<p>“Don’t touch me…” Maxx repeated.</p>
<p>“I’m not…” Mavis whispered confused.</p>
<p>“Shut up!” the same guy shouted again. “What are you talking about?”</p>
<p>“Nothing, nothing!” Maxx shouted quickly and brought his hands up in a defensive position. He looked at Mavis who stared at him confused and gave him a reassuring smile. Unexpectedly, he pointed with his right hand at the angry guy with the gun. Mavis’ mouth fell open as a blue bolt of electricity burst from Maxx’s hand. It streaked through the air with a sharp hissing sound. It hit the first guy in the chest, tossing him through the air like a doll. He slammed painfully into the tree and lay there twitching uncontrollably for a few seconds and then became motionless. Before the other guy could comprehend what had happened to his companion, a blue bolt of electricity slammed into him and threw him clear over the barbed-wire fence. He landed on the other side with a thud, rolling through the dirt and then stopping somewhere in the dark.</p>
<p>“That’s for hurting my aunt’s dog!” Maxx said and clenched his fist, making small little static sparks jump around his body in the darkness. He turned around to see his friend staring at him wide-eyed in the dying light of the fire.</p>
<p>“What the hell was that?” Mavis asked in shock.</p>
<p>“I would think it’s obvious,” Maxx said nonchalant.</p>
<p>“What did you do? How did you do it?”</p>
<p>“I’ve… uh…got special powers,” Maxx said and suddenly realized how ridiculous this must sound.</p>
<p>“Was that lightning?” Mavis asked wide-eyed. “You can shoot lightning?”</p>
<p>“Something like that! I can generate static electricity inside my body the same way you do when you walk over a carpet, only mine is much more powerful,” Maxx explained.</p>
<p>“How?”</p>
<p>“That is a long story!” Maxx said. “I’ll tell you about it later. You have to get out of here!”</p>
<p>“Me? What about you?”</p>
<p>[br][size=1]Posted at: September 24, 2006, 05:41:02 AM[/size][hr]“This is my grandfather’s farm and I’ll be damned if I’m going to allow these pond scum to plunder it!”</p>
<p>“I’m staying too,” Mavis said forcefully and Maxx’s heart jumped in surprise.</p>
<p>“It’s too dangerous…”</p>
<p>“I’m staying too!” Mavis said again, even more determined. “Just because you’ve got powers and I don’t, it that doesn’t mean that I can’t help.”</p>
<p>“You can do one thing!” Maxx said anxiously.</p>
<p>“Yes?”</p>
<p>“Quickly pull that guy out from under the tree and into the bushes where he can’t be seen!”</p>
<p>“Okay,” Mavis said and ran towards the guy lying under the tree. He grabbed the guy by the wrists and started pulling.</p>
<p>“A little help?” Mavis said irritably when he saw Maxx looking at him while he worked.</p>
<p>“I can’t,” Maxx answered, looking somewhat guilty.</p>
<p>“Why not?” Mavis asked as he contiued to drag the huge man, almost twice his size, across the ground and into the bushes.</p>
<p>“I’m charged with electricity at the moment, if I touch him I’ll discharge, probably killing him and myself in the process! That’s why I told you earlier not to touch me!”</p>
<p>“Cool. What do we do about the others now?” Mavis asked as he stashed the guy beneath a small tree and out of sight.</p>
<p>Before Maxx could answer, he heard someone talking loudly in the house. A few seconds later he heard the kitchen door open and close. He quickly beckoned to Mavis to follow him.</p>
<ol start="3">
<li>
</li>
</ol>
<p>“Where’s the other two?”</p>
<p>“Probably burying the two boys!”</p>
<p>“I didn’t hear any shots!”</p>
<p>“Shooting is not the only way to kill someone.”</p>
<p>The two men walked lazily towards the fire, obviously unaware that they’re being watched. One of them, the particularly fat one with a piggish face, bent down and threw some more logs on the fire. Maxx sat under the large metal table his family uses when they barbecue under the tree. He panted heavily, but sat upright, making sure not to touch the metal table. A long, dirty tablecloth hung loosely over the table, hiding him from view. A loud clang suddenly came from inside the house and a deep anger rose up in Maxx. What are they doing to his grandparents’ house?</p>
<p>“What the hell are they doing in there?” the fat one said irritably, almost like he read Maxx’s mind.</p>
<p>“They’re trying to break open the safe with a crowbar!” the other answered.</p>
<p>Maxx sighed. He has to do something soon or they will start to realize that their two comrades have not returned from ‘burying’ him and Mavis. He readied himself and gave the metal table a sharp kick.</p>
<p>“What was that?” the fat one said and looked around in panic.</p>
<p>“It came from the table,” the other one beckoned. “Check it out, it’s probably a rat or something!”</p>
<p>Maxx smiled and watched from under the tablecloth as the man approached. The fat man bent down with some difficulty, lifted a part of the tablecloth and peered in under the table. For a second he and Maxx stared into each other’s eyes. Maxx smiled when he saw that the guy had placed his hand on the table. Before the guy could react, Maxx grabbed the metal leg of the table and pushed hard from inside his guts. For a good five seconds the guy stood by the table shaking uncontrollably as the electricity passed through his body, making him unable to let go of the table. As soon as Maxx let go of the table’s leg, the guy toppled forward unconscious. His hair smoldered slightly and his left leg shook like a lizard’s lost tail. Maxx smiled and slowly slid out from under the table, only to be greeted by the barrel of a gun.</p>
<p>Maxx looked up into the eyes of the fat guy’s friend. The eyes burned with hatred and vengeance. Maxx could see in his eyes that he was going to kill him now. The guy’s finger closed around the trigger and Maxx closed his eyes, awaiting the bullet.</p>
<p>To his surprise there was a shout and he opened his eyes just in time to see Mavis dropping onto the guy like a human bomb, sending him stumbling forwards until he fell face first in the dirt. Mavis also stumbled forward with momentum and stopped just in time to avoid falling in the fire. Maxx did not waste any time and immediately a bolt of electricity tunneled into the guy as he scrambled to get up. His arms and legs immediately gave way and he fell unconscious onto his face.</p>
<p>“I told you to stay in the tree,” Maxx said angrily, but his entire body shook from fear and shock.</p>
<p>“Riiiiiiiight!” Mavis said sarcastically. “And just let him kill you? Thank you would be better.”</p>
<p>“Sorry…” Maxx said sheepishly, trying to get a grip on his body and mind, who was just realizing how close he just came to being shot. “Thanks!”</p>
<p>“What now?” Mavis asked and walked up to Maxx, while his eyes drifted towards the house.</p>
<p>“I’m going into the house to get rid of the two crooks!” Maxx said sternly. “You follow me and try to get to our cellphones. The idiots should be in my grandparents’ room, which is on the other side of the house. The cellphones are in the kitchen. Get them and call the police.”</p>
<p>“Why do you have all the fun?” Mavis said, but the look in his eyes betrayed his tough act.</p>
<p>“I’m supposed to be some sort of super hero, aren’t I?” Maxx smiled and they slowly made their way towards the house.</p>
<ol start="4">
<li>
</li>
</ol>
<p>Maxx and Mavis slowly opened the kitchen door and peeked inside. The kitchen was dark and quiet. A faint smell of barbecue hung in the air and Maxx noticed that the meat they had cooked earlier had been opened and eaten. Like cats, they slowly sneaked across the kitchen. Maxx could hear voices coming from the master bedroom down the hall. He gestured to Mavis to continue looking for the cellphones and made his way into the hall.</p>
<p>Slowly and surely he walked down the hall where photographs of his family hung against the walls. He rubbed his feet across the carpet to create more static electricity that added to the already enormous amount of energy stored inside him. By the time he reached the main bedroom, he was so charged up with energy that small sparks of voltage ran across his skin and occasionally jumped into the walls around him. Upon reaching the bedroom at the end of the hall, he peeked in. A dark figure sat crouched in the corner with a flashlight, clanging loudly as he tried to break open the safe. From what he can tell, the safe isn’t very far away from giving up its contents.</p>
<p>Maxx smiled to himself as he crept silently into the room. The idiot was so busy with the safe that he did not even notice that someone else had entered the room. Maxx sat behind his grandmother’s wooden dresser and lifted his hands towards the intruder. He was just about to fire when he heard the door to the bathroom behind him open.</p>
<p>“What the?” a deep voice said.</p>
<p>Maxx jumped around to see the leader of the intruders standing in the door, looking at him surprised. He had been concentrating so much on the guy by the safe that he had completely forgotten that there had been six intruders. For a few seconds the room was quiet in awe and then Maxx’s attacker tensed for the attack.</p>
<p>“NO! DON’T TOUCH M…!” Maxx tried to scream, but was cut short by the guy tackling him. The instant his attacker made contact, there was a deafening crack that sounded like lightning had struck right next to him and a blinding flash lit up the room for a second. His attacker could just as well have jumped into a high-voltage power line and was immediately thrown back by the voltage. He flew violently across the room and smashed so hard through the window that he tore the burglar-bars that covered the window straight out of the wall. He finally lay twitching between pieces of metal and broken glass, smoldering like he was on fire. A very nasty smell of burning hair and flesh filled the room.</p>
<p>Maxx lay next to the dresser. He was struggling to remain conscious. Every muscle in his body covulsed in spasms and where his attacker had made contact on his side was now a blue-purple spot that bled through the skin. The pain was unbearable.</p>
<p>“What did you do?” the final intruder said and approached him hesitantly. Maxx tried to move or get up, but not one of his muscles would listen. They all just twitched uncontrollably. His final opponent bent down beside him and placed his gun against Maxx’s temple. With all his energy now discharged, Maxx knew that he had no more defense. This time he was going to die for real! Yet he did not care! Anything to stop the pain! He would rather die than continue feeling like this. He closed his eyes tightly and awaited the shot.</p>
<p>For the second time that night the shot did not fire, instead there was a loud crash that sounded disturbingly enough like another window breaking. Maxx looked up to see the final attacker unconscious on the floor next to him. Behind him stood Mavis holding a large broken bottle.</p>
<p>“I’ve always wanted to do that!” Mavis smiled satisfactory and threw the bottle to one side. “Every time they did that on TV, I never really believed that a soda bottle could really be hard enough to knock someone unconscious!”</p>
<p>“What… a time to… test it!” Maxx said with much pain.</p>
<p>“Can I touch you now?” Mavis asked apprehensively, he had obviously seen what had happened to the other guy.</p>
<p>Maxx only nodded and Mavis approached him slowly. After first poking Maxx a few times with his finger to assure it is safe, he helped him up and let him rest on his shoulder. With much difficulty Maxx’s legs finally began responding again. They slowly made their way to the broken window and looked through at the smoldering man lying in the glittering pool of glass and metal.</p>
<p>“Oh man that’s nasty!” Mavis said and brought his free hand up to his nose. “I really hope he’s dead for his own sake!”</p>
<p>“He was dead long before he hit the window!” Maxx said sadly. The stench made him want to gag, but even those muscles weren’t working properly. He felt very guilty for killing the man, but how was he supposed to know that the guy would jump him?</p>
<p>“Did you call the police?” Maxx asked nervously.</p>
<p>“No…” Mavis said and Maxx could feel his friend’s body shaking slightly. “The signal kept dying on me and the house phone are cut off. I stopped trying when I saw the guy coming up behind you from the bathroom. I’ll try to call them again now, but first we have to decide what to tell them. I assume we can’t tell them that you’re a Pikachu wannabe?”</p>
<p>“No. I think I’ll call my brother or one of his friends,” Maxx said softly. “They’ll know what to do! We can hold of calling the police until they arrive.”</p>
<p>“Your brother?” Mavis asked. “What has he got to do with this and how on earth will he get here so quickly? He’s just under two hours drive from here.”</p>
<p>“He’ll probably fly or get Blink to bring him!”</p>
<p>“Fly? Blink?”</p>
<p>Maxx just smiled and rolled his eyes.</p>
<p>“While I call my brother, you go get us a few beers from the cooler. I’ve got a LOT to tell you my friend!”</p>
<p>Thats mines <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=9" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/lets-have-a-story-of-the-week-competition/15740/46">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/lets-have-a-story-of-the-week-competition/15740/46</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 24 Sep 2006 15:41:44 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-15740-46</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/lets-have-a-story-of-the-week-competition/15740.rss">Lets have a &quot;story of the week&quot; competition?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Lets have a &quot;story of the week&quot; competition?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Ron Ron]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/ron">@Ron</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Or how about just a Writing Section?</p>
<p>For Stories, Poetry, Essays, etc. <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=9" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/lets-have-a-story-of-the-week-competition/15740/45">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/lets-have-a-story-of-the-week-competition/15740/45</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 24 Sep 2006 10:01:31 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-15740-45</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/lets-have-a-story-of-the-week-competition/15740.rss">Lets have a &quot;story of the week&quot; competition?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Lets have a &quot;story of the week&quot; competition?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@wall_of_fir wall of fir]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/wall_of_fir">@wall_of_fir</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>oops…lol</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/lets-have-a-story-of-the-week-competition/15740/44">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/lets-have-a-story-of-the-week-competition/15740/44</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 24 Sep 2006 09:44:35 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-15740-44</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/lets-have-a-story-of-the-week-competition/15740.rss">Lets have a &quot;story of the week&quot; competition?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Lets have a &quot;story of the week&quot; competition?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@XxKanexX Kane.]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/xxkanexx">@XxKanexX</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>You guys do realise that this hasn’t even started yet?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/lets-have-a-story-of-the-week-competition/15740/43">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/lets-have-a-story-of-the-week-competition/15740/43</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 24 Sep 2006 08:16:49 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-15740-43</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/lets-have-a-story-of-the-week-competition/15740.rss">Lets have a &quot;story of the week&quot; competition?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Lets have a &quot;story of the week&quot; competition?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@wall_of_fir wall of fir]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/wall_of_fir">@wall_of_fir</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>sorry lol, got a little mad, peopel do that alot.it get really annoying</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/lets-have-a-story-of-the-week-competition/15740/42">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/lets-have-a-story-of-the-week-competition/15740/42</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 24 Sep 2006 07:26:41 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-15740-42</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/lets-have-a-story-of-the-week-competition/15740.rss">Lets have a &quot;story of the week&quot; competition?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Lets have a &quot;story of the week&quot; competition?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Drunk_On_Java Drunk On Java]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/drunk_on_java">@Drunk_On_Java</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote no-group quote-modified" data-post="40" data-topic="15740">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 wall of fir:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>he did, but he accidentily put his text in his quote lookit theirs differently, see javas has the “meh, I got all that in my story,except resolution.Seeing as its not over” see how yours doenst say that?what a noob typer.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Mistakes happen. No need to flame.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/lets-have-a-story-of-the-week-competition/15740/41">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/lets-have-a-story-of-the-week-competition/15740/41</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 24 Sep 2006 07:22:59 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-15740-41</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/lets-have-a-story-of-the-week-competition/15740.rss">Lets have a &quot;story of the week&quot; competition?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Lets have a &quot;story of the week&quot; competition?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@wall_of_fir wall of fir]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/wall_of_fir">@wall_of_fir</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>he did, but he accidentily put his text in his quote lookit theirs differently, see javas has the “meh, I got all that in my story,except resolution.Seeing as its not over” see how yours doenst say that?what a noob typer.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/lets-have-a-story-of-the-week-competition/15740/40">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/lets-have-a-story-of-the-week-competition/15740/40</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 24 Sep 2006 06:45:52 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-15740-40</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/lets-have-a-story-of-the-week-competition/15740.rss">Lets have a &quot;story of the week&quot; competition?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Lets have a &quot;story of the week&quot; competition?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@leader leader]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/leader">@leader</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>You quoted the text, but didn’t write anything.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/lets-have-a-story-of-the-week-competition/15740/39">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/lets-have-a-story-of-the-week-competition/15740/39</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 24 Sep 2006 06:40:45 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-15740-39</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/lets-have-a-story-of-the-week-competition/15740.rss">Lets have a &quot;story of the week&quot; competition?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Lets have a &quot;story of the week&quot; competition?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Drunk_On_Java Drunk On Java]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/drunk_on_java">@Drunk_On_Java</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“leader, post:37, topic:15740”][quote author=frost21 link=topic=23503.msg267697#msg267697 date=1159072947]<br>
I want leader to write a story =)<br>
[/quote]<br>
Meh, I got all that in my story except resolution, seeing as it’s not over.</p>
<p>When I have time. I have a very imaginative, and creative mind.</p>
<h2>Anyone can write a story, but it might not be interesting. If you want to write good stories then you have to practice. For those who want to write a story, but don’t know where to start, this for you.</h2>
<p>You can write a story about anything you want. All you need are the basics. You wouldn’t bake a cake without knowing the ingredients, right?</p>
<p>So before you write, it helps to know the ingredients of a story. That means you know what you want to write about.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Story Structure</span><br>
It has a beginning, a middle and an end. Some stories even end up in the same place they started. It is like a snake that has its tail in its mouth, the head is the beginning, and the tail is the end.</p>
<p>For example, in The Wizard of Oz, Dorothy starts out in Kansas, travels to Oz in a cyclone and ends up back in Kansas.</p>
<p>Ready to start your story? Then grab a pencil and paper, or open up a new file on your computer, and away we go!</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Main Character</span> - <span class="bbcode-i">The person, animal or thing your story is about</span><br>
Every story starts with a main character. It can be any animal, human or anything else you want it to be. Make sure you focus mostly on the main character in the story, but add other characters to make the story more interesting.</p>
<p>Start by asking yourself some questions:<br>
• Who or what is your main character?<br>
• What does he, she or it like/dislike?<br>
• What is your character’s personality?<br>
• What does your character look like?</p>
<p>When you start getting answers, you can write a brief description of your character. Describe his/her characteristics.</p>
<p>Example: Josh, a student, attends Benix High School in Urville, Newcountry. Althought he is shorter than most 15 year olds, he can win anyone in a arm wrestling match. He plays for the Benix Tigers, the school football team. Etcetera…</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Setting</span> - <span class="bbcode-i">Where your story takes place</span><br>
Every story needs to take place somewhere. Of course, you might say. But your story’s setting can have either a big or little impact on the story. What would The Wizard of Oz be without Oz? Just a story about a girl and a dog in dusty old Kansas.</p>
<p>Ask yourself these questions:<br>
• Where does your story take place - on the moon, in Hawaii, inside your dad’s nose, or someplace completely different?<br>
• When does your story take place: past, present or future?<br>
• How much does your setting affect your main character’s problem?</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Problem/Conflict</span> - <span class="bbcode-i">The challenge your character must face and overcome</span><br>
Without a problem, your story would be very boring. But when you give your main character a problem to solve, your story comes alive. Be sure to make it a big enough problem. In stories, the main character solves the problem, but then more problems come. This is called <span class="bbcode-b">Complication</span>.</p>
<p>Important tip: The more times your character tries and fails, the better.</p>
<p>Ask yourself these questions:<br>
• What is your main character’s problem?<br>
• Is it a big enough problem that it will take a whole story to solve it?<br>
• How does your main character try and fail to solve her or his problem?</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Resolution</span> - <span class="bbcode-i">How the character finally solves the problem</span><br>
The most satisfying resolutions come when you think your hero is about to give up. When they’ve tried everything else, they finally solve the problem. It’s best if your main character solves the problem on his or her own, but you can also use other characters to help the main character solve the problem.</p>
<p>*Remember to have fun and be creative. If your not having fun then make it fun.<br>
*Be descriptive, and explain the most important parts of your story in good detail.<br>
*Use adjectives, to express the characters.</p>
<p>Your friend,<br>
Leader[/quote]</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/lets-have-a-story-of-the-week-competition/15740/38">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/lets-have-a-story-of-the-week-competition/15740/38</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 24 Sep 2006 06:32:53 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-15740-38</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/lets-have-a-story-of-the-week-competition/15740.rss">Lets have a &quot;story of the week&quot; competition?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Lets have a &quot;story of the week&quot; competition?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@leader leader]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/leader">@leader</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote no-group" data-post="36" data-topic="15740">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 frost21:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>I want leader to write a story =)</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>When I have time. I have a very imaginative, and creative mind.</p>
<h2>Anyone can write a story, but it might not be interesting. If you want to write good stories then you have to practice. For those who want to write a story, but don’t know where to start, this for you.</h2>
<p>You can write a story about anything you want. All you need are the basics. You wouldn’t bake a cake without knowing the ingredients, right?</p>
<p>So before you write, it helps to know the ingredients of a story. That means you know what you want to write about.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Story Structure</span><br>
It has a beginning, a middle and an end. Some stories even end up in the same place they started. It is like a snake that has its tail in its mouth, the head is the beginning, and the tail is the end.</p>
<p>For example, in The Wizard of Oz, Dorothy starts out in Kansas, travels to Oz in a cyclone and ends up back in Kansas.</p>
<p>Ready to start your story? Then grab a pencil and paper, or open up a new file on your computer, and away we go!</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Main Character</span> - <span class="bbcode-i">The person, animal or thing your story is about</span><br>
Every story starts with a main character. It can be any animal, human or anything else you want it to be. Make sure you focus mostly on the main character in the story, but add other characters to make the story more interesting.</p>
<p>Start by asking yourself some questions:<br>
• Who or what is your main character?<br>
• What does he, she or it like/dislike?<br>
• What is your character’s personality?<br>
• What does your character look like?</p>
<p>When you start getting answers, you can write a brief description of your character. Describe his/her characteristics.</p>
<p>Example: Josh, a student, attends Benix High School in Urville, Newcountry. Althought he is shorter than most 15 year olds, he can win anyone in a arm wrestling match. He plays for the Benix Tigers, the school football team. Etcetera…</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Setting</span> - <span class="bbcode-i">Where your story takes place</span><br>
Every story needs to take place somewhere. Of course, you might say. But your story’s setting can have either a big or little impact on the story. What would The Wizard of Oz be without Oz? Just a story about a girl and a dog in dusty old Kansas.</p>
<p>Ask yourself these questions:<br>
• Where does your story take place - on the moon, in Hawaii, inside your dad’s nose, or someplace completely different?<br>
• When does your story take place: past, present or future?<br>
• How much does your setting affect your main character’s problem?</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Problem/Conflict</span> - <span class="bbcode-i">The challenge your character must face and overcome</span><br>
Without a problem, your story would be very boring. But when you give your main character a problem to solve, your story comes alive. Be sure to make it a big enough problem. In stories, the main character solves the problem, but then more problems come. This is called <span class="bbcode-b">Complication</span>.</p>
<p>Important tip: The more times your character tries and fails, the better.</p>
<p>Ask yourself these questions:<br>
• What is your main character’s problem?<br>
• Is it a big enough problem that it will take a whole story to solve it?<br>
• How does your main character try and fail to solve her or his problem?</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Resolution</span> - <span class="bbcode-i">How the character finally solves the problem</span><br>
The most satisfying resolutions come when you think your hero is about to give up. When they’ve tried everything else, they finally solve the problem. It’s best if your main character solves the problem on his or her own, but you can also use other characters to help the main character solve the problem.</p>
<p>*Remember to have fun and be creative. If your not having fun then make it fun.<br>
*Be descriptive, and explain the most important parts of your story in good detail.<br>
*Use adjectives, to express the characters.</p>
<p>Your friend,<br>
Leader</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/lets-have-a-story-of-the-week-competition/15740/37">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/lets-have-a-story-of-the-week-competition/15740/37</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 24 Sep 2006 04:48:28 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-15740-37</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/lets-have-a-story-of-the-week-competition/15740.rss">Lets have a &quot;story of the week&quot; competition?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Lets have a &quot;story of the week&quot; competition?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@system system]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/system">@system</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I want leader to write a story =)</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/lets-have-a-story-of-the-week-competition/15740/36">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/lets-have-a-story-of-the-week-competition/15740/36</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 24 Sep 2006 04:42:27 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-15740-36</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/lets-have-a-story-of-the-week-competition/15740.rss">Lets have a &quot;story of the week&quot; competition?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Lets have a &quot;story of the week&quot; competition?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@chad_haynes chad haynes]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/chad_haynes">@chad_haynes</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>i will…</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/lets-have-a-story-of-the-week-competition/15740/35">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/lets-have-a-story-of-the-week-competition/15740/35</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 24 Sep 2006 04:41:52 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-15740-35</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/lets-have-a-story-of-the-week-competition/15740.rss">Lets have a &quot;story of the week&quot; competition?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Lets have a &quot;story of the week&quot; competition?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@leader leader]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/leader">@leader</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Wait and see.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/lets-have-a-story-of-the-week-competition/15740/34">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/lets-have-a-story-of-the-week-competition/15740/34</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 24 Sep 2006 04:39:39 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-15740-34</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/lets-have-a-story-of-the-week-competition/15740.rss">Lets have a &quot;story of the week&quot; competition?</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
