<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Account Deletion Request</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/account-deletion-request/556406</link>
    <description>Hello,

I used to use your wonderful community a long time ago (under the name dragonfire455) around the time when I was 15.

I&#39;ve always loved your community and how you managed to build it into what it is today.

I won&#39;t lie, I was a kid and I acted hella retarded. That&#39;s no excuse, however it is for that reason I humbly request that my account and my posts be purged from your site.

I don&#39;t have access to my old email (dragonfire455@yahoo.com) but is there any way you could help me? I know it has been a long time, but I would just like to be forgotten. I hope you understand where I&#39;m coming from, and that you have a wonderful day.

Thank you.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2017 13:09:48 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Staff Help</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/account-deletion-request/556406.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Account Deletion Request</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Anal_beads Anal beads]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/anal_beads">@Anal_beads</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Hello,</p>
<p>I used to use your wonderful community a long time ago (under the name dragonfire455) around the time when I was 15.</p>
<p>I’ve always loved your community and how you managed to build it into what it is today.</p>
<p>I won’t lie, I was a kid and I acted hella retarded. That’s no excuse, however it is for that reason I humbly request that my account and my posts be purged from your site.</p>
<p>I don’t have access to my old email (<a href="mailto:dragonfire455@yahoo.com">dragonfire455@yahoo.com</a>) but is there any way you could help me? I know it has been a long time, but I would just like to be forgotten. I hope you understand where I’m coming from, and that you have a wonderful day.</p>
<p>Thank you.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/account-deletion-request/556406/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/account-deletion-request/556406/1</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2017 13:09:48 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-556406-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/account-deletion-request/556406.rss">Account Deletion Request</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
