<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Tutorial Section Change</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/tutorial-section-change/261235</link>
    <description>By staff request, Taharok along with Moparisthebest, have created a package that require all tutorials to be approved before they can be seen by other members.  This is due to improper use of the tutorial section.  Since the staff will now have to approve tutorials, they will not show up instantly.  This does not mean you can PM us asking why it isn&#39;t showing up; it only makes it longer.  

We hope this new feature will bring MoparScape forward and prevent the use of &#39;copy and paste&#39; tutorials and &#39;five minute&#39; tutorials.  If you have any questions regarding the new system, please feel free to PM myself or another staff member.

Edit: This also changes the way people get punished based on posting tutorials. Tutorials should no longer result in dot punishments unless the person is excessively breaking the rules. In most other cases, the user may be private messaged by the moderator who declined their post to verbally warn them not to break the rules again. This is optional but recommended.

- The Staff Team</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2009 03:19:53 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Community Suggestions</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/tutorial-section-change/261235.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Tutorial Section Change</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Tico135 Tico]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/tico135">@Tico135</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>By staff request, Taharok along with Moparisthebest, have created a package that require all tutorials to be approved before they can be seen by other members.  This is due to improper use of the tutorial section.  Since the staff will now have to approve tutorials, they will not show up instantly.  This does not mean you can PM us asking why it isn’t showing up; it only makes it longer.</p>
<p>We hope this new feature will bring MoparScape forward and prevent the use of ‘copy and paste’ tutorials and ‘five minute’ tutorials.  If you have any questions regarding the new system, please feel free to PM myself or another staff member.</p>
<p>Edit: This also changes the way people get punished based on posting tutorials. Tutorials should no longer result in dot punishments unless the person is excessively breaking the rules. In most other cases, the user may be private messaged by the moderator who declined their post to verbally warn them not to break the rules again. This is optional but recommended.</p>
<ul>
<li>The Staff Team</li>
</ul>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/tutorial-section-change/261235/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/tutorial-section-change/261235/1</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2009 03:19:53 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-261235-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/tutorial-section-change/261235.rss">Tutorial Section Change</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
