<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Looking for a lead coder/Helper!</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/looking-for-a-lead-coder-helper/542518</link>
    <description>To begin with, my name is Perfekt, I&#39;ve been apart of the rsps community for around 4+ years. However, in these 4+ years, I&#39;ve only hosted and coded one server. This server was hosted 3+ years ago and died off fairly quickly due to lack of my time into the server, and some coding problems.
I&#39;m not the best coder, I can say that without a doubt. Hell, I&#39;m not very good at all. I used to be decent, but so much has changed during my time away. However, I really have the hopes of running a RSPS once again. I can host the RSPS without any problems whatsoever, that part is easy, I just need someone to guide me through some things of coding. I&#39;m not asking for someone who will code the whole server from top to bottom, I just need someone who will answer Skype, maybe teamview once in a while to lead me in the right direction as to what I&#39;m trying to accomplish. As I said, I&#39;m not the best coder, so someone who could deal with my stupid questions would be very helpful. I now have multiple friends who can help populate the server, and have agreed to help in doing so.
My future plans with the server include 
-A lot of coding
-VPS hosted once things get running, until then I will host.
-Donator system
-Fully run economy
-Advertising on many toplist websites
-Webclient and Webhosted forums.

I really hope somebody can and will help me with this RSPS, or even head me in the right direction when I need a little guidance. I feel the forums take too long to respond, and half the time you don&#39;t even get a reply and the thread dies. Anyways, if anyone is interested, add me on Skype at : gerald.gorritz
or reply to this thread and i will reply as soon as possible!</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 28 Apr 2014 04:42:59 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/looking-for-a-lead-coder-helper/542518.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Looking for a lead coder/Helper!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Project_Territh Project Territh]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/project_territh">@Project_Territh</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I’m interested added you on Skype.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/looking-for-a-lead-coder-helper/542518/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/looking-for-a-lead-coder-helper/542518/2</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 28 Apr 2014 04:42:59 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-542518-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/looking-for-a-lead-coder-helper/542518.rss">Looking for a lead coder/Helper!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Looking for a lead coder/Helper!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Notsoperfekt Notsoperfekt]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/notsoperfekt">@Notsoperfekt</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>To begin with, my name is Perfekt, I’ve been apart of the rsps community for around 4+ years. However, in these 4+ years, I’ve only hosted and coded one server. This server was hosted 3+ years ago and died off fairly quickly due to lack of my time into the server, and some coding problems.<br>
I’m not the best coder, I can say that without a doubt. Hell, I’m not very good at all. I used to be decent, but so much has changed during my time away. However, I really have the hopes of running a RSPS once again. I can host the RSPS without any problems whatsoever, that part is easy, I just need someone to guide me through some things of coding. I’m not asking for someone who will code the whole server from top to bottom, I just need someone who will answer Skype, maybe teamview once in a while to lead me in the right direction as to what I’m trying to accomplish. As I said, I’m not the best coder, so someone who could deal with my stupid questions would be very helpful. I now have multiple friends who can help populate the server, and have agreed to help in doing so.<br>
My future plans with the server include<br>
-A lot of coding<br>
-VPS hosted once things get running, until then I will host.<br>
-Donator system<br>
-Fully run economy<br>
-Advertising on many toplist websites<br>
-Webclient and Webhosted forums.</p>
<p>I really hope somebody can and will help me with this RSPS, or even head me in the right direction when I need a little guidance. I feel the forums take too long to respond, and half the time you don’t even get a reply and the thread dies. Anyways, if anyone is interested, add me on Skype at : gerald.gorritz<br>
or reply to this thread and i will reply as soon as possible!</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/looking-for-a-lead-coder-helper/542518/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/looking-for-a-lead-coder-helper/542518/1</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2014 16:22:06 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-542518-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/looking-for-a-lead-coder-helper/542518.rss">Looking for a lead coder/Helper!</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
