<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Wizarding World of youknowwho</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/wizarding-world-of-youknowwho/543060</link>
    <description>[center]Hello everyone,

First of all please forgive me and feel free to correct any grammar mistakes, I am dutch and my English isn&#39;t the best :)
Yesterday I was reading one of my favorite franchises, harry potter and I was wondering, wouldn&#39;t it be amazing to combine all the harry potter stuff into one mmorpg where people could create their own wizards and such. But to actually make this it would require all kinds of copyrights and big game businesses. So my idea is to use the runescape base to build off and create a amazing harry potter like experience.
Oh and yeah I won&#39;t be developing since I have so much to learn and am not ready to do something big like this. :)

[b]My idea:[/b]

So to actually make people understand what my idea contains i should divide it in several parts.
[i][b]
Part 1 Skills[/b][/i]

We all know how the skills work in runescape, in this rsps I would like to combine several skills into each other and also remove skills which doesn&#39;t add anything to the game experience. Some skills will become more important than other skills. For example magic, magic is ofcourse the most important skill but I think it should be removed from this rsps. You may think now wtf Stan you&#39;re mental but no, Magic should be the main thing in the game not something you could train and then just stop using it. In this game magic should be the uhm mother of all skills if you know what I mean and this mother of all skills is divided into several other skills, like defensive charms, curses, healing, potions etc.. So we still keep the defensive/attack/strength stuff but now it is going to be done in a unique way. You may wonder now if you could still be a warrior or an archer? The answer to this specific question I am not sure about, yet.

[i][b]Part 2 Armour/Weapons[/b][/i]

So in this game, no one has guessed it, magic is going to be the strongest style (if ranged and the warrior stuff will be included) so we&#39;ll have to create new weapons, especially wands. There are already a couple of wands in the game but I would like to have new and refreshing wands with so much more power then they have right now. This game would also gives you the ability to use staffs which are more powerful then wands but probably slower and heavier. Now for the armour, the magic armour in the current game is complete shit and the most of it looks like crap. This have to be different but we do not want armour to be difference between life and death. In this game you have to earn your power and not buy it.

[b][i]Part 3 Quests[/i][/b]

This is probably the part where I am most excited over, I&#39;ve got so many ideas for cool quests and cool rewards. I really want quests to be important in the game and like monthly or weekly adds to keep players interested in the game so they won&#39;t get bored. I really need those quests carefully developed.

[b][i]Part 4 Animations[/i][/b]

I would love to have new animations for this game but to be honest my knowledge of animating is like 0 so I would love to hear from anyone if this is possible and how much time it will require. Anyways we will be using new animations (mostly unseen but added in the game as well.) I do know that int he script we can decide how fast the animation/gfx will go or how high it should be etc.. But like I said I aint a expert.
[b][i]
Part 5 Custom models[/i][/b]

In the game I would love to have custom models from objects to npc&#39;s to items, I&#39;ve seen some awesome work on mopar from some people and I hope they would like to join this project and help to make this big.
[i][b]
The base[/b][/i]

The base we&#39;re going to use depends on our developers, they could use any base they want if it&#39;s stable and going to be able to hold around 500-1k players. So I think we&#39;ll need something like runesource or something else with good networking etc...


So that&#39;s pretty much it, I am really looking forward to start with this project. Before people start appealing for a place in the team please remember this is a serious project and only apply if you really know what you&#39;re doing.
[b]
The team:[/b]
[b]
Project Leader:[/b]
[i]Luna-scape(Stan)[/i]
[b]
Server developers:[/b]
[i]-open-
-open-[/i]
[b]
Client developer:[/b]
[i]-open-
[/i]
[b]Modelers:[/b]
[i]-open-
-open-[/i]

[b]Animator(s)?:[/b]
[i]-open-
-open-[/i]


If you would like to join please fill in this application form:
[code]
What is your name?

What is your experience with object orientated programming?

Could you link me to some work [b]you[/b]&#39;ve done?

Reason why you would like to help me with this project?

Your skypename?

Which IDE do you prefer?[/code]

Just fill that in and you can pm me it or post it here.

Thanks for reading!

If anyone has some brilliant ideas which you like to share with me please pm me or add me on skype.

Skypename: stanownd

(iknow it&#39;s a gay name)
[/center]</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 14 May 2014 15:20:08 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/wizarding-world-of-youknowwho/543060.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Wizarding World of youknowwho</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@luna-scape luna-scape]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/luna-scape">@luna-scape</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[center]Hello everyone,</p>
<p>First of all please forgive me and feel free to correct any grammar mistakes, I am dutch and my English isn’t the best <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=5" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"><br>
Yesterday I was reading one of my favorite franchises, harry potter and I was wondering, wouldn’t it be amazing to combine all the harry potter stuff into one mmorpg where people could create their own wizards and such. But to actually make this it would require all kinds of copyrights and big game businesses. So my idea is to use the runescape base to build off and create a amazing harry potter like experience.<br>
Oh and yeah I won’t be developing since I have so much to learn and am not ready to do something big like this. <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=5" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">My idea:</span></p>
<p>So to actually make people understand what my idea contains i should divide it in several parts.<br>
<span class="bbcode-i"><span class="bbcode-b"><br>
Part 1 Skills</span></span></p>
<p>We all know how the skills work in runescape, in this rsps I would like to combine several skills into each other and also remove skills which doesn’t add anything to the game experience. Some skills will become more important than other skills. For example magic, magic is ofcourse the most important skill but I think it should be removed from this rsps. You may think now wtf Stan you’re mental but no, Magic should be the main thing in the game not something you could train and then just stop using it. In this game magic should be the uhm mother of all skills if you know what I mean and this mother of all skills is divided into several other skills, like defensive charms, curses, healing, potions etc… So we still keep the defensive/attack/strength stuff but now it is going to be done in a unique way. You may wonder now if you could still be a warrior or an archer? The answer to this specific question I am not sure about, yet.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-i"><span class="bbcode-b">Part 2 Armour/Weapons</span></span></p>
<p>So in this game, no one has guessed it, magic is going to be the strongest style (if ranged and the warrior stuff will be included) so we’ll have to create new weapons, especially wands. There are already a couple of wands in the game but I would like to have new and refreshing wands with so much more power then they have right now. This game would also gives you the ability to use staffs which are more powerful then wands but probably slower and heavier. Now for the armour, the magic armour in the current game is complete shit and the most of it looks like crap. This have to be different but we do not want armour to be difference between life and death. In this game you have to earn your power and not buy it.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b"><span class="bbcode-i">Part 3 Quests</span></span></p>
<p>This is probably the part where I am most excited over, I’ve got so many ideas for cool quests and cool rewards. I really want quests to be important in the game and like monthly or weekly adds to keep players interested in the game so they won’t get bored. I really need those quests carefully developed.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b"><span class="bbcode-i">Part 4 Animations</span></span></p>
<p>I would love to have new animations for this game but to be honest my knowledge of animating is like 0 so I would love to hear from anyone if this is possible and how much time it will require. Anyways we will be using new animations (mostly unseen but added in the game as well.) I do know that int he script we can decide how fast the animation/gfx will go or how high it should be etc… But like I said I aint a expert.<br>
<span class="bbcode-b"><span class="bbcode-i"><br>
Part 5 Custom models</span></span></p>
<p>In the game I would love to have custom models from objects to npc’s to items, I’ve seen some awesome work on mopar from some people and I hope they would like to join this project and help to make this big.<br>
<span class="bbcode-i"><span class="bbcode-b"><br>
The base</span></span></p>
<p>The base we’re going to use depends on our developers, they could use any base they want if it’s stable and going to be able to hold around 500-1k players. So I think we’ll need something like runesource or something else with good networking etc…</p>
<p>So that’s pretty much it, I am really looking forward to start with this project. Before people start appealing for a place in the team please remember this is a serious project and only apply if you really know what you’re doing.<br>
<span class="bbcode-b"><br>
The team:</span><br>
<span class="bbcode-b"><br>
Project Leader:</span><br>
<span class="bbcode-i">Luna-scape(Stan)</span><br>
<span class="bbcode-b"><br>
Server developers:</span><br>
<span class="bbcode-i">-open-<br>
-open-</span><br>
<span class="bbcode-b"><br>
Client developer:</span><br>
<span class="bbcode-i">-open-<br>
</span><br>
<span class="bbcode-b">Modelers:</span><br>
<span class="bbcode-i">-open-<br>
-open-</span></p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Animator(s)?:</span><br>
<span class="bbcode-i">-open-<br>
-open-</span></p>
<p>If you would like to join please fill in this application form:</p>
<p>[code]<br>
What is your name?</p>
<p>What is your experience with object orientated programming?</p>
<p>Could you link me to some work <span class="bbcode-b">you</span>’ve done?</p>
<p>Reason why you would like to help me with this project?</p>
<p>Your skypename?</p>
<p>Which IDE do you prefer?[/code]</p>
<p>Just fill that in and you can pm me it or post it here.</p>
<p>Thanks for reading!</p>
<p>If anyone has some brilliant ideas which you like to share with me please pm me or add me on skype.</p>
<p>Skypename: stanownd</p>
<p>(iknow it’s a gay name)<br>
[/center]</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/wizarding-world-of-youknowwho/543060/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/wizarding-world-of-youknowwho/543060/1</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2014 15:20:08 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-543060-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/wizarding-world-of-youknowwho/543060.rss">Wizarding World of youknowwho</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
