<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Problems with server.. :o</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/problems-with-server-o/406201</link>
    <description>Okay um.. I have a problem some reason I have to use utorrent &amp; pfconfig to put my server online it seems i can&#39;t have one without the other if I want my server online. It&#39;s a problem because when I try to load the server/client it keeps saying that it&#39;s already in use only because I have to port connections one with utorrent and one with pfconfig. Anyone have any idea&#39;s how I can get just one port to let my server go online?

Cheers.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 24 Jul 2011 23:45:37 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/problems-with-server-o/406201.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Problems with server.. :o</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@laurensman laurensman]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/laurensman">@laurensman</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>lol… you would go to your start bar. type in cmd, press enter type ipconfig, and your default ip is the ip you will type in your web browsers bar, then it should take you to your router control panel, then you go into something like single port fowarding, depending on what kind of router you have, then you would type where it says application name put w\e you want there, then the first port slot u will put 43594, then the second 43594, then put udp/tcp both of them thats what i did, and then make sure you check it in the check box if  theres one and save and then it should work.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/problems-with-server-o/406201/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/problems-with-server-o/406201/2</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 24 Jul 2011 23:45:37 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-406201-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/problems-with-server-o/406201.rss">Problems with server.. :o</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Problems with server.. :o</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Carbon_X12 Carbon X12]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/carbon_x12">@Carbon_X12</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Okay um… I have a problem some reason I have to use utorrent &amp; pfconfig to put my server online it seems i can’t have one without the other if I want my server online. It’s a problem because when I try to load the server/client it keeps saying that it’s already in use only because I have to port connections one with utorrent and one with pfconfig. Anyone have any idea’s how I can get just one port to let my server go online?</p>
<p>Cheers.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/problems-with-server-o/406201/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/problems-with-server-o/406201/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 24 Jul 2011 21:44:06 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-406201-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/problems-with-server-o/406201.rss">Problems with server.. :o</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
