<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>FlowLayout Vertical Gap</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/flowlayout-vertical-gap/404054</link>
    <description>Is there a way to temporarily change the vertical gap between two lines in a FlowLayout? I&#39;ve got two lines that I want closer to each other than the rest. Example:
[code]line of text (original)

line of text (original)

line of text (closer)
line of text (closer)

line of text (original)[/code]
Setting the layout&#39;s vertical gap before the add and then changing it back to the default after adding the component does not work. I.E.
[code]layout.setVgap(5);
...
layout.setVgap(15);[/code]
I understand why this doesn&#39;t work ^

Any ideas how this could be done? Or is it not a good idea with a FlowLayout? I&#39;ve restricted resizing and maximizing the internal frame, so I know that the window will never change it&#39;s size.

Anyways, thanks for any help or opinions.
Adam

[b]EDIT:[/b] I understand the concept of a FlowLayout and why this functionality may not work. I&#39;m pretty much trying to specify at a certain line to change the gap, yet with FlowLayout, technically we don&#39;t know how many lines we would have because the user could resize the window; however, in my situation I do know how many lines there would be.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 14 Jul 2011 06:40:46 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>General Programming</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/flowlayout-vertical-gap/404054.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>FlowLayout Vertical Gap</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Mod_Adam Adam]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/mod_adam">@Mod_Adam</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Is there a way to temporarily change the vertical gap between two lines in a FlowLayout? I’ve got two lines that I want closer to each other than the rest. Example:</p>
<p>[code]line of text (original)</p>
<p>line of text (original)</p>
<p>line of text (closer)<br>
line of text (closer)</p>
<p>line of text (original)[/code]<br>
Setting the layout’s vertical gap before the add and then changing it back to the default after adding the component does not work. I.E.</p>
<p><code>layout.setVgap(5);
...
layout.setVgap(15);</code><br>
I understand why this doesn’t work ^</p>
<p>Any ideas how this could be done? Or is it not a good idea with a FlowLayout? I’ve restricted resizing and maximizing the internal frame, so I know that the window will never change it’s size.</p>
<p>Anyways, thanks for any help or opinions.<br>
Adam</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">EDIT:</span> I understand the concept of a FlowLayout and why this functionality may not work. I’m pretty much trying to specify at a certain line to change the gap, yet with FlowLayout, technically we don’t know how many lines we would have because the user could resize the window; however, in my situation I do know how many lines there would be.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/flowlayout-vertical-gap/404054/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/flowlayout-vertical-gap/404054/1</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 14 Jul 2011 06:40:46 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-404054-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/flowlayout-vertical-gap/404054.rss">FlowLayout Vertical Gap</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
