<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Anna Nicole Smith Died</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/anna-nicole-smith-died/56389</link>
    <description>[quote=&quot;Yahoo&quot;]LOS ANGELES (AFP) -
Anna Nicole Smith will be remembered as the stripper who married an aged oil billionaire and became a pop-culture icon before her life collapsed under the weight of tragedy and legal woes.
ADVERTISEMENT

The former Playboy model was once seen as one of the world&#39;s most desirable women and appeared on the road to supermodel status when she replaced Claudia Schiffer as Guess Jeans model in the early 1990s.

But the platinum-blonde facade crumbled over the course of the next decade as her life unraveled in the full glare of a voracious US tabloid media.

The mysterious sudden death of Smith&#39;s son Daniel in the Bahamas just days after the birth of her daughter last September, and her &quot;commitment ceremony&quot; days later with lawyer Howard K. Stern enhanced her notoriety.

Tabloid critics accused her of profiting from her son&#39;s death to the tune of around 600,000 dollars after she reportedly sold the last photos of her and her son together to media outlets.

Smith was also embroiled in twin legal actions -- a paternity suit from Los Angeles-based photographer Larry Birkhead who claimed Smith&#39;s daughter Dannielynn as his own, and a class action case over diet pills she endorsed.

Born in Houston, Texas, as Vickie Lynn Hogan in 1967, the young Smith once said she grew up dreaming of being latter-day Marilyn Monroe.

Like Monroe, she would eventually model for Playboy.

Like Monroe, she would be dead before she was 40.

In her teens she worked as a waitress in at a fast-food restaurant where she met and married her first husband Billy Smith in 1985 aged 17, giving birth to her son Daniel the same year.

That marriage ended in divorce two years later, and after a string of minimum wage jobs she turned to work as a stripper in Houston.

It was during this period that the course of her life was to change irrevocably, when she met and formed a friendship with billionaire oil baron J. Howard Marshall, a man 63 years her senior, in 1991.

As her relationship with Marshall developed, so too did her modeling career. In March 1992 she graced the cover of Playboy for the first time, her bottle blonde hairstyle earning comparisons with her idol Monroe, and she posed nude for the magazine -- just as Monroe had done -- two months later.

In 1993, she was named Playmate of the Year and secured a contract to model for Guess Jeans.

Then, on June 27, 1994, she married Marshall, appalling the tycoon&#39;s family who would later paint her as a gold-digger out to grab a large slice of the billionaire&#39;s fortune.

Smith insisted that she and Marshall were in love, and that they had married for companionship.

Marshall&#39;s death in August 1995 was the signal for a bitter decade-long legal battle between Smith and the mogul&#39;s family, who sought to block her from claiming any of the estate.

Smith was awarded 88 million dollars when the case went to court in 2002 but later saw that judgement reversed by the Circuit Court of Appeal in 2004. However in 2005 the Supreme Court heard Smith&#39;s appeal and ruled unanimously in May 2006 that she had the right to contest the judgement.

At the time of her death Smith was still yet to be granted her share of the fortune and the legal fight was complicated when Marshall&#39;s son, E. Pierce Marshall, died suddenly in June last year.

Smith also landed small roles in spoof movies such as &quot;Naked Gun 33 1/3&quot; and &quot;Illegal Aliens&quot; and also had a 2002 reality television series &quot;The Anna Nicole Show&quot; which was a ratings hit initially before it was cancelled in 2004.[/quote]

[quote=&quot;WashingtonPost&quot;]Anna Nicole Smith, a former Playboy playmate who became tabloid fodder when she married an elderly billionaire, collapsed in a South Florida hotel room today and died in a local hospital, police said. She was 39.

The cause of her death is under investigation, Police Chief Charlie Tiger of Seminole, Fla., told reporters this afternoon.

He said Smith&#39;s private nurse called the hotel operator at 1:38 p.m. to report that Smith had collapsed. Her bodyguard administered CPR to her several minutes later, and she was rushed to Hollywood Memorial Regional Hospital in Hollywood, Fla., Tiger said. Hospital officials informed police at 2:49 p.m. that Smith was dead, the police chief said.

He said the cause of death will be determined by the Broward County medical examiner and that police from the local crime lab are processing the scene as a precautionary measure. There was no indication yet that any crime was committed, Tiger said, adding, &quot;We&#39;re just taking all precautions at this time.&quot;

Smith checked into the Seminole Hard Rock Hotel and Casino on Monday and was staying with Howard K. Stern, her lawyer and companion. Stern was not present when she collapsed, Tiger said, and his whereabouts were not immediately known.

Tiger said it was not clear why Smith had a private nurse with her or precisely what she was doing in South Florida. He said she had previously stayed at the hotel and that he presumed she had come there again &quot;to relax.&quot;

Edwina Johnson, chief investigator for the Broward County Medical Examiner&#39;s Office, said an autopsy would be performed on Smith&#39;s body Friday, the Associated Press reported.

Her attorney, Ron Rale, told the news agency that he had talked to Smith on Tuesday or Wednesday and that she had flu symptoms and a fever and was still grieving over her death of her son last year.

&quot;Poor Anna Nicole,&quot; Rale said, according to AP. &quot;She&#39;s been the underdog. She&#39;s been besieged . . . and nobody should have to endure what she&#39;s endured.&quot;

In a statement, Hugh Hefner, the founder of Playboy magazine, said he was &quot;very saddened&quot; to learn of Smith&#39;s death. &quot;She was a dear friend who meant a great deal to the Playboy family and to me personally,&quot; he said.

Smith, born Vickie Lynn Hogan in Houston in November 1967, parlayed her resemblance to Marilyn Monroe and her bubbly personality into a tumultuous career as a topless dancer, model, actress, reality TV star, weight-loss product spokeswoman and all-purpose &quot;celebrity.&quot;

Catapulted to fame on the March 1992 cover of Playboy and by her selection as the 1993 Playmate of the Year, the buxom blonde married oil tycoon J. Howard Marshall II in 1994 when she was 26 and he was 89. She had met him three years earlier when she was performing in a Houston strip club.

After Marshall&#39;s death 14 months after their marriage, Smith became embroiled in a lengthy legal dispute with his son, E. Pierce Marshall, over her late husband&#39;s estate, valued at $1.6 billion. She was awarded $474 million by a federal court in California, a ruling that was subsequently overturned. The case ultimately wound up in the Supreme Court last year, but E. Pierce Marshall died a month later at age 67.

Tragedy struck Smith in September last year when her 20-year-old son by her first marriage, Daniel Smith, died in his mother&#39;s hospital room in the Bahamas. Smith had just given birth to a daughter, whose paternity is in dispute. Her son&#39;s death was ruled the accidental result of a combination of drugs, including methadone and two antidepressants.

After appearing in Playboy, Smith began an acting career and had roles in several movies in the 1990s. Her performances were generally panned, but her protracted legal battle over her late husband&#39;s estate, her ballooning weight and episodes of bizarre behavior kept her in the pages of supermarket tabloids.

In 2002, she appeared in her own reality TV series, &quot;The Anna Nicole Show&quot; on the E! Entertainment Television cable channel. The show, which featured Smith, her entourage and her miniature poodle and focused on her struggles with her weight and her precarious financial situation, lasted until 2004, when it was canceled.

Then came a strange appearance in November 2004 at the American Music Awards, where a slimmed-down Smith slurred her speech introducing a musical act and referred to the weight-loss product TrimSpa, which was employing her as a spokeswoman. Although she had reportedly lost nearly 70 pounds and had regained her voluptuous figure, the episode fueled speculation that she was on drugs, which her representatives denied.

Smith announced in June 2006 that she was pregnant, and she gave birth to a daughter, Dannielynn Hope Marshall Stern, in September in the Bahamas. She said the father was Stern, her longtime attorney, but a former boyfriend, photographer Larry Birkhead, asserted that he had fathered the girl, and he filed a lawsuit to press his claim.

Smith&#39;s son Daniel died three days after the birth while visiting his mother and his newborn sister at Doctors Hospital in Nassau. Later that month, Smith and Stern exchanged vows aboard a catamaran off the coast of the Bahamas. Although a Baptist minister was reportedly present, no formal marriage certificate was issued, and another lawyer for Smith told reporters that the union was not legally binding.[/quote]

Kind of odd how she just died...

~Leader

P.S. I posted in the wrong section, sorry.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 10 Feb 2007 07:34:14 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>General Discussion</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/anna-nicole-smith-died/56389.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Anna Nicole Smith Died</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Cabby Cabby]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/cabby">@Cabby</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Ok, Why Reply if you dont even know who this girl is?<br>
Well, Clearly it must be spam…<br>
And If you read other peoples posts in this thread, You’ll see some information about her… <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=6" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/anna-nicole-smith-died/56389/25">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/anna-nicole-smith-died/56389/25</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 10 Feb 2007 07:34:14 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-56389-25</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/anna-nicole-smith-died/56389.rss">Anna Nicole Smith Died</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Anna Nicole Smith Died</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Cabby Cabby]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/cabby">@Cabby</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I Agree, I don’t think that she died from choking on vomit.<br>
But I dont know, She may have ;(</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/anna-nicole-smith-died/56389/24">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/anna-nicole-smith-died/56389/24</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 10 Feb 2007 07:25:44 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-56389-24</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/anna-nicole-smith-died/56389.rss">Anna Nicole Smith Died</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Anna Nicole Smith Died</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Fuzzycracker Fuzzycracker]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/fuzzycracker">@Fuzzycracker</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I read this yesterday on the news, that’s an odd death if you ask me.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/anna-nicole-smith-died/56389/23">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/anna-nicole-smith-died/56389/23</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 10 Feb 2007 00:57:21 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-56389-23</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/anna-nicole-smith-died/56389.rss">Anna Nicole Smith Died</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Anna Nicole Smith Died</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@ownagesbot ownagesbot]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/ownagesbot">@ownagesbot</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>No one deserves to die, I guess there are exceptions like mass murderers, but really, no one deserves to die, especially not early, atleast show a lil respect.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/anna-nicole-smith-died/56389/22">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/anna-nicole-smith-died/56389/22</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 10 Feb 2007 00:17:40 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-56389-22</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/anna-nicole-smith-died/56389.rss">Anna Nicole Smith Died</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Anna Nicole Smith Died</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@system system]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/system">@system</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <blockquote>And in an explosive new claim, Access Hollywood is citing what it is calling a credible source, and has a report that claims an employee of Anna Nicole Smith found her in her room in the Hard Rock Hotel and Casino in Hollywood, Florida. The employee pulled back a sheet and discovered that she appeared to have choked on her own vomit.</blockquote> 
<blockquote>A report from the syndicated entertainment news show also cites the same source that makes the claim that Smith took what was referred to as a "children's sedative," and had "kept passing out" before her death.</blockquote>
<p>btw nice usefull post bebe</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/anna-nicole-smith-died/56389/21">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/anna-nicole-smith-died/56389/21</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Feb 2007 19:47:31 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-56389-21</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/anna-nicole-smith-died/56389.rss">Anna Nicole Smith Died</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Anna Nicole Smith Died</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@silabsoft RuneAgent]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/silabsoft">@silabsoft</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>i wonder if she was surprised her husband died.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/anna-nicole-smith-died/56389/20">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/anna-nicole-smith-died/56389/20</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Feb 2007 19:44:46 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-56389-20</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/anna-nicole-smith-died/56389.rss">Anna Nicole Smith Died</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Anna Nicole Smith Died</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Bebemycat2 Bebe]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/bebemycat2">@Bebemycat2</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“moparisthebest, post:2, topic:56389”]She probably overdosed on drugs.</p>
<p>People die every day, she wasn’t anything special.[/quote]</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/anna-nicole-smith-died/56389/19">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/anna-nicole-smith-died/56389/19</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Feb 2007 19:39:44 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-56389-19</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/anna-nicole-smith-died/56389.rss">Anna Nicole Smith Died</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Anna Nicole Smith Died</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@93dcthugs93 93dcthugs93]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/93dcthugs93">@93dcthugs93</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Yes I saw this on the news this morning, it was quite shocking. She was on the news yesterday live talking about the death of her son &amp; such, I cba to read all that but I think she died of a drug overdose.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/anna-nicole-smith-died/56389/18">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/anna-nicole-smith-died/56389/18</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Feb 2007 19:36:32 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-56389-18</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/anna-nicole-smith-died/56389.rss">Anna Nicole Smith Died</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Anna Nicole Smith Died</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@system system]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/system">@system</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“moparisthebest, post:2, topic:56389”]She probably overdosed on drugs.</p>
<p>People die every day, she wasn’t anything special.[/quote]</p>
<p>she did was on the news.</p>
<p>whore deserved it.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/anna-nicole-smith-died/56389/17">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/anna-nicole-smith-died/56389/17</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Feb 2007 18:38:04 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-56389-17</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/anna-nicole-smith-died/56389.rss">Anna Nicole Smith Died</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Anna Nicole Smith Died</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Portal Portal]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/portal">@Portal</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Its about time we have one less dumb blonde in the freaking news…although even when shes dead she will be on for some while.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/anna-nicole-smith-died/56389/16">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/anna-nicole-smith-died/56389/16</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Feb 2007 18:32:39 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-56389-16</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/anna-nicole-smith-died/56389.rss">Anna Nicole Smith Died</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Anna Nicole Smith Died</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Bang_Train Bang Train]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/bang_train">@Bang_Train</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“XxKanexX, post:13, topic:56389”][quote author=jme_009 link=topic=80197.msg879903#msg879903 date=1171012917]<br>
That is really strange. I just watched the other night about some guy claiming to own her daughter, and I’ve seen her a lot recently on “entertainment tonight.” They even video tapped her giving birth just a few weeks ago. Of course, they didn’t show it all (Thankfully, tbh) <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/wink.png?v=6" title=":wink:" class="emoji" alt=":wink:"></p>
<p>[quote=PETA]PETA released the following statement: She was a great friend to animals and used every opportunity to speak out against senseless cruelty. We always thought Anna Nicole was a perfect fit for PETA because, just like us, she not only hated cruelty to animals and loved her dogs but also couldn’t be ignored, and no matter what people thought of her, they always had an opinion, one way or another. … It is a tragedy when anyone passes away before their time, but with Anna Nicole, animals have lost a true hero and PETA has lost a good friend. We will miss her.<br>
[/quote]<br>
Hehe, I’m sure Smith has worn her fair share of fur coats.</p>
<p>I have a funny feeling it was suicide. She had a lot of crap about to happen, and I could tell she was lying in her interviews.</p>
<p>[/quote]<br>
Same! I got home yesterday and turned a random channel on, and it was E! So i watched it about that guy who yeh, said it was his son… And then the story about her son and how he died, ect, came on.</p>
<p>I didn’t know who she was when people told me today.[/quote]</p>
<p>I am ashamed to say the PETA HQs is in norfolk, VA.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/anna-nicole-smith-died/56389/15">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/anna-nicole-smith-died/56389/15</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Feb 2007 18:01:23 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-56389-15</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/anna-nicole-smith-died/56389.rss">Anna Nicole Smith Died</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Anna Nicole Smith Died</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@azn_pker1 azn pker1]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/azn_pker1">@azn_pker1</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Dude that was kind of perverting, but still</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/anna-nicole-smith-died/56389/14">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/anna-nicole-smith-died/56389/14</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Feb 2007 15:56:43 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-56389-14</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/anna-nicole-smith-died/56389.rss">Anna Nicole Smith Died</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Anna Nicole Smith Died</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@XxKanexX Kane.]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/xxkanexx">@XxKanexX</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“jme_009, post:10, topic:56389”]That is really strange. I just watched the other night about some guy claiming to own her daughter, and I’ve seen her a lot recently on “entertainment tonight.” They even video tapped her giving birth just a few weeks ago. Of course, they didn’t show it all (Thankfully, tbh) <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/wink.png?v=6" title=":wink:" class="emoji" alt=":wink:"></p>
<p>[quote=PETA]PETA released the following statement: She was a great friend to animals and used every opportunity to speak out against senseless cruelty. We always thought Anna Nicole was a perfect fit for PETA because, just like us, she not only hated cruelty to animals and loved her dogs but also couldn’t be ignored, and no matter what people thought of her, they always had an opinion, one way or another. … It is a tragedy when anyone passes away before their time, but with Anna Nicole, animals have lost a true hero and PETA has lost a good friend. We will miss her.<br>
[/quote]<br>
Hehe, I’m sure Smith has worn her fair share of fur coats.</p>
<p>I have a funny feeling it was suicide. She had a lot of crap about to happen, and I could tell she was lying in her interviews.[/quote]<br>
Same! I got home yesterday and turned a random channel on, and it was E! So i watched it about that guy who yeh, said it was his son… And then the story about her son and how he died, ect, came on.</p>
<p>I didn’t know who she was when people told me today.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/anna-nicole-smith-died/56389/13">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/anna-nicole-smith-died/56389/13</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Feb 2007 14:19:10 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-56389-13</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/anna-nicole-smith-died/56389.rss">Anna Nicole Smith Died</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Anna Nicole Smith Died</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@davidude36 Brolapse]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/davidude36">@davidude36</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote no-group quote-modified" data-post="11" data-topic="56389">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/usernamelol/40/5_6259e4fa9dfe0dec282fb0955bb1974c.png" class="avatar"> usernamelol:</div>
<blockquote>
<p><img src="http://www.intomyhealth.com/trimspa/anna-nicole-weight-loss.jpg" alt></p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>as you can see here, the tumor on her head was growing at rapid speeds.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/anna-nicole-smith-died/56389/12">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/anna-nicole-smith-died/56389/12</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Feb 2007 12:53:38 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-56389-12</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/anna-nicole-smith-died/56389.rss">Anna Nicole Smith Died</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Anna Nicole Smith Died</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@usernamelol .Fusion]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/usernamelol">@usernamelol</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p><img src="http://www.intomyhealth.com/trimspa/anna-nicole-weight-loss.jpg" alt width="" height=""></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/anna-nicole-smith-died/56389/11">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/anna-nicole-smith-died/56389/11</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Feb 2007 10:24:57 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-56389-11</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/anna-nicole-smith-died/56389.rss">Anna Nicole Smith Died</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Anna Nicole Smith Died</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@jme jme]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/jme">@jme</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>That is really strange. I just watched the other night about some guy claiming to own her daughter, and I’ve seen her a lot recently on “entertainment tonight.” They even video tapped her giving birth just a few weeks ago. Of course, they didn’t show it all (Thankfully, tbh) <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/wink.png?v=6" title=":wink:" class="emoji" alt=":wink:"></p>
<blockquote>PETA released the following statement: She was a great friend to animals and used every opportunity to speak out against senseless cruelty. We always thought Anna Nicole was a perfect fit for PETA because, just like us, she not only hated cruelty to animals and loved her dogs but also couldn't be ignored, and no matter what people thought of her, they always had an opinion, one way or another. ... It is a tragedy when anyone passes away before their time, but with Anna Nicole, animals have lost a true hero and PETA has lost a good friend. We will miss her.</blockquote>
Hehe, I'm sure Smith has worn her fair share of fur coats.
<p>I have a funny feeling it was suicide. She had a lot of crap about to happen, and I could tell she was lying in her interviews.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/anna-nicole-smith-died/56389/10">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/anna-nicole-smith-died/56389/10</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Feb 2007 09:21:57 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-56389-10</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/anna-nicole-smith-died/56389.rss">Anna Nicole Smith Died</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Anna Nicole Smith Died</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@bobby Bobby]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/bobby">@bobby</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>that to…</p>
<p>ps: thatw as when I was born</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/anna-nicole-smith-died/56389/9">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/anna-nicole-smith-died/56389/9</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Feb 2007 09:14:56 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-56389-9</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/anna-nicole-smith-died/56389.rss">Anna Nicole Smith Died</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Anna Nicole Smith Died</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@frank frank_]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/frank">@frank</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <blockquote>The unlikely couple married in 1994, when she was 26 and he was 89</blockquote>lel
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/anna-nicole-smith-died/56389/8">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/anna-nicole-smith-died/56389/8</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Feb 2007 09:14:05 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-56389-8</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/anna-nicole-smith-died/56389.rss">Anna Nicole Smith Died</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Anna Nicole Smith Died</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@bobby Bobby]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/bobby">@bobby</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I no but  I had to post since it was ana anna nicole smith topic. i mean comon he was like 60 or something.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/anna-nicole-smith-died/56389/7">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/anna-nicole-smith-died/56389/7</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Feb 2007 09:11:35 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-56389-7</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/anna-nicole-smith-died/56389.rss">Anna Nicole Smith Died</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Anna Nicole Smith Died</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@frank frank_]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/frank">@frank</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“bobby, post:5, topic:56389”]All I can say is GOLD DIGGER</p>
<p>that reminds me in hostory class my teacher hinted that muhammed ( the starter guy of Islam) was a gold digger, since he maried someone who was rich and 20 years older.[/quote]oooooh ur gunna get bashed</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/anna-nicole-smith-died/56389/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/anna-nicole-smith-died/56389/6</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Feb 2007 09:09:12 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-56389-6</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/anna-nicole-smith-died/56389.rss">Anna Nicole Smith Died</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Anna Nicole Smith Died</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@bobby Bobby]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/bobby">@bobby</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>All I can say is GOLD DIGGER</p>
<p>that reminds me in hostory class my teacher hinted that muhammed ( the starter guy of Islam) was a gold digger, since he maried someone who was rich and 20 years older.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/anna-nicole-smith-died/56389/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/anna-nicole-smith-died/56389/5</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Feb 2007 09:06:37 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-56389-5</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/anna-nicole-smith-died/56389.rss">Anna Nicole Smith Died</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Anna Nicole Smith Died</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@frank frank_]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/frank">@frank</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“moparisthebest, post:2, topic:56389”]She probably overdosed on drugs.</p>
<p>People die every day, she wasn’t anything special.[/quote]QFT</p>
<p>[quote=“leader, post:3, topic:56389”]She tried to get rich an easy and fast way…didn’t work too well for her, did it?[/quote]it did until she died</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/anna-nicole-smith-died/56389/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/anna-nicole-smith-died/56389/4</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Feb 2007 09:06:10 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-56389-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/anna-nicole-smith-died/56389.rss">Anna Nicole Smith Died</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Anna Nicole Smith Died</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@leader leader]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/leader">@leader</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote no-group quote-modified" data-post="2" data-topic="56389">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/user_avatar/forum.moparisthebest.com/moparisthebest/40/30_2.png" class="avatar"> moparisthebest:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>People die every day, she wasn’t anything special.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>That’s right. She tried to get rich an easy and fast way…didn’t work too well for her, did it?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/anna-nicole-smith-died/56389/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/anna-nicole-smith-died/56389/3</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Feb 2007 09:03:35 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-56389-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/anna-nicole-smith-died/56389.rss">Anna Nicole Smith Died</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Anna Nicole Smith Died</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@moparisthebest Moparisthebest]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/moparisthebest">@moparisthebest</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>She probably overdosed on drugs.</p>
<p>People die every day, she wasn’t anything special.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/anna-nicole-smith-died/56389/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/anna-nicole-smith-died/56389/2</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Feb 2007 09:01:50 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-56389-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/anna-nicole-smith-died/56389.rss">Anna Nicole Smith Died</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Anna Nicole Smith Died</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@leader leader]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/leader">@leader</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“Yahoo”]LOS ANGELES (AFP) -<br>
Anna Nicole Smith will be remembered as the stripper who married an aged oil billionaire and became a pop-culture icon before her life collapsed under the weight of tragedy and legal woes.<br>
ADVERTISEMENT</p>
<p>The former Playboy model was once seen as one of the world’s most desirable women and appeared on the road to supermodel status when she replaced Claudia Schiffer as Guess Jeans model in the early 1990s.</p>
<p>But the platinum-blonde facade crumbled over the course of the next decade as her life unraveled in the full glare of a voracious US tabloid media.</p>
<p>The mysterious sudden death of Smith’s son Daniel in the Bahamas just days after the birth of her daughter last September, and her “commitment ceremony” days later with lawyer Howard K. Stern enhanced her notoriety.</p>
<p>Tabloid critics accused her of profiting from her son’s death to the tune of around 600,000 dollars after she reportedly sold the last photos of her and her son together to media outlets.</p>
<p>Smith was also embroiled in twin legal actions – a paternity suit from Los Angeles-based photographer Larry Birkhead who claimed Smith’s daughter Dannielynn as his own, and a class action case over diet pills she endorsed.</p>
<p>Born in Houston, Texas, as Vickie Lynn Hogan in 1967, the young Smith once said she grew up dreaming of being latter-day Marilyn Monroe.</p>
<p>Like Monroe, she would eventually model for Playboy.</p>
<p>Like Monroe, she would be dead before she was 40.</p>
<p>In her teens she worked as a waitress in at a fast-food restaurant where she met and married her first husband Billy Smith in 1985 aged 17, giving birth to her son Daniel the same year.</p>
<p>That marriage ended in divorce two years later, and after a string of minimum wage jobs she turned to work as a stripper in Houston.</p>
<p>It was during this period that the course of her life was to change irrevocably, when she met and formed a friendship with billionaire oil baron J. Howard Marshall, a man 63 years her senior, in 1991.</p>
<p>As her relationship with Marshall developed, so too did her modeling career. In March 1992 she graced the cover of Playboy for the first time, her bottle blonde hairstyle earning comparisons with her idol Monroe, and she posed nude for the magazine – just as Monroe had done – two months later.</p>
<p>In 1993, she was named Playmate of the Year and secured a contract to model for Guess Jeans.</p>
<p>Then, on June 27, 1994, she married Marshall, appalling the tycoon’s family who would later paint her as a gold-digger out to grab a large slice of the billionaire’s fortune.</p>
<p>Smith insisted that she and Marshall were in love, and that they had married for companionship.</p>
<p>Marshall’s death in August 1995 was the signal for a bitter decade-long legal battle between Smith and the mogul’s family, who sought to block her from claiming any of the estate.</p>
<p>Smith was awarded 88 million dollars when the case went to court in 2002 but later saw that judgement reversed by the Circuit Court of Appeal in 2004. However in 2005 the Supreme Court heard Smith’s appeal and ruled unanimously in May 2006 that she had the right to contest the judgement.</p>
<p>At the time of her death Smith was still yet to be granted her share of the fortune and the legal fight was complicated when Marshall’s son, E. Pierce Marshall, died suddenly in June last year.</p>
<p>Smith also landed small roles in spoof movies such as “Naked Gun 33 1/3” and “Illegal Aliens” and also had a 2002 reality television series “The Anna Nicole Show” which was a ratings hit initially before it was cancelled in 2004.[/quote]</p>
<p>[quote=“WashingtonPost”]Anna Nicole Smith, a former Playboy playmate who became tabloid fodder when she married an elderly billionaire, collapsed in a South Florida hotel room today and died in a local hospital, police said. She was 39.</p>
<p>The cause of her death is under investigation, Police Chief Charlie Tiger of Seminole, Fla., told reporters this afternoon.</p>
<p>He said Smith’s private nurse called the hotel operator at 1:38 p.m. to report that Smith had collapsed. Her bodyguard administered CPR to her several minutes later, and she was rushed to Hollywood Memorial Regional Hospital in Hollywood, Fla., Tiger said. Hospital officials informed police at 2:49 p.m. that Smith was dead, the police chief said.</p>
<p>He said the cause of death will be determined by the Broward County medical examiner and that police from the local crime lab are processing the scene as a precautionary measure. There was no indication yet that any crime was committed, Tiger said, adding, “We’re just taking all precautions at this time.”</p>
<p>Smith checked into the Seminole Hard Rock Hotel and Casino on Monday and was staying with Howard K. Stern, her lawyer and companion. Stern was not present when she collapsed, Tiger said, and his whereabouts were not immediately known.</p>
<p>Tiger said it was not clear why Smith had a private nurse with her or precisely what she was doing in South Florida. He said she had previously stayed at the hotel and that he presumed she had come there again “to relax.”</p>
<p>Edwina Johnson, chief investigator for the Broward County Medical Examiner’s Office, said an autopsy would be performed on Smith’s body Friday, the Associated Press reported.</p>
<p>Her attorney, Ron Rale, told the news agency that he had talked to Smith on Tuesday or Wednesday and that she had flu symptoms and a fever and was still grieving over her death of her son last year.</p>
<p>“Poor Anna Nicole,” Rale said, according to AP. “She’s been the underdog. She’s been besieged . . . and nobody should have to endure what she’s endured.”</p>
<p>In a statement, Hugh Hefner, the founder of Playboy magazine, said he was “very saddened” to learn of Smith’s death. “She was a dear friend who meant a great deal to the Playboy family and to me personally,” he said.</p>
<p>Smith, born Vickie Lynn Hogan in Houston in November 1967, parlayed her resemblance to Marilyn Monroe and her bubbly personality into a tumultuous career as a topless dancer, model, actress, reality TV star, weight-loss product spokeswoman and all-purpose “celebrity.”</p>
<p>Catapulted to fame on the March 1992 cover of Playboy and by her selection as the 1993 Playmate of the Year, the buxom blonde married oil tycoon J. Howard Marshall II in 1994 when she was 26 and he was 89. She had met him three years earlier when she was performing in a Houston strip club.</p>
<p>After Marshall’s death 14 months after their marriage, Smith became embroiled in a lengthy legal dispute with his son, E. Pierce Marshall, over her late husband’s estate, valued at $1.6 billion. She was awarded $474 million by a federal court in California, a ruling that was subsequently overturned. The case ultimately wound up in the Supreme Court last year, but E. Pierce Marshall died a month later at age 67.</p>
<p>Tragedy struck Smith in September last year when her 20-year-old son by her first marriage, Daniel Smith, died in his mother’s hospital room in the Bahamas. Smith had just given birth to a daughter, whose paternity is in dispute. Her son’s death was ruled the accidental result of a combination of drugs, including methadone and two antidepressants.</p>
<p>After appearing in Playboy, Smith began an acting career and had roles in several movies in the 1990s. Her performances were generally panned, but her protracted legal battle over her late husband’s estate, her ballooning weight and episodes of bizarre behavior kept her in the pages of supermarket tabloids.</p>
<p>In 2002, she appeared in her own reality TV series, “The Anna Nicole Show” on the E! Entertainment Television cable channel. The show, which featured Smith, her entourage and her miniature poodle and focused on her struggles with her weight and her precarious financial situation, lasted until 2004, when it was canceled.</p>
<p>Then came a strange appearance in November 2004 at the American Music Awards, where a slimmed-down Smith slurred her speech introducing a musical act and referred to the weight-loss product TrimSpa, which was employing her as a spokeswoman. Although she had reportedly lost nearly 70 pounds and had regained her voluptuous figure, the episode fueled speculation that she was on drugs, which her representatives denied.</p>
<p>Smith announced in June 2006 that she was pregnant, and she gave birth to a daughter, Dannielynn Hope Marshall Stern, in September in the Bahamas. She said the father was Stern, her longtime attorney, but a former boyfriend, photographer Larry Birkhead, asserted that he had fathered the girl, and he filed a lawsuit to press his claim.</p>
<p>Smith’s son Daniel died three days after the birth while visiting his mother and his newborn sister at Doctors Hospital in Nassau. Later that month, Smith and Stern exchanged vows aboard a catamaran off the coast of the Bahamas. Although a Baptist minister was reportedly present, no formal marriage certificate was issued, and another lawyer for Smith told reporters that the union was not legally binding.[/quote]</p>
<p>Kind of odd how she just died…</p>
<p>~Leader</p>
<p>P.S. I posted in the wrong section, sorry.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/anna-nicole-smith-died/56389/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/anna-nicole-smith-died/56389/1</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Feb 2007 08:59:24 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-56389-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/anna-nicole-smith-died/56389.rss">Anna Nicole Smith Died</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
