<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Fallout General</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/fallout-general/455230</link>
    <description>I&#39;ve started to do another playthough of Fallout and Fallout 2. Just thought I&#39;d start a general thread so everyone can talk about the series. Oh and also, if you&#39;ve never bothered to play the original 2 games. They&#39;re on sale for 2.99$ each I believe.

Couple tips:
Always, always have Intelligence 9. Why? It gives more points when you level up. If you&#39;d like you can always upgrade. (Fallout 1 with the Brotherhood of Steel.) (Fallout 2 via ACE once you get to the point where he can preform surgery upon you.) (Fallout 3 via the bobblehead) and finally (New Vegas via implants.)
Look up character builds. If you plan on being a melee guy/gal, find out what will work best for you.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 21 Aug 2012 02:55:01 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Games</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/fallout-general/455230.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Fallout General</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Stupit Stu]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/stupit">@Stupit</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I’ve started to do another playthough of Fallout and Fallout 2. Just thought I’d start a general thread so everyone can talk about the series. Oh and also, if you’ve never bothered to play the original 2 games. They’re on sale for 2.99$ each I believe.</p>
<p>Couple tips:<br>
Always, always have Intelligence 9. Why? It gives more points when you level up. If you’d like you can always upgrade. (Fallout 1 with the Brotherhood of Steel.) (Fallout 2 via ACE once you get to the point where he can preform surgery upon you.) (Fallout 3 via the bobblehead) and finally (New Vegas via implants.)<br>
Look up character builds. If you plan on being a melee guy/gal, find out what will work best for you.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/fallout-general/455230/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/fallout-general/455230/1</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 21 Aug 2012 02:55:01 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-455230-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/fallout-general/455230.rss">Fallout General</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
