<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>[517]Barrows Chest[508/525]</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/517-barrows-chest-508-525/344988</link>
    <description>Hey, I have My Server&#39;s Barrows System Coded about 90% Theres only like 2 things i have to Do but the other thing i can do with ease. lol XD
(Btw Base: Codeusa Deob 517 A.K.A 508 Loading 525 Cache)

What i need to do is Make it so The Barrows Chest rewards a Random reward (runes, bolt racks, barrows item Just 1 barrows item) and after the reward is received it teleports you to the top of Ahrim&#39;s Hill.

Any help would be Very appreciated and whoever can give me the correct way to code this will get partial credit in my server XD I&#39;ve tried to use tutorials but all of the barrows chest&#39;s have failed for some reason i get no error&#39;s but nothing happens no reward no animation no message. Please help XD Thank You.

Kind Reguards, 
               ~~~~MusicMasta~~~~</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 20 Jun 2010 03:21:41 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/517-barrows-chest-508-525/344988.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>[517]Barrows Chest[508/525]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@musicmasta musicmasta]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/musicmasta">@musicmasta</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Hey, I have My Server’s Barrows System Coded about 90% Theres only like 2 things i have to Do but the other thing i can do with ease. lol XD<br>
(Btw Base: Codeusa Deob 517 A.K.A 508 Loading 525 Cache)</p>
<p>What i need to do is Make it so The Barrows Chest rewards a Random reward (runes, bolt racks, barrows item Just 1 barrows item) and after the reward is received it teleports you to the top of Ahrim’s Hill.</p>
<p>Any help would be Very appreciated and whoever can give me the correct way to code this will get partial credit in my server XD I’ve tried to use tutorials but all of the barrows chest’s have failed for some reason i get no error’s but nothing happens no reward no animation no message. Please help XD Thank You.</p>
<p>Kind Reguards,<br>
<s><s>MusicMasta</s></s></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/517-barrows-chest-508-525/344988/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/517-barrows-chest-508-525/344988/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 20 Jun 2010 03:21:41 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-344988-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/517-barrows-chest-508-525/344988.rss">[517]Barrows Chest[508/525]</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
