<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>PK servers have gone downhill</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/pk-servers-have-gone-downhill/346485</link>
    <description>Recently I decided to come back to Runescape (the real game) out of boredness.. and that means AFK training. I like to play RSPS while I afk train because it passes time by really fast. That is what I did with my main back in 2006 (while afking @ bandits). I was afk training and at the same thing playing a PK server.

Today I decided to try this again.. and I started downloading &quot;PK servers&quot;. I was hoping PK servers have gotten better but to my surprise, nope. You have to spend some hours training, a couple more hours getting money &amp; the gear, and finally PK. By the time you are ready to PK, it is hard to find anyone because the areas are not &quot;concentrated&quot;. Too spread out. It really feels like a desert.

Back in 2006 this was very different. You logged in at West Varrock Bank with a 200m cash pile and other &quot;starter items&quot;. There were always 20 players in this area alone - as it was the &quot;PK place&quot;. You were lucky if you could make it over to the dummies and if you did - great! Begin to train =]. Once you had your desired stats (within 10-15 minutes!) you would head over to the bank and begin mass spawning the items you would need, and then bank them. Now you would head out and begin owning people! Make teams, kill teams, be a soloer, ect. If you had a great pure and the correct gear, you could rape but if your pure sucked and/or incorrect gear you would be the one getting raped.

I remember running in from the north and blitzing teams of people, then barraging, and ranging them at the same time.. killed them so fast they didn&#39;t realize who or what it was that killed them. Man I made killer pures xD...

PK servers back in 2006 were so simple yet so fun.. now it&#39;s too boring. There may be 20 people connected in nowadays PK servers, but they are spread throughout the whole map.. instead of EVERYONE being in one small place.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 29 Jun 2010 20:40:06 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>General Discussion</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/pk-servers-have-gone-downhill/346485.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>PK servers have gone downhill</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@noobs_are_ftw noobs are ftw]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/noobs_are_ftw">@noobs_are_ftw</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>well too fucking bad that ur lazy now we like economies if u dont like it make ur own server</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/pk-servers-have-gone-downhill/346485/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/pk-servers-have-gone-downhill/346485/3</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jun 2010 20:40:06 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-346485-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/pk-servers-have-gone-downhill/346485.rss">PK servers have gone downhill</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>PK servers have gone downhill</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@ziplock ziplock]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/ziplock">@ziplock</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Make your own just how you would like it? These are open source projects…</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/pk-servers-have-gone-downhill/346485/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/pk-servers-have-gone-downhill/346485/2</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jun 2010 20:39:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-346485-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/pk-servers-have-gone-downhill/346485.rss">PK servers have gone downhill</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>PK servers have gone downhill</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Rare_z Rare z]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/rare_z">@Rare_z</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Recently I decided to come back to Runescape (the real game) out of boredness… and that means AFK training. I like to play RSPS while I afk train because it passes time by really fast. That is what I did with my main back in 2006 (while afking @ bandits). I was afk training and at the same thing playing a PK server.</p>
<p>Today I decided to try this again… and I started downloading “PK servers”. I was hoping PK servers have gotten better but to my surprise, nope. You have to spend some hours training, a couple more hours getting money &amp; the gear, and finally PK. By the time you are ready to PK, it is hard to find anyone because the areas are not “concentrated”. Too spread out. It really feels like a desert.</p>
<p>Back in 2006 this was very different. You logged in at West Varrock Bank with a 200m cash pile and other “starter items”. There were always 20 players in this area alone - as it was the “PK place”. You were lucky if you could make it over to the dummies and if you did - great! Begin to train =]. Once you had your desired stats (within 10-15 minutes!) you would head over to the bank and begin mass spawning the items you would need, and then bank them. Now you would head out and begin owning people! Make teams, kill teams, be a soloer, ect. If you had a great pure and the correct gear, you could rape but if your pure sucked and/or incorrect gear you would be the one getting raped.</p>
<p>I remember running in from the north and blitzing teams of people, then barraging, and ranging them at the same time… killed them so fast they didn’t realize who or what it was that killed them. Man I made killer pures xD…</p>
<p>PK servers back in 2006 were so simple yet so fun… now it’s too boring. There may be 20 people connected in nowadays PK servers, but they are spread throughout the whole map… instead of EVERYONE being in one small place.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/pk-servers-have-gone-downhill/346485/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/pk-servers-have-gone-downhill/346485/1</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jun 2010 20:35:46 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-346485-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/pk-servers-have-gone-downhill/346485.rss">PK servers have gone downhill</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
