<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>A Guide to Creating Appealing Graphics</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/a-guide-to-creating-appealing-graphics/430523</link>
    <description>I&#39;m sure there&#39;s a million articles on the web for this sorta thing, but I find myself wanting to say the same thing to many of the games on this forum. So, without further ado, here&#39;s a little guide to creating not necessarily good graphics but blending graphics - meaning they can all look like garbage but still have a style that fits and doesn&#39;t suck too much.

First off, I wanna take a moment to look at old games. All these pictures are ones I found from searching Google Images, mainly because I don&#39;t want to re-invent the wheel by taking screenshots of things that have already been captured. Why do this? Because successful commercial games had blending graphics dated back to the NES. Take a look at some of these games:

[img]http://freexbresse.free.fr/mmf/megaman1/castle1/m1c1p01.gif[/img]

[img]http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/310316-castlevania-nes-screenshot-oh-my-god-what-a-despicable-monstrosity.png[/img]

[img]http://www.emuparadise.me/fup/up/67754-Megaman_Xtreme_2_%28USA,_Europe%29-4.png[/img]

I could create a big list, but I think I can make my point here. Graphics artists way back in the day had very few colors to work with - 32 on the background for the GBC, and even less on the NES, yet look at how everything follows the same style. What&#39;s the main key to this? Palettes. By sticking to a palette, you&#39;re much better off creating graphics that blend. With modern-day technology, color bitness isn&#39;t an issue, meaning there isn&#39;t a limit to what colors we can choose to create images. This in my opinion is the biggest cause for unappealing GUIs, sprites, and backgrounds.

Check out a sprite I made a while back for the main character from Dark Cloud. Notice how I used a palette and consistent shading.

[img]http://img408.imageshack.us/img408/5381/toan.png[/img]

The only thing I must point out that is wrong about this image is I simply mirrored the side view of the character, which created improper shading. Anyway though, I want you to take a close look at the palettes. For each general color (orange, green, etc...), there are only 3 colors and they all have nearly-identical saturation (Saturation is basically the strength of the color). And the shades don&#39;t differentiate greatly either - They really only go down in luminance about 40... uhm... units... This is generally the idea to stick to when creating palettes - find an appealing saturation that fits for your graphic and create a few shades of each color. Here&#39;s the palette the GBA game Dragonball Z Buu&#39;s Fury uses throughout the [b]entire[/b] game for backgrounds (top-left):

[img]http://img842.imageshack.us/img842/6148/dbzbuusfurymultiple.png[/img]

As you can see, it follows the same principle I explained and the graphics look fantastic. Now I&#39;d like to turn your attention to the Megaman Xtreme screenshot (the 3rd image). Look at X in his... whatever you wanna call it. Know how many colors are there? 4. Yep, only 4. And you can tell what everything is, and it looks great. Wanna know how many colors the Gameboy had to use? 4 Again, and not even real colors. Just white, black, and 2 shades of gray. Graphics looked great then too. Take a look at Zelda Link&#39;s Awakening:

[img]http://www.consoleclassix.com/info_img/Legend_of_Zelda_Links_Awakening_GBC_ScreenShot3.gif[/img]

Personally, I couldn&#39;t make graphics nearly as appealing with all the colors in the world. The game artists created a style and stuck with it. This is important with any game - whether it&#39;s 2D or 3D, a fighter or a shooter, the goal is always the same. I know this seems ironic, but look at Minecraft. The graphics all blend and are appealing because Notch created a style (with a form of a palette of course) and stuck with it. Notice how most HD texture packs ruin the game&#39;s look and feel (another important aspect) because high-res professional graphics are being thrown into a world with the most basic possible terrain and models. They don&#39;t fit together. Hopefully you can see what I&#39;m talking about.

I don&#39;t mean to be cocky, but I want to show you an example of how using very basic graphics and a very limited palette can look nice in a modern game. Pay attention to how many colors the window has (excluding the font).

[img]http://img855.imageshack.us/img855/6134/datastuff.png[/img]

There are exactly two colors for each section. The frame consists of two colors, and then 4 for each button - 2 when the mouse isn&#39;t hovering on it and 2 for when it is. So there&#39;s a grand total of 6 colors on the GUI for a 3D game that uses pixel shaders. Oh, actually, there&#39;s more because of the close button, but I&#39;m sure if you&#39;ve read up to this point you can understand why I chose the colors I did.

Now, I know it may seem like a lot to keep in mind, but your games will turn out so much nicer if you follow this guide (I think anyway. Maybe I&#39;m totally wrong and have no idea what I&#39;m talking about). The things to keep in mind are the style, the blending, and the look and feel. Now, go make your game not use a Windows scrollbar on your custom chatbox with an unfitting background.

~Lin</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 10 Apr 2012 00:42:45 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Game Development</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/a-guide-to-creating-appealing-graphics/430523.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>A Guide to Creating Appealing Graphics</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@imsuperman05 imsuperman05]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/imsuperman05">@imsuperman05</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Thank you for this, I will keep this in mind if I ever decide to create something where graphics will be a main feature.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/a-guide-to-creating-appealing-graphics/430523/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/a-guide-to-creating-appealing-graphics/430523/4</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 10 Apr 2012 00:42:45 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-430523-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/a-guide-to-creating-appealing-graphics/430523.rss">A Guide to Creating Appealing Graphics</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>A Guide to Creating Appealing Graphics</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@JaydenD12 JaydenD12]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/jaydend12">@JaydenD12</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Thanks for that; I’ll keep it in mind if I decide to create a game at some point in my life.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/a-guide-to-creating-appealing-graphics/430523/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/a-guide-to-creating-appealing-graphics/430523/3</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jan 2012 04:34:12 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-430523-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/a-guide-to-creating-appealing-graphics/430523.rss">A Guide to Creating Appealing Graphics</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>A Guide to Creating Appealing Graphics</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Frell Frell]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/frell">@Frell</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Great point you bring up lin.</p>
<p>I can’t stress enough how important a working color palette is so your design is actually pleasing to the eye and readable. You cannot just say grass is green dirt is brown and the sky is blue, you get a bunch of ugly contrasting colors and the game does not feel complete.</p>
<p>Here is a really cool site you can load a picture with a mood you want and sample colors from: <a href="http://kuler.adobe.com/#create/fromanimage">http://kuler.adobe.com/#create/fromanimage</a></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/a-guide-to-creating-appealing-graphics/430523/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/a-guide-to-creating-appealing-graphics/430523/2</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 24 Jan 2012 23:52:24 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-430523-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/a-guide-to-creating-appealing-graphics/430523.rss">A Guide to Creating Appealing Graphics</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>A Guide to Creating Appealing Graphics</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Lin Lin]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/lin">@Lin</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I’m sure there’s a million articles on the web for this sorta thing, but I find myself wanting to say the same thing to many of the games on this forum. So, without further ado, here’s a little guide to creating not necessarily good graphics but blending graphics - meaning they can all look like garbage but still have a style that fits and doesn’t suck too much.</p>
<p>First off, I wanna take a moment to look at old games. All these pictures are ones I found from searching Google Images, mainly because I don’t want to re-invent the wheel by taking screenshots of things that have already been captured. Why do this? Because successful commercial games had blending graphics dated back to the NES. Take a look at some of these games:</p>
<p><img src="http://freexbresse.free.fr/mmf/megaman1/castle1/m1c1p01.gif" alt width="256" height="224"></p>
<p><img src="http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/310316-castlevania-nes-screenshot-oh-my-god-what-a-despicable-monstrosity.png" alt width="256" height="224"></p>
<p><img src="http://www.emuparadise.me/fup/up/67754-Megaman_Xtreme_2_%28USA,_Europe%29-4.png" alt width="640" height="456"></p>
<p>I could create a big list, but I think I can make my point here. Graphics artists way back in the day had very few colors to work with - 32 on the background for the GBC, and even less on the NES, yet look at how everything follows the same style. What’s the main key to this? Palettes. By sticking to a palette, you’re much better off creating graphics that blend. With modern-day technology, color bitness isn’t an issue, meaning there isn’t a limit to what colors we can choose to create images. This in my opinion is the biggest cause for unappealing GUIs, sprites, and backgrounds.</p>
<p>Check out a sprite I made a while back for the main character from Dark Cloud. Notice how I used a palette and consistent shading.</p>
<p><img src="http://img408.imageshack.us/img408/5381/toan.png" alt width="" height=""></p>
<p>The only thing I must point out that is wrong about this image is I simply mirrored the side view of the character, which created improper shading. Anyway though, I want you to take a close look at the palettes. For each general color (orange, green, etc…), there are only 3 colors and they all have nearly-identical saturation (Saturation is basically the strength of the color). And the shades don’t differentiate greatly either - They really only go down in luminance about 40… uhm… units… This is generally the idea to stick to when creating palettes - find an appealing saturation that fits for your graphic and create a few shades of each color. Here’s the palette the GBA game Dragonball Z Buu’s Fury uses throughout the <span class="bbcode-b">entire</span> game for backgrounds (top-left):</p>
<p><img src="http://img842.imageshack.us/img842/6148/dbzbuusfurymultiple.png" alt width="" height=""></p>
<p>As you can see, it follows the same principle I explained and the graphics look fantastic. Now I’d like to turn your attention to the Megaman Xtreme screenshot (the 3rd image). Look at X in his… whatever you wanna call it. Know how many colors are there? 4. Yep, only 4. And you can tell what everything is, and it looks great. Wanna know how many colors the Gameboy had to use? 4 Again, and not even real colors. Just white, black, and 2 shades of gray. Graphics looked great then too. Take a look at Zelda Link’s Awakening:</p>
<p><img src="http://www.consoleclassix.com/info_img/Legend_of_Zelda_Links_Awakening_GBC_ScreenShot3.gif" alt width="256" height="224"></p>
<p>Personally, I couldn’t make graphics nearly as appealing with all the colors in the world. The game artists created a style and stuck with it. This is important with any game - whether it’s 2D or 3D, a fighter or a shooter, the goal is always the same. I know this seems ironic, but look at Minecraft. The graphics all blend and are appealing because Notch created a style (with a form of a palette of course) and stuck with it. Notice how most HD texture packs ruin the game’s look and feel (another important aspect) because high-res professional graphics are being thrown into a world with the most basic possible terrain and models. They don’t fit together. Hopefully you can see what I’m talking about.</p>
<p>I don’t mean to be cocky, but I want to show you an example of how using very basic graphics and a very limited palette can look nice in a modern game. Pay attention to how many colors the window has (excluding the font).</p>
<p><img src="http://img855.imageshack.us/img855/6134/datastuff.png" alt width="" height=""></p>
<p>There are exactly two colors for each section. The frame consists of two colors, and then 4 for each button - 2 when the mouse isn’t hovering on it and 2 for when it is. So there’s a grand total of 6 colors on the GUI for a 3D game that uses pixel shaders. Oh, actually, there’s more because of the close button, but I’m sure if you’ve read up to this point you can understand why I chose the colors I did.</p>
<p>Now, I know it may seem like a lot to keep in mind, but your games will turn out so much nicer if you follow this guide (I think anyway. Maybe I’m totally wrong and have no idea what I’m talking about). The things to keep in mind are the style, the blending, and the look and feel. Now, go make your game not use a Windows scrollbar on your custom chatbox with an unfitting background.</p>
<p>~Lin</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/a-guide-to-creating-appealing-graphics/430523/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/a-guide-to-creating-appealing-graphics/430523/1</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 24 Jan 2012 23:41:22 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-430523-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/a-guide-to-creating-appealing-graphics/430523.rss">A Guide to Creating Appealing Graphics</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
