<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Difference</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/difference/451337</link>
    <description>I don&#39;t need help specifically in the client, just need to find that (Read the bold) for other things as well.

I have two clients, one that&#39;s been highly edited and one that&#39;s just been extracted. Both came from the same .rar file, so they are exactly the same; the only difference is what I&#39;ve edited. My edited client got messed up at some point, not even sure how and It wouldn&#39;t let me log in, while the newly extracted client has no errors and functions correctly. [b]Do any of you know a way or a program which can find the differences between two folders or files.[/b] I need to find out what caused the problem and probably redo the client with the differences I find.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 26 Jul 2012 04:56:52 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/difference/451337.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Difference</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@xknightpk xknightpk]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/xknightpk">@xknightpk</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I don’t need help specifically in the client, just need to find that (Read the bold) for other things as well.</p>
<p>I have two clients, one that’s been highly edited and one that’s just been extracted. Both came from the same .rar file, so they are exactly the same; the only difference is what I’ve edited. My edited client got messed up at some point, not even sure how and It wouldn’t let me log in, while the newly extracted client has no errors and functions correctly. <span class="bbcode-b">Do any of you know a way or a program which can find the differences between two folders or files.</span> I need to find out what caused the problem and probably redo the client with the differences I find.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/difference/451337/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/difference/451337/1</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jul 2012 04:56:52 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-451337-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/difference/451337.rss">Difference</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
