<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Best branch of computers to get into? (work wise)</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/best-branch-of-computers-to-get-into-work-wise/478162</link>
    <description>There are many different branches of work revolving around computers. Networking, Programming, Designing, Hardware, Software, etc. I&#39;m wanting to do a professional job in a few years working with computers. Currently I got an internship working with a computer business as an IT person in an office setting. This involves primarily software and hardware work, rarely hardware though. I know a lot about all branches, especially programming, and networking. I&#39;m not wanting to be an IT forever, and I know there are many other companies that want me to work for them. I wanted a few different view points on what the best area of work would be best getting in to. I can do most, and have tons of knowledge on all of them.

Also, what jobs would you recommend (eg. Software Architect/Game Developer)

Here&#39;s what I&#39;m professional level with.

- Various different types of computer languages. (HTML, CSS, PHP, Ajax, SQL, C, C#, Java, Javascript)
- Security and Networking (Working with smooth and efficient network systems, including servers, switches, etc.)
- Software (I can name about six different programs that can be used to do something on a computer. Eg. I can name several different text editors, understand how they work, and troubleshoot them if a problem occurs.)
- Hardware (I can put together a computer in a matter of minutes, and I know about how all of the components of a computer work, and how they work together.)

I&#39;m only 15, but, it&#39;s always good to plan for the future. Thanks for any suggestions you guys may have!</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 11 Jan 2013 16:55:55 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>General Discussion</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/best-branch-of-computers-to-get-into-work-wise/478162.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Best branch of computers to get into? (work wise)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Team_Rocket Team_Rocket]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/team_rocket">@Team_Rocket</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>In my personal opinion, Designers have the best job out of everyone. I won’t write a wall of text in response to this, because I’m very tired, but feel free to send me a Private Message and I’ll get back to you when I return. You must be as good as you say if you’re interning in an I.T. Department at the age of 15 (lol).</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/best-branch-of-computers-to-get-into-work-wise/478162/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/best-branch-of-computers-to-get-into-work-wise/478162/2</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 11 Jan 2013 16:55:55 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-478162-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/best-branch-of-computers-to-get-into-work-wise/478162.rss">Best branch of computers to get into? (work wise)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Best branch of computers to get into? (work wise)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@The_Web_Guy The Web Guy]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/the_web_guy">@The_Web_Guy</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>There are many different branches of work revolving around computers. Networking, Programming, Designing, Hardware, Software, etc. I’m wanting to do a professional job in a few years working with computers. Currently I got an internship working with a computer business as an IT person in an office setting. This involves primarily software and hardware work, rarely hardware though. I know a lot about all branches, especially programming, and networking. I’m not wanting to be an IT forever, and I know there are many other companies that want me to work for them. I wanted a few different view points on what the best area of work would be best getting in to. I can do most, and have tons of knowledge on all of them.</p>
<p>Also, what jobs would you recommend (eg. Software Architect/Game Developer)</p>
<p>Here’s what I’m professional level with.</p>
<ul>
<li>Various different types of computer languages. (HTML, CSS, PHP, Ajax, SQL, C, C#, Java, Javascript)</li>
<li>Security and Networking (Working with smooth and efficient network systems, including servers, switches, etc.)</li>
<li>Software (I can name about six different programs that can be used to do something on a computer. Eg. I can name several different text editors, understand how they work, and troubleshoot them if a problem occurs.)</li>
<li>Hardware (I can put together a computer in a matter of minutes, and I know about how all of the components of a computer work, and how they work together.)</li>
</ul>
<p>I’m only 15, but, it’s always good to plan for the future. Thanks for any suggestions you guys may have!</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/best-branch-of-computers-to-get-into-work-wise/478162/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/best-branch-of-computers-to-get-into-work-wise/478162/1</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 11 Jan 2013 15:08:24 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-478162-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/best-branch-of-computers-to-get-into-work-wise/478162.rss">Best branch of computers to get into? (work wise)</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
