<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Zombie Apocalypse Unturned - Free!</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/zombie-apocalypse-unturned-free/539711</link>
    <description>I found unturned not to long ago, I had been searching for zombie apocalyptic games and fell on Unturned it&#39;s free and fun and it has a webclient/webplayer based platform so it&#39;s easy to play. The game has a singleplayer which is basically survival by yourself and it&#39;s also multiplayer. The game has over 15,000+ registered accounts, and the gameplay is intense. I myself as a horrible survivalist very enjoyed this game, the game is built out of strategy, survival, and if on multiplayer team work.

The multiplayer offers Player Versus player and player versus Environment servers, the server capacity seems to be unlimited depicting on what the host has selected. Very fun game and I think if you&#39;re looking for a survivalist game it should be this one. 

I&#39;m posting this in Games and Reviews just so I don&#39;t have people ranting because I&#39;m kind of reviewing and sharing the game.

[Unturned links] Game: http://smartlydressedgames.com/unturned/ Blog: http://sdgdevelopment.blogspot.ca/</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2014 00:43:56 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Games</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/zombie-apocalypse-unturned-free/539711.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Zombie Apocalypse Unturned - Free!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@blddyboy blddyboy]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/blddyboy">@blddyboy</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I found unturned not to long ago, I had been searching for zombie apocalyptic games and fell on Unturned it’s free and fun and it has a webclient/webplayer based platform so it’s easy to play. The game has a singleplayer which is basically survival by yourself and it’s also multiplayer. The game has over 15,000+ registered accounts, and the gameplay is intense. I myself as a horrible survivalist very enjoyed this game, the game is built out of strategy, survival, and if on multiplayer team work.</p>
<p>The multiplayer offers Player Versus player and player versus Environment servers, the server capacity seems to be unlimited depicting on what the host has selected. Very fun game and I think if you’re looking for a survivalist game it should be this one.</p>
<p>I’m posting this in Games and Reviews just so I don’t have people ranting because I’m kind of reviewing and sharing the game.</p>
<p>[Unturned links] Game: <a href="http://smartlydressedgames.com/unturned/" rel="nofollow noopener">http://smartlydressedgames.com/unturned/</a> Blog: <a href="http://sdgdevelopment.blogspot.ca/" rel="nofollow noopener">http://sdgdevelopment.blogspot.ca/</a></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/zombie-apocalypse-unturned-free/539711/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/zombie-apocalypse-unturned-free/539711/1</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2014 00:43:56 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-539711-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/zombie-apocalypse-unturned-free/539711.rss">Zombie Apocalypse Unturned - Free!</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
