<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>I need a Hoster please</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/i-need-a-hoster-please/228701</link>
    <description>Okay, now you&#39;re all probably asking, why can&#39;t you host yourself? well here&#39;s that answer..
I can&#39;t host myself because I don&#39;t think my router can port forward properly, i have tried everything, i have called my ISP, they haven&#39;t got a clue about anything i&#39;m saying, So that is why I need a host.

Now, getting to the point. I need a server host, if you can host 24/7 that&#39;d be great, but I am not looking for that, I just want atleast 10/7 ... You have to have a fairly fast computer, You must know excactly how to host (I don&#39;t want people asking &quot;oh wut button i press here?b howv u portforward?????&quot; that gets really annoying, max players, well, i Don&#39;t want many, it must be able to host 15 players without lag, and you must have knowledge to be able to Edit characters files, to make them admin, do little updates ect. 

If you host the server, you can become joint owner with me, If you would like to Host my server, please add me on msn: Dylza@jagex.com or Dylza.rocks.bmx.and.afl.footy@hotmail.com or post here in this topic..

Thanks,
Dylza


Anyone?[br][br][size=1]Posted on: August 29, 2008, 08:12:24 pm[/size][hr]Anyone?[br][br][size=1]Posted on: September 01, 2008, 03:58:03 am[/size][hr]noone going to reply?</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2008 23:50:51 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/i-need-a-hoster-please/228701.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>I need a Hoster please</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Dylza Dylza]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/dylza">@Dylza</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Okay, now you’re all probably asking, why can’t you host yourself? well here’s that answer…<br>
I can’t host myself because I don’t think my router can port forward properly, i have tried everything, i have called my ISP, they haven’t got a clue about anything i’m saying, So that is why I need a host.</p>
<p>Now, getting to the point. I need a server host, if you can host 24/7 that’d be great, but I am not looking for that, I just want atleast 10/7 … You have to have a fairly fast computer, You must know excactly how to host (I don’t want people asking “oh wut button i press here?b howv u portforward???” that gets really annoying, max players, well, i Don’t want many, it must be able to host 15 players without lag, and you must have knowledge to be able to Edit characters files, to make them admin, do little updates ect.</p>
<p>If you host the server, you can become joint owner with me, If you would like to Host my server, please add me on msn: <a href="mailto:Dylza@jagex.com">Dylza@jagex.com</a> or <a href="mailto:Dylza.rocks.bmx.and.afl.footy@hotmail.com">Dylza.rocks.bmx.and.afl.footy@hotmail.com</a> or post here in this topic…</p>
<p>Thanks,<br>
Dylza</p>
<p>Anyone?[br][br][size=1]Posted on: August 29, 2008, 08:12:24 pm[/size][hr]Anyone?[br][br][size=1]Posted on: September 01, 2008, 03:58:03 am[/size][hr]noone going to reply?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/i-need-a-hoster-please/228701/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/i-need-a-hoster-please/228701/1</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2008 23:50:51 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-228701-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/i-need-a-hoster-please/228701.rss">I need a Hoster please</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
