<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Fatal Commands</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/fatal-commands/194031</link>
    <description>Hey guys,

I&#39;m using Devolution 7.0 server source and I am about to give my whole server to my friend for a month before i make it dedicated. Now i am removing the java files so he can&#39;t editit. But when i dedicate it i can tell him to delete but he never will. So i need a command that i will be able to do. One that will either delete server or do something so he will not be able to repair. He can&#39;t code well, so anything will do. Maybe even add a few uneeded {&#39;s in anywhere or delete files. But he will have backups so any suggestions or commands would be great. Letting him host the server is unnegotiable.

All help is appreciated

Thanx :)</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 29 Mar 2008 16:02:36 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/fatal-commands/194031.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Fatal Commands</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@akanaz akanaz]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/akanaz">@akanaz</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Hey guys,</p>
<p>I’m using Devolution 7.0 server source and I am about to give my whole server to my friend for a month before i make it dedicated. Now i am removing the java files so he can’t editit. But when i dedicate it i can tell him to delete but he never will. So i need a command that i will be able to do. One that will either delete server or do something so he will not be able to repair. He can’t code well, so anything will do. Maybe even add a few uneeded {'s in anywhere or delete files. But he will have backups so any suggestions or commands would be great. Letting him host the server is unnegotiable.</p>
<p>All help is appreciated</p>
<p>Thanx <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=6" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/fatal-commands/194031/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/fatal-commands/194031/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 29 Mar 2008 16:02:36 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-194031-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/fatal-commands/194031.rss">Fatal Commands</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
