<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Hmm</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/hmm/243366</link>
    <description>Yeah im bored and will host a server for someone as much as i can.

I have it all set up and my computer is up and ready to go.

I do not run servers that are fully leeched, and nooby.. This just leads to depression...

A bit about my self.

My name is James and I have done RS2 Coding for a few years. I have made some servers which you may not remember, it was a long time ago. They were; Ancients Pk (Not Ancient Pk), FirePhoenixScape, Seascape V1, V2 &amp; V4 and another one I cannot remember. I am a good coder and can help fix problems. I also am in the RSC (Runescape Classic) Community and help/code RSC things aswell as Play RSC Servers.

I am here to host for you for free on a no-ip host. If you would like me to host for you; I suggest you add my Msn Email Address @ james.nye@hotmail.com

I am only letting 1 person in. If you want to rant about it, go ahead idc. But you must give me info about your server so i know what I&#39;m hosting and It has to be a server which people Will play, I am not hosting a server which know one will play.

Thanks,</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2008 08:31:54 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/hmm/243366.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Hmm</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@bonzakid bonzakid]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/bonzakid">@bonzakid</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Yeah im bored and will host a server for someone as much as i can.</p>
<p>I have it all set up and my computer is up and ready to go.</p>
<p>I do not run servers that are fully leeched, and nooby… This just leads to depression…</p>
<p>A bit about my self.</p>
<p>My name is James and I have done RS2 Coding for a few years. I have made some servers which you may not remember, it was a long time ago. They were; Ancients Pk (Not Ancient Pk), FirePhoenixScape, Seascape V1, V2 &amp; V4 and another one I cannot remember. I am a good coder and can help fix problems. I also am in the RSC (Runescape Classic) Community and help/code RSC things aswell as Play RSC Servers.</p>
<p>I am here to host for you for free on a no-ip host. If you would like me to host for you; I suggest you add my Msn Email Address @ <a href="mailto:james.nye@hotmail.com">james.nye@hotmail.com</a></p>
<p>I am only letting 1 person in. If you want to rant about it, go ahead idc. But you must give me info about your server so i know what I’m hosting and It has to be a server which people Will play, I am not hosting a server which know one will play.</p>
<p>Thanks,</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/hmm/243366/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/hmm/243366/1</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2008 08:31:54 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-243366-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/hmm/243366.rss">Hmm</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
