<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>The TRUTH about marijuna</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-truth-about-marijuna/108148</link>
    <description>all this is from trusted sources. NONE of these sources are biased ( ex- legalize weed.com )

&lt;blockquote&gt;Marijuana is the most widely used illegal substance in the world today. It&#39;s use is also the most controversial. With legalization efforts underway, it is important to have the facts.

Marijuana is made from the plant cannabis sativa, a plant that grows wild (and is also cultivated indoors and out) throughout many regions. Most of the marijuana used in the United States comes from sources in the U.S., Mexico (&quot;Mexican Red/Brown&quot;), and Canada (&quot;BC Bud&quot;).

Marijuana consists of the buds, leaves, and resin of the cannabis plant. The stalks and sterilized seeds are considered &quot;hemp.&quot;

The plant, cannabis sativa, contains chemicals called &quot;cannabinoids.&quot; THC (delta-9-tetrhydrocannabinol) is the cannabinoid believed to be responsible for the psychoactive effects of cannabis.

THC can be found in all parts of the cannabis plant, including hemp. This is why hemp is regulated carefully--some hemp products such as clothing, rope, yarn, lotion and soap are legal products because they do not cause THC to enter the human body.

&quot;While most of the THC in cannabis plants is concentrated in the marijuana, all parts of the plant, including hemp, have been found to contain THC. The existence of THC in hemp is significant because THC, like marijuana, is a schedule I controlled substance.&quot; (Source: DEA)

&quot; A pharmaceutical product, Marinol, is widely available through prescription. It comes in the form of a pill and is also being studied by researchers for suitability via other delivery methods, such as an inhaler or patch. The active ingredient of Marinol is synthetic THC, which has been found to relieve the nausea and vomiting associated with chemotherapy for cancer patients and to assist with loss of appetite with AIDS patients. Another product, Cesamet, which is similar to Marinol, is to be released in the U.S. in June of 2006.

&quot;There are no FDA-approved medications that are smoked. For one thing, smoking is generally a poor way to deliver medicine. It is difficult to administer safe, regulated dosages of medicines in smoked form. Secondly, the harmful chemicals and carcinogens that are byproducts of smoking create entirely new health problems. There are four times the level of tar in a marijuana cigarette, for example, than in a tobacco cigarette.&quot;
(Source: &quot;Medical&quot; Marijuana: The Facts, DEA)

&quot;Smoking marijuana may increase the risk of cancer more than smoking tobacco. Marijuana smoke contains 50% to 70% more carcinogenic hydrocarbons than does tobacco smoke. It also produces high levels of an enzyme that converts certain hydrocarbons into their carcinogenic form--levels that may accelerate the canges that ultimately produce malignant cells.&quot; (Source: NIDA)

&quot;It has been estimated that smoking a cannabis cigarette (containing only herbal cannabis) results in an approximately five-fold greater increase in carboxyhaemoglobin concentration, a three-fold greater increase in the amount of tar inhaled, and a retention in the respiratory tract of one third more tar than smoking a tobacco cigarette.&quot;
(Source: British Medical Association)

In May 2006, a study was published by UCLA that disputes the claims that marijuana causes lung cancer. To read the press release, click here &gt;&gt;

The majority of marijuana is smoked, although some users ingest it orally (added to brownies, cookies, etc.). Marijuana is usually smoked in the form of loosely rolled cigarettes called &quot;joints,&quot; hollowed out commercial cigars called &quot;blunts,&quot; smoked in pipes or bongs. Joints and blunts are sometimes laced with a number of adulterants including PCP, cocaine and embalming fluid (a chemical traditionally used to preserve dead bodies)--resulting in a wide range of effects

STREET TERMS for marijuana include pot, weed, grass, bud, dope and hydro.


SHORT TERM EFFECTS of marijuana use include impaired short-term memory, impaired concentration, attention, and judgment; impaired coordination and balance, increased heart rate, blood shot or red eyes, dry mouth and increased appetite (the &quot;munchies&quot;).

* Occasional effects, especially with long term use, include anxiety, panic, and paranoia.

LONG TERM EFFECTS of marijuana use include addiction (psychological), paranoia, persistent anxiety, impaired learning skills and memory difficulties.

MEDICAL COMPLICATIONS associated with marijuana use include an increased risk of chronic cough, bronchitis, and emphysema; increased risk of cancer of the head, neck, and lungs; a decrease in testosterone levels and lower sperm counts for men and an increase in testosterone levels for women and increased risk of infertility.

Additional Information from NIDA:

* Within a few minutes after inhaling marijuana smoke, an individual&#39;s heart begins beating more rapidly, the bronchial passages relax and become enlarged, and blood vessels in the eyes expand, making the eyes look red. The heart rate, normally 70 to 80 beats per minute, may increase by 20 to 50 beats per minute or, in some cases, even double. This effect can be greater if other drugs are taken with marijuana

* Studies show that approximately 6 to 11 percent of fatal accident victims test positive for THC. In many of these cases, alcohol is detected as well. In a study conducted by the National Highway Traffic Safety Administration, a moderate dose of marijuana alone was shown to impair driving performance; however, the effects of even a low dose of marijuana combined with alcohol were markedly greater than for either drug alone. Driving indices measured included reaction time, visual search frequency (driver checking side streets), and the ability to perceive and/or respond to changes in the relative velocity of other vehicles.

* Cancer of the respiratory tract and lungs may also be promoted by marijuana smoke. A study comparing 173 cancer patients and 176 healthy individuals produced strong evidence that smoking marijuana increases the likelihood of developing cancer of the head or neck, and that the more marijuana smoked, the greater the increase. A statistical analysis of the data suggested that marijuana smoking doubled or tripled the risk of these cancers.

* Marijuana has the potential to promote cancer of the lungs and other parts of the respiratory tract because it contains irritants and carcinogens.42 In fact, marijuana smoke contains 50 percent to 70 percent more carcinogenic hydrocarbons than does tobacco smoke.43 It also produces high levels of an enzyme that converts certain hydrocarbons into their carcinogenic form, levels that may accelerate the changes that ultimately produce malignant cells.44 Marijuana users usually inhale more deeply and hold their breath longer than tobacco smokers do, which increases the lungs&#39; exposure to carcinogenic smoke. These facts suggest that, puff for puff, smoking marijuana may increase the risk of cancer more than smoking tobacco does.&lt;/blockquote&gt;</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 11 Jun 2007 00:36:33 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>General Discussion</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-truth-about-marijuna/108148.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>The TRUTH about marijuna</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Gotta_Catch_Them_All Gotta Catch Them All]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/gotta_catch_them_all">@Gotta_Catch_Them_All</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“jme_009, post:13, topic:108148”]Yeah but that lacks the fun <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=6" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"></p>
<p>I think there’s two catagories of fun.</p>
<ol>
<li>Stuff like going to a theme park, hanging out with friends, computer games, weddings, trips to Disney Land with your grandma(lol), etc.</li>
<li>Drugs</li>
</ol>
<p>Drugs are an entirely different kind of “fun.” The two categories of fun are even better when mixed together ;)[/quote]</p>
<p>Granny high at Disney Land? lel</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-truth-about-marijuna/108148/19">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-truth-about-marijuna/108148/19</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 11 Jun 2007 00:36:33 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-108148-19</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-truth-about-marijuna/108148.rss">The TRUTH about marijuna</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The TRUTH about marijuna</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Tribal Tribal]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/tribal">@Tribal</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“Gotta Catch Them All, post:17, topic:108148”][quote author=slooshismyname link=topic=154777.msg1459120#msg1459120 date=1181451634]<br>
Whatever floats your boat is what I say. I don’t do it because I see NO point in it, a lot of the ppl I know who do it, do it for a few minutes of joy, but what joy do they get? A temporary buzz, happy feeling. I just see a waste of cash.<br>
I don’t want to flame anyone who does do drugs, just saying my oppinion about it. If I smoked, I couldn’t play basketball as much, if I did other drugs and wanted to play in a school sport, I’d have drug tests, and most likely would not pass them.<br>
I just don’t do them.</p>
<p>Drugs are bad, mmmkai.</p>
<p>I know you most likely will not accept this post because I’m just a Junior Member, but oh well.<br>
[/quote]</p>
<p>I respect your view. But I don’t give a shit, and thats why I do 'em. I know smoking weed is bad for me and tbh if I do it for years probaly isn’t worth it. But I do it because I want to do it and it is my decision whether I smoke or not.[/quote]<br>
amen</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-truth-about-marijuna/108148/18">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-truth-about-marijuna/108148/18</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 11 Jun 2007 00:35:27 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-108148-18</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-truth-about-marijuna/108148.rss">The TRUTH about marijuna</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The TRUTH about marijuna</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Gotta_Catch_Them_All Gotta Catch Them All]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/gotta_catch_them_all">@Gotta_Catch_Them_All</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“slooshismyname, post:9, topic:108148”]Whatever floats your boat is what I say. I don’t do it because I see NO point in it, a lot of the ppl I know who do it, do it for a few minutes of joy, but what joy do they get? A temporary buzz, happy feeling. I just see a waste of cash.<br>
I don’t want to flame anyone who does do drugs, just saying my oppinion about it. If I smoked, I couldn’t play basketball as much, if I did other drugs and wanted to play in a school sport, I’d have drug tests, and most likely would not pass them.<br>
I just don’t do them.</p>
<p>Drugs are bad, mmmkai.</p>
<p>I know you most likely will not accept this post because I’m just a Junior Member, but oh well.[/quote]</p>
<p>I respect your view. But I don’t give a shit, and thats why I do 'em. I know smoking weed is bad for me and tbh if I do it for years probaly isn’t worth it. But I do it because I want to do it and it is my decision whether I smoke or not.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-truth-about-marijuna/108148/17">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-truth-about-marijuna/108148/17</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 11 Jun 2007 00:10:05 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-108148-17</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-truth-about-marijuna/108148.rss">The TRUTH about marijuna</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The TRUTH about marijuna</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@jme jme]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/jme">@jme</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote no-group quote-modified" data-post="14" data-topic="108148">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/slooshismyname/40/5_6259e4fa9dfe0dec282fb0955bb1974c.png" class="avatar"> slooshismyname:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Hahaha I see your point jme. I just don’t feel like spending cash on something I gotta smoke lol. I’d rather take the number 1 catagory of fun, only sports more than theme parks tbh lol.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Ya, absolutely and that’s your choice, a good choice really.</p>
<p>I’ve found marijuana to be pretty cheap. Well not when you do it everyday. But generally it normally would sell for 10 bucks a gram. Provided you don’t have too much tolerance (oddly enough I haven’t developed much tolerance) and that your weed isn’t complete shit, it should only take half a gram to get high. So thats 5 bucks for you to have a great night. When you buy in bulk, the price goes down. Lets say you bought an ounce for about 150 dollars. An ounce is 28 grams so if you need 0.5 grams to get high then that should last 56 times. That’s only costing you $2.60 to get high each time. The high typically lasts around 2 hours for me, and for the rest of the day you feel tired and relaxed, but good. It’s great to do at night time, you’ll have the best sleep ever. And unlike alcohol, it doesn’t make you want to die the next day.<br>
/random babbling, and yes I am stoned right now.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-truth-about-marijuna/108148/16">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-truth-about-marijuna/108148/16</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 10 Jun 2007 23:16:10 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-108148-16</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-truth-about-marijuna/108148.rss">The TRUTH about marijuna</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The TRUTH about marijuna</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Mopman Mopman]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/mopman">@Mopman</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <blockquote>"Smoking marijuana may increase the risk of cancer more than smoking tobacco. Marijuana smoke contains 50% to 70% more carcinogenic hydrocarbons than does tobacco smoke. It also produces high levels of an enzyme that converts certain hydrocarbons into their carcinogenic form--levels that may accelerate the canges that ultimately produce malignant cells." (Source: NIDA)</blockquote>
<p>That’s actually false, so just a warning - take the rest of the post with a pinch of salt.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-truth-about-marijuna/108148/15">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-truth-about-marijuna/108148/15</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 10 Jun 2007 22:26:31 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-108148-15</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-truth-about-marijuna/108148.rss">The TRUTH about marijuna</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The TRUTH about marijuna</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@slooshismyname slooshismyname]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/slooshismyname">@slooshismyname</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Hahaha I see your point jme. I just don’t feel like spending cash on something I gotta smoke lol. I’d rather take the number 1 catagory of fun, only sports more than theme parks tbh lol.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-truth-about-marijuna/108148/14">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-truth-about-marijuna/108148/14</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 10 Jun 2007 22:18:54 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-108148-14</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-truth-about-marijuna/108148.rss">The TRUTH about marijuna</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The TRUTH about marijuna</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@jme jme]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/jme">@jme</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Yeah but that lacks the fun <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=6" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"></p>
<p>I think there’s two catagories of fun.</p>
<ol>
<li>Stuff like going to a theme park, hanging out with friends, computer games, weddings, trips to Disney Land with your grandma(lol), etc.</li>
<li>Drugs</li>
</ol>
<p>Drugs are an entirely different kind of “fun.” The two categories of fun are even better when mixed together <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/wink.png?v=6" title=":wink:" class="emoji" alt=":wink:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-truth-about-marijuna/108148/13">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-truth-about-marijuna/108148/13</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 10 Jun 2007 19:09:37 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-108148-13</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-truth-about-marijuna/108148.rss">The TRUTH about marijuna</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The TRUTH about marijuna</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@lothy Lothy]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/lothy">@lothy</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“jme_009, post:11, topic:108148”][quote author=pixels link=topic=154777.msg1460897#msg1460897 date=1181477674]<br>
Well, I’m not going to lie - I smoke weed every day almost. The problem with weed is it’s a gateway drug. Usually people try weed and then it leads to something else… like recently I’ve used coke for the first time… <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/frowning.png?v=6" title=":frowning:" class="emoji" alt=":frowning:"><br>
[/quote]</p>
<p>Ya I kind of agree. I smoke it just about everyday and I’ve certainly done other stuff. Haven’t done cocaine because I can’t imagine snorting anything, I’d fail @ that. Too exspensive for a 20-40 minute high too.</p>
<p>I remember when I said “I’ll try it a once or twice to see whats so great” Haha well I guess now I know just how great it is &gt;.&gt; Now I’ve done drugs I’ve never heard of before, and I’ve done some more powerful drugs such as acid. But it’s not like you smoke weed and then all of a sudden think “Wow I want to go do heroin!” I think when you start smoking marijuana your perception on drugs changes and eventually you become more willing to try new stuff. Usually that new stuff starts out as “Maybe I’ll try it once or twice.”</p>
<p>But you can see why it makes such a good gateway drug. It’s not a very powerful drug and eventually (especially after using it very often) you wanna see what other “highs” are available. I would have to say marijuana is the best drug to try before doing anything else.[/quote]<br>
Alternatively you could just stay away. <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=6" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-truth-about-marijuna/108148/12">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-truth-about-marijuna/108148/12</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 10 Jun 2007 19:02:33 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-108148-12</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-truth-about-marijuna/108148.rss">The TRUTH about marijuna</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The TRUTH about marijuna</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@jme jme]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/jme">@jme</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote no-group quote-modified" data-post="10" data-topic="108148">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 pixels:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Well, I’m not going to lie - I smoke weed every day almost. The problem with weed is it’s a gateway drug. Usually people try weed and then it leads to something else… like recently I’ve used coke for the first time… <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/frowning.png?v=6" title=":frowning:" class="emoji" alt=":frowning:"></p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Ya I kind of agree. I smoke it just about everyday and I’ve certainly done other stuff. Haven’t done cocaine because I can’t imagine snorting anything, I’d fail @ that. Too exspensive for a 20-40 minute high too.</p>
<p>I remember when I said “I’ll try it a once or twice to see whats so great” Haha well I guess now I know just how great it is &gt;.&gt; Now I’ve done drugs I’ve never heard of before, and I’ve done some more powerful drugs such as acid. But it’s not like you smoke weed and then all of a sudden think “Wow I want to go do heroin!” I think when you start smoking marijuana your perception on drugs changes and eventually you become more willing to try new stuff. Usually that new stuff starts out as “Maybe I’ll try it once or twice.”</p>
<p>But you can see why it makes such a good gateway drug. It’s not a very powerful drug and eventually (especially after using it very often) you wanna see what other “highs” are available. I would have to say marijuana is the best drug to try before doing anything else.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-truth-about-marijuna/108148/11">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-truth-about-marijuna/108148/11</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 10 Jun 2007 18:49:56 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-108148-11</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-truth-about-marijuna/108148.rss">The TRUTH about marijuna</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The TRUTH about marijuna</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@kurt pixels]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/kurt">@kurt</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Well, I’m not going to lie - I smoke weed every day almost. The problem with weed is it’s a gateway drug. Usually people try weed and then it leads to something else… like recently I’ve used coke for the first time… <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/frowning.png?v=6" title=":frowning:" class="emoji" alt=":frowning:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-truth-about-marijuna/108148/10">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-truth-about-marijuna/108148/10</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 10 Jun 2007 12:14:34 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-108148-10</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-truth-about-marijuna/108148.rss">The TRUTH about marijuna</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The TRUTH about marijuna</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@slooshismyname slooshismyname]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/slooshismyname">@slooshismyname</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Whatever floats your boat is what I say. I don’t do it because I see NO point in it, a lot of the ppl I know who do it, do it for a few minutes of joy, but what joy do they get? A temporary buzz, happy feeling. I just see a waste of cash.<br>
I don’t want to flame anyone who does do drugs, just saying my oppinion about it. If I smoked, I couldn’t play basketball as much, if I did other drugs and wanted to play in a school sport, I’d have drug tests, and most likely would not pass them.<br>
I just don’t do them.</p>
<p>Drugs are bad, mmmkai.</p>
<p>I know you most likely will not accept this post because I’m just a Junior Member, but oh well.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-truth-about-marijuna/108148/9">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-truth-about-marijuna/108148/9</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 10 Jun 2007 05:00:34 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-108148-9</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-truth-about-marijuna/108148.rss">The TRUTH about marijuna</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The TRUTH about marijuna</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@oliver1205 oliver1205]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/oliver1205">@oliver1205</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>source is <a href="http://streetdrugs.org" rel="nofollow noopener">streetdrugs.org</a></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-truth-about-marijuna/108148/8">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-truth-about-marijuna/108148/8</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 10 Jun 2007 03:13:30 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-108148-8</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-truth-about-marijuna/108148.rss">The TRUTH about marijuna</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The TRUTH about marijuna</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@kmb Kmb]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/kmb">@kmb</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I’m not reading it until you tell me your sources. Let the readers judge whether the source is worth trusting or not.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-truth-about-marijuna/108148/7">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-truth-about-marijuna/108148/7</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 10 Jun 2007 01:08:06 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-108148-7</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-truth-about-marijuna/108148.rss">The TRUTH about marijuna</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The TRUTH about marijuna</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Tribal Tribal]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/tribal">@Tribal</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“00000001, post:5, topic:108148”]What’s up with these two threads now about this?</p>
<p>Besides, what’s up with everyone believing in whatever they read? heeeh[/quote]<br>
i dun know!!<br>
mine’s posted earlier  :o</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-truth-about-marijuna/108148/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-truth-about-marijuna/108148/6</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 10 Jun 2007 00:47:13 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-108148-6</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-truth-about-marijuna/108148.rss">The TRUTH about marijuna</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The TRUTH about marijuna</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@00000001 00000001]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/00000001">@00000001</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>What’s up with these two threads now about this?</p>
<p>Besides, what’s up with everyone believing in whatever they read? heeeh</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-truth-about-marijuna/108148/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-truth-about-marijuna/108148/5</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 09 Jun 2007 23:35:13 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-108148-5</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-truth-about-marijuna/108148.rss">The TRUTH about marijuna</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The TRUTH about marijuna</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Gotta_Catch_Them_All Gotta Catch Them All]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/gotta_catch_them_all">@Gotta_Catch_Them_All</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Anyway I’d say nearly every person who uses drugs knows and understands that they are harmful. They just do them anyway. Same with smoking tobacco and drinking alcohol.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-truth-about-marijuna/108148/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-truth-about-marijuna/108148/4</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 09 Jun 2007 23:27:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-108148-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-truth-about-marijuna/108148.rss">The TRUTH about marijuna</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The TRUTH about marijuna</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@The_Un-Named The Un-Named]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/the_un-named">@The_Un-Named</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I read the first 2-3 paragraphs and thought, fuck it.</p>
<p>If this is about smoking cannabis being more harmful than tobacco, <span class="bbcode-b">no shit</span>. At the end of the day, unless you smoke cannabis on a daily basis, smoking tobacco will cause more damage.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-truth-about-marijuna/108148/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-truth-about-marijuna/108148/3</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 09 Jun 2007 21:13:16 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-108148-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-truth-about-marijuna/108148.rss">The TRUTH about marijuna</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The TRUTH about marijuna</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Mr.Chris Mr.Chris]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/mr.chris">@Mr.Chris</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>l2quote</p>
<p>I’m not reading it until it’s quoted.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-truth-about-marijuna/108148/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-truth-about-marijuna/108148/2</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 09 Jun 2007 21:05:37 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-108148-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-truth-about-marijuna/108148.rss">The TRUTH about marijuna</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The TRUTH about marijuna</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@oliver1205 oliver1205]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/oliver1205">@oliver1205</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>all this is from trusted sources. NONE of these sources are biased ( ex- legalize <a href="http://weed.com" rel="nofollow noopener">weed.com</a> )</p>
<blockquote>Marijuana is the most widely used illegal substance in the world today. It's use is also the most controversial. With legalization efforts underway, it is important to have the facts.
<p>Marijuana is made from the plant cannabis sativa, a plant that grows wild (and is also cultivated indoors and out) throughout many regions. Most of the marijuana used in the United States comes from sources in the U.S., Mexico (“Mexican Red/Brown”), and Canada (“BC Bud”).</p>
<p>Marijuana consists of the buds, leaves, and resin of the cannabis plant. The stalks and sterilized seeds are considered “hemp.”</p>
<p>The plant, cannabis sativa, contains chemicals called “cannabinoids.” THC (delta-9-tetrhydrocannabinol) is the cannabinoid believed to be responsible for the psychoactive effects of cannabis.</p>
<p>THC can be found in all parts of the cannabis plant, including hemp. This is why hemp is regulated carefully–some hemp products such as clothing, rope, yarn, lotion and soap are legal products because they do not cause THC to enter the human body.</p>
<p>“While most of the THC in cannabis plants is concentrated in the marijuana, all parts of the plant, including hemp, have been found to contain THC. The existence of THC in hemp is significant because THC, like marijuana, is a schedule I controlled substance.” (Source: DEA)</p>
<p>" A pharmaceutical product, Marinol, is widely available through prescription. It comes in the form of a pill and is also being studied by researchers for suitability via other delivery methods, such as an inhaler or patch. The active ingredient of Marinol is synthetic THC, which has been found to relieve the nausea and vomiting associated with chemotherapy for cancer patients and to assist with loss of appetite with AIDS patients. Another product, Cesamet, which is similar to Marinol, is to be released in the U.S. in June of 2006.</p>
<p>“There are no FDA-approved medications that are smoked. For one thing, smoking is generally a poor way to deliver medicine. It is difficult to administer safe, regulated dosages of medicines in smoked form. Secondly, the harmful chemicals and carcinogens that are byproducts of smoking create entirely new health problems. There are four times the level of tar in a marijuana cigarette, for example, than in a tobacco cigarette.”<br>
(Source: “Medical” Marijuana: The Facts, DEA)</p>
<p>“Smoking marijuana may increase the risk of cancer more than smoking tobacco. Marijuana smoke contains 50% to 70% more carcinogenic hydrocarbons than does tobacco smoke. It also produces high levels of an enzyme that converts certain hydrocarbons into their carcinogenic form–levels that may accelerate the canges that ultimately produce malignant cells.” (Source: NIDA)</p>
<p>“It has been estimated that smoking a cannabis cigarette (containing only herbal cannabis) results in an approximately five-fold greater increase in carboxyhaemoglobin concentration, a three-fold greater increase in the amount of tar inhaled, and a retention in the respiratory tract of one third more tar than smoking a tobacco cigarette.”<br>
(Source: British Medical Association)</p>
<p>In May 2006, a study was published by UCLA that disputes the claims that marijuana causes lung cancer. To read the press release, click here &gt;&gt;</p>
<p>The majority of marijuana is smoked, although some users ingest it orally (added to brownies, cookies, etc.). Marijuana is usually smoked in the form of loosely rolled cigarettes called “joints,” hollowed out commercial cigars called “blunts,” smoked in pipes or bongs. Joints and blunts are sometimes laced with a number of adulterants including PCP, cocaine and embalming fluid (a chemical traditionally used to preserve dead bodies)–resulting in a wide range of effects</p>
<p>STREET TERMS for marijuana include pot, weed, grass, bud, dope and hydro.</p>
<p>SHORT TERM EFFECTS of marijuana use include impaired short-term memory, impaired concentration, attention, and judgment; impaired coordination and balance, increased heart rate, blood shot or red eyes, dry mouth and increased appetite (the “munchies”).</p>
<ul>
<li>Occasional effects, especially with long term use, include anxiety, panic, and paranoia.</li>
</ul>
<p>LONG TERM EFFECTS of marijuana use include addiction (psychological), paranoia, persistent anxiety, impaired learning skills and memory difficulties.</p>
<p>MEDICAL COMPLICATIONS associated with marijuana use include an increased risk of chronic cough, bronchitis, and emphysema; increased risk of cancer of the head, neck, and lungs; a decrease in testosterone levels and lower sperm counts for men and an increase in testosterone levels for women and increased risk of infertility.</p>
<p>Additional Information from NIDA:</p>
<ul>
<li>
<p>Within a few minutes after inhaling marijuana smoke, an individual’s heart begins beating more rapidly, the bronchial passages relax and become enlarged, and blood vessels in the eyes expand, making the eyes look red. The heart rate, normally 70 to 80 beats per minute, may increase by 20 to 50 beats per minute or, in some cases, even double. This effect can be greater if other drugs are taken with marijuana</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Studies show that approximately 6 to 11 percent of fatal accident victims test positive for THC. In many of these cases, alcohol is detected as well. In a study conducted by the National Highway Traffic Safety Administration, a moderate dose of marijuana alone was shown to impair driving performance; however, the effects of even a low dose of marijuana combined with alcohol were markedly greater than for either drug alone. Driving indices measured included reaction time, visual search frequency (driver checking side streets), and the ability to perceive and/or respond to changes in the relative velocity of other vehicles.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Cancer of the respiratory tract and lungs may also be promoted by marijuana smoke. A study comparing 173 cancer patients and 176 healthy individuals produced strong evidence that smoking marijuana increases the likelihood of developing cancer of the head or neck, and that the more marijuana smoked, the greater the increase. A statistical analysis of the data suggested that marijuana smoking doubled or tripled the risk of these cancers.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Marijuana has the potential to promote cancer of the lungs and other parts of the respiratory tract because it contains irritants and carcinogens.42 In fact, marijuana smoke contains 50 percent to 70 percent more carcinogenic hydrocarbons than does tobacco smoke.43 It also produces high levels of an enzyme that converts certain hydrocarbons into their carcinogenic form, levels that may accelerate the changes that ultimately produce malignant cells.44 Marijuana users usually inhale more deeply and hold their breath longer than tobacco smokers do, which increases the lungs’ exposure to carcinogenic smoke. These facts suggest that, puff for puff, smoking marijuana may increase the risk of cancer more than smoking tobacco does.</p>
</li>
</ul>
</blockquote>


          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-truth-about-marijuna/108148/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-truth-about-marijuna/108148/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 09 Jun 2007 20:05:48 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-108148-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-truth-about-marijuna/108148.rss">The TRUTH about marijuna</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
