<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>A few questions for advanced coders</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/a-few-questions-for-advanced-coders/114908</link>
    <description>[size=15pt]A few questions for advanced coders...[/size]

1: Attacking Error
I) OK, when I use a melee weapon and attack a player, it hits them. Then when they walk away, my character doesn&#39;t follow them and they still get damaged. My character doesn&#39;t move, and still they get damaged even if they are far away. Does anyone know how to solve this?

II) [b]Sometimes[/b] when I click to attack somebody, it does the hitting emote but the other player doesn&#39;t get hit at all. I have to wait a few seconds then click on them again for it to attack properly. Why is this?

: Mage/Range NPC
How do I make an NPC attack with mage or range instead of melee?

3: Anti-lag
I assume that you&#39;ve heard of ZdiddyScape? Around a month ago, there was a poll on which server was the best. ZdiddyScape was ranked 1. That server, and all the other popular servers are lag-proof. Whenever I mass click on training objects, such as dummies, on their server, it doesn&#39;t lag. My server lags when I do hat. The ZdiddyScape owner said that there is no anti-lag code. He told me to just base my training on NPCs. A few people told me to add timers - but I already have actionTimer in the object case. Others said they saw a tutorial on how to make it lag-proof, but they won&#39;t give me the link. Just want to ask if there is a code that makes it anti-lag, and what the link to the tutorial is.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 22 Jun 2007 12:51:01 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/a-few-questions-for-advanced-coders/114908.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>A few questions for advanced coders</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@NexondotNet NexondotNet]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/nexondotnet">@NexondotNet</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[size=15pt]A few questions for advanced coders…[/size]</p>
<p>1: Attacking Error<br>
I) OK, when I use a melee weapon and attack a player, it hits them. Then when they walk away, my character doesn’t follow them and they still get damaged. My character doesn’t move, and still they get damaged even if they are far away. Does anyone know how to solve this?</p>
<p>II) <span class="bbcode-b">Sometimes</span> when I click to attack somebody, it does the hitting emote but the other player doesn’t get hit at all. I have to wait a few seconds then click on them again for it to attack properly. Why is this?</p>
<p>: Mage/Range NPC<br>
How do I make an NPC attack with mage or range instead of melee?</p>
<p>3: Anti-lag<br>
I assume that you’ve heard of ZdiddyScape? Around a month ago, there was a poll on which server was the best. ZdiddyScape was ranked 1. That server, and all the other popular servers are lag-proof. Whenever I mass click on training objects, such as dummies, on their server, it doesn’t lag. My server lags when I do hat. The ZdiddyScape owner said that there is no anti-lag code. He told me to just base my training on NPCs. A few people told me to add timers - but I already have actionTimer in the object case. Others said they saw a tutorial on how to make it lag-proof, but they won’t give me the link. Just want to ask if there is a code that makes it anti-lag, and what the link to the tutorial is.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/a-few-questions-for-advanced-coders/114908/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/a-few-questions-for-advanced-coders/114908/1</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 22 Jun 2007 12:51:01 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-114908-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/a-few-questions-for-advanced-coders/114908.rss">A few questions for advanced coders</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
