<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Beginner that needs help please?</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/beginner-that-needs-help-please/546491</link>
    <description>Alrighty so as the title suggests i&#39;m a beginner and i barely know what i am doing but i need some help, Alrighty so my 1st Problem, i have dled a client and got it online using no-ip and stuff, so then i needed to make it a jar file so my friend could get on or whatever, so i dled JAR Maker and it took me like 5 tries but i finally got it to jar, but i think in the process i messed something up because now with every jarred client (even ones that aren&#39;t mine that worked perfectly fine before i did the JAR Maker thing) when i double click it it says: &quot;Error: Could not find or load main class C:\Users\Kelly\Desktop\US2Launcher.jar (as you can see i am trying to open UltimateScape&#39;s jar which isnt the one im working on obviously) but if i right click is and click Open With then Java(TM) Platform SE Binary it loads right up, no problems, so obviously i messed something up somewhere does anyone know how to fix this? Also now hat i have made the Jar for the server i am attempting to work on, i sent the jar file to my friend and when he tries to open it he gets a error that say&#39;s: Java Virtual Machine Loader: A Java Exception has occured. On my computer when i try to open up my jarred file it does the same thing as mentioned above, but when i right click it and run with java, it works, so yeah i&#39;ve got something messed up..:/
 MY 2nd problem, I am trying to use Eclipse to help me with my server coding and stuff, but when i try to run my server through Eclipse i get to the part where you Run Configurations\Java Application\new, then i name my thing or whatever but when i click on search under Main Class, nothing comes up, on tutorials i&#39;ve watched you have to find server.Server and when they click search they have a list of things that pop up but absolutely nothing comes up on mine, i was wondering what was up with that, i was thinking maybe that is linked to my jar files acting funny also, like maybe i didnt get some type of file when i dled this server? idk, im sorry for the essay and im not even sure if this goes here tbh but i need help, someone might be able to help me that would be amazing, Thanks Everyone.
-Skullbandit</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2014 16:49:26 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Game Development</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/beginner-that-needs-help-please/546491.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Beginner that needs help please?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Skullbandit Skullbandit]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/skullbandit">@Skullbandit</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Alrighty so as the title suggests i’m a beginner and i barely know what i am doing but i need some help, Alrighty so my 1st Problem, i have dled a client and got it online using no-ip and stuff, so then i needed to make it a jar file so my friend could get on or whatever, so i dled JAR Maker and it took me like 5 tries but i finally got it to jar, but i think in the process i messed something up because now with every jarred client (even ones that aren’t mine that worked perfectly fine before i did the JAR Maker thing) when i double click it it says: "Error: Could not find or load main class C:\Users\Kelly\Desktop\US2Launcher.jar (as you can see i am trying to open UltimateScape’s jar which isnt the one im working on obviously) but if i right click is and click Open With then Java™ Platform SE Binary it loads right up, no problems, so obviously i messed something up somewhere does anyone know how to fix this? Also now hat i have made the Jar for the server i am attempting to work on, i sent the jar file to my friend and when he tries to open it he gets a error that say’s: Java Virtual Machine Loader: A Java Exception has occured. On my computer when i try to open up my jarred file it does the same thing as mentioned above, but when i right click it and run with java, it works, so yeah i’ve got something messed up…<img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/confused.png?v=5" title=":confused:" class="emoji" alt=":confused:"><br>
MY 2nd problem, I am trying to use Eclipse to help me with my server coding and stuff, but when i try to run my server through Eclipse i get to the part where you Run Configurations\Java Application\new, then i name my thing or whatever but when i click on search under Main Class, nothing comes up, on tutorials i’ve watched you have to find server.Server and when they click search they have a list of things that pop up but absolutely nothing comes up on mine, i was wondering what was up with that, i was thinking maybe that is linked to my jar files acting funny also, like maybe i didnt get some type of file when i dled this server? idk, im sorry for the essay and im not even sure if this goes here tbh but i need help, someone might be able to help me that would be amazing, Thanks Everyone.<br>
-Skullbandit</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/beginner-that-needs-help-please/546491/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/beginner-that-needs-help-please/546491/1</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2014 16:49:26 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-546491-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/beginner-that-needs-help-please/546491.rss">Beginner that needs help please?</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
