<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Need Administrative assistance</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/need-administrative-assistance/440661</link>
    <description>I&#39;m completely new to this forums and currently am not sure where to post this thread so if it is the wrong place then please move it without hesistation, sorry if I cause any distraught. 

Regarding the title, I have a single concern. I currently just switched VPS hosts for my server in hopes to require better service, specifically uptime. On the host I am unable to login because it says I am banned and therefor am unable to even access registering and other simple tasks. The ban is also not set to expire. I can honestly say myself that I was not the one that got the IP banned, it is a managed VPS so I assume someone on the same host had been ip banned for reasons unknown. That being said I understand that unbanning the Ip would be dangerous because potentially this could be harmful, I only request you look at the situation and see if it&#39;s possible to Unipban, otherwise I will have to request a host migration. I am looking to remove my current advertisement and completely start fresh but I am unable to do so without being able to login. I can obviously ask my provider to do a host change, I have asked but they don&#39;t seem to be responding, even thought it&#39;s only been 2 hours I wan&#39;t this done as soon as possible and I didn&#39;t see any other way of getting this done without contacting these forum administrators. I also only switched providers yesterday and I don&#39;t see them doing a host change this early into the service and it would also be very inconvenient to myself.

[size=12pt]TL;DR[/size]
My VPS is ipbaned, I cannot register from it. I was not the reason. I am requesting being unipbanned and also an advertisement cancellation/removal. Is this possible? 

Note: If you need any proof that I have not even visisted the Moparscape.org/smf forums from my host then I am sure I can figure out some way to get the track record. Thank you very much if you reply, the assistance is muchly appreciated.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 26 Apr 2012 04:54:33 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>General Discussion</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/need-administrative-assistance/440661.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Need Administrative assistance</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@silabsoft RuneAgent]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/silabsoft">@silabsoft</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>PM FUNCTION PLEASE</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/need-administrative-assistance/440661/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/need-administrative-assistance/440661/4</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 Apr 2012 04:54:33 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-440661-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/need-administrative-assistance/440661.rss">Need Administrative assistance</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Need Administrative assistance</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Veldahar Veldahar]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/veldahar">@Veldahar</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Thank you, I just did. I truly appreciate the feedback.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/need-administrative-assistance/440661/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/need-administrative-assistance/440661/3</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 Apr 2012 03:16:31 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-440661-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/need-administrative-assistance/440661.rss">Need Administrative assistance</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Need Administrative assistance</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Acorn1 Acorn_]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/acorn1">@Acorn1</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Private Message Moparisthebest</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/need-administrative-assistance/440661/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/need-administrative-assistance/440661/2</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 Apr 2012 03:15:25 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-440661-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/need-administrative-assistance/440661.rss">Need Administrative assistance</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Need Administrative assistance</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Veldahar Veldahar]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/veldahar">@Veldahar</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I’m completely new to this forums and currently am not sure where to post this thread so if it is the wrong place then please move it without hesistation, sorry if I cause any distraught.</p>
<p>Regarding the title, I have a single concern. I currently just switched VPS hosts for my server in hopes to require better service, specifically uptime. On the host I am unable to login because it says I am banned and therefor am unable to even access registering and other simple tasks. The ban is also not set to expire. I can honestly say myself that I was not the one that got the IP banned, it is a managed VPS so I assume someone on the same host had been ip banned for reasons unknown. That being said I understand that unbanning the Ip would be dangerous because potentially this could be harmful, I only request you look at the situation and see if it’s possible to Unipban, otherwise I will have to request a host migration. I am looking to remove my current advertisement and completely start fresh but I am unable to do so without being able to login. I can obviously ask my provider to do a host change, I have asked but they don’t seem to be responding, even thought it’s only been 2 hours I wan’t this done as soon as possible and I didn’t see any other way of getting this done without contacting these forum administrators. I also only switched providers yesterday and I don’t see them doing a host change this early into the service and it would also be very inconvenient to myself.</p>
<p>[size=12pt]TL;DR[/size]<br>
My VPS is ipbaned, I cannot register from it. I was not the reason. I am requesting being unipbanned and also an advertisement cancellation/removal. Is this possible?</p>
<p>Note: If you need any proof that I have not even visisted the <a href="http://Moparscape.org/smf" rel="nofollow noopener">Moparscape.org/smf</a> forums from my host then I am sure I can figure out some way to get the track record. Thank you very much if you reply, the assistance is muchly appreciated.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/need-administrative-assistance/440661/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/need-administrative-assistance/440661/1</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 Apr 2012 02:42:02 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-440661-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/need-administrative-assistance/440661.rss">Need Administrative assistance</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
