<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Failed Presedent Dies</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/failed-presedent-dies/261601</link>
    <description>Well actualy it was a mistake!

&lt;blockquote&gt;A TV station in South Africa mistakenly broadcast that former US President George Bush had died. For three seconds, ETV News ran a moving banner headline saying &#39;George Bush is dead&#39;.

Apparently, a member of staff wanted to see how a rolling banner headline looked. The error happened when a technician pressed the &#39;broadcast live for transmission&#39; button instead of the one for a test-run. &quot;The technical director pressed the wrong button, it took a second for the words to appear and then the words were on screen for only three seconds before they were taken off,&quot; said spokesman Vasili Vass. &quot;We&#39;ve learned from it, all test banners will now be done in gobbledegook,&quot; he added. He would not comment on whether the person responsible faces disciplinary action.

This blunder reinforces the unwritten live TV rule: always expect the unexpected. From Kerry Katona slurring her way through This Morning to Heather McCartney breaking down in tears during a GMTV interview, we highlight some moments when it wasn&#39;t quite alright on the night in our gallery below.&lt;/blockquote&gt;
Sauce:http://entertainment.uk.msn.com/tv/galleries/gallery.aspx?cp-documentid=13799360</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2009 16:55:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>General Discussion</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/failed-presedent-dies/261601.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Failed Presedent Dies</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Fat_Cookies Fat Cookies]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/fat_cookies">@Fat_Cookies</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Well actualy it was a mistake!</p>
<blockquote>A TV station in South Africa mistakenly broadcast that former US President George Bush had died. For three seconds, ETV News ran a moving banner headline saying 'George Bush is dead'.
<p>Apparently, a member of staff wanted to see how a rolling banner headline looked. The error happened when a technician pressed the ‘broadcast live for transmission’ button instead of the one for a test-run. “The technical director pressed the wrong button, it took a second for the words to appear and then the words were on screen for only three seconds before they were taken off,” said spokesman Vasili Vass. “We’ve learned from it, all test banners will now be done in gobbledegook,” he added. He would not comment on whether the person responsible faces disciplinary action.</p>
<p>This blunder reinforces the unwritten live TV rule: always expect the unexpected. From Kerry Katona slurring her way through This Morning to Heather McCartney breaking down in tears during a GMTV interview, we highlight some moments when it wasn’t quite alright on the night in our gallery below.</p>
</blockquote><br>
Sauce:<a href="http://entertainment.uk.msn.com/tv/galleries/gallery.aspx?cp-documentid=13799360" rel="nofollow noopener">http://entertainment.uk.msn.com/tv/galleries/gallery.aspx?cp-documentid=13799360</a>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/failed-presedent-dies/261601/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/failed-presedent-dies/261601/1</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2009 16:55:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-261601-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/failed-presedent-dies/261601.rss">Failed Presedent Dies</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
