<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Logout button case?</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/logout-button-case/72422</link>
    <description>Hi.
I&#39;m making fishing for my server, and i&#39;m done with the main things, i have fishing stuff appear in your hand when you are fishing, it&#39;s possible by putting the thing in your shield slot, it&#39;s like it gets an &quot;original weapon and shield&quot; int when you start fishing which remembers your original wep ID. If i walk away, it&#39;s fine, BUT if i click logout, the original weapon doesn&#39;t get back in your hand, so i would need to set the logout button te set the weapon and shield back, before the player logs out, but after it pressed the logout button.

I think this would be in a case. but which one? I&#39;ve tried searching and i found destruct() void, but it doesnt seem to work with that, so i guess i need to assign it to the &quot;case&quot; of the button. like with the emote buttons.

Anybody knows the logout button&#39;s case number?</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 30 Mar 2007 23:07:20 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/logout-button-case/72422.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Logout button case?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@1337_king 1337 king]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/1337_king">@1337_king</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Hi.<br>
I’m making fishing for my server, and i’m done with the main things, i have fishing stuff appear in your hand when you are fishing, it’s possible by putting the thing in your shield slot, it’s like it gets an “original weapon and shield” int when you start fishing which remembers your original wep ID. If i walk away, it’s fine, BUT if i click logout, the original weapon doesn’t get back in your hand, so i would need to set the logout button te set the weapon and shield back, before the player logs out, but after it pressed the logout button.</p>
<p>I think this would be in a case. but which one? I’ve tried searching and i found destruct() void, but it doesnt seem to work with that, so i guess i need to assign it to the “case” of the button. like with the emote buttons.</p>
<p>Anybody knows the logout button’s case number?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/logout-button-case/72422/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/logout-button-case/72422/1</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 30 Mar 2007 23:07:20 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-72422-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/logout-button-case/72422.rss">Logout button case?</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
