<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Multiple Directory Compiler</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/multiple-directory-compiler/310023</link>
    <description>Does anyone know how to refer to multiple directories whilst compiling? I&#39;ve looked at java docs, and all I could find was this:

&lt;blockquote&gt;Specifying a User Class Path

Having changed one of the source files in the previous example, we recompile it:
C:&gt; cd
\examples
C:&gt; javac greetings\Hi.java
Since greetings.Hi refers to other classes in the greetings package, the compiler needs to find these other classes. The example above works, because our default user class path happens to be the directory containing the package directory. But suppose we want to recompile this file and not worry about which directory we&#39;re in? Then we need to add \examples to the user class path. We can do this by setting CLASSPATH, but here we&#39;ll use the -classpath option.
C:&gt;javac -classpath \examples \examples\greetings\Hi.java
If we change greetings.Hi again, to use a banner utility, that utility also needs to be accessible through the user class path.
C:&gt;javac -classpath \examples;\lib\Banners.jar \
			  \examples\greetings\Hi.java
To execute a class in greetings, we need access both to greetings and to the classes it uses.
C:&gt;java -classpath \examples;\lib\Banners.jar greetings.Hi&lt;/blockquote&gt;

I&#39;ve tried that, and apparently I&#39;m doing it wrong. Either that, or that&#39;s not what I&#39;m supposed to be doing.

I&#39;m trying to make a batch for Hyperion, and the files refer to each other in different directories and won&#39;t compile successfully unless the examples are specified. Errors come up with invalid referrals, methods don&#39;t exist, etc.

If anyone&#39;s made a batch compiler for Hyperion rather than helping me create one, I&#39;d be glad to just accept that.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 22 Oct 2009 13:35:14 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/multiple-directory-compiler/310023.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Multiple Directory Compiler</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@The_Reaper_X The Reaper X]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/the_reaper_x">@The_Reaper_X</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Does anyone know how to refer to multiple directories whilst compiling? I’ve looked at java docs, and all I could find was this:</p>
<blockquote>Specifying a User Class Path
<p>Having changed one of the source files in the previous example, we recompile it:<br>
C:&gt; cd<br>
\examples<br>
C:&gt; javac greetings\Hi.java<br>
Since greetings.Hi refers to other classes in the greetings package, the compiler needs to find these other classes. The example above works, because our default user class path happens to be the directory containing the package directory. But suppose we want to recompile this file and not worry about which directory we’re in? Then we need to add \examples to the user class path. We can do this by setting CLASSPATH, but here we’ll use the -classpath option.<br>
C:&gt;javac -classpath \examples \examples\greetings\Hi.java<br>
If we change greetings.Hi again, to use a banner utility, that utility also needs to be accessible through the user class path.<br>
C:&gt;javac -classpath \examples;\lib\Banners.jar <br>
\examples\greetings\Hi.java<br>
To execute a class in greetings, we need access both to greetings and to the classes it uses.<br>
C:&gt;java -classpath \examples;\lib\Banners.jar greetings.Hi</p>
</blockquote>
<p>I’ve tried that, and apparently I’m doing it wrong. Either that, or that’s not what I’m supposed to be doing.</p>
<p>I’m trying to make a batch for Hyperion, and the files refer to each other in different directories and won’t compile successfully unless the examples are specified. Errors come up with invalid referrals, methods don’t exist, etc.</p>
<p>If anyone’s made a batch compiler for Hyperion rather than helping me create one, I’d be glad to just accept that.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/multiple-directory-compiler/310023/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/multiple-directory-compiler/310023/1</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 22 Oct 2009 13:35:14 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-310023-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/multiple-directory-compiler/310023.rss">Multiple Directory Compiler</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
