<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Can someone recommend me a source?</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/can-someone-recommend-me-a-source/470258</link>
    <description>Hi, I am going to start a Runescape Private Server but I don&#39;t have a source code or client. I always like the latest stuff so I don&#39;t really want 317. I would like it to be 508+ and have MySQL as I have experience with queries, web management, databases and some PHP Coding. If you think that it&#39;s stupid just to get a source and make a server based on it as it will be the same thing, I can code a little bit in Java, I can&#39;t write my own from scratch but I can edit anything from commands to shops, NPCs exp rates and I am a fast learner. I was trying out Jolt Environment v2 which was coded in C# as it has mysql and you can add worlds and it was pretty stable, But I found that I didn&#39;t really like it as no npcs were spawned and I just couldn&#39;t get used to it.


Thanks guys!</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2012 15:25:47 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/can-someone-recommend-me-a-source/470258.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Can someone recommend me a source?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Bubbsy7 Bubbsy7]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/bubbsy7">@Bubbsy7</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>If you wanna start from scratch, testscape  <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=5" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/can-someone-recommend-me-a-source/470258/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/can-someone-recommend-me-a-source/470258/2</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2012 15:25:47 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-470258-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/can-someone-recommend-me-a-source/470258.rss">Can someone recommend me a source?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Can someone recommend me a source?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Andy89898 Andy89898]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/andy89898">@Andy89898</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Hi, I am going to start a Runescape Private Server but I don’t have a source code or client. I always like the latest stuff so I don’t really want 317. I would like it to be 508+ and have MySQL as I have experience with queries, web management, databases and some PHP Coding. If you think that it’s stupid just to get a source and make a server based on it as it will be the same thing, I can code a little bit in Java, I can’t write my own from scratch but I can edit anything from commands to shops, NPCs exp rates and I am a fast learner. I was trying out Jolt Environment v2 which was coded in C# as it has mysql and you can add worlds and it was pretty stable, But I found that I didn’t really like it as no npcs were spawned and I just couldn’t get used to it.</p>
<p>Thanks guys!</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/can-someone-recommend-me-a-source/470258/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/can-someone-recommend-me-a-source/470258/1</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2012 14:49:50 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-470258-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/can-someone-recommend-me-a-source/470258.rss">Can someone recommend me a source?</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
