<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>667 Protocol</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/667-protocol/440808</link>
    <description>I am trying to edit the server Matrix. I do not want it to just be another &quot;leeched&quot; server. and we will not be releasing it soon. maybe in 4 more weeks. however i am having the following problem.

My coding friend can connect and load the server. However My other friend cannot and it states
&quot;Loading Please Wait 1%&quot; and does not continue to load. Someone told me it was my &quot;protocol&quot; but i do not know how to fix it. I want my friend to play so he can tell us what to add and shit. If you might know the problem please comment or message me, i promise after i set up a paypal im willing to give a good amount or what ever. I need help really bad. Please Comment or even PM me, and i have Team Viewer so maybe you can help me through there. Thank you... Alot</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 28 Apr 2012 02:22:14 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/667-protocol/440808.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>667 Protocol</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@king_prodigy king prodigy]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/king_prodigy">@king_prodigy</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I am trying to edit the server Matrix. I do not want it to just be another “leeched” server. and we will not be releasing it soon. maybe in 4 more weeks. however i am having the following problem.</p>
<p>My coding friend can connect and load the server. However My other friend cannot and it states<br>
“Loading Please Wait 1%” and does not continue to load. Someone told me it was my “protocol” but i do not know how to fix it. I want my friend to play so he can tell us what to add and shit. If you might know the problem please comment or message me, i promise after i set up a paypal im willing to give a good amount or what ever. I need help really bad. Please Comment or even PM me, and i have Team Viewer so maybe you can help me through there. Thank you… Alot</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/667-protocol/440808/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/667-protocol/440808/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 28 Apr 2012 02:22:14 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-440808-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/667-protocol/440808.rss">667 Protocol</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
