<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Help me with webclient</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/help-me-with-webclient/372812</link>
    <description>Alright, so basically I&#39;m having a problem. See, I&#39;ve decided to stick with a 525 server. Mostly because of the GUI and items. I&#39;ve also heard they&#39;re more stable. Anyways... So I&#39;m trying to set up a webclient. You see, I&#39;ve done this with 317&#39;s.. Never was very good at it. I&#39;ve used the search button, google, checked different websites. I just can&#39;t seem to find a tutorial. I&#39;ve looked at the 317 tutorials to see if anything matches up, ut some of the methods don&#39;t even exist where they say they should. So if somebody could direct me to the proper tutorial that would help me I would greatly appreciate it. Thanks.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 11 Dec 2010 16:13:10 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Game Development</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/help-me-with-webclient/372812.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Help me with webclient</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Soul3ss Soul3ss]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/soul3ss">@Soul3ss</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Alright, so basically I’m having a problem. See, I’ve decided to stick with a 525 server. Mostly because of the GUI and items. I’ve also heard they’re more stable. Anyways… So I’m trying to set up a webclient. You see, I’ve done this with 317’s… Never was very good at it. I’ve used the search button, google, checked different websites. I just can’t seem to find a tutorial. I’ve looked at the 317 tutorials to see if anything matches up, ut some of the methods don’t even exist where they say they should. So if somebody could direct me to the proper tutorial that would help me I would greatly appreciate it. Thanks.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/help-me-with-webclient/372812/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/help-me-with-webclient/372812/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 11 Dec 2010 16:13:10 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-372812-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/help-me-with-webclient/372812.rss">Help me with webclient</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
