<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>[Non]Map not loading?</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/non-map-not-loading/537616</link>
    <description>Now it just started recently that when I tele to gwd I started getting a &quot;map loading error&quot;, not an error but i go in a loop of logging out and logging in on the server and it won&#39;t load my character in gwds map, so im a little stuck on why this is happening.  I haven&#39;t&#39;t changed any of the code.  I re-uploaded the files and redid the coding for gwd map, yet I&#39;m still getting this weird map error.  I can spawn to the saradomin boss room with only one logout and relogin, but once I get the second level, the main room, it goes hay weird.  If I close the source the client shows all the npcs i spawn and my character for a sec until it says lost connection to the server.  What did I do wrong?  I&#39;m pretty sure its not the server side since all the gwd coding is in the client.

*Note*
I loads everything else besides the area of gwd map</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 26 Dec 2013 04:50:36 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Game Development</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/non-map-not-loading/537616.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>[Non]Map not loading?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@MrFun MrFun]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/mrfun">@MrFun</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Now it just started recently that when I tele to gwd I started getting a “map loading error”, not an error but i go in a loop of logging out and logging in on the server and it won’t load my character in gwds map, so im a little stuck on why this is happening.  I haven’t’t changed any of the code.  I re-uploaded the files and redid the coding for gwd map, yet I’m still getting this weird map error.  I can spawn to the saradomin boss room with only one logout and relogin, but once I get the second level, the main room, it goes hay weird.  If I close the source the client shows all the npcs i spawn and my character for a sec until it says lost connection to the server.  What did I do wrong?  I’m pretty sure its not the server side since all the gwd coding is in the client.</p>
<p><em>Note</em><br>
I loads everything else besides the area of gwd map</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/non-map-not-loading/537616/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/non-map-not-loading/537616/1</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 Dec 2013 04:50:36 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-537616-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/non-map-not-loading/537616.rss">[Non]Map not loading?</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
