<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Guthans | Economy | Worldwide PvP | Server Events | NR Remake |</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/guthans-economy-worldwide-pvp-server-events-nr-remake/545876</link>
    <description>[center][img]https://dl.dropboxusercontent.com/u/47837233/Banner.png[/img]

[b]Guthans uses the actual NR source, from before it shutdown.[/b] 
Guthans is a brand new server based on one of the most successful private server to ever exist. The server uses the exact same source of Near Reality V13, with even more features being added day by day. The server has only just been released, which gives us hope that this server will soon become the number one place for Runescape Private Server fans to come and play, if we get that far.

[u][b]Quick Links:[/b][/u]
[img]https://cdn1.iconfinder.com/data/icons/large-home-icons/16/Small_house_home_arrow_building.png[/img][url=http://www.guthans.com]Home[/url]
[img]http://i.imgur.com/9eAt7MP.png[/img][url=http://www.guthans.com/lic]Forums[/url]
[img]http://i.imgur.com/fC6mT3t.png[/img][url=http://www.guthans.com/play.html]Play Webclient[/url]
[img]http://cdn2.iconfinder.com/data/icons/splashyIcons/download.png[/img][url=http://www.guthans.com/Client.zip]Download Client[/url]
[img]http://runetrack.com/images/skill_icons/overall.gif[/img][url=http://guthans.com/wiki/index.php/Main_Page]Wiki/Still in Development[/url]
[img]http://www.tradearcadepro.com/images/CheckIconSmall.png[/img][url=http://www.guthans.com/vote/#?step=1]Vote[/url]

[u][b]Update Log:[/b][/u]
8/8/14 - Started working on source, Removed the horrific jframe in my opinion on client, Changed everything to Guthans.
8/9/14 - Fixed most if not all of the errors in eclipse that is affecting server performance and character saving.
8/10/14 - Started working on content updates to give it more of a Guthans feel and less of a NR leech. Gave client a &quot;Logo in taskbar..
8/11/14 - Added better level-up interface, Added Auto voting with rewards &quot;GTLVOTE&quot;. Starting advertisements to get players suggestions on what to work on and what to fix.

[center][img]http://i.imgur.com/zAPJroe.png[/img][/center]
[u][b]Guthans is an Economy server: [/b][/u]

[b]This basically means there&#39;s no spawning[/b] and any items people obtain will have been earned through PVM or from PKing. This means our items will have value, making everything more fun, giving players something to aim for and of course making it so much better when you finally get that kill for rare items. There are tons of different ways to exchange your items including specific market areas, clan chats, and even a dedicated section on forums. Being a new server we want to get our economy right the first time. To ensure we achieve this we have made drop rates at a perfect level to maintain item drops for PvMers, but also to give just enough that we&#39;re not flooded with items and massive inflation like you see on most other private servers.


[u][b]The Guthans Experience:[/b][/u]

Guthans community is like no other! As soon as you join you will notice our wilderness, forums, and active PvMing and Clan communities. Here at Guthans, we don’t like to mess around, we want to bring you the players the best possible experience that we can give you. 

Our community gives a warm welcome to all new players, and presents them with many opportunity to get involded with activities and get to know existing members. We have many events and tournaments in and out of the wilderness that makes this possible. These can be anything from Clan based PKing, to a simple games of Hide and Seek. 


[u][b]The Guthans Staff Team:[/b][/u]

All of Guthans staff are hand-picked based off applications anyone is free to submit, &quot;[b]NO AUTO PROMOTIONS[/b]&quot; These application then get voted on by our staff team and those few that provide the best application will get a chance to prove themselves by starting as a Server Support member. Not only do we make sure we have staff from EVERY different time zone. We make sure we have the nicest most helpful staff available for you, Which means you get professional support and help when ever you may need it, [b]If that quota is not met we will not hesitate to remove the staff that is affecting this experience.[/b]

[u][b]Guthans Development &amp; Progress:[/b][/u]

The development team here at Guthans, Consists of myself and my Client Dev. and we know quality updates have to come from what the community wants. Once you&#39;ve become a part of the Guthans experience, you’ll notice weekly updates &quot;[b]Even Daily[/b]&quot;, with polls that you can vote on to bring what you want and enjoy into the game. Alternatively you can put your ideas forward as suggestions on our forums and have your voice heard and see your ideas implemented if fellow players support you. [b]The players are in full control of what they want added, based on a 70/30 vote.[/b]

[u][b]Guthans Forums:[/b][/u]

Not only will you notice our active forums, you’ll notice banter ranging from the PVM section to our clan discussion to even the marketplace, you&#39;ll notice an uncontrollable amount of topics and giveaways which no other RSPS can provide you. Here at Guthans we have already accumulated over 30+ members and are still growing at a rapid and uncontrollable pace.

[u][b]Features:[/b][/u]
- Flawless skills, excluding Agility and Farming
- Perfect Duel Arena
- Custom Barrows Minigame
- Custom PK system where you can turn in your PK Points for various rewards
- Friendly Staff and Active staff from all over the globe.
- Hundreds of PVM and PVP opportunities with countless rewards
- Custom Whips Including Lava and Lime whip
- Perfect PKing with flawless switching and perfect hybriding
- Clans in Single and Multi
- Every working special attack you can think of
- Quick, Fast, Reliable auto donation system
- Custom Donator Islands with lots of helpful donation perks!
- IPB Forums
-Custom Wilderness teleports
-Better Level Up Interface than NR had.

[u][b]Media:[/b][/u]
Better Level Up Sprites
[IMG]http://i.imgur.com/4w4AixI.png[/img]
MORE TO COME!
[/center]</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2014 01:04:44 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/guthans-economy-worldwide-pvp-server-events-nr-remake/545876.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Guthans | Economy | Worldwide PvP | Server Events | NR Remake |</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@GuthansRSPS GuthansRSPS]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/guthansrsps">@GuthansRSPS</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[center]<img src="https://dl.dropboxusercontent.com/u/47837233/Banner.png" alt width="" height=""></p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Guthans uses the actual NR source, from before it shutdown.</span><br>
Guthans is a brand new server based on one of the most successful private server to ever exist. The server uses the exact same source of Near Reality V13, with even more features being added day by day. The server has only just been released, which gives us hope that this server will soon become the number one place for Runescape Private Server fans to come and play, if we get that far.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-u"><span class="bbcode-b">Quick Links:</span></span><br>
<img src="https://cdn1.iconfinder.com/data/icons/large-home-icons/16/Small_house_home_arrow_building.png" alt width="" height=""><a href="http://www.guthans.com" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">Home</a><br>
<img src="http://i.imgur.com/9eAt7MP.png" alt width="" height=""><a href="http://www.guthans.com/lic" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">Forums</a><br>
<img src="http://i.imgur.com/fC6mT3t.png" alt width="" height=""><a href="http://www.guthans.com/play.html" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">Play Webclient</a><br>
<img src="http://cdn2.iconfinder.com/data/icons/splashyIcons/download.png" alt width="" height=""><a href="http://www.guthans.com/Client.zip" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">Download Client</a><br>
<img src="http://runetrack.com/images/skill_icons/overall.gif" alt width="" height=""><a href="http://guthans.com/wiki/index.php/Main_Page" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">Wiki/Still in Development</a><br>
<img src="http://www.tradearcadepro.com/images/CheckIconSmall.png" alt width="" height=""><a href="http://www.guthans.com/vote/#?step=1" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">Vote</a></p>
<p><span class="bbcode-u"><span class="bbcode-b">Update Log:</span></span><br>
8/8/14 - Started working on source, Removed the horrific jframe in my opinion on client, Changed everything to Guthans.<br>
8/9/14 - Fixed most if not all of the errors in eclipse that is affecting server performance and character saving.<br>
8/10/14 - Started working on content updates to give it more of a Guthans feel and less of a NR leech. Gave client a "Logo in taskbar…<br>
8/11/14 - Added better level-up interface, Added Auto voting with rewards “GTLVOTE”. Starting advertisements to get players suggestions on what to work on and what to fix.</p>
<p>[center]<img src="http://i.imgur.com/zAPJroe.png" alt width="" height="">[/center]<br>
<span class="bbcode-u"><span class="bbcode-b">Guthans is an Economy server: </span></span></p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">This basically means there’s no spawning</span> and any items people obtain will have been earned through PVM or from PKing. This means our items will have value, making everything more fun, giving players something to aim for and of course making it so much better when you finally get that kill for rare items. There are tons of different ways to exchange your items including specific market areas, clan chats, and even a dedicated section on forums. Being a new server we want to get our economy right the first time. To ensure we achieve this we have made drop rates at a perfect level to maintain item drops for PvMers, but also to give just enough that we’re not flooded with items and massive inflation like you see on most other private servers.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-u"><span class="bbcode-b">The Guthans Experience:</span></span></p>
<p>Guthans community is like no other! As soon as you join you will notice our wilderness, forums, and active PvMing and Clan communities. Here at Guthans, we don’t like to mess around, we want to bring you the players the best possible experience that we can give you.</p>
<p>Our community gives a warm welcome to all new players, and presents them with many opportunity to get involded with activities and get to know existing members. We have many events and tournaments in and out of the wilderness that makes this possible. These can be anything from Clan based PKing, to a simple games of Hide and Seek.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-u"><span class="bbcode-b">The Guthans Staff Team:</span></span></p>
<p>All of Guthans staff are hand-picked based off applications anyone is free to submit, “<span class="bbcode-b">NO AUTO PROMOTIONS</span>” These application then get voted on by our staff team and those few that provide the best application will get a chance to prove themselves by starting as a Server Support member. Not only do we make sure we have staff from EVERY different time zone. We make sure we have the nicest most helpful staff available for you, Which means you get professional support and help when ever you may need it, <span class="bbcode-b">If that quota is not met we will not hesitate to remove the staff that is affecting this experience.</span></p>
<p><span class="bbcode-u"><span class="bbcode-b">Guthans Development &amp; Progress:</span></span></p>
<p>The development team here at Guthans, Consists of myself and my Client Dev. and we know quality updates have to come from what the community wants. Once you’ve become a part of the Guthans experience, you’ll notice weekly updates “<span class="bbcode-b">Even Daily</span>”, with polls that you can vote on to bring what you want and enjoy into the game. Alternatively you can put your ideas forward as suggestions on our forums and have your voice heard and see your ideas implemented if fellow players support you. <span class="bbcode-b">The players are in full control of what they want added, based on a 70/30 vote.</span></p>
<p><span class="bbcode-u"><span class="bbcode-b">Guthans Forums:</span></span></p>
<p>Not only will you notice our active forums, you’ll notice banter ranging from the PVM section to our clan discussion to even the marketplace, you’ll notice an uncontrollable amount of topics and giveaways which no other RSPS can provide you. Here at Guthans we have already accumulated over 30+ members and are still growing at a rapid and uncontrollable pace.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-u"><span class="bbcode-b">Features:</span></span></p>
<ul>
<li>Flawless skills, excluding Agility and Farming</li>
<li>Perfect Duel Arena</li>
<li>Custom Barrows Minigame</li>
<li>Custom PK system where you can turn in your PK Points for various rewards</li>
<li>Friendly Staff and Active staff from all over the globe.</li>
<li>Hundreds of PVM and PVP opportunities with countless rewards</li>
<li>Custom Whips Including Lava and Lime whip</li>
<li>Perfect PKing with flawless switching and perfect hybriding</li>
<li>Clans in Single and Multi</li>
<li>Every working special attack you can think of</li>
<li>Quick, Fast, Reliable auto donation system</li>
<li>Custom Donator Islands with lots of helpful donation perks!</li>
<li>IPB Forums<br>
-Custom Wilderness teleports<br>
-Better Level Up Interface than NR had.</li>
</ul>
<p><span class="bbcode-u"><span class="bbcode-b">Media:</span></span><br>
Better Level Up Sprites<br>
<img src="http://i.imgur.com/4w4AixI.png" alt width="" height=""><br>
MORE TO COME!<br>
[/center]</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/guthans-economy-worldwide-pvp-server-events-nr-remake/545876/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/guthans-economy-worldwide-pvp-server-events-nr-remake/545876/1</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2014 01:04:44 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-545876-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/guthans-economy-worldwide-pvp-server-events-nr-remake/545876.rss">Guthans | Economy | Worldwide PvP | Server Events | NR Remake |</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
