<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Rant time? Maybe</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rant-time-maybe/445051</link>
    <description>
So I&#39;ve been an avid &quot;game developer&quot; since I made my first game (which was actually just a really bad PHP browser based game. and that was back when I was only 12 years old (now 19, 20 in june! :D) Anywho, over the years, I&#39;ve been attempting to make many different games. different genres, platforms, different languages, makers, and engines! It&#39;s a damn hassle no doubt. However, throughout all that time wasted, I am able to look back and realize, it&#39;s not time wasted at all. Yeah, out of 63 attempts at making games, I failed at 58 of them, but I succeeded at 5 of them creating working games. And even though there was 58 ones that had failed, I still learned a lot by working on them whether it be the language, some html or PHP I didn&#39;t know, how to paperdoll, make 3d models... There&#39;s a lot. Heck, I&#39;m proud to say I learned how to make MySQL tables and scripts at the ripe age of 12! not many can say that. To this day, I still attempt every once in awhile to create another game and I&#39;m sure I&#39;ll fail at it again but atleast I learn something.

Now, my point after all that is simply don&#39;t be discouraged by what most people say. Someone says you can&#39;t use this program because it&#39;s difficult? Prove them wrong! try to use it anyway. Take some time and learn before you start. You can jump right in to making a game and creating a very basic game that only your and your weird nose picking neighbor will play, or you can have some knowledge and create a decent game that you can get a few more people to play. Another thing, and I can&#39;t stress this enough, Get a lot of scrap paper and write things down! It takes so much longer but the results are ALWAYS so much better. I won&#39;t sugar coat it, things always look better in your head. That&#39;s because in your head, you want it to work and your mind will make it work. If you can write it down, chances are that it&#39;s do-able and understandable. If you have friends who are gamers, ask them about the idea and see what they think about it. 

Read books, is another great tip. Many people look on forums and web sites for small posts about game developing, but it&#39;s so much more worth it to get some books. You have no idea how many books there are tailored to making games. It&#39;s ridiculous! Heck, go to a library. I bet ya they have at least 1 book on some shelf collecting dust waiting for that one person who will finally pick them up and enjoy it. I personally have 19 different books ranging from old NES game developing to MMORPG developing books. You can learn a lot, even from old books.

Ask others. I&#39;m not talking on forums though, unless it&#39;s a forum for pro developers. I&#39;m saying try emailing some people that are involved in developing AAA games. Ya never know who might respond to ya willing to answer some questions or talk to you about it. They are the people to ask about the pros and cons of game developing. Personally, I&#39;ve visited Zenimax a few years ago. I never thought they&#39;d let me in but a friend said that we should go down anyway. Well, we drove down, came up to the building (which is a pretty sweet place i must say), and we actually not only got to tour there, but we got to go over to bethesda and meet some developers! It was the second best day of my life! Never underestimate any possibility. Yes you&#39;ll get unresponded e-mails and some people will be an @$$ to you, but that&#39;s life. Ya learn from it and move on. But a few months later, come back to that person and try asking again. Maybe they were in a bad mood that day.

So... That&#39;s my rant for tonight. I actually feel so much better after posting this. So, have fun and happy developing!</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 15 Jun 2012 13:01:41 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Game Development</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rant-time-maybe/445051.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Rant time? Maybe</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@MistaBigBoss MistaBigBoss]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/mistabigboss">@MistaBigBoss</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Great story, and indeed, experience, whether good or bad, is always the key to success.</p>
<p>I started making games, private servers, programs,… at that age too (12). Now that I’m turning 18, I’m a lot more experienced because I’ve never stopped. I am actually capable of making a game out of a concept in my mind without failing. All that because of the experience I gained over the years. Not just at making games, but overall computer knowledge (hardware, networking, how processor architectures work, how OS’s work,…).</p>
<p>The biggest problem now, is time and money.</p>
<ol>
<li>School, takes A LOT of time, luckily, I’m going to be graduated around this time next year, and I’ll be heading over to a game development college here in Belgium.</li>
<li>Muay Thai (thaibox), takes a lot of time, around 3 hours a day.</li>
<li>Money, as a soon to be 18 year old I need money, because I have a life outside of computers. I need money to do stuff, to be able to pay for petrol,…</li>
</ol>
<p>So, when you combine those 3 ^ together, you notice that there is pretty much 0 time left for making games.</p>
<p>1 and 2 are always going to be there, but 3 (money) can be replaced by game development. But in order for me to do that, I need to have some sort of income, because instead of working, I would be making games. Earning money from games is way too hard because games are not fast abnd easily made.</p>
<p>That is why I’m doing a project atm, which is some sort of social network (not like facebook, but I’m not going to go into detail), which can make me money. By that I mean, there is a possibility.</p>
<p>After I finish and launch the project, hopefully I can earn enough money to be able to scratch getting a job from my list and focus on making GAMES.</p>
<p>I don’t know why I just said all that ^^^^</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rant-time-maybe/445051/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rant-time-maybe/445051/3</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Jun 2012 13:01:41 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-445051-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rant-time-maybe/445051.rss">Rant time? Maybe</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Rant time? Maybe</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@eyeownyew Eyeownyew]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/eyeownyew">@eyeownyew</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I don’t see how your personally failed experiences relate to bad feedback from a community. Also, this isn’t even a rant about overcoming difficulty, it’s more like a thread filled with boasting.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rant-time-maybe/445051/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rant-time-maybe/445051/2</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 14 Jun 2012 04:07:38 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-445051-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rant-time-maybe/445051.rss">Rant time? Maybe</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Rant time? Maybe</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@ninja1377 ninja1377]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/ninja1377">@ninja1377</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>So I’ve been an avid “game developer” since I made my first game (which was actually just a really bad PHP browser based game. and that was back when I was only 12 years old (now 19, 20 in june! :D) Anywho, over the years, I’ve been attempting to make many different games. different genres, platforms, different languages, makers, and engines! It’s a damn hassle no doubt. However, throughout all that time wasted, I am able to look back and realize, it’s not time wasted at all. Yeah, out of 63 attempts at making games, I failed at 58 of them, but I succeeded at 5 of them creating working games. And even though there was 58 ones that had failed, I still learned a lot by working on them whether it be the language, some html or PHP I didn’t know, how to paperdoll, make 3d models… There’s a lot. Heck, I’m proud to say I learned how to make MySQL tables and scripts at the ripe age of 12! not many can say that. To this day, I still attempt every once in awhile to create another game and I’m sure I’ll fail at it again but atleast I learn something.</p>
<p>Now, my point after all that is simply don’t be discouraged by what most people say. Someone says you can’t use this program because it’s difficult? Prove them wrong! try to use it anyway. Take some time and learn before you start. You can jump right in to making a game and creating a very basic game that only your and your weird nose picking neighbor will play, or you can have some knowledge and create a decent game that you can get a few more people to play. Another thing, and I can’t stress this enough, Get a lot of scrap paper and write things down! It takes so much longer but the results are ALWAYS so much better. I won’t sugar coat it, things always look better in your head. That’s because in your head, you want it to work and your mind will make it work. If you can write it down, chances are that it’s do-able and understandable. If you have friends who are gamers, ask them about the idea and see what they think about it.</p>
<p>Read books, is another great tip. Many people look on forums and web sites for small posts about game developing, but it’s so much more worth it to get some books. You have no idea how many books there are tailored to making games. It’s ridiculous! Heck, go to a library. I bet ya they have at least 1 book on some shelf collecting dust waiting for that one person who will finally pick them up and enjoy it. I personally have 19 different books ranging from old NES game developing to MMORPG developing books. You can learn a lot, even from old books.</p>
<p>Ask others. I’m not talking on forums though, unless it’s a forum for pro developers. I’m saying try emailing some people that are involved in developing AAA games. Ya never know who might respond to ya willing to answer some questions or talk to you about it. They are the people to ask about the pros and cons of game developing. Personally, I’ve visited Zenimax a few years ago. I never thought they’d let me in but a friend said that we should go down anyway. Well, we drove down, came up to the building (which is a pretty sweet place i must say), and we actually not only got to tour there, but we got to go over to bethesda and meet some developers! It was the second best day of my life! Never underestimate any possibility. Yes you’ll get unresponded e-mails and some people will be an @$$ to you, but that’s life. Ya learn from it and move on. But a few months later, come back to that person and try asking again. Maybe they were in a bad mood that day.</p>
<p>So… That’s my rant for tonight. I actually feel so much better after posting this. So, have fun and happy developing!</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rant-time-maybe/445051/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rant-time-maybe/445051/1</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 14 Jun 2012 00:33:10 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-445051-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rant-time-maybe/445051.rss">Rant time? Maybe</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
