<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Height Glitch</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/height-glitch/516329</link>
    <description>Hi I was on my server walking around, testing doors on buildings, and testing stairs. I was in Camelot and tested some stairs and I went up, but couldn&#39;t go back down. So I typed ::home and I went to my EdgeVille home... But I was pretty much on top of the bank. It was like I was walking on air. I logged out, shut down the server and client, went to my character files, and changed my height from 1 to 0. Everyone else&#39;s height is 0. After i saved the character file, I even compiled it. I went to run my server again, and I was still in mid-air. I then went back to my character files and it changed my height back to 1. Can anyone please help? Thanks!
-------------------EDITED------------------------
I fixed this problem myself. I used my Command ::shops and went down stairs and i fixed it.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2013 22:24:20 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/height-glitch/516329.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Height Glitch</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@GodexCAB GodexCAB]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/godexcab">@GodexCAB</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Hi I was on my server walking around, testing doors on buildings, and testing stairs. I was in Camelot and tested some stairs and I went up, but couldn’t go back down. So I typed ::home and I went to my EdgeVille home… But I was pretty much on top of the bank. It was like I was walking on air. I logged out, shut down the server and client, went to my character files, and changed my height from 1 to 0. Everyone else’s height is 0. After i saved the character file, I even compiled it. I went to run my server again, and I was still in mid-air. I then went back to my character files and it changed my height back to 1. Can anyone please help? Thanks!<br>
-------------------EDITED------------------------<br>
I fixed this problem myself. I used my Command ::shops and went down stairs and i fixed it.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/height-glitch/516329/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/height-glitch/516329/1</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2013 22:24:20 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-516329-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/height-glitch/516329.rss">Height Glitch</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
