<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Help starting a Moparscape private server</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/help-starting-a-moparscape-private-server/377962</link>
    <description>I have very minimal programing experience, most I can do is python, so I really need help with this.   I&#39;ve been trying to log into servers since I downloaded the client today, and I am having no luck.  I can&#39;t even get into one that I supposedly create for my self (create server option).  It either says the server is down or I&#39;m already logged in.  Well that can&#39;t be because I haven&#39;t been able to log in yet.

What should I do, because I have no clue.

Oh, btw, my system is a 64 bit windows 7.  Don&#39;t know if that changes anything, but just in case it does.

EDIT:I have reinstalled Java, restarted my computer, redownloaded moparscape twice, and I have gotten the same error that i&#39;m either logged in already or that the server is down.  Please help, I really would like to play this.
EDIT: I still can&#39;t get it to run ANY server.  I&#39;ve used ones from moparscapes list of online servers, and it doesn&#39;t work at all, just says I&#39;m already logged in.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 12 Jan 2011 03:22:04 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/help-starting-a-moparscape-private-server/377962.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Help starting a Moparscape private server</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Echo3 Echo_]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/echo3">@Echo3</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Make sure that the server itself is running, not just the client. Also make sure that your client ip is set to localhost, or 127.0.0.1.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/help-starting-a-moparscape-private-server/377962/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/help-starting-a-moparscape-private-server/377962/2</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 12 Jan 2011 03:22:04 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-377962-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/help-starting-a-moparscape-private-server/377962.rss">Help starting a Moparscape private server</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Help starting a Moparscape private server</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@shmeves16 shmeves16]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/shmeves16">@shmeves16</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I have very minimal programing experience, most I can do is python, so I really need help with this.   I’ve been trying to log into servers since I downloaded the client today, and I am having no luck.  I can’t even get into one that I supposedly create for my self (create server option).  It either says the server is down or I’m already logged in.  Well that can’t be because I haven’t been able to log in yet.</p>
<p>What should I do, because I have no clue.</p>
<p>Oh, btw, my system is a 64 bit windows 7.  Don’t know if that changes anything, but just in case it does.</p>
<p>EDIT:I have reinstalled Java, restarted my computer, redownloaded moparscape twice, and I have gotten the same error that i’m either logged in already or that the server is down.  Please help, I really would like to play this.<br>
EDIT: I still can’t get it to run ANY server.  I’ve used ones from moparscapes list of online servers, and it doesn’t work at all, just says I’m already logged in.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/help-starting-a-moparscape-private-server/377962/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/help-starting-a-moparscape-private-server/377962/1</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 12 Jan 2011 02:40:19 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-377962-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/help-starting-a-moparscape-private-server/377962.rss">Help starting a Moparscape private server</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
