<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Is it just me or</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/is-it-just-me-or/139005</link>
    <description>Is this community losing it&#39;s thunder. I remember I practically lived on these forums for about a year and a half. Choosing one board and sticking with it for a few months, and then switching and going to a new one. I remember posting all my tuts for cool real life and tech stuff, and people actually giving feedback instead of telling me good or bad job, for the post count. I remember when the people on this community actually knew each other. I would bet half of these little noobs that call themselves active Mopar users can&#39;t tell you anything about this community besides moparscape. This is really getting to me. I never understood how anyone could ever want to leave. I mean sure there was a few noobs here and there, but it never really got to me. But now I&#39;m really starting to see it. People are ruining these forums. It&#39;s horrible. People care more about how much rep, and post count, and what the mods opinions of them are to realize why this forum is here. There&#39;s almost no more sharing actual ideas, it&#39;s all oh, this site has a pretty cool thing, let&#39;s post it on mopar tuts and maybe I can get some rep. I&#39;m sick of it. I&#39;m not leaving the forums. They mean to much to me, but I am getting fed up. I guess there isn&#39;t much anyone could do, and I guess this is just Mopar&#39;s forums evolving. But to be honest, I can&#39;t say I like what these people have turned it into. I miss the old days, and I don&#39;t think many can say they don&#39;t... Please argue with me and tell me I&#39;m a lying noob. It will just tell me I&#39;m right.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 01 Sep 2007 01:38:04 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>General Discussion</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/is-it-just-me-or/139005.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Is it just me or</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@pko pko]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/pko">@pko</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I agree. I remember about 6 months ago I posted on these forums 10-20 times a day, now I come on just to flame losers, or see if anything has happend.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/is-it-just-me-or/139005/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/is-it-just-me-or/139005/4</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 01 Sep 2007 01:38:04 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-139005-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/is-it-just-me-or/139005.rss">Is it just me or</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Is it just me or</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@1337h4x 1337h4x]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/1337h4x">@1337h4x</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>A community needs initiative. RSR has arga. This has nothing, so only loyal people are actually active and helpful. And they’ve been here so long, that they can’t really be assed anymore. I’d post a good job/bad job kind of post, but not for the post count.</p>
<p>Sorry if I made no sense…I feel really retarded atm.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/is-it-just-me-or/139005/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/is-it-just-me-or/139005/3</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 01 Sep 2007 01:33:03 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-139005-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/is-it-just-me-or/139005.rss">Is it just me or</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Is it just me or</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@therealjdb JDB`]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/therealjdb">@therealjdb</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Unfortunately you are right and you will probably get flamed for this post, I have seen this happen to a number of communities degrade like this and usually it means the end of the community all together but due to the huge user base and moparscape this community is sticking together, I can say I know a few people and talk to them regularly but not nearly as many as before the moparscape craze. I guess it’s unavoidable. Oh well, I don’t plan on leaving.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/is-it-just-me-or/139005/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/is-it-just-me-or/139005/2</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 01 Sep 2007 01:21:38 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-139005-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/is-it-just-me-or/139005.rss">Is it just me or</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Is it just me or</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Buzzy Buzzy]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/buzzy">@Buzzy</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Is this community losing it’s thunder. I remember I practically lived on these forums for about a year and a half. Choosing one board and sticking with it for a few months, and then switching and going to a new one. I remember posting all my tuts for cool real life and tech stuff, and people actually giving feedback instead of telling me good or bad job, for the post count. I remember when the people on this community actually knew each other. I would bet half of these little noobs that call themselves active Mopar users can’t tell you anything about this community besides moparscape. This is really getting to me. I never understood how anyone could ever want to leave. I mean sure there was a few noobs here and there, but it never really got to me. But now I’m really starting to see it. People are ruining these forums. It’s horrible. People care more about how much rep, and post count, and what the mods opinions of them are to realize why this forum is here. There’s almost no more sharing actual ideas, it’s all oh, this site has a pretty cool thing, let’s post it on mopar tuts and maybe I can get some rep. I’m sick of it. I’m not leaving the forums. They mean to much to me, but I am getting fed up. I guess there isn’t much anyone could do, and I guess this is just Mopar’s forums evolving. But to be honest, I can’t say I like what these people have turned it into. I miss the old days, and I don’t think many can say they don’t… Please argue with me and tell me I’m a lying noob. It will just tell me I’m right.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/is-it-just-me-or/139005/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/is-it-just-me-or/139005/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 01 Sep 2007 01:15:06 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-139005-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/is-it-just-me-or/139005.rss">Is it just me or</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
