<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>NEW: Question and CPU and Memory</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-question-and-cpu-and-memory/338250</link>
    <description>[b]New: Well as you may or may have not know my motherboard fucked up a couple days ago and I had to send in a new motherboard because thats what I though was broke because the board wouldn&#39;t post. Ok so now Im getting nervous and starting to think that the cpu might have got fried or the memory fucked up If there was a spark on the motherboard while the computer was running and it shut off, would it be the motherboard that fucked up or the cpu/memoy?[/b]

OLD :Well I just hooked up my new setup which includeds the processor listed in the title. It is dual core by default but you have about a 30% chance of unlocking a 3rd or 4th core. Well I seem to be one of these lucky people who paid for a dual core and got a quad core. One question though. I unlocked the 4th core  through the BIOS and it runs fine (ive been running it for about an hour no problems) does this mean im good from now on to forever or will I experience problems with the 4th core unlocked possibly. It seems performance is different. Is it plain and simply that it ethier does or does not work or can you have it unlocked experiencing performance differences. Or am I just a little crazy because I can&#39;t believe I got the two cores unlocked?</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 28 Apr 2010 09:58:42 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Technology</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-question-and-cpu-and-memory/338250.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>NEW: Question and CPU and Memory</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@mwiebelhaus mwiebelhaus]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/mwiebelhaus">@mwiebelhaus</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Nothing should have happened at all. I had taken all the parts out of one of my newer computers to put this inside and thats where it was running, besides the fact that I am still waiting for parts that all shipped from the same place all with the same shipping method.</p>
<p>[quote=“Lothy, post:19, topic:338250”][quote author=Mopman link=topic=434642.msg3192872#msg3192872 date=1272435291]<br>
wait… so you did something that you knew was possibly going to fry your pc and then your pc got fried and you’re angry?<br>
[/quote]<br>
Haven’t been introduced to that side of the American attitude? It’d be wrong to say that all Americans are this ridiculous, because it isn’t true.<br>
But suing people despite something being a person’s own fault isn’t new in America. Look at all of the idiot attention-seeking teenagers who can’t understand policies that their school has in place for things such as prom, who then go and try to sue the state or their school.[/quote]<br>
Obviously I’m not actually going to sue them, but there are people here that actually would which is the reason that new-egg would believe me. I’f don’t get the motherboard this week i’ll be fine. It wasn’t my fault anyway, I had reseated a ram stick in a different slot because it was running at 733MHz INSTEAD of 1800MHz which it should be running at. When I clicked the power button on the computer I see a spark on the motherboard and it shuts off, I then disconnect the power, put the ram back, and reconnect…nothing happens, fan spins up in an unusual fashion and then just sits there, nothing on screen. Unless I did something wrong, which I doubt I did because Ive built about 5 computers so far and Ive never encountered a DOA part or any problems EVER. There probably was a faulty ram slot and if anything I should be mad at the manufacturer (ASUS) not Newegg, though I didn’t not receive the shipping I paid for. Your correct when you say it isn’t new in American I see this kind of shit all the time. I wouldn’t sue over something that was under a contract I agreed to because I would lose. But when you say this isn’t new in America i’m sure and I know that this happens in other countries also.</p>
<p>Also everything was resolved all I had to do was pay for a new one and they will refund me the amount when the receive the dead one. They also gave me free FedEx overnight shipping. Newegg da best, I didn’t think it was going to go that easy.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-question-and-cpu-and-memory/338250/20">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-question-and-cpu-and-memory/338250/20</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 28 Apr 2010 09:58:42 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-338250-20</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-question-and-cpu-and-memory/338250.rss">NEW: Question and CPU and Memory</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>NEW: Question and CPU and Memory</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@lothy Lothy]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/lothy">@lothy</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote no-group quote-modified" data-post="18" data-topic="338250">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/user_avatar/forum.moparisthebest.com/mopman/40/33_1.png" class="avatar"> Mopman:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>wait… so you did something that you knew was possibly going to fry your pc and then your pc got fried and you’re angry?</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Haven’t been introduced to that side of the American attitude? It’d be wrong to say that all Americans are this ridiculous, because it isn’t true.<br>
But suing people despite something being a person’s own fault isn’t new in America. Look at all of the idiot attention-seeking teenagers who can’t understand policies that their school has in place for things such as prom, who then go and try to sue the state or their school.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-question-and-cpu-and-memory/338250/19">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-question-and-cpu-and-memory/338250/19</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 28 Apr 2010 07:54:48 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-338250-19</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-question-and-cpu-and-memory/338250.rss">NEW: Question and CPU and Memory</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>NEW: Question and CPU and Memory</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Mopman Mopman]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/mopman">@Mopman</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>wait… so you did something that you knew was possibly going to fry your pc and then your pc got fried and you’re angry?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-question-and-cpu-and-memory/338250/18">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-question-and-cpu-and-memory/338250/18</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 28 Apr 2010 06:14:51 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-338250-18</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-question-and-cpu-and-memory/338250.rss">NEW: Question and CPU and Memory</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>NEW: Question and CPU and Memory</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@lawl lawl]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/lawl">@lawl</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>lol owned</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-question-and-cpu-and-memory/338250/17">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-question-and-cpu-and-memory/338250/17</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 28 Apr 2010 03:43:45 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-338250-17</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-question-and-cpu-and-memory/338250.rss">NEW: Question and CPU and Memory</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>NEW: Question and CPU and Memory</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@mwiebelhaus mwiebelhaus]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/mwiebelhaus">@mwiebelhaus</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>It seems to be running fine now but im going to switch back to 2 cores to see if I see performance improvment because as of now I see only a medium improvement over my pentium 4 which part is that i can actually game. But stuff does seem to load faster. of course windows 7 made my pentium 4 seem alot faster maybe its because i never really ran things that required alot of processor power.</p>
<p>EDIT: Seeing as my computer went into sleep mode in prime testing last night I decided to try overclocking more! Well Ive managed to get it stable (it seems) at 3.7GHZ on all 4 Cores thats one hell of a deal for a processor which I got for 79.99. Now to test it in Prime95 before the 4 cores at 3.2GHZ was 7.3 I will see if it changes.</p>
<p>EDIT: It froze on 3.7 randomly, then I started stress testing on 3.63 and it was going good for about 10 minutes until core 3 failed I could see it happen and actually the computer ran a bit even after it failed about 10 seconds because I saw the worker stop in Prime95. Now im at 3.61 which probably fail again but I think the problem is heat because It was getting to about 60C which might not be good with all this overclocking but im buying a new heatsink soon anyways.</p>
<p>EDIT: Well im using stock and I can go to 3.52 and its stable I can say that. I have to use Asus overlocking profiles though. The Quad clocked at 3.52 gets up tp 70C (thats where I stopped because thats fucking hot and I didn’t want to ruin it) and it still runs. As soon as I stop the prime test it drops 10 degrees instantly and as I talk is running at 36C thats crazy. It goes up 34 degrees C just for the prime test. Im going to buy a new cooler soon so im just going to run it at 3.2ghz until then.</p>
<p>EDIT: My fun has ended, my motherboard some how short circuted and it is dead I hope my CPU didn’t get fried also. I really feel bad tommorow for whoever gets me on the phone from newegg because im pissed, if all of the shit would have came on schedule (I ordered it the same day and selected 3 day shipping UPS) paid about $30 for it just to see half my parts come another 3 days late) then it would have been in my case and not fucked up. Since the motherboard and CPU were in a combo deal I have to ship both back together which is sure as fuck not going to happen just to get a new motherboard because then I can’t be certain I will get another CPU that will have a 3rd and 4th core unlocked. Also on top of all of that, I want the motherboard shipped with next day shipping before I even send the other one back. If there service is lacking from what it was last time (it was good last time) then I will just threaten to sue them (even though there is no reason) but small claims court donesn’t give a fuck and it will cost more for them to send out a attorney than it will for them to just send me the parts that work. All of this is hypothetical btw because I think they will agree to my demands. I just want my plan laid out before I call up tommorow and become angry.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-question-and-cpu-and-memory/338250/16">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-question-and-cpu-and-memory/338250/16</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 27 Apr 2010 21:01:37 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-338250-16</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-question-and-cpu-and-memory/338250.rss">NEW: Question and CPU and Memory</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>NEW: Question and CPU and Memory</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Fat_Cookies Fat Cookies]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/fat_cookies">@Fat_Cookies</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Do modern AMD processors shut down when they overheat like Intel cpus do, or do they just keep going until you see smoke appearing from the top?</p>
<p>I’m not sure about the TDP of my pentium 4’s compared to your phenom II, but they run at around 55c <span class="bbcode-b">idle</span> with a big 120mm fan. At full load they push 70c.</p>
<p>ps, like Mopman said, cpus that have “hidden” cores often failed some sort of test so the manufacturer will brand it as a slower cpu. Same thing happens with clock speed; almost all components are designed to operate at the highest frequency possible, cpus that fail the test are then sold as cpus with a lower clock speed.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-question-and-cpu-and-memory/338250/15">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-question-and-cpu-and-memory/338250/15</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 27 Apr 2010 19:45:52 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-338250-15</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-question-and-cpu-and-memory/338250.rss">NEW: Question and CPU and Memory</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>NEW: Question and CPU and Memory</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@xEnt xEnt]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/xent">@xEnt</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>uh thug-life you sounds like your talking about vid card temps, which can handle a lot more than CPU. worry if your CPU gets over 70c in stress tests.</p>
<p>a long time ago my E6850 was playing COD4 and i must have not had the CPU cooler on properly or it came undone slightly, my cod4 started getting fps lag and i didnt know wtf was going on, so i checked temps and cpu was at 105c, ever since that day my cpu felt quite unstable so i got another one.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-question-and-cpu-and-memory/338250/14">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-question-and-cpu-and-memory/338250/14</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 27 Apr 2010 17:52:08 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-338250-14</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-question-and-cpu-and-memory/338250.rss">NEW: Question and CPU and Memory</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>NEW: Question and CPU and Memory</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@mwiebelhaus mwiebelhaus]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/mwiebelhaus">@mwiebelhaus</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Well right now it has been running for an hour. And nothing has happened nor has it got past 60C. So I guess I may as well stop.</p>
<p>EDIT: Well just as I thought everything was ok maybe things are not what they seem. As I was logging in I was pushing my wireless card back and forth and all of the sudden the system froze…I hard reset it and it said unleashing mode failed (unlocking 3rd or 4th core) im not sure if this was due to me rocking my wireless card back and forth and causing some kind of short or because of a bad core. Ethier way im now just going to continue running the benchmark tests until wensdeday because I want to make sure everything is ok. But the 3rd and 4th core are working now so I’m not sure what the hell happened I guess time will tell.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-question-and-cpu-and-memory/338250/13">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-question-and-cpu-and-memory/338250/13</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 26 Apr 2010 23:30:49 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-338250-13</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-question-and-cpu-and-memory/338250.rss">NEW: Question and CPU and Memory</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>NEW: Question and CPU and Memory</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@tL tL]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/tl">@tL</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>There wouldn’t really be much point, if it manages to get through an hour of it, i don’t think there is much more you could gain from leaving it running.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-question-and-cpu-and-memory/338250/12">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-question-and-cpu-and-memory/338250/12</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 26 Apr 2010 23:27:54 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-338250-12</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-question-and-cpu-and-memory/338250.rss">NEW: Question and CPU and Memory</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>NEW: Question and CPU and Memory</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@mwiebelhaus mwiebelhaus]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/mwiebelhaus">@mwiebelhaus</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Whould it hurt to leave Prime 95 on until Wednesday? My Case (CM690II) Cd drive (Asus), and Hard drive (Western Digital 500GB Caviar Black) are coming then and I won’t really be doing anything with it until then. Currently it is just the new motherboard, ram, and cpu with old harddrive, cd drive, and psu. Strung across my desk running.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-question-and-cpu-and-memory/338250/11">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-question-and-cpu-and-memory/338250/11</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 26 Apr 2010 23:22:52 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-338250-11</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-question-and-cpu-and-memory/338250.rss">NEW: Question and CPU and Memory</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>NEW: Question and CPU and Memory</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@lawl lawl]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/lawl">@lawl</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>it depends on the cpu, c2ds have a ‘max’ of 60, mines gone to 100 though</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-question-and-cpu-and-memory/338250/10">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-question-and-cpu-and-memory/338250/10</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 26 Apr 2010 23:11:32 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-338250-10</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-question-and-cpu-and-memory/338250.rss">NEW: Question and CPU and Memory</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>NEW: Question and CPU and Memory</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@tL tL]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/tl">@tL</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>It wouldn’t do any damage to it, but i didn’t know AMD put their recommendations that low. You see overclockers testing them up to 90c in a fairly regular basis. Intel say they test their CPU’s at around 110c in manufacturing, and i’ve had my i7 at 100c (unintentionally, of course) i assumed AMDs would be similar.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-question-and-cpu-and-memory/338250/9">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-question-and-cpu-and-memory/338250/9</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 26 Apr 2010 22:37:39 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-338250-9</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-question-and-cpu-and-memory/338250.rss">NEW: Question and CPU and Memory</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>NEW: Question and CPU and Memory</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Mopman Mopman]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/mopman">@Mopman</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote no-group quote-modified" data-post="6" data-topic="338250">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/thug-life/40/5_513041d5f7104045db30895d3b90af16.png" class="avatar"> Thug-life:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Don’t worry about it till it gets to around 80c</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>um, thats pretty dangerous advice, 80c is pretty hot (well above the published max, for a start) for multicore amd cpus</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-question-and-cpu-and-memory/338250/8">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-question-and-cpu-and-memory/338250/8</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 26 Apr 2010 22:32:38 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-338250-8</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-question-and-cpu-and-memory/338250.rss">NEW: Question and CPU and Memory</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>NEW: Question and CPU and Memory</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@mwiebelhaus mwiebelhaus]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/mwiebelhaus">@mwiebelhaus</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote no-group" data-post="6" data-topic="338250">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/thug-life/40/5_513041d5f7104045db30895d3b90af16.png" class="avatar"> Thug-life:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Oh 55c is perfectly fine. Don’t worry about it till it gets to around 80c, but even then, it would go up to 100c without any damage to the CPU… as long as you don’t keep it at 100c for any long periods of time.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Sounds good. Currently it is oscillating between 57 and 59 and hasn’t gone above 60 so Im not worried anymore.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-question-and-cpu-and-memory/338250/7">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-question-and-cpu-and-memory/338250/7</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 26 Apr 2010 22:30:24 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-338250-7</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-question-and-cpu-and-memory/338250.rss">NEW: Question and CPU and Memory</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>NEW: Question and CPU and Memory</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@tL tL]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/tl">@tL</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Oh 55c is perfectly fine. Don’t worry about it till it gets to around 80c, but even then, it would go up to 100c without any damage to the CPU… as long as you don’t keep it at 100c for any long periods of time.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-question-and-cpu-and-memory/338250/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-question-and-cpu-and-memory/338250/6</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 26 Apr 2010 22:26:45 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-338250-6</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-question-and-cpu-and-memory/338250.rss">NEW: Question and CPU and Memory</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>NEW: Question and CPU and Memory</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@mwiebelhaus mwiebelhaus]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/mwiebelhaus">@mwiebelhaus</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote no-group" data-post="4" data-topic="338250">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/thug-life/40/5_513041d5f7104045db30895d3b90af16.png" class="avatar"> Thug-life:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Run prime95 for an hour or so on small FFTs. Makes sure to watch the temperatures though.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Ok I have SpeedFan controlling the fan and watching the temperatures I started the test now with 4 threads do you think that is enough?</p>
<p>EDIT wow these things run hot. I have fan speed on max and another fan supplementing. Its about 55C when should I start getting worried?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-question-and-cpu-and-memory/338250/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-question-and-cpu-and-memory/338250/5</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 26 Apr 2010 22:08:02 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-338250-5</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-question-and-cpu-and-memory/338250.rss">NEW: Question and CPU and Memory</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>NEW: Question and CPU and Memory</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@tL tL]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/tl">@tL</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Run prime95 for an hour or so on small FFTs. Makes sure to watch the temperatures though.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-question-and-cpu-and-memory/338250/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-question-and-cpu-and-memory/338250/4</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 26 Apr 2010 21:56:40 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-338250-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-question-and-cpu-and-memory/338250.rss">NEW: Question and CPU and Memory</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>NEW: Question and CPU and Memory</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@mwiebelhaus mwiebelhaus]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/mwiebelhaus">@mwiebelhaus</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“Mopman, post:2, topic:338250”]nobody can tell you, they’re sold like that because they thought something was wrong with them, but you never know what showed up on the QA that led them to believe this</p>
<p>you’ll find out, i guess <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=5" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"> run a burn in test maybe[/quote]</p>
<p>How would I go about doing this? Is this like Prime testing? Ethier way I won’t be unhappy going back to a 2 Core Setup because its quick enough for me but having 4 cores is nice.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-question-and-cpu-and-memory/338250/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-question-and-cpu-and-memory/338250/3</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 26 Apr 2010 21:34:51 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-338250-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-question-and-cpu-and-memory/338250.rss">NEW: Question and CPU and Memory</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>NEW: Question and CPU and Memory</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Mopman Mopman]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/mopman">@Mopman</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>nobody can tell you, they’re sold like that because they thought something was wrong with them, but you never know what showed up on the QA that led them to believe this</p>
<p>you’ll find out, i guess <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=5" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"> run a burn in test maybe</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-question-and-cpu-and-memory/338250/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-question-and-cpu-and-memory/338250/2</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 26 Apr 2010 21:32:07 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-338250-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-question-and-cpu-and-memory/338250.rss">NEW: Question and CPU and Memory</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>NEW: Question and CPU and Memory</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@mwiebelhaus mwiebelhaus]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/mwiebelhaus">@mwiebelhaus</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p><span class="bbcode-b">New: Well as you may or may have not know my motherboard fucked up a couple days ago and I had to send in a new motherboard because thats what I though was broke because the board wouldn’t post. Ok so now Im getting nervous and starting to think that the cpu might have got fried or the memory fucked up If there was a spark on the motherboard while the computer was running and it shut off, would it be the motherboard that fucked up or the cpu/memoy?</span></p>
<p>OLD :Well I just hooked up my new setup which includeds the processor listed in the title. It is dual core by default but you have about a 30% chance of unlocking a 3rd or 4th core. Well I seem to be one of these lucky people who paid for a dual core and got a quad core. One question though. I unlocked the 4th core  through the BIOS and it runs fine (ive been running it for about an hour no problems) does this mean im good from now on to forever or will I experience problems with the 4th core unlocked possibly. It seems performance is different. Is it plain and simply that it ethier does or does not work or can you have it unlocked experiencing performance differences. Or am I just a little crazy because I can’t believe I got the two cores unlocked?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-question-and-cpu-and-memory/338250/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-question-and-cpu-and-memory/338250/1</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 26 Apr 2010 21:15:04 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-338250-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-question-and-cpu-and-memory/338250.rss">NEW: Question and CPU and Memory</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
