<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>MoparCraft merge</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/moparcraft-merge/519301</link>
    <description>There was recently a topic in the MSCP staff board discussing the potential for MCRFT to be merged back into MoparScape, I wanted to get the staff&#39;s opinion on this and whether they think it would be beneficial or not. I&#39;ve posted my views below, please remember that we don&#39;t currently have any specifics such as a reworked board layout and I can&#39;t answer questions such as what happens with the status page, this is merely to get your thoughts on the surface of the idea, perhaps even so staff can suggest a board layout.

[quote=&quot;Tom, post:8, topic:519236&quot;]I&#39;m not going to refute the idea on sight, even though I&#39;ve spent huge amounts of time on MoparCraft over the past 2 years, and even contributed money out of my own pocket to ensure the construction of a separate community. The idea of a separate community for MineCraft a few years back was a good idea, but unfortunately along the way things took longer and longer to get done, to a point where we probably have 1/5 of the active traffic we used to. If anything, MoparCraft is nothing more than another missed opportunity for the site as a whole. 

MoparCraft still has a reasonably active userbase though:

http://www.moparcraft.net/smf/index.php/topic,635860.0.html

So it&#39;s important the forum if it were to be ported here isn&#39;t devalued, and compressed too much, as it certainly wouldn&#39;t make me happy as an active member of the community to loose a significant amount of what the site used to be. I&#39;ve brought the matter up with the staff who are active on the IRC, and will quote my post on this in the MoparCraft staff section just to get the thoughts of those who are most active on the site. 

There are still a lot of issues beyond just moving the forum here as well. For example, the Server status page, the hostnames connected to the servers, the staff structure and so on. This is all assuming a full port would be made, obviously right now such an idea is in early days so a full port might not even be the case. I do think bringing MoparCraft back to MoparScape would generate more traffic for both sides at this stage. I&#39;ll be on the IRC if you want to talk in detail about this, Taharok.[/quote]

This is by no means something that must be complied with, and is nothing more than a brainstorm as it stands.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 15 May 2013 12:55:23 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Games</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/moparcraft-merge/519301.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>MoparCraft merge</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Phaze_One Fuscate]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/phaze_one">@Phaze_One</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>As I expressed on irc, I am all for the merge. The potential for traffic onto here and on the vanilla server is quite large should it happen. However, that being said I believe with a merge we may need to structure the rules slightly differently (mainly regarding the ftb server, how we will base whitelist applications and the such).</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/moparcraft-merge/519301/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/moparcraft-merge/519301/4</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2013 12:55:23 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-519301-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/moparcraft-merge/519301.rss">MoparCraft merge</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>MoparCraft merge</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@kickingjamie kickingjamie]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/kickingjamie">@kickingjamie</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Like Si force said, as long as structure remains and we have a level of control over the idiots that reside on the moparscape community I think it will be a good change. I don’t want the high level of trolls being a pain in the ass on the feed the beast server as right now we have no bukkit plugins to control things. I also think that if we do merge with Moparscape there should be a place(section) to apply for the feed the beast white-list as it without a doubt will probably draw the most interest from people over there.</p>
<p>On the other hand it seems a little unusual having a minecraft area on a forum based around Runescape hacking, private servers and so on.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/moparcraft-merge/519301/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/moparcraft-merge/519301/3</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2013 11:13:24 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-519301-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/moparcraft-merge/519301.rss">MoparCraft merge</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>MoparCraft merge</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@si_force Si Force]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/si_force">@si_force</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I think that as long as we keep our identity (staff structure, important boards and awards, etc) then I’ll have no problem with it. It’s a step in the right direction in terms of generating new activity, renewing old interest, etc.</p>
<p>I’m sure we’ll benefit from this.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/moparcraft-merge/519301/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/moparcraft-merge/519301/2</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2013 10:52:12 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-519301-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/moparcraft-merge/519301.rss">MoparCraft merge</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>MoparCraft merge</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Tom Tom]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/tom">@Tom</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>There was recently a topic in the MSCP staff board discussing the potential for MCRFT to be merged back into MoparScape, I wanted to get the staff’s opinion on this and whether they think it would be beneficial or not. I’ve posted my views below, please remember that we don’t currently have any specifics such as a reworked board layout and I can’t answer questions such as what happens with the status page, this is merely to get your thoughts on the surface of the idea, perhaps even so staff can suggest a board layout.</p>
<p>[quote=“Tom, post:8, topic:519236”]I’m not going to refute the idea on sight, even though I’ve spent huge amounts of time on MoparCraft over the past 2 years, and even contributed money out of my own pocket to ensure the construction of a separate community. The idea of a separate community for MineCraft a few years back was a good idea, but unfortunately along the way things took longer and longer to get done, to a point where we probably have 1/5 of the active traffic we used to. If anything, MoparCraft is nothing more than another missed opportunity for the site as a whole.</p>
<p>MoparCraft still has a reasonably active userbase though:</p>
<p><a href="http://www.moparcraft.net/smf/index.php/topic,635860.0.html" class="onebox" target="_blank">http://www.moparcraft.net/smf/index.php/topic,635860.0.html</a></p>
<p>So it’s important the forum if it were to be ported here isn’t devalued, and compressed too much, as it certainly wouldn’t make me happy as an active member of the community to loose a significant amount of what the site used to be. I’ve brought the matter up with the staff who are active on the IRC, and will quote my post on this in the MoparCraft staff section just to get the thoughts of those who are most active on the site.</p>
<p>There are still a lot of issues beyond just moving the forum here as well. For example, the Server status page, the hostnames connected to the servers, the staff structure and so on. This is all assuming a full port would be made, obviously right now such an idea is in early days so a full port might not even be the case. I do think bringing MoparCraft back to MoparScape would generate more traffic for both sides at this stage. I’ll be on the IRC if you want to talk in detail about this, Taharok.[/quote]</p>
<p>This is by no means something that must be complied with, and is nothing more than a brainstorm as it stands.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/moparcraft-merge/519301/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/moparcraft-merge/519301/1</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2013 09:58:33 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-519301-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/moparcraft-merge/519301.rss">MoparCraft merge</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
