<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>[C++] Pointers</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/c-pointers/37488</link>
    <description>[b]Introduction[/b]
We don&#39;t have many C++ programmers in the community, which I find quite strange since a large portion of us use Java and the syntax is very similar. I realise it is perhaps less useful than Java for Runescape cheating (since it can&#39;t as easily be used for client hacks) but it definately has its place when coding private servers, clickers and all the non-rs applications we seem to have expanded to. I think even people who know quite a bit of Java are a bit wary of giving C++ a go due to various myths that float about regarding it&#39;s problems - most of which are based in fact, but are nothing you have to worry about yet. :)

Anyway, I&#39;m going to be writing a few posts/tutorials on the aspects of C++ that I think scare away new programmers the most, in an attempt to get more people interested. This is Pointers, I&#39;m going to do a quick run-through of the STL at some point as well as some basic stuff on Memory Management and writing portable code. I&#39;m no expert by the way, just another hobbyist who found C++ a bastard to learn and is bored enough today to try and relieve that pain for other people. ;)

[b]Declaring a Pointer[/b]
Okiedokie, so what is a pointer? Think about your computer&#39;s memory as a large jumble of random information with no real structure or form (because it is). When you declare a variable, you are setting aside enough space to hold whatever you&#39;ve said you&#39;re putting in it (1 byte if it&#39;s a char, for example) and giving that space a name so you can refer to it later. In addition to this, each byte of memory has an address, which the operating system can use to refer to a certain part of memory. The addresses are successive, that is, if you goto byte 1057, you find byte 1058 after it and 1059 after that.

A pointer is a type of variable which holds the address where something is stored, rather than referring to the &quot;something&quot; itself. It points to something in memory. Hence the name. :p

We declare a pointer like any other variable, but preceded with the * sign. For example:

[code]
int *anIntPointer;
char *aCharPointer;
[/code]

Note: Even though we are just pointing to a space in memory, we still need to have a type (Int/Char/Etc.). This is the type of the data we are going to point to.

[b]Referencing and Dereferencing[/b]
To reference a pointer simply means to get the address of a variable we have created. You have already seen the operator used to do this if you have played with C and used scanf, but if not don&#39;t worry. It&#39;s the &amp; sign.

Using it is very simple:

[code]
int yearOfBirth;
int *aPointer;

yearOfBirth = 1988;
aPointer = &amp;yearOfBirth;
[/code]

At the end of this code, &quot;yearOfBirth&quot; would of course contain 1988. &quot;aPointer&quot; would contain the memory address yearOfBirth was stored in.

Dereferencing means to take a pointer, and get the data stored at that location. So if we had a pointer named thePointer, which we knew pointed to an int representing a year but didn&#39;t know what the year was, we could do:

[code]
int mysteryYear;

mysteryYear = *thePointer;
[/code]

The * is the dereference operator, the opposite of the &amp; if you like. It means &quot;the value pointed to by thePointer&quot;.

[b]Pointer Arithmetic[/b]
Performing arithmetic on pointers is slightly different than on normal variables. If your aim is just to add/subtract/whatever the values the variable points to, then this isn&#39;t the section. You want to look at dereferencing again :) The main thing to bear in mind when adding and subtracting pointers is the size of the data type you are working with. Say we have a pointer to a char, called myCharPointer, and this pointed at the memory address 1500. If we were to do myCharPointer++ (add 1 to it), this would now point to the memory address 1501 - just as you would expect. However, if we have another pointer, which points to a long integer value in memory address 2500 and we do myLongPointer++, we are now pointing to 2504. Why? Because a long is 4 bytes. Rather than moving along one memory &quot;block&quot;, we are moving along one long - 4 bytes.

[b]Special Pointers[/b]
There are a few types of pointers that take on slightly unusual behaviour, that it pays to know about before they crop up and leave you feeling confused. Firstly, null pointers and void pointers. A null pointer is an &quot;empty&quot; pointer - it points nowhere. It is created by assigning 0 (int *nullPointer = 0;). A void pointer is a pointer without a type - it points to a space in memory, but gives no indication of the length of the data it points to. This allows a void pointer to point to anything, but at the cost that dereferencing it becomes harder as you have no type to work with. I will post a code snippet for doing this if anyone cares or you can google &quot;void pointers&quot;, this post is getting rather long already.

A pointer can also point to another pointer, which in turn points to some data. We use two * signs to denote this. For example:

[code]
char aVar;
char *aPointer;
char **aPointerPointer;

aVar = &#39;X&#39;;
aPointer = &amp;aVar;
aPointerPointer = &amp;aPointer;
[/code]

After running this, aPointerPointer would contain the address of a space in memory which holds the address of aVar. A bit of a brain twister. :/

[b]So what&#39;s it good for?[/b]
At first glance, not a lot! Pointers are one of the things that many newcomers to the language don&#39;t think hold much weight and so don&#39;t look into them much - then run into trouble when they need to use them.

I tried desperately to think of an idea for a fun example covering everything above and couldn&#39;t - so I thought I&#39;d include a snippet of function pointers, since I didn&#39;t explain those yet... haha.

[code]
#include &lt;iostream&gt;

using namespace std;

int addition (int a, int b)
{ 
	return (a + b);
}

int subtraction (int a, int b)
{
	return (a - b); 
}

int operation (int x, int y, int (*functocall)(int,int))
{
  int answer;
  answer = (*functocall)(x,y);
  return (answer);
}

int (*minus)(int,int) = subtraction;

int main ()
{
  int m, n;
  m = operation (7, 5, addition); // add 7 and 5
  n = operation (20, m, minus); // subtact m [12] from 20
  cout &lt;&lt; n &lt;&lt; endl;
  return 0;
}
[/code]

To anyone who has read a lot of C++ tutorials - yes, that example is shamelessly adapted (read: stolen) from cplusplus.com. The cool bit is the call to operation() - notice we are passing the name of the function we want to call as an argument, then using a pointer (functocall) to call it. If we wanted we could modify this example to take two numbers from the user and the name of the function they wish to pass the numbers to.

The other use of function pointers in this example is the &quot;int (*minus)...&quot; line. In this line we are creating a pointer called minus that points to the function subtraction(). Later on, we go to call &quot;minus()&quot;. You can think of this as like an alias - minus(5, 3) and subtraction(5, 3) would now give the same result.

That was quite possibly the quickest flyby of pointers I could have done and if you don&#39;t know any C++ at all you gave up ages ago or are now sitting here thinking &quot;what the shit?&quot;. If you don&#39;t get something, feel free to post a question in this thread, I have a very boring day ahead of me and will relish the oppurtunity to fill it with answering a question for 5 minutes :(</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2007 12:33:04 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>General Programming</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/c-pointers/37488.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>[C++] Pointers</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@YourDistracted YourDistracted]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/yourdistracted">@YourDistracted</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Im starting to learn to code teh C++. This was useful.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/c-pointers/37488/12">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/c-pointers/37488/12</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2007 12:33:04 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-37488-12</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/c-pointers/37488.rss">[C++] Pointers</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[C++] Pointers</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Mopman Mopman]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/mopman">@Mopman</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“wL, post:10, topic:37488”][quote author=Mopman link=topic=53098.msg676039#msg676039 date=1166951227]</p>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p>Im going to be covering DMA […]</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Now you’re going to tell us about driver coding? Seriously, thats the last thing I would have expected here :eek:</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Leik, dynamic memory allocation, not direct memory access.</p>
<p>Now stop trying to discredit me and go back to being “contributing” members of the community.<br>
[/quote]<br>
Hey, I wasn’t discreditising you, that was meant seriously. That just jumped into my mind when i saw the term DMA (which brought up old memories of times when we programmed the hardware directly). That was actually the reason for me to open this thread.<br>
After all dynamic memory allocation isn’t that special to have an abbreviation tributed to it, i mean c/c++,pascal,… guys just do it – and to be honest, i never heard that term in conjunction with this before.<br>
Anyway, direct memory access is much more fun :)[/quote]</p>
<p>Hehe, I shouldn’t drink and mopar.</p>
<p>The abbreviation DMA is used quite a bit in the game trainers world because of the need to employ special techniques when a game is using it… I suppose it’s easier to say “this game is DMA”.</p>
<p>Direct Memory Access just screams of blue screens and f-bombs to me - fun, but my resting heart rate is high enough already if we’re honest <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=6" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/c-pointers/37488/11">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/c-pointers/37488/11</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2007 18:20:56 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-37488-11</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/c-pointers/37488.rss">[C++] Pointers</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[C++] Pointers</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@wL1 wL]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/wl1">@wL1</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“Mopman, post:7, topic:37488”][quote author=wL link=topic=53098.msg674990#msg674990 date=1166926171]</p>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p>Im going to be covering DMA […]</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Now you’re going to tell us about driver coding? Seriously, thats the last thing I would have expected here :eek:</p>
<p>[/quote]</p>
<p>Leik, dynamic memory allocation, not direct memory access.</p>
<p>Now stop trying to discredit me and go back to being “contributing” members of the community.[/quote]<br>
Hey, I wasn’t discreditising you, that was meant seriously. That just jumped into my mind when i saw the term DMA (which brought up old memories of times when we programmed the hardware directly). That was actually the reason for me to open this thread.<br>
After all dynamic memory allocation isn’t that special to have an abbreviation tributed to it, i mean c/c++,pascal,… guys just do it – and to be honest, i never heard that term in conjunction with this before.<br>
Anyway, direct memory access is much more fun <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=6" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/c-pointers/37488/10">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/c-pointers/37488/10</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2007 17:27:28 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-37488-10</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/c-pointers/37488.rss">[C++] Pointers</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[C++] Pointers</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@sicarius99 sicarius99]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/sicarius99">@sicarius99</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>yeah nice points and like someone said previously i just dont post about c++ to much…i dont post much at all</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/c-pointers/37488/9">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/c-pointers/37488/9</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 04 Jan 2007 07:38:52 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-37488-9</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/c-pointers/37488.rss">[C++] Pointers</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[C++] Pointers</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Pwnd Pwnd]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/pwnd">@Pwnd</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“lawl, post:1, topic:39131”]lerl i posted about pointers on pwnd’s site, I KEN CODE CPP[/quote]You didn’t discuss DMA either <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=6" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/c-pointers/37488/8">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/c-pointers/37488/8</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 03 Jan 2007 16:14:33 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-37488-8</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/c-pointers/37488.rss">[C++] Pointers</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[C++] Pointers</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Mopman Mopman]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/mopman">@Mopman</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“wL, post:6, topic:37488”][quote author=Mopman link=topic=53098.msg656199#msg656199 date=1166661804]<br>
Im going to be covering DMA […]<br>
[/quote]<br>
Now you’re going to tell us about driver coding? Seriously, thats the last thing I would have expected here :eek:[/quote]</p>
<p>Leik, dynamic memory allocation, not direct memory access.</p>
<p>Now stop trying to discredit me and go back to being “contributing” members of the community.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/c-pointers/37488/7">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/c-pointers/37488/7</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 24 Dec 2006 09:07:07 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-37488-7</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/c-pointers/37488.rss">[C++] Pointers</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[C++] Pointers</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@wL1 wL]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/wl1">@wL1</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote no-group quote-modified" data-post="5" data-topic="37488">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/user_avatar/forum.moparisthebest.com/mopman/40/33_2.png" class="avatar"> Mopman:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Im going to be covering DMA […]</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Now you’re going to tell us about driver coding? Seriously, thats the last thing I would have expected here :eek:</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/c-pointers/37488/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/c-pointers/37488/6</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 24 Dec 2006 02:09:31 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-37488-6</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/c-pointers/37488.rss">[C++] Pointers</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[C++] Pointers</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Mopman Mopman]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/mopman">@Mopman</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Im going to be covering DMA when I decide to get off my arse and say a bit about memory management (which is another “C++ suckzz!!” topic, I constantly hear people say memory management is one reason they use Java over C++) - I couldn’t really work out how to break it up, I wanted to expand on a lot of the stuff I quickly glossed over here too but couldn’t work out how to keep it concise - not really a writer. <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=6" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
<p>EDIT: I can see now that “What is it good for” was a stupid name for that heading.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/c-pointers/37488/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/c-pointers/37488/5</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Dec 2006 00:43:24 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-37488-5</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/c-pointers/37488.rss">[C++] Pointers</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[C++] Pointers</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@byte byte]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/byte">@byte</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I think it’s great that more people are getting involved in C and I congratulate you for doing so. However, I do find it weird that in a tutorial about pointers you didn’t mention dynamic memory allocation. That is the reason why you would use pointers in real world applications. It’s fine and dandy to learn how an int* type points to an int somewhere else in memory, but no useful code can come from it.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/c-pointers/37488/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/c-pointers/37488/4</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Dec 2006 00:38:53 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-37488-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/c-pointers/37488.rss">[C++] Pointers</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[C++] Pointers</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Zach1188 Zach1188]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/zach1188">@Zach1188</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>You rock, I finally understand pointers for the first time since I started learning C++.</p>
<p>And you’re right. It is pretty weird that we don’t have many C++ programmers here, I wish we had more.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/c-pointers/37488/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/c-pointers/37488/3</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 20 Dec 2006 23:09:21 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-37488-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/c-pointers/37488.rss">[C++] Pointers</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[C++] Pointers</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Tree Tree]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/tree">@Tree</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>dis rely helped me plz give dis guy da first togepi…</p>
<p>he told me to say it…</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/c-pointers/37488/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/c-pointers/37488/2</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 20 Dec 2006 22:33:18 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-37488-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/c-pointers/37488.rss">[C++] Pointers</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[C++] Pointers</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Mopman Mopman]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/mopman">@Mopman</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p><span class="bbcode-b">Introduction</span><br>
We don’t have many C++ programmers in the community, which I find quite strange since a large portion of us use Java and the syntax is very similar. I realise it is perhaps less useful than Java for Runescape cheating (since it can’t as easily be used for client hacks) but it definately has its place when coding private servers, clickers and all the non-rs applications we seem to have expanded to. I think even people who know quite a bit of Java are a bit wary of giving C++ a go due to various myths that float about regarding it’s problems - most of which are based in fact, but are nothing you have to worry about yet. <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=6" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
<p>Anyway, I’m going to be writing a few posts/tutorials on the aspects of C++ that I think scare away new programmers the most, in an attempt to get more people interested. This is Pointers, I’m going to do a quick run-through of the STL at some point as well as some basic stuff on Memory Management and writing portable code. I’m no expert by the way, just another hobbyist who found C++ a bastard to learn and is bored enough today to try and relieve that pain for other people. <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/wink.png?v=6" title=":wink:" class="emoji" alt=":wink:"></p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Declaring a Pointer</span><br>
Okiedokie, so what is a pointer? Think about your computer’s memory as a large jumble of random information with no real structure or form (because it is). When you declare a variable, you are setting aside enough space to hold whatever you’ve said you’re putting in it (1 byte if it’s a char, for example) and giving that space a name so you can refer to it later. In addition to this, each byte of memory has an address, which the operating system can use to refer to a certain part of memory. The addresses are successive, that is, if you goto byte 1057, you find byte 1058 after it and 1059 after that.</p>
<p>A pointer is a type of variable which holds the address where something is stored, rather than referring to the “something” itself. It points to something in memory. Hence the name. <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=6" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"></p>
<p>We declare a pointer like any other variable, but preceded with the * sign. For example:</p>
<pre><code class="lang-auto">int *anIntPointer;
char *aCharPointer;</code></pre>
<p>Note: Even though we are just pointing to a space in memory, we still need to have a type (Int/Char/Etc.). This is the type of the data we are going to point to.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Referencing and Dereferencing</span><br>
To reference a pointer simply means to get the address of a variable we have created. You have already seen the operator used to do this if you have played with C and used scanf, but if not don’t worry. It’s the &amp; sign.</p>
<p>Using it is very simple:</p>
<pre><code class="lang-auto">int yearOfBirth;
int *aPointer;

yearOfBirth = 1988;
aPointer = &amp;yearOfBirth;</code></pre>
<p>At the end of this code, “yearOfBirth” would of course contain 1988. “aPointer” would contain the memory address yearOfBirth was stored in.</p>
<p>Dereferencing means to take a pointer, and get the data stored at that location. So if we had a pointer named thePointer, which we knew pointed to an int representing a year but didn’t know what the year was, we could do:</p>
<pre><code class="lang-auto">int mysteryYear;

mysteryYear = *thePointer;</code></pre>
<p>The * is the dereference operator, the opposite of the &amp; if you like. It means “the value pointed to by thePointer”.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Pointer Arithmetic</span><br>
Performing arithmetic on pointers is slightly different than on normal variables. If your aim is just to add/subtract/whatever the values the variable points to, then this isn’t the section. You want to look at dereferencing again <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=6" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"> The main thing to bear in mind when adding and subtracting pointers is the size of the data type you are working with. Say we have a pointer to a char, called myCharPointer, and this pointed at the memory address 1500. If we were to do myCharPointer++ (add 1 to it), this would now point to the memory address 1501 - just as you would expect. However, if we have another pointer, which points to a long integer value in memory address 2500 and we do myLongPointer++, we are now pointing to 2504. Why? Because a long is 4 bytes. Rather than moving along one memory “block”, we are moving along one long - 4 bytes.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Special Pointers</span><br>
There are a few types of pointers that take on slightly unusual behaviour, that it pays to know about before they crop up and leave you feeling confused. Firstly, null pointers and void pointers. A null pointer is an “empty” pointer - it points nowhere. It is created by assigning 0 (int *nullPointer = 0;). A void pointer is a pointer without a type - it points to a space in memory, but gives no indication of the length of the data it points to. This allows a void pointer to point to anything, but at the cost that dereferencing it becomes harder as you have no type to work with. I will post a code snippet for doing this if anyone cares or you can google “void pointers”, this post is getting rather long already.</p>
<p>A pointer can also point to another pointer, which in turn points to some data. We use two * signs to denote this. For example:</p>
<pre><code class="lang-auto">char aVar;
char *aPointer;
char **aPointerPointer;

aVar = 'X';
aPointer = &amp;aVar;
aPointerPointer = &amp;aPointer;</code></pre>
<p>After running this, aPointerPointer would contain the address of a space in memory which holds the address of aVar. A bit of a brain twister. <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/confused.png?v=6" title=":confused:" class="emoji" alt=":confused:"></p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">So what’s it good for?</span><br>
At first glance, not a lot! Pointers are one of the things that many newcomers to the language don’t think hold much weight and so don’t look into them much - then run into trouble when they need to use them.</p>
<p>I tried desperately to think of an idea for a fun example covering everything above and couldn’t - so I thought I’d include a snippet of function pointers, since I didn’t explain those yet… haha.</p>
<pre><code class="lang-auto">#include &lt;iostream&gt;

using namespace std;

int addition (int a, int b)
{ 
	return (a + b);
}

int subtraction (int a, int b)
{
	return (a - b); 
}

int operation (int x, int y, int (*functocall)(int,int))
{
  int answer;
  answer = (*functocall)(x,y);
  return (answer);
}

int (*minus)(int,int) = subtraction;

int main ()
{
  int m, n;
  m = operation (7, 5, addition); // add 7 and 5
  n = operation (20, m, minus); // subtact m [12] from 20
  cout &lt;&lt; n &lt;&lt; endl;
  return 0;
}</code></pre>
<p>To anyone who has read a lot of C++ tutorials - yes, that example is shamelessly adapted (read: stolen) from <a href="http://cplusplus.com" rel="nofollow noopener">cplusplus.com</a>. The cool bit is the call to operation() - notice we are passing the name of the function we want to call as an argument, then using a pointer (functocall) to call it. If we wanted we could modify this example to take two numbers from the user and the name of the function they wish to pass the numbers to.</p>
<p>The other use of function pointers in this example is the “int (*minus)…” line. In this line we are creating a pointer called minus that points to the function subtraction(). Later on, we go to call “minus()”. You can think of this as like an alias - minus(5, 3) and subtraction(5, 3) would now give the same result.</p>
<p>That was quite possibly the quickest flyby of pointers I could have done and if you don’t know any C++ at all you gave up ages ago or are now sitting here thinking “what the shit?”. If you don’t get something, feel free to post a question in this thread, I have a very boring day ahead of me and will relish the oppurtunity to fill it with answering a question for 5 minutes <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/frowning.png?v=6" title=":frowning:" class="emoji" alt=":frowning:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/c-pointers/37488/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/c-pointers/37488/1</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 20 Dec 2006 20:01:25 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-37488-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/c-pointers/37488.rss">[C++] Pointers</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
