<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Long time no see Hisotyr =\</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/long-time-no-see-hisotyr/2883</link>
    <description>1: Native Americans passed down their traditions from generation to generation through
barter
oral history
written records
trade routes

2: Spain decided to back Columbus&#39; voyage to the west in the hopes that it would
help to finally defeat the Muslims
make Columbus rich and famous
give Spain a trading advantage over Portugal
bring an end to feudalism in Europe

3: Which of the following best describes the Northwest Passage?
John Cabot&#39;s sailing across the Atlantic Ocean from England
Ferdinand Magellan&#39;s circumnavigating the globe
water route across North America
the Puritan&#39;s route from England to Massachusetts

4: English explorers like Cabot, Frobisher, and Hudson were searching for
the seven golden cities
the Great Migration
a Northwest Passage
a land route to California

5: The Virginia colony survived largely because the English colonists
were well cared for by the Virginia Company
developed lasting friendships with Native Americans
worked cooperatively for the good of the colony
began growing tobacco for sale

6: The Puritans migrated to New England to
escape religious persecution
establish Catholic missions
maintain the practices of the Anglican Church
start tobacco plantations

7: England prized its North American colonies because
they provided England with natural resources of gold and silver
they provided soldiers for the British Army to fight in European wars
they supplied England with food and raw materials and bought English goods
they manufactured goods for England

8: In colonial South Carolina and Georgia, most slaves worked
in cities
on fishing ships
in factories
on plantations

9: Which of the following caused Jamestown&#39;s near failure?
the discovery of gold and silver in the colony
John Smith&#39;s leadership
the failure of the tobacco crop
the swampy site chosen for this settlement

10: In what part of North America did the Hopi and Zuni develop their way of life?
Southwest
Northeast
Plains
Northwest Coast

11: An example of an uprising by slaves to free themselves in the mid-1700s is the
Great Awakening
Stono Rebellion
Middle Passage
Great Migration

12: Which of the following was a driving force in Puritan settlements?
a love of luxury and wealth
a desire to live free of religious persecution
a passion for social order
a desire to return to England

13: The population of the Middle Colonies was known for its
lack of farming skills
hatred of the other colonies
diversity
lack of religion

14: As a result of the French and Indian War,
Native Americans gained control of the Great Lakes region
Britain lost control of lands east of the Mississippi River
France turned Canada over to Britain
France gained control of Florida

15: The Sugar Act and Stamp Act are examples of how the
British continued to leave the colonies alone
British tried to raise money in the colonies
colonists eagerly sacraficed to pay their war debts
British tried to stimulate colonial economies

16: The Revolutionary War began with the
Battle of Saratoga
Battle of Trenton
Bettles of Lexington and Concord
Battle of Bunker Hill

17: What was a major advantage of the American side in the Revolutionary War?
Patriot forces were fighting on their own territory
British forces were not well equipped
Americans had a well-supplied, stable, and effective fighting force
The British people strongly supported their forces fighting in the colonies

18: American victory in the Revolutionary War led to
expanded political and legal power for women
the abolition of slavery in the Southern Colonies
the strengthening of the Iroquois League
the spread of the idea of liberty at home and abroad

19: In the 1780s, the Nationalists organized to
create a unicameral legislature
strengthen the power of the states
promote the need for a stronger central government
fight against taxation

20: What issue did the Great Compromise resolve?
representation in the legislature
abolition of slavery
the veto power of the executive
when taxes were to be paid

21: The anti-Federalists argued against the Constitution because they felt
it gave too much power to the people
it created a weak executive branch
it made the national government too strong
the Articles of Confederation did not need to be reformed

22: Some anti-Federalists agreed to support the Constitution after the Federalists added the
separation of powers
Bill of Rights
Preamble
system of checks and balances

23: During his term in office, President Washington worked to develop a tone
that was dictatorial
that was nonthreatening
of modesty
of dignity

24: Why was Jefferson not named President after he won the popular vote in 1800?
John Adams had more Electoral College votes
Aaron Burr had more Electoral College votes
Congress refused to agree to Jefferson&#39;s election
Jefferson did not have any Electoral College votes

25: Which of the following occurred during the War of 1812?
Tecumseh&#39;s warriors won the Battle of Tippecanoe
The British navy lost many sea batles
British troops set fire to Washington DC
Unites States forces captured Canada

26: Which was a provision of the Missouri Compromise of 1820?
Missouri and Maine were denied statehood
States north of 36o 30 &#39; N latitude would be free states
Slavery could not spread into any western lands
Free states could never outnumber slave states

27: The First Continental Congress voted to
end the boycott of imports from Britain
call for the formation of colonial militias
imprison all British tax collectors
adopt the Declaration of Independence

28: The Three-Fifths Compromise resolved the issue of
how enslaved people were to be counted in the population
whether the larger states could have more representatives in Congress
whether Congress would have one or two houses
how many representatives each state would have in he Senate

29: Which of the following was designed to ensure that one branch of government would never become too powerful?
the Electoral College
the Cabinet
the Bill of Rights
the system of checks and balances

30: One purpose of the Lewis and Clark expedition was to
explore the lands of the Louisiana Purchase
gain control over the Native Americans living west of the Mississippi
drive the Spanish out of the lands of the Southwest
drive the French out of fur trading forts along the Mississippi

31: Why did many colonists oppose the Stamp Act?
The act enabled the British to censor all written materials in the colonies
The act threatened to disrupt trading patterns with overseas markets
The act increased the cost of British imports
The act taxed the colonists without their consent

32: Delegates to the Constitutional Convention were initially supposed to
throw out the Articles of Confederation and start all over
write new constitutions for the states they represented
amend the Articles of Confederation
determine whether slavery would be allowed to continue

33: Which one of the following was a major accomplishment of the Jefferson administration?
increasing the size of the army
destroying the Bank of the United States
the Louisiana Purchase
driving the British out of Canada

34: In the Adams-Onis Treaty of 1819,
the United States doubled its size
the Cherokees settled their dispute with the American government
Spain ceded Florida to the United States
the United States gained the right to build the Erie Canal

35: How did Native American migration differ from that of white Americans in the early 1800s?
Most Native Americans migrated after being forced from their land
Most Native Americans migrated south instead of west
Most Native Americans migrated to reclaim their homelands, not to explore
Most Native Americans migrated to cities along the Atlantic Coast

36: What was one important efect of the invenetion of the cotton gin in 1793?
Thousands of southern plantation owners went bankrupt
The demand for slave labor increased
Laws called black codes were passed
Migration from the South to undeveloped lands in the West declined

37: Steam power and canal building wer important because they
allowed farmers to ship their goods to markets around the country
caused a decline in the demand for slave labor
discouraged the settlement of western regions
increased the cost of transportation and communication

38: The South in the early 1800s was
crowded and bustling
mainly rural
an area of high population density
predominantly an industrial society

39: After the importation of slaves to the United States was banned,
the number of enslaved people shrunk by one half
the slave trade continued within the United States
slavery grew faster in the North than in the South
Virginia outlawed slavery

40: Which was a result of industralization in the United States?
a decrease in available jobs
a sharp decline in poverty
an increase in women in factory jobs
the growth of cities

41: All abolitionists agreed about
the importance of women&#39;s participation
the need to work within the political system
what tactics to use in their struggle
the need to end slavery

42: Which reform movement caused the greatest tension between the North and South?
the drive for temperance
women&#39;s rights
abolitionism
discrimination against immigrants

43: The purpose of the Fugitive Slave Act was to
provide safety for escaped slaves
force all Americans to help catch escaped slaves
offer freed slaves land in the West
ban slavery in Washington DC</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2006 16:11:44 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>General Discussion</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/long-time-no-see-hisotyr/2883.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Long time no see Hisotyr =\</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Pk3r_Dale Pk3r Dale]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/pk3r_dale">@Pk3r_Dale</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>mmmhmm</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/long-time-no-see-hisotyr/2883/10">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/long-time-no-see-hisotyr/2883/10</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2006 16:11:44 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-2883-10</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/long-time-no-see-hisotyr/2883.rss">Long time no see Hisotyr =\</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Long time no see Hisotyr =\</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@afi afi]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/afi">@afi</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Heres some eaiser ones about the civil war +D<br>
1: Robert E. Lee surrendered because<br>
his troops were trapped by General Grant’s army<br>
he realized that the South had been wrong to secede<br>
Lincoln visited him and asked him to stop fighting<br>
he was seriously wounded<br>
he had lost at Gettysburg</p>
<p>2: As the Civil War began, the North had all of the following advantages EXCEPT:<br>
a larger population<br>
more railroads<br>
more industrial capacity<br>
superior military leadership<br>
more gold</p>
<p>3: General Grant planned to end the war by:<br>
leading a slave rebellion in the South.<br>
persuading southern civilians to support the North<br>
fighting a total war to ruin the South’s ability to fight<br>
waiting until the South was tired of the war and then offering terms for surrender<br>
none of the above</p>
<p>4: In the Gettysburg Address, Lincoln stated that his main goal was:<br>
to maintain a nation devoted to equality<br>
to punish the Confederacy<br>
convince the Confederates to abolish slavery<br>
to negotiate a compromise peace<br>
all of the above</p>
<p>5: Which of the following is NOT TRUE of the battle of the Merrimac and the Monitor?<br>
The Merrimac was renamed the Virginia<br>
The Confederate ship destroyed several Union wooden ships on the first day.<br>
After this battle, wooden ships in battle were obsolete<br>
The Union ship won a decisive victory<br>
After this battle, the Union was able to resume its blockade of Southern ports</p>
<p>6: Which Union victory gave Lincoln the right moment to make the Emancipation Proclamation?<br>
Chancellorsville<br>
Shiloh<br>
Gettysburg<br>
Second Bull Run<br>
Antietam</p>
<p>7: Which of the following statements about women’s roles during the Civil War is NOT true?<br>
They worked in jobs that had not been open to women before the war.<br>
Some women were employed in the armies as cooks and laundresses.<br>
Both armies drafted women into the service near the end of the war when there were not enough soldiers.<br>
Some women disguised themselves as men to serve in the army and to be close to their husbands.<br>
Women served as spies for both sides.</p>
<p>8: Which of the following statements about the election of 1864 is TRUE?<br>
The Democrats nominated a popular southern leader to oppose Lincoln.<br>
Lincoln barely won and did not get much support from the soldiers serving in the field.<br>
The Democrats nominated a popular Union general to oppose Lincoln<br>
The Democrat candidate proposed a more vigorous campaign to win the war<br>
Lincoln ran unopposed.</p>
<p>9: Which of the following battles meant that the Union controlled the entire Mississippi River?<br>
Mobile Bay<br>
Vicksburg<br>
Shiloh<br>
Chickamauga<br>
Chattanooga</p>
<p>10: Which of the following battles did NOT take place in Virginia?<br>
Spotsylvania<br>
Chancellorsville<br>
First Bull Run<br>
Vicksburg<br>
Fredericksburg</p>
<p>11: Which battle marks the farthest north that the Confederate army got and so is called “the high water mark of the Confederacy”?<br>
Antietam<br>
First Bull Run<br>
Perryville<br>
Fredericksburg<br>
Gettysburg</p>
<p>12: Which Confederate victory turned sour when General Stonewall Jackson was shot by his own men?<br>
First Bull Run<br>
Seven Day’s Battle<br>
Second Bull Run<br>
Fredericksburg<br>
Chancellorsville</p>
<p>13: The Union army was able to end the siege and capture which southern city the day after Gettysburg?<br>
Atlanta<br>
Nashville<br>
Vicksburg<br>
Petersburg<br>
Shiloh</p>
<p>14: Which of the following battles did NOT take place in 1862?<br>
First Bull Run<br>
Hampton Roads<br>
Shiloh<br>
Second Bull Run<br>
Antietam</p>
<p>15: Food, clothing, and education were provided to former slaves by the:<br>
Congressional Reconstruction Acts<br>
Thirteenth Amendment<br>
Ku Klux Klan<br>
Freedmen’s Bureau<br>
Wade-Davis Bill</p>
<p>16: An important result of the presidential election of 1876 was the:<br>
Democrat party regaining the presidency<br>
end of Reconstruction<br>
impeachment of Andrew Johnson<br>
creation of the Freedmen’s Bureau<br>
establishment of military rule in the South</p>
<p>17: After Reconstruction, blacks in the South began to:<br>
gain more seats in state legislatures<br>
lose interest in politics and government<br>
segregate themselves from southern whites<br>
lose political power<br>
vote in ever larger numbers</p>
<p>18: Which of the following was NOT a cause of conflict between President Johnson and the Republicans in Congress?<br>
The President vetoed their Civil Rights Bill<br>
The President tried to fire the Secretary of War<br>
the President was too lenient in allowing former Confederate officials to vote and serve in government<br>
The President was too harsh in his treatment of the former Confederate states<br>
The President campaigned against the Republican candidates for Congress</p>
<p>19: What did the 14th Amendment do?<br>
Prohibited the denial of voting rights on the basis of race<br>
Defined citizenship<br>
Prohibited slavery<br>
Prohibited poll taxes<br>
All of the above</p>
<p>20: The Freedmen’s Bureau did all of the following EXCEPT:<br>
provide food and clothing to former slaves<br>
send agents to set up schools<br>
encourage former slaves to move north<br>
provide medical care for former slaves<br>
all of the above</p>
<p>21: Which of the following is in the correct chronological order?<br>
Wade-Davis Bill, 15th Amendment, 1st Reconstruction Act, Grant elected<br>
1st Reconstruction Act, Wade-Davis Bill, Grant elected, 15th Amendment<br>
Wade-Davis Bill, 1st Reconstruction Act, 15th Amendment, Grant elected<br>
Wade-Davis Bill, 1st Reconstruction Act, Grant elected, 15th Amendment<br>
Wade-Davis Bill, 15th Amendment, Grant elected, 1st Reconstruction Act</p>
<p>22: One reason the Radical Republicans began to lose power was that:<br>
leaders such as Stevens and Sumner opposed their policies<br>
many northerners lost interest in changing the South<br>
the southern states were recovering on their own<br>
President Grant urged them to step aside<br>
None of the above</p>
<p>23: Which Reconstruction plan dissolved the governments of the Confederate states and divided them into five districts?<br>
Lincoln’s plan<br>
Wade-Davis Bill<br>
Johnson’s plan<br>
Military Reconstruction Acts<br>
15th Amendment</p>
<p>24: Who were native white Southerners who cooperated with the Republicans during Reconstruction?<br>
Carpetbaggers<br>
Radicals<br>
Scalawags<br>
Redeemers<br>
None of the above</p>
<p>25: The 15th Amendment:<br>
officially banned slavery throughout the country<br>
made blacks citizens<br>
guaranteed blacks the right to hold public office<br>
guaranteed blacks the right to vote<br>
guaranteed women the right to vote</p>
<p>26: During Reconstruction, all of the following groups took part in southern governments EXCEPT:<br>
former Confederate officers<br>
northerners who went South<br>
white Southerners who supported the Republicans<br>
freedmen<br>
all of the above</p>
<p>27: President Andrew Johnson vetoed the:<br>
Wade-Davis Bill<br>
Civil Rights Act<br>
14th Amendment<br>
Black Codes<br>
15th Amendment</p>
<p>28: Congress’ decision to bring impeachment charges against President Johnson was most immediately provoked by his:<br>
campaigning against the Radical Republicans in the 1866 Congressional elections<br>
readmission of former Confederate states<br>
dismissal of the Secretary of War<br>
vetoing of the Freedmen’s Bureau<br>
ending of Reconstruction</p>
<p>29: Which of the following occurred first?<br>
Slaves were freed<br>
Hayes elected<br>
Blacks get voting rights<br>
Johnson impeached<br>
Reconstruction ends</p>
<p>30: Andrew Johnson was made President Lincoln’s running mate in 1864 primarily for the political benefits that would result from his:<br>
being a Radical Republican leader<br>
patient and compromising manner.<br>
being a Democrat from a southern slave state<br>
having been a southern slave owner<br>
all of the above</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/long-time-no-see-hisotyr/2883/9">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/long-time-no-see-hisotyr/2883/9</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 19 May 2006 00:25:09 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-2883-9</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/long-time-no-see-hisotyr/2883.rss">Long time no see Hisotyr =\</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Long time no see Hisotyr =\</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Duncan Duncan]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/duncan">@Duncan</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>God Bless America,<br>
Land that I love.<br>
Stand beside her, and guide her<br>
Thru the night with a light from above.<br>
From the mountains, to the prairies,<br>
To the oceans, white with foam<br>
God bless America, My home sweet home.</p>
<p><img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/smiley.png?v=9" title=":smiley:" class="emoji" alt=":smiley:"> <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/smiley.png?v=9" title=":smiley:" class="emoji" alt=":smiley:"> <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/smiley.png?v=9" title=":smiley:" class="emoji" alt=":smiley:"></p>
<p><img src="http://foxtrotters.tripod.com/us_rite.gif" alt width="195" height="49"></p>
<p><img src="http://www.mathworks.com/matlabcentral/files/1225/usflag.jpg" alt width="" height=""></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/long-time-no-see-hisotyr/2883/8">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/long-time-no-see-hisotyr/2883/8</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 19 May 2006 00:13:24 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-2883-8</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/long-time-no-see-hisotyr/2883.rss">Long time no see Hisotyr =\</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Long time no see Hisotyr =\</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@afi afi]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/afi">@afi</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Me either =\</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/long-time-no-see-hisotyr/2883/7">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/long-time-no-see-hisotyr/2883/7</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 18 May 2006 19:15:53 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-2883-7</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/long-time-no-see-hisotyr/2883.rss">Long time no see Hisotyr =\</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Long time no see Hisotyr =\</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Friday13th Friday13th]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/friday13th">@Friday13th</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>sorry cant help. Dont know mutch about USA <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=9" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/long-time-no-see-hisotyr/2883/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/long-time-no-see-hisotyr/2883/6</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 18 May 2006 08:16:10 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-2883-6</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/long-time-no-see-hisotyr/2883.rss">Long time no see Hisotyr =\</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Long time no see Hisotyr =\</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@afi afi]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/afi">@afi</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>thanks duncan</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/long-time-no-see-hisotyr/2883/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/long-time-no-see-hisotyr/2883/5</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 18 May 2006 02:45:51 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-2883-5</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/long-time-no-see-hisotyr/2883.rss">Long time no see Hisotyr =\</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Long time no see Hisotyr =\</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Duncan Duncan]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/duncan">@Duncan</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <ol start="3">
<li>Water Route Across America</li>
<li>British Troops set fire to Washington D.C.</li>
</ol>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/long-time-no-see-hisotyr/2883/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/long-time-no-see-hisotyr/2883/4</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 15 May 2006 21:30:07 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-2883-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/long-time-no-see-hisotyr/2883.rss">Long time no see Hisotyr =\</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Long time no see Hisotyr =\</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@afi afi]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/afi">@afi</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Thanks Yna, Told You Long time NO see LOl</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/long-time-no-see-hisotyr/2883/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/long-time-no-see-hisotyr/2883/3</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 15 May 2006 20:23:44 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-2883-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/long-time-no-see-hisotyr/2883.rss">Long time no see Hisotyr =\</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Long time no see Hisotyr =\</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@yna_ajhear5 yna_ajhear5]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/yna_ajhear5">@yna_ajhear5</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>God that’s alot.</p>
<p>Hold on.</p>
<ol>
<li>oral history.<br>
2.give Spain a trading advantage over Portugal<br>
3.?<br>
4.the seven golden cities I believe<br>
5.worked cooperatively for the good of the colony<br>
6.escape religious persecution<br>
7.they supplied England with food and raw materials and bought English goods<br>
8.on plantations<br>
9.the swampy site chosen for this settlement I think<br>
10.Southwest<br>
11.Great Migration<br>
12.a desire to live free of religious persecution<br>
13.lack of religion I think.<br>
14.Britain lost control of lands east of the Mississippi River<br>
15.British tried to raise money in the colonies<br>
16.Either Battle of Saratoga or Battle of Bunker Hill<br>
17.Patriot forces were fighting on their own territory<br>
18.the spread of the idea of liberty at home and abroad<br>
19.promote the need for a stronger central government<br>
20.representation in the legislature I think<br>
21.it gave too much power to the people<br>
22.separation of powers<br>
23.of dignity I think.<br>
24.John Adams had more Electoral College votes<br>
25.?</li>
</ol>
<p>Well shit I’m out of time now sorry.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/long-time-no-see-hisotyr/2883/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/long-time-no-see-hisotyr/2883/2</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 15 May 2006 19:56:16 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-2883-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/long-time-no-see-hisotyr/2883.rss">Long time no see Hisotyr =\</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Long time no see Hisotyr =\</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@afi afi]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/afi">@afi</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>1: Native Americans passed down their traditions from generation to generation through<br>
barter<br>
oral history<br>
written records<br>
trade routes</p>
<p>2: Spain decided to back Columbus’ voyage to the west in the hopes that it would<br>
help to finally defeat the Muslims<br>
make Columbus rich and famous<br>
give Spain a trading advantage over Portugal<br>
bring an end to feudalism in Europe</p>
<p>3: Which of the following best describes the Northwest Passage?<br>
John Cabot’s sailing across the Atlantic Ocean from England<br>
Ferdinand Magellan’s circumnavigating the globe<br>
water route across North America<br>
the Puritan’s route from England to Massachusetts</p>
<p>4: English explorers like Cabot, Frobisher, and Hudson were searching for<br>
the seven golden cities<br>
the Great Migration<br>
a Northwest Passage<br>
a land route to California</p>
<p>5: The Virginia colony survived largely because the English colonists<br>
were well cared for by the Virginia Company<br>
developed lasting friendships with Native Americans<br>
worked cooperatively for the good of the colony<br>
began growing tobacco for sale</p>
<p>6: The Puritans migrated to New England to<br>
escape religious persecution<br>
establish Catholic missions<br>
maintain the practices of the Anglican Church<br>
start tobacco plantations</p>
<p>7: England prized its North American colonies because<br>
they provided England with natural resources of gold and silver<br>
they provided soldiers for the British Army to fight in European wars<br>
they supplied England with food and raw materials and bought English goods<br>
they manufactured goods for England</p>
<p>8: In colonial South Carolina and Georgia, most slaves worked<br>
in cities<br>
on fishing ships<br>
in factories<br>
on plantations</p>
<p>9: Which of the following caused Jamestown’s near failure?<br>
the discovery of gold and silver in the colony<br>
John Smith’s leadership<br>
the failure of the tobacco crop<br>
the swampy site chosen for this settlement</p>
<p>10: In what part of North America did the Hopi and Zuni develop their way of life?<br>
Southwest<br>
Northeast<br>
Plains<br>
Northwest Coast</p>
<p>11: An example of an uprising by slaves to free themselves in the mid-1700s is the<br>
Great Awakening<br>
Stono Rebellion<br>
Middle Passage<br>
Great Migration</p>
<p>12: Which of the following was a driving force in Puritan settlements?<br>
a love of luxury and wealth<br>
a desire to live free of religious persecution<br>
a passion for social order<br>
a desire to return to England</p>
<p>13: The population of the Middle Colonies was known for its<br>
lack of farming skills<br>
hatred of the other colonies<br>
diversity<br>
lack of religion</p>
<p>14: As a result of the French and Indian War,<br>
Native Americans gained control of the Great Lakes region<br>
Britain lost control of lands east of the Mississippi River<br>
France turned Canada over to Britain<br>
France gained control of Florida</p>
<p>15: The Sugar Act and Stamp Act are examples of how the<br>
British continued to leave the colonies alone<br>
British tried to raise money in the colonies<br>
colonists eagerly sacraficed to pay their war debts<br>
British tried to stimulate colonial economies</p>
<p>16: The Revolutionary War began with the<br>
Battle of Saratoga<br>
Battle of Trenton<br>
Bettles of Lexington and Concord<br>
Battle of Bunker Hill</p>
<p>17: What was a major advantage of the American side in the Revolutionary War?<br>
Patriot forces were fighting on their own territory<br>
British forces were not well equipped<br>
Americans had a well-supplied, stable, and effective fighting force<br>
The British people strongly supported their forces fighting in the colonies</p>
<p>18: American victory in the Revolutionary War led to<br>
expanded political and legal power for women<br>
the abolition of slavery in the Southern Colonies<br>
the strengthening of the Iroquois League<br>
the spread of the idea of liberty at home and abroad</p>
<p>19: In the 1780s, the Nationalists organized to<br>
create a unicameral legislature<br>
strengthen the power of the states<br>
promote the need for a stronger central government<br>
fight against taxation</p>
<p>20: What issue did the Great Compromise resolve?<br>
representation in the legislature<br>
abolition of slavery<br>
the veto power of the executive<br>
when taxes were to be paid</p>
<p>21: The anti-Federalists argued against the Constitution because they felt<br>
it gave too much power to the people<br>
it created a weak executive branch<br>
it made the national government too strong<br>
the Articles of Confederation did not need to be reformed</p>
<p>22: Some anti-Federalists agreed to support the Constitution after the Federalists added the<br>
separation of powers<br>
Bill of Rights<br>
Preamble<br>
system of checks and balances</p>
<p>23: During his term in office, President Washington worked to develop a tone<br>
that was dictatorial<br>
that was nonthreatening<br>
of modesty<br>
of dignity</p>
<p>24: Why was Jefferson not named President after he won the popular vote in 1800?<br>
John Adams had more Electoral College votes<br>
Aaron Burr had more Electoral College votes<br>
Congress refused to agree to Jefferson’s election<br>
Jefferson did not have any Electoral College votes</p>
<p>25: Which of the following occurred during the War of 1812?<br>
Tecumseh’s warriors won the Battle of Tippecanoe<br>
The British navy lost many sea batles<br>
British troops set fire to Washington DC<br>
Unites States forces captured Canada</p>
<p>26: Which was a provision of the Missouri Compromise of 1820?<br>
Missouri and Maine were denied statehood<br>
States north of 36o 30 ’ N latitude would be free states<br>
Slavery could not spread into any western lands<br>
Free states could never outnumber slave states</p>
<p>27: The First Continental Congress voted to<br>
end the boycott of imports from Britain<br>
call for the formation of colonial militias<br>
imprison all British tax collectors<br>
adopt the Declaration of Independence</p>
<p>28: The Three-Fifths Compromise resolved the issue of<br>
how enslaved people were to be counted in the population<br>
whether the larger states could have more representatives in Congress<br>
whether Congress would have one or two houses<br>
how many representatives each state would have in he Senate</p>
<p>29: Which of the following was designed to ensure that one branch of government would never become too powerful?<br>
the Electoral College<br>
the Cabinet<br>
the Bill of Rights<br>
the system of checks and balances</p>
<p>30: One purpose of the Lewis and Clark expedition was to<br>
explore the lands of the Louisiana Purchase<br>
gain control over the Native Americans living west of the Mississippi<br>
drive the Spanish out of the lands of the Southwest<br>
drive the French out of fur trading forts along the Mississippi</p>
<p>31: Why did many colonists oppose the Stamp Act?<br>
The act enabled the British to censor all written materials in the colonies<br>
The act threatened to disrupt trading patterns with overseas markets<br>
The act increased the cost of British imports<br>
The act taxed the colonists without their consent</p>
<p>32: Delegates to the Constitutional Convention were initially supposed to<br>
throw out the Articles of Confederation and start all over<br>
write new constitutions for the states they represented<br>
amend the Articles of Confederation<br>
determine whether slavery would be allowed to continue</p>
<p>33: Which one of the following was a major accomplishment of the Jefferson administration?<br>
increasing the size of the army<br>
destroying the Bank of the United States<br>
the Louisiana Purchase<br>
driving the British out of Canada</p>
<p>34: In the Adams-Onis Treaty of 1819,<br>
the United States doubled its size<br>
the Cherokees settled their dispute with the American government<br>
Spain ceded Florida to the United States<br>
the United States gained the right to build the Erie Canal</p>
<p>35: How did Native American migration differ from that of white Americans in the early 1800s?<br>
Most Native Americans migrated after being forced from their land<br>
Most Native Americans migrated south instead of west<br>
Most Native Americans migrated to reclaim their homelands, not to explore<br>
Most Native Americans migrated to cities along the Atlantic Coast</p>
<p>36: What was one important efect of the invenetion of the cotton gin in 1793?<br>
Thousands of southern plantation owners went bankrupt<br>
The demand for slave labor increased<br>
Laws called black codes were passed<br>
Migration from the South to undeveloped lands in the West declined</p>
<p>37: Steam power and canal building wer important because they<br>
allowed farmers to ship their goods to markets around the country<br>
caused a decline in the demand for slave labor<br>
discouraged the settlement of western regions<br>
increased the cost of transportation and communication</p>
<p>38: The South in the early 1800s was<br>
crowded and bustling<br>
mainly rural<br>
an area of high population density<br>
predominantly an industrial society</p>
<p>39: After the importation of slaves to the United States was banned,<br>
the number of enslaved people shrunk by one half<br>
the slave trade continued within the United States<br>
slavery grew faster in the North than in the South<br>
Virginia outlawed slavery</p>
<p>40: Which was a result of industralization in the United States?<br>
a decrease in available jobs<br>
a sharp decline in poverty<br>
an increase in women in factory jobs<br>
the growth of cities</p>
<p>41: All abolitionists agreed about<br>
the importance of women’s participation<br>
the need to work within the political system<br>
what tactics to use in their struggle<br>
the need to end slavery</p>
<p>42: Which reform movement caused the greatest tension between the North and South?<br>
the drive for temperance<br>
women’s rights<br>
abolitionism<br>
discrimination against immigrants</p>
<p>43: The purpose of the Fugitive Slave Act was to<br>
provide safety for escaped slaves<br>
force all Americans to help catch escaped slaves<br>
offer freed slaves land in the West<br>
ban slavery in Washington DC</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/long-time-no-see-hisotyr/2883/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/long-time-no-see-hisotyr/2883/1</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 15 May 2006 19:43:57 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-2883-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/long-time-no-see-hisotyr/2883.rss">Long time no see Hisotyr =\</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
