<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Good Rendering (in my opinion)</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/good-rendering-in-my-opinion/73171</link>
    <description>I&#39;ve noticed more and more than newbies to PhotoShop cut there renders out with the Lasso Tool. This is not the best, or technically correct way to do this.

First of all, a render is basically something (a person usually) cut out of a picture, and put into another picture, with effects and what not added.

Before I go into this, be aware there are many sites that have renders already, including [url=http://www.gamerenders.com]GameRenders[/url] and [url=http://www.planetrenders.net]PlanetRenders[/url]. Sign up for them , then when you open the picture to the full view drag it into PhotoShop.

Do a [url=http://www.google.com/images]Google Image[/url] search on something of your topic. For this I&#39;ll be using Baraka from Mortal Kombat.

I&#39;ll be using this picture for this tutorial.

[img]http://www.totalmortalkombat.com/mksm/renders/mksm_baraka_render.jpg[/img]
[i]
Note: When measuring the size of pictures it&#39;s always better to use the width before height
Note: If none of these boxes or Tool Bars I&#39;m talking about are there, click the Window in the Tool Bar (on top of PhotoShop), hover your mouse over Workspace, and click default workspace
[/i]
This is way too big, as almost all renders are used for signatures, and they range from 90 X 250 to 300 X 400. Just for future reference I&#39;d recommend 410 X 115 or 400 X 130.

After clicking the thumbnails in Google, when your on the actual page with only the picture, drag the image into PhotoShop. It may look smaller for some reason here, this is because PhotoShop automatically zoomed out on the image. You&#39;ll notice on the top right of PhotoShop (PS from here on) a smaller portion of your picture. It has a slider and percentage. The percentage is how zoomed out you are. Change it to 100%, if not already there.

Now, if it looks like anything past 500 X 700 you&#39;ll wanna shrink it.

In the top Tool Bar of PS, click Image, from here click Image Size. Make sure Constrain Proportions is checked (bottom left of the pop-up box), and resize it. Change the height to 500. This should give you a good sized render to start with. Now click OK. On the bottom right of PS you&#39;ll notice it says Background with another smaller image of the picture. Double click it and click OK on the window that popped up. This simply makes it not a background layer, which is good in all scenarios (I believe, it&#39;s never helped before and has held back options).

On the left you should see a Tool Bar with a bunch of small icons. Theres one that looks like a Lasso, unless you&#39;ve been clicking all of the buttons to test them out, it will be one of these three icons- [img]http://img473.imageshack.us/img473/5450/lassokt6.png[/img][img]http://img473.imageshack.us/img473/9669/polygonallassose3.png[/img][img]http://img473.imageshack.us/img473/4360/magneticlassoap3.png[/img]
Right click it, and click Polygonal Lasso Tool

Now, click somewhere on your soon-to-be-render. I&#39;d suggest starting at the head. From here, click all the way around your stbr (soon-to-be-render). Click every half centimeter. Or about every [s]  [/s]  length. When you get to where you started clicking, put the mouse onto the beginning of the line. Keep hovering around it until you see a small circle pop up, from here click it. You should now have an outline on your render.
[img]http://img87.imageshack.us/img87/5633/outlinedrp5.jpg[/img]

On the top of PS, in the Tool Bar, click Select. Now click Inverse. You&#39;ll notice the moving dot thingies (the outline), has been inverted and now outlines everything around your render. Again in Select, click Feather. Set it to 1. Click OK. Now, hit delete. You should have a decent looking render. From here make a new layer. In the PS Tool Bar, click layer, hover over new, then click Layer. Click OK. Now you have another layer. On the bottom right in your layers panel, drag layer 2 below layer 1. Now, take the bucket tool, and fill it with black. If you don&#39;t see a bucket on the left in your Tool Bar, it will look like a square with black fading to white, right click it and click bucket. Once you&#39;ve filled the new layer with black, a few mess ups will be revealed on your render. Click back onto the layer with the render, and again with the Polygonal Lasso tool, go around the messed up parts and, when over where you started, and theres a small circle, click, then hit delete. Do this until you have a good looking render, almost perfect. At the end, right click the layer with black in the layers panel, and hit delete, in the box that comes up hit OK. From here save your render, as a PSD, for future use. This is my final render&gt;
[img]http://img58.imageshack.us/img58/1096/baraka01bg5.jpg[/img]

In future tutorials, or in your own makings, when you need your render, open it, press ctrl and a, and press ctrl and c (copy). From here, in your signature or picture with your render, press ctrl and v (paste). Now press ctrl and d (deselect). From here take the Magic Wand Tool. It&#39;s a little wand thats next to the Lasso Tools. Click outside of the render, click Select, then Feather, then set it to 1, then hit OK, then delete. Wala, your render fits in with the background. If it doesn&#39;t, hit delete until it does.

I hope my tutorial helps out new people to PhotoShop. It may take a while to get a good render, but in a signature it makes a large difference.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 02 Apr 2007 05:15:18 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Graphics</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/good-rendering-in-my-opinion/73171.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Good Rendering (in my opinion)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@LegendaryLoser .Flair]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/legendaryloser">@LegendaryLoser</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>How do I make the background transparent -.- ??</p>
<p>I said it my opinion, this works just fine</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/good-rendering-in-my-opinion/73171/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/good-rendering-in-my-opinion/73171/3</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 02 Apr 2007 05:15:18 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-73171-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/good-rendering-in-my-opinion/73171.rss">Good Rendering (in my opinion)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Good Rendering (in my opinion)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@FastBallz FastBawlz]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/fastballz">@FastBallz</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Srry…But that sucks…+ The white…</p>
<p>Use the pen tool…</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/good-rendering-in-my-opinion/73171/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/good-rendering-in-my-opinion/73171/2</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 02 Apr 2007 05:13:54 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-73171-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/good-rendering-in-my-opinion/73171.rss">Good Rendering (in my opinion)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Good Rendering (in my opinion)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@LegendaryLoser .Flair]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/legendaryloser">@LegendaryLoser</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I’ve noticed more and more than newbies to PhotoShop cut there renders out with the Lasso Tool. This is not the best, or technically correct way to do this.</p>
<p>First of all, a render is basically something (a person usually) cut out of a picture, and put into another picture, with effects and what not added.</p>
<p>Before I go into this, be aware there are many sites that have renders already, including <a href="http://www.gamerenders.com" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">GameRenders</a> and <a href="http://www.planetrenders.net" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">PlanetRenders</a>. Sign up for them , then when you open the picture to the full view drag it into PhotoShop.</p>
<p>Do a <a href="http://www.google.com/images" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">Google Image</a> search on something of your topic. For this I’ll be using Baraka from Mortal Kombat.</p>
<p>I’ll be using this picture for this tutorial.</p>
<p><div class="lightbox-wrapper"><a class="lightbox" href="http://www.totalmortalkombat.com/mksm/renders/mksm_baraka_render.jpg" title="mksm_baraka_render.jpg" rel="nofollow noopener"><img src="http://www.totalmortalkombat.com/mksm/renders/mksm_baraka_render.jpg" alt width="375" height="500"><div class="meta">
<svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-far-image svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#far-image"></use></svg><span class="filename">mksm_baraka_render.jpg</span><span class="informations">1200×1600</span><svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-discourse-expand svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#discourse-expand"></use></svg>
</div></a></div><br>
<span class="bbcode-i"><br>
Note: When measuring the size of pictures it’s always better to use the width before height<br>
Note: If none of these boxes or Tool Bars I’m talking about are there, click the Window in the Tool Bar (on top of PhotoShop), hover your mouse over Workspace, and click default workspace<br>
</span><br>
This is way too big, as almost all renders are used for signatures, and they range from 90 X 250 to 300 X 400. Just for future reference I’d recommend 410 X 115 or 400 X 130.</p>
<p>After clicking the thumbnails in Google, when your on the actual page with only the picture, drag the image into PhotoShop. It may look smaller for some reason here, this is because PhotoShop automatically zoomed out on the image. You’ll notice on the top right of PhotoShop (PS from here on) a smaller portion of your picture. It has a slider and percentage. The percentage is how zoomed out you are. Change it to 100%, if not already there.</p>
<p>Now, if it looks like anything past 500 X 700 you’ll wanna shrink it.</p>
<p>In the top Tool Bar of PS, click Image, from here click Image Size. Make sure Constrain Proportions is checked (bottom left of the pop-up box), and resize it. Change the height to 500. This should give you a good sized render to start with. Now click OK. On the bottom right of PS you’ll notice it says Background with another smaller image of the picture. Double click it and click OK on the window that popped up. This simply makes it not a background layer, which is good in all scenarios (I believe, it’s never helped before and has held back options).</p>
<p>On the left you should see a Tool Bar with a bunch of small icons. Theres one that looks like a Lasso, unless you’ve been clicking all of the buttons to test them out, it will be one of these three icons- <img src="http://img473.imageshack.us/img473/5450/lassokt6.png" alt width="" height=""><img src="http://img473.imageshack.us/img473/9669/polygonallassose3.png" alt width="" height=""><img src="http://img473.imageshack.us/img473/4360/magneticlassoap3.png" alt width="" height=""><br>
Right click it, and click Polygonal Lasso Tool</p>
<p>Now, click somewhere on your soon-to-be-render. I’d suggest starting at the head. From here, click all the way around your stbr (soon-to-be-render). Click every half centimeter. Or about every <span class="bbcode-s">  </span>  length. When you get to where you started clicking, put the mouse onto the beginning of the line. Keep hovering around it until you see a small circle pop up, from here click it. You should now have an outline on your render.<br>
<img src="http://img87.imageshack.us/img87/5633/outlinedrp5.jpg" alt width="" height=""></p>
<p>On the top of PS, in the Tool Bar, click Select. Now click Inverse. You’ll notice the moving dot thingies (the outline), has been inverted and now outlines everything around your render. Again in Select, click Feather. Set it to 1. Click OK. Now, hit delete. You should have a decent looking render. From here make a new layer. In the PS Tool Bar, click layer, hover over new, then click Layer. Click OK. Now you have another layer. On the bottom right in your layers panel, drag layer 2 below layer 1. Now, take the bucket tool, and fill it with black. If you don’t see a bucket on the left in your Tool Bar, it will look like a square with black fading to white, right click it and click bucket. Once you’ve filled the new layer with black, a few mess ups will be revealed on your render. Click back onto the layer with the render, and again with the Polygonal Lasso tool, go around the messed up parts and, when over where you started, and theres a small circle, click, then hit delete. Do this until you have a good looking render, almost perfect. At the end, right click the layer with black in the layers panel, and hit delete, in the box that comes up hit OK. From here save your render, as a PSD, for future use. This is my final render&gt;<br>
<img src="http://img58.imageshack.us/img58/1096/baraka01bg5.jpg" alt width="" height=""></p>
<p>In future tutorials, or in your own makings, when you need your render, open it, press ctrl and a, and press ctrl and c (copy). From here, in your signature or picture with your render, press ctrl and v (paste). Now press ctrl and d (deselect). From here take the Magic Wand Tool. It’s a little wand thats next to the Lasso Tools. Click outside of the render, click Select, then Feather, then set it to 1, then hit OK, then delete. Wala, your render fits in with the background. If it doesn’t, hit delete until it does.</p>
<p>I hope my tutorial helps out new people to PhotoShop. It may take a while to get a good render, but in a signature it makes a large difference.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/good-rendering-in-my-opinion/73171/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/good-rendering-in-my-opinion/73171/1</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 02 Apr 2007 03:19:05 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-73171-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/good-rendering-in-my-opinion/73171.rss">Good Rendering (in my opinion)</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
