<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Custom Items For 718&#39;s ( Models and Inserting Into Cache )</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/custom-items-for-718s-models-and-inserting-into-cache/543345</link>
    <description>[center]
[size=6]Custom Item&#39;s For 718&#39;s[/size]
[size=5]Models &amp; Inserting Into Cache[/size]




[b][i][u][size=5]Intro[/size][/u][/i][/b]
[size=4]Hello Rune-Server users! Im new to the website so please ignore any silly mistakes i make in my spelling and exscuse my crappy teaching skills, as this is my first tutorial on the forums. Well, first post! Anyways, time to get to the topic. In this post i will be covering the basics of making a custom item with its own custom 3d model for a 718+ RSPS![/size]






[b][i][u][size=5]Creating The Model For The Item![/size][/u][/i][/b]
[size=4]Alright, well first thing we need to do is to download all the tools we will need, which i will provide a link to a rar with all of them in one rar file [url=https://mega.co.nz/#!E95i1C5K!OiWmTJPuCMXYpPEsYsQrq7uudN6XIZzWbhxGSCyp_80]here[/url]. After you have those tools the next thing you need to do is go to the folder named &quot;FrostysCacheEditor&quot; and click file on the top right of the tool selection window, click load cache, and direct it to yhte path of your server&#39;s cache, choose the option &quot;Items&quot;, and find the weapon that you want to have as your base ( What you will use to have a idea of where to have the hilt, and etc, you will be able to replace it all later! ). Once your done with this, write the ID down somewhere and close the cache editor. Now open rsdatasuite.jar and find the id that you wrote down from the cache editor, and click it, then click save model, and save it somewhere you can find it. After this what you need to do is close rsdatasuite and open Datmaker. Go to file, then open and open the file you just exported from rsdatasuite. After this what you need to do file and click export, and export it as a mqo. I believe it exports it in the same folder as the original. Now what you need to do is go to the folder named &quot;Metasequoia&quot; and run the program. Open the file you just exported with this program, and use Metasequoia to make your own weapon, if you need a tutorial on how to use it go [url=http://lmgtfy.com/?q=Metasequoia+tutorial]here[/url]. After you have done that you need to save the new 3d model, and open Datmaker again, and open the file you exported last time, now make sure its the right look and everything in the previewer built into datmaker, if it is, then click convert ,and it will be in the same folder as the file you opened. After you are done with that you need to add the item to the cache![/size].




[b][i][u][size=5]Inserting The Item Into Your Cache!![/size][/u][/i][/b]

[size=4]Assuming you have done everything about we will not start to import the item into your RSPS, which is the easier part. You will need to have the tools we were talking about earlier, specifically the Somethin_Catchy.jar and FrostyCacheEditor.jar. Once you have those two programs open its time to start working on fixing it all up. Open FrostyCacheEditor, and do what you did last time, load the cache, open the Items tool. Now what you need to do is find the item you used last time, with the id you wrote down, and click it, now click duplicate, and put a large id like 29995. Repeat this again but do the id 1 less. Now keep this program open. Open Sometin_Catchy.jar. You should be prompted with a ui asking for three paths for cache packing and what you want to pack, for the first to direct them to the cache you been working on this entire time, and leave the third alone, and for what you want to pack choose &quot;Custom Item Packing&quot;, and click &quot;Lets do it!&quot;. Now go to the model tab, and for Male Model Equip 1 and Female Model Equip 1, click browse, and navigate to the .dat you made for your 3d model, and select it. You should get a ID for each of those fields, you need to write those down somewhere and put what they are for in that note. Now you need to go to basic options again and put the second item id you added earlier , and click pack item, and close something_catchy.jar and un-minimize frostycacheeditor.jar and click the first id you added and click edit. Edit the name to what you want the name of the item to be, any of the basic vars that you want actually, like value, and etc. Now go to the model options tab and put the model id for Male Equip 1 and Female Equip 1 what it was in the note you made, and click save under file, and close the program. Now restart your server, and get on your server. Spawn it with ::item 29995 and there is your item! Congratulations! ^_^[/size]





[size=6][i]Thank you for reading my tutorial and if you want some pictures because this was not wordy enough , just say so! I rather not do the pictures though as it just makes it more complicated for me because i have to make a object i dont want to! Either way, if this helps please put a thankyou below! ^_^[/i][/size]
 [/center]</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 24 May 2014 06:20:01 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/custom-items-for-718s-models-and-inserting-into-cache/543345.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Custom Items For 718&#39;s ( Models and Inserting Into Cache )</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Damien113 Damien113]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/damien113">@Damien113</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Im assuming so, i would say just to do the samething but with the npc option for all the software. But i will look into it, cause you might have to animate them your self</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/custom-items-for-718s-models-and-inserting-into-cache/543345/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/custom-items-for-718s-models-and-inserting-into-cache/543345/3</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 24 May 2014 06:20:01 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-543345-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/custom-items-for-718s-models-and-inserting-into-cache/543345.rss">Custom Items For 718&#39;s ( Models and Inserting Into Cache )</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Custom Items For 718&#39;s ( Models and Inserting Into Cache )</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@hadlich4 hadlich4]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/hadlich4">@hadlich4</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Is there a way to add custom npc’s as well?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/custom-items-for-718s-models-and-inserting-into-cache/543345/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/custom-items-for-718s-models-and-inserting-into-cache/543345/2</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 24 May 2014 06:17:21 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-543345-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/custom-items-for-718s-models-and-inserting-into-cache/543345.rss">Custom Items For 718&#39;s ( Models and Inserting Into Cache )</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Custom Items For 718&#39;s ( Models and Inserting Into Cache )</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Damien113 Damien113]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/damien113">@Damien113</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[center]<br>
[size=6]Custom Item’s For 718’s[/size]<br>
[size=5]Models &amp; Inserting Into Cache[/size]</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b"><span class="bbcode-i"><span class="bbcode-u">[size=5]Intro[/size]</span></span></span><br>
[size=4]Hello Rune-Server users! Im new to the website so please ignore any silly mistakes i make in my spelling and exscuse my crappy teaching skills, as this is my first tutorial on the forums. Well, first post! Anyways, time to get to the topic. In this post i will be covering the basics of making a custom item with its own custom 3d model for a 718+ RSPS![/size]</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b"><span class="bbcode-i"><span class="bbcode-u">[size=5]Creating The Model For The Item![/size]</span></span></span><br>
[size=4]Alright, well first thing we need to do is to download all the tools we will need, which i will provide a link to a rar with all of them in one rar file <a href="https://mega.co.nz/#!E95i1C5K!OiWmTJPuCMXYpPEsYsQrq7uudN6XIZzWbhxGSCyp_80" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">here</a>. After you have those tools the next thing you need to do is go to the folder named “FrostysCacheEditor” and click file on the top right of the tool selection window, click load cache, and direct it to yhte path of your server’s cache, choose the option “Items”, and find the weapon that you want to have as your base ( What you will use to have a idea of where to have the hilt, and etc, you will be able to replace it all later! ). Once your done with this, write the ID down somewhere and close the cache editor. Now open rsdatasuite.jar and find the id that you wrote down from the cache editor, and click it, then click save model, and save it somewhere you can find it. After this what you need to do is close rsdatasuite and open Datmaker. Go to file, then open and open the file you just exported from rsdatasuite. After this what you need to do file and click export, and export it as a mqo. I believe it exports it in the same folder as the original. Now what you need to do is go to the folder named “Metasequoia” and run the program. Open the file you just exported with this program, and use Metasequoia to make your own weapon, if you need a tutorial on how to use it go <a href="http://lmgtfy.com/?q=Metasequoia+tutorial" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">here</a>. After you have done that you need to save the new 3d model, and open Datmaker again, and open the file you exported last time, now make sure its the right look and everything in the previewer built into datmaker, if it is, then click convert ,and it will be in the same folder as the file you opened. After you are done with that you need to add the item to the cache![/size].</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b"><span class="bbcode-i"><span class="bbcode-u">[size=5]Inserting The Item Into Your Cache!![/size]</span></span></span></p>
<p>[size=4]Assuming you have done everything about we will not start to import the item into your RSPS, which is the easier part. You will need to have the tools we were talking about earlier, specifically the Somethin_Catchy.jar and FrostyCacheEditor.jar. Once you have those two programs open its time to start working on fixing it all up. Open FrostyCacheEditor, and do what you did last time, load the cache, open the Items tool. Now what you need to do is find the item you used last time, with the id you wrote down, and click it, now click duplicate, and put a large id like 29995. Repeat this again but do the id 1 less. Now keep this program open. Open Sometin_Catchy.jar. You should be prompted with a ui asking for three paths for cache packing and what you want to pack, for the first to direct them to the cache you been working on this entire time, and leave the third alone, and for what you want to pack choose “Custom Item Packing”, and click “Lets do it!”. Now go to the model tab, and for Male Model Equip 1 and Female Model Equip 1, click browse, and navigate to the .dat you made for your 3d model, and select it. You should get a ID for each of those fields, you need to write those down somewhere and put what they are for in that note. Now you need to go to basic options again and put the second item id you added earlier , and click pack item, and close something_catchy.jar and un-minimize frostycacheeditor.jar and click the first id you added and click edit. Edit the name to what you want the name of the item to be, any of the basic vars that you want actually, like value, and etc. Now go to the model options tab and put the model id for Male Equip 1 and Female Equip 1 what it was in the note you made, and click save under file, and close the program. Now restart your server, and get on your server. Spawn it with ::item 29995 and there is your item! Congratulations! ^_^[/size]</p>
<p>[size=6]<span class="bbcode-i">Thank you for reading my tutorial and if you want some pictures because this was not wordy enough , just say so! I rather not do the pictures though as it just makes it more complicated for me because i have to make a object i dont want to! Either way, if this helps please put a thankyou below! <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=5" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></span>[/size]<br>
[/center]</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/custom-items-for-718s-models-and-inserting-into-cache/543345/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/custom-items-for-718s-models-and-inserting-into-cache/543345/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 24 May 2014 05:55:59 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-543345-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/custom-items-for-718s-models-and-inserting-into-cache/543345.rss">Custom Items For 718&#39;s ( Models and Inserting Into Cache )</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
