<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Staff reform (revised)</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/staff-reform-revised/420922</link>
    <description>Another staff reform topic by yours truly. 


[b]Section 1: Activity[/b]
Activity from the current staff members here has been seriously lacking. A few examples of this are found here:

http://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php/topic,523577.0.html
Advertisement thread, took about 5 hours to get locked.

http://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php/topic,523532.0.html
Took an hour or so (this thread was in multiple sections if I recall correctly).

Not to mention all of the server help threads with &quot;REP++ IF U HALP ME&quot; in the title that are NEVER locked (even though against the rules). If the staff are going to use the rules as a shield, like they did in the last staff reform topic, I expect them to be able to enforce them. This leads me to the next section.


[b]Section 2: Rules[/b]

Examples of rules that are never enforced: 

Rule 2 - Everybody is equal, don&#39;t treat people worse than you do others(E.G., don&#39;t isolate someone and flame them).

Examples of this can be found all over the general discussion section. I&#39;m sure I don&#39;t need to tell the reader that flame exists in this community. 

Rule 3 - 
Posts should be knowledgeable, try to put some effort into them, it&#39;ll save hassle and stop you from looking like an idiot.

Examples: 
http://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php/topic,523568.0.html

Rule 8 - We don&#39;t sell anything (paraphrased).

Examples:
http://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php/topic,523562.0.html

Rule 11 - 
Never ask for reputation(rep). Reputation is to be handed out, at the forum members digression, as a reward for adding quality content to a thread, or the forum in general. Reputation abuse is punished. 

http://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php/topic,523349.0.html
http://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php/topic,523531.0.html
http://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php/topic,523586.0.html
(Plenty more, this is just a few on the first page of server help). 

Rule 12 - 
We respect each other and other communities. We do not flame. There is to be no fighting on the forums. 

Refer to rule 1.

If I could find these examples (with a quick breeze through TWO of the boards on this site, no less) we have a serious problem. If you aren&#39;t going to enforce the rules, edit or abolish them. I don&#39;t care if the rules aren&#39;t considered important. If they aren&#39;t important, someone needs to edit the rules thread for the first time in TWO YEARS. 


[b]Section 3: Moderating positions[/b]

Moparscape moderators:
While great and all for this forum board, they are pretty useless in dealing with issues that aren&#39;t pointed out to them (this is NOT THEIR FAULT, I&#39;d like to emphasize that). Moparscape would be MUCH better with numerous sectional moderators, instead of global (relatively) ones. 

Global moderators:
A good chunk of the global moderators are inactive (some haven&#39;t been on in MONTHS). The ones that aren&#39;t inactive are on MITB. These same moderators claim they don&#39;t do anything because there isn&#39;t anything to moderate on the mitb forums. SINCE WHEN DOES GLOBAL ENCOMPASS ONE HALF OF A COMMUNITY? Not even the more active half, either. Make all of the gmods who cbf to come on this side of the community something like &quot;MITB moderators&quot;. I&#39;m not going to name names but I&#39;m sure you all know the truly helpful and global gmods. 

The staff will back themselves up saying &quot;what bad is it doing keeping them there&quot;. The answer is none, but it&#39;s not doing ANY good either, why not reform it so that good IS being done? 


[b]Intel:[/b]
Frell, The_Soul, Davidi2, Tom_BETA, Fat_Cookies, Deathschaos9, Frell, SilentCJ
those have all moderated this week

algas has posted once in the last year
on his birthday thread



[b]Final note:[/b]
I know that it seems useless that I&#39;m actually trying to help a dying community, but that&#39;s just the attitude that needs to change.


I might expand on this later. Post your thoughts below.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 11 Nov 2011 12:45:08 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>General Discussion</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/staff-reform-revised/420922.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Staff reform (revised)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@davidi2 Davidi2]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/davidi2">@davidi2</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Your post contained nothing except a picture, so I considered it a ‘funny picture’ and nothing more. If you wanted discussion you probably should have started it out yourself. Feel free to remake the thread with more than just a picture this time <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/wink.png?v=5" title=":wink:" class="emoji" alt=":wink:"></p>
<p>And you’re implying all rule breaking is of the same stature and severity – that just isn’t true.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/staff-reform-revised/420922/79">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/staff-reform-revised/420922/79</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 11 Nov 2011 12:45:08 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-420922-79</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/staff-reform-revised/420922.rss">Staff reform (revised)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Staff reform (revised)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Rixxx Rix_]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/rixxx">@Rixxx</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Having the words “funny” in bold makes me think you’re an idiot. You’re even trying so hard by inferring the purpose of my thread. That’s cute. Anyway, I’ll just tell you the purpose of my thread (and no, I won’t bother to post another thread and argue how not funny it is :P). It’s simple, post first world solutions. It’s just mind-blowing concepts of items that easily solve daily problems we see.</p>
<p>If I didn’t expect discussion, why in the world would I even make a new thread for it?!  <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/cool.png?v=5" title=":cool:" class="emoji" alt=":cool:"> That’s flawed logic right there. Just so you know, the original gif was from The Hitchhiker’s Guide to the Galaxy. An item of the same concept can be found here: <a href="http://news.cnet.com/8301-17938_105-10234923-1.html" rel="nofollow noopener">http://news.cnet.com/8301-17938_105-10234923-1.html</a>  <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=5" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
<p>Having read your post, you’re undoubtedly a moderator with firm views. It certainly helps in enforcing blatantly obvious rules but not taking it lightly on other threads… that’s just annoying. It’s as though you’re trying to censor everything. Maybe this is why we can’t have nice things!</p>
<p>Back to staff breaking rules, Tico was once warned by Freddy1990 for flaming someone (as a global moderator). That’s fair moderating right there. I reported a post by you (I just checked, it’s been deleted) when Tom_BETA was online. He was the one who warned me. So he either completely missed the report or just deleted your post without warning you. That’s unfair. My point is moderators shouldn’t be let off for what other users may get warned for.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/staff-reform-revised/420922/78">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/staff-reform-revised/420922/78</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 11 Nov 2011 12:34:14 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-420922-78</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/staff-reform-revised/420922.rss">Staff reform (revised)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Staff reform (revised)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@davidi2 Davidi2]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/davidi2">@davidi2</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I’m not going to explain it again about your threads.</p>
<p><a href="http://www.funnyjunk.com/funny_pictures/2000767/Toaster+Knife/" data-bbcode="true">http://www.<span class="bbcode-b">funny</span>junk.com/<span class="bbcode-b">funny_pictures</span>/2000767/<span class="bbcode-b">Toaster+Knife</span></a></p>
<p>The image is faked of course, and its intent is to be funny in relation to first world countries being lazy (hence your title even relating to it) and I believe it belongs in the funny pictures thread. You didn’t have a single word in your thread besides the picture, so it’s not like you expected discussion.  It’s not really that complicated…</p>
<p>Which post was it? It may have been deleted, that’s probably what I would have done myself if there’s a single spam post you don’t think deserves a warning but still should be removed. Like I said, I doubt a normal user would have gotten a warning for it either.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/staff-reform-revised/420922/77">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/staff-reform-revised/420922/77</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 11 Nov 2011 12:02:32 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-420922-77</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/staff-reform-revised/420922.rss">Staff reform (revised)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Staff reform (revised)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Rixxx Rix_]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/rixxx">@Rixxx</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I don’t think it was even a mistake, in fact I feel you were using the “moderator’s discretion” bullshit to your advantage. It was a legitimate thread but you didn’t allow it. I thought it was hilarious that you felt that the gif of the toaster-knife was funny. I requested it to be removed because I don’t want to see two threads locked before the thread even received relevant replies.</p>
<p>Regarding your post, I notice that it’s been removed. Perhaps I can’t even find it because of your many posts within the last few weeks. Whoever didn’t warn you but removed it instead (if it’s the moderator who warned me for posting “stupid and gibberish” stuff) is truly biased. A moderator should be a role model of the community. Just because it happened only once (as it was in the case for me) doesn’t mean the moderator can be given a chance.</p>
<p>Staff should be equally subjected to the same rules as all other members and should be handled accordingly.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/staff-reform-revised/420922/76">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/staff-reform-revised/420922/76</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 11 Nov 2011 11:55:30 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-420922-76</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/staff-reform-revised/420922.rss">Staff reform (revised)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Staff reform (revised)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@davidi2 Davidi2]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/davidi2">@davidi2</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>You remade a thread I locked about a minute earlier without contacting me at all, and didn’t expect to be warned?</p>
<p>You obviously realized your mistake later which is why you requested them to be deleted, and I didn’t feel the need to oblige to be honest.</p>
<p>And no, I wouldn’t warn a user for my post (unless it was one of many recent ones), and I wont warn myself (possibly delete it, but that’s a different story). A different mod can if they see it differently and I wont complain, it’s all interpretation mod-to-mod.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/staff-reform-revised/420922/75">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/staff-reform-revised/420922/75</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 11 Nov 2011 11:46:15 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-420922-75</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/staff-reform-revised/420922.rss">Staff reform (revised)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Staff reform (revised)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Rixxx Rix_]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/rixxx">@Rixxx</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I blame your terrible perception on locking both threads and warning me for “spam”. 2 posts surely count for spam. <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=5" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"> Then there’s you on IRC always trying to avoid me when I wanted to question you about that and requested removal of both threads.</p>
<p>If you’ve already figured which post it was, you should probably warn yourself. That will make things a little fairer. Moderators can’t go around occasionally making mistakes of a normal member who got warned for it.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/staff-reform-revised/420922/74">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/staff-reform-revised/420922/74</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 11 Nov 2011 11:41:28 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-420922-74</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/staff-reform-revised/420922.rss">Staff reform (revised)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Staff reform (revised)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@davidi2 Davidi2]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/davidi2">@davidi2</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“Rix_, post:71, topic:420922”][quote author=Tom_BETA link=topic=523596.msg3809706#msg3809706 date=1320793437]<br>
Many? I can understand the CM part but I haven’t seen many staff members doing it. If you feel someone is getting away with breaking the rules then make your voice heard and link a staff member to it.<br>
[/quote]<br>
I’m sure you remember warning me for posting something relevant but you judged it to be “stupid and gibberish”. I reported a post by a moderator for the same reason but he hasn’t been warned at all. Was the report disregarded just because the reported person is a moderator?[/quote]Could be. Whenever I warn someone for spam/flame it’s usually a repeated offense (like remaking deleted/locked posts without asking :rolleyes: [but you’re not the only one ;)] type of thing – I’m not going to warn someone for making a spam post or getting angry once in a while. If someone continually does it, then sure, they need a slap on the wrist. That’s just my view.</p>
<p>[quote=“Rix_, post:71, topic:420922”][quote author=Davidi2 link=topic=523596.msg3809891#msg3809891 date=1320802361]<br>
Yea, at least t4 has a clean rec- oh wait…<br>
[/quote]<br>
I’m willing to bet that almost every moderator in the current staff team has been warned many times before.  ;)[/quote]No, that’s just me. I can’t speak for when they were new members (because those warnings aren’t in the log since we’ve upgraded [afaik], and they may have been mods since then). I plead guilty, and any look at any of my posts from before late 2011 it will probably support that haha.</p>
<p>Soulcist, I don’t think they would even know if they are inactive or not. Keeping them around doesn’t really seem lazy…</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/staff-reform-revised/420922/73">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/staff-reform-revised/420922/73</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 11 Nov 2011 11:37:26 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-420922-73</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/staff-reform-revised/420922.rss">Staff reform (revised)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Staff reform (revised)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Ix_Soulcist_xI Soulcist]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/ix_soulcist_xi">@Ix_Soulcist_xI</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>This forum will never change, this forum will never become one, this forum will never become something that a lot of posts have been created this board talking about how to change when we can’t even have those influential moderators to help us show us the correct way of doing things, enforcing the rules etc., showing members that we keep inactive moderators on the staff team isn’t a good thing either, shows that we’re lazy or something.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/staff-reform-revised/420922/72">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/staff-reform-revised/420922/72</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 11 Nov 2011 11:32:22 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-420922-72</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/staff-reform-revised/420922.rss">Staff reform (revised)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Staff reform (revised)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Rixxx Rix_]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/rixxx">@Rixxx</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote quote-modified" data-post="51" data-topic="420922">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 Tom_BETA:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Many? I can understand the CM part but I haven’t seen many staff members doing it. If you feel someone is getting away with breaking the rules then make your voice heard and link a staff member to it.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I’m sure you remember warning me for posting something relevant but you judged it to be “stupid and gibberish”. I reported a post by a moderator for the same reason but he hasn’t been warned at all. Was the report disregarded just because the reported person is a moderator?</p>
<aside class="quote quote-modified" data-post="57" data-topic="420922">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/user_avatar/forum.moparisthebest.com/davidi2/40/2579_1.png" class="avatar"> Davidi2:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Yea, at least t4 has a clean rec- oh wait…</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I’m willing to bet that almost every moderator in the current staff team has been warned many times before.  <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/wink.png?v=5" title=":wink:" class="emoji" alt=":wink:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/staff-reform-revised/420922/71">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/staff-reform-revised/420922/71</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 11 Nov 2011 11:24:43 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-420922-71</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/staff-reform-revised/420922.rss">Staff reform (revised)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Staff reform (revised)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@marcbob marcbob]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/marcbob">@marcbob</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>People having lives = demotion - That doesn’t make sense. If someone hasn’t even posted in a year or some insane amount of time, that is different. Otherwise who cares, just chill damn.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/staff-reform-revised/420922/70">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/staff-reform-revised/420922/70</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 09 Nov 2011 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-420922-70</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/staff-reform-revised/420922.rss">Staff reform (revised)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Staff reform (revised)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@CoonHunter CoonHunter]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/coonhunter">@CoonHunter</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I’m kinda agreeing that demoting staff isn’t necessary just because they are inactive. Only time for that is when that member gets out of hand. May just need a new mod or 2 but I really don’t think it will help too much in the long run. A new mod goes crazy in the report solving and eventually goes to the status most of the mods currently hold.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/staff-reform-revised/420922/69">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/staff-reform-revised/420922/69</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 09 Nov 2011 02:56:39 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-420922-69</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/staff-reform-revised/420922.rss">Staff reform (revised)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Staff reform (revised)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@krackkid Krackkid]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/krackkid">@krackkid</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“reyx7, post:66, topic:420922”]About 4 minutes. Nice time, staff.[/quote]I told chaos in 2, But you know david.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/staff-reform-revised/420922/68">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/staff-reform-revised/420922/68</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 09 Nov 2011 02:50:17 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-420922-68</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/staff-reform-revised/420922.rss">Staff reform (revised)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Staff reform (revised)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@davidi2 Davidi2]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/davidi2">@davidi2</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Thanks <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/wink.png?v=5" title=":wink:" class="emoji" alt=":wink:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/staff-reform-revised/420922/67">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/staff-reform-revised/420922/67</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 09 Nov 2011 02:49:02 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-420922-67</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/staff-reform-revised/420922.rss">Staff reform (revised)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Staff reform (revised)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@reyx7 reyx7]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/reyx7">@reyx7</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>About 4 minutes. Nice time, staff.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/staff-reform-revised/420922/66">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/staff-reform-revised/420922/66</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 09 Nov 2011 02:48:22 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-420922-66</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/staff-reform-revised/420922.rss">Staff reform (revised)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Staff reform (revised)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Stupit Stu]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/stupit">@Stupit</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote" data-post="64" data-topic="420922">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/reyx7/40/5_e05bb34c421432ee4d40de30c10af3e5.png" class="avatar"> reyx7:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Is someone testing the staff with the bots?</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Wouldn’t doubt it.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/staff-reform-revised/420922/65">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/staff-reform-revised/420922/65</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 09 Nov 2011 02:45:13 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-420922-65</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/staff-reform-revised/420922.rss">Staff reform (revised)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Staff reform (revised)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@reyx7 reyx7]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/reyx7">@reyx7</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Is someone testing the staff with the bots?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/staff-reform-revised/420922/64">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/staff-reform-revised/420922/64</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 09 Nov 2011 02:44:11 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-420922-64</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/staff-reform-revised/420922.rss">Staff reform (revised)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Staff reform (revised)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Stupit Stu]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/stupit">@Stupit</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“t4, post:62, topic:420922”][quote author=Davidi2 link=topic=523596.msg3809891#msg3809891 date=1320802361]<br>
Yea, at least t4 has a clean rec-</p>
<p>oh wait…<br>
[/quote]<br>
i’d lay down the law, though :P[/quote]<br>
t4 would have a massive e-peen by the end of his banhammar spree if he ever got moderator.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/staff-reform-revised/420922/63">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/staff-reform-revised/420922/63</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 09 Nov 2011 02:43:54 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-420922-63</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/staff-reform-revised/420922.rss">Staff reform (revised)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Staff reform (revised)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@T41 t4]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/t41">@T41</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“Davidi2, post:57, topic:420922”]Yea, at least t4 has a clean rec-</p>
<p>oh wait…[/quote]<br>
i’d lay down the law, though <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=5" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/staff-reform-revised/420922/62">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/staff-reform-revised/420922/62</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 09 Nov 2011 02:25:58 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-420922-62</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/staff-reform-revised/420922.rss">Staff reform (revised)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Staff reform (revised)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Ix_Soulcist_xI Soulcist]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/ix_soulcist_xi">@Ix_Soulcist_xI</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote quote-modified" data-post="58" data-topic="420922">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/frell/40/5_e05bb34c421432ee4d40de30c10af3e5.png" class="avatar"> Frell:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Id like to add in i’ve always supported the idea for single section moparscape moderators along with global moderators. I know when I was the sectional of the models section I turned that bitch around and didn’t take any shit <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=5" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>What the Hell ever happened to that? I believe that is so much better, take that position and then be promoted to full moderator.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/staff-reform-revised/420922/61">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/staff-reform-revised/420922/61</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 09 Nov 2011 01:37:25 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-420922-61</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/staff-reform-revised/420922.rss">Staff reform (revised)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Staff reform (revised)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Frell Frell]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/frell">@Frell</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>No, although Dylan was very helpful.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/staff-reform-revised/420922/60">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/staff-reform-revised/420922/60</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 09 Nov 2011 01:37:14 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-420922-60</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/staff-reform-revised/420922.rss">Staff reform (revised)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Staff reform (revised)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@davidi2 Davidi2]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/davidi2">@davidi2</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“Frell, post:58, topic:420922”]Id like to add in i’ve always supported the idea for single section moparscape moderators along with global moderators. I know when I was the sectional of the models section I turned that bitch around and didn’t take any shit :)[/quote]dude i remember that, wasn’t there someone else with you?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/staff-reform-revised/420922/59">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/staff-reform-revised/420922/59</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 09 Nov 2011 01:36:34 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-420922-59</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/staff-reform-revised/420922.rss">Staff reform (revised)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Staff reform (revised)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Frell Frell]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/frell">@Frell</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Id like to add in i’ve always supported the idea for single section moparscape moderators along with global moderators. I know when I was the sectional of the models section I turned that bitch around and didn’t take any shit <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=5" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/staff-reform-revised/420922/58">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/staff-reform-revised/420922/58</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 09 Nov 2011 01:35:10 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-420922-58</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/staff-reform-revised/420922.rss">Staff reform (revised)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Staff reform (revised)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@davidi2 Davidi2]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/davidi2">@davidi2</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Yea, at least t4 has a clean rec-</p>
<p>oh wait…</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/staff-reform-revised/420922/57">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/staff-reform-revised/420922/57</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 09 Nov 2011 01:32:41 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-420922-57</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/staff-reform-revised/420922.rss">Staff reform (revised)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Staff reform (revised)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@T41 t4]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/t41">@T41</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>you guys no like me :’(</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/staff-reform-revised/420922/56">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/staff-reform-revised/420922/56</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 09 Nov 2011 01:30:52 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-420922-56</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/staff-reform-revised/420922.rss">Staff reform (revised)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Staff reform (revised)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Frell Frell]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/frell">@Frell</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>No need to reform really. The staff turnover rate is pretty fast here but ill usually go out of my way to stop a board spamming etc.</p>
<p>Our staff is secure for the most part, which I can’t say for some other forums…</p>
<p>I am also in my final year of highschool and sort of need the time right now. Im also involved in something else but no info about that goes to you guys <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/smiley.png?v=5" title=":smiley:" class="emoji" alt=":smiley:"></p>
<p>As for MGD, me and Taharok were sort of hit with the aforementioned ‘project’ and we became really diverted, and only 7 people signed up for moparmon…</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/staff-reform-revised/420922/55">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/staff-reform-revised/420922/55</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 09 Nov 2011 01:29:23 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-420922-55</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/staff-reform-revised/420922.rss">Staff reform (revised)</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
