<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Nice going</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/nice-going/449840</link>
    <description>who the hell gave sinisoul his cup back, and why?

Edit:
If the logic is that he knows java then well yeah, anyone can learn a language (syntax and such) and create compilable, working code. My main complaint is that his designs are flawed and he has a knack for over complicating some procedures just for the hell of it - see: linked list impl that shows up in every damn release he makes. Not to mention in a conversation with him he didn&#39;t know what the time complexity of a linked lost was :/...

So, yeah... This thread is more about a frustration with standards and what makes a personal qualified than a flat out rant against the guy. But, uh if the standards are just knowing the language enough to make a working application then I feel that a lot of people qualify... Which sort of defeats the entire purpose of the award. Hell, by those standards I should have a mew - and I&#39;m sure there&#39;d be some speculation and concern from the old guard over that...</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 16 Jul 2012 14:06:45 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Community Suggestions</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/nice-going/449840.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Nice going</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@T41 t4]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/t41">@T41</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Stupid network</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/nice-going/449840/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/nice-going/449840/2</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 16 Jul 2012 14:06:45 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-449840-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/nice-going/449840.rss">Nice going</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Nice going</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@T41 t4]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/t41">@T41</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>who the hell gave sinisoul his cup back, and why?</p>
<p>Edit:<br>
If the logic is that he knows java then well yeah, anyone can learn a language (syntax and such) and create compilable, working code. My main complaint is that his designs are flawed and he has a knack for over complicating some procedures just for the hell of it - see: linked list impl that shows up in every damn release he makes. Not to mention in a conversation with him he didn’t know what the time complexity of a linked lost was :/…</p>
<p>So, yeah… This thread is more about a frustration with standards and what makes a personal qualified than a flat out rant against the guy. But, uh if the standards are just knowing the language enough to make a working application then I feel that a lot of people qualify… Which sort of defeats the entire purpose of the award. Hell, by those standards I should have a mew - and I’m sure there’d be some speculation and concern from the old guard over that…</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/nice-going/449840/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/nice-going/449840/1</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 16 Jul 2012 12:28:03 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-449840-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/nice-going/449840.rss">Nice going</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
