<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Client Help</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/client-help/305018</link>
    <description>[b]Ok, I&#39;ve came on here quite a bit to look stuff up, and this is the first time I&#39;ve actually had to ask for help. I&#39;ve searched for this, but everything is just out of whack. I&#39;m so terrible at coding things. Just to get that out of the way. 

I just want to add one code into the client.

::setobject

Easy as hell for a lot of people. Not for me. If you can I need the code and where to put it at and what to edit. I seriously suck at clients this much, so if anyone can help me out; it would be greatly appreciated!

If it helps any, I&#39;m wanting to add this onto Webber&#39;s Cheat Client V1. The first one he came out with when he was an Admin on Dodian. In fact, I think it may be the only Cheat Client, he&#39;s came out with so far. Plus if you just want to be cool, and throw in some more cool stuff that isn&#39;t too hard for someone like me go right ahead. :) 

~Matt[/b]</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 28 Sep 2009 14:45:13 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Game Development</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/client-help/305018.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Client Help</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@omgjeez omgjeez]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/omgjeez">@omgjeez</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[b]Ok, I’ve came on here quite a bit to look stuff up, and this is the first time I’ve actually had to ask for help. I’ve searched for this, but everything is just out of whack. I’m so terrible at coding things. Just to get that out of the way.</p>
<p>I just want to add one code into the client.</p>
<p>::setobject</p>
<p>Easy as hell for a lot of people. Not for me. If you can I need the code and where to put it at and what to edit. I seriously suck at clients this much, so if anyone can help me out; it would be greatly appreciated!</p>
<p>If it helps any, I’m wanting to add this onto Webber’s Cheat Client V1. The first one he came out with when he was an Admin on Dodian. In fact, I think it may be the only Cheat Client, he’s came out with so far. Plus if you just want to be cool, and throw in some more cool stuff that isn’t too hard for someone like me go right ahead. <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=5" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
<p>~Matt[/b]</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/client-help/305018/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/client-help/305018/1</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 28 Sep 2009 14:45:13 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-305018-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/client-help/305018.rss">Client Help</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
