<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Client help</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/client-help/371349</link>
    <description>Can someone please tell me how to fix this.. I have a 508 client a 525 client the whole 9 yards.. these 614 sources are looking really cool so i decideds to get a 614 client. I got the 614cache with it and put it into my C drive or whatever its called. so anyway i changed the host names from 127.0.0.1 to my hamachi, I click run with the client ( my source is running fine and yes its a 614 ) and i get this mssge system cannot find the path specifyed or whatever. can somebody please tell me why this is happening. i fixed this problem in the past , I tryed switching the java by right clicking run and switching java i tryed a few diffrent java things for windows 7 so anyway this problem is getting me mad.. if smeone has team viewer and thinks they can do it for me just mssge me thanks.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 02 Dec 2010 01:17:45 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/client-help/371349.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Client help</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@runyluny runyluny]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/runyluny">@runyluny</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Can someone please tell me how to fix this… I have a 508 client a 525 client the whole 9 yards… these 614 sources are looking really cool so i decideds to get a 614 client. I got the 614cache with it and put it into my C drive or whatever its called. so anyway i changed the host names from 127.0.0.1 to my hamachi, I click run with the client ( my source is running fine and yes its a 614 ) and i get this mssge system cannot find the path specifyed or whatever. can somebody please tell me why this is happening. i fixed this problem in the past , I tryed switching the java by right clicking run and switching java i tryed a few diffrent java things for windows 7 so anyway this problem is getting me mad… if smeone has team viewer and thinks they can do it for me just mssge me thanks.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/client-help/371349/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/client-help/371349/1</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 02 Dec 2010 01:17:45 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-371349-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/client-help/371349.rss">Client help</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
