<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Multiple Thread Pools</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/multiple-thread-pools/538632</link>
    <description>I&#39;ve been designing how the threading will work in my game to allow the best usage of multiple cores. Clearly a thread pool is the best way to go, but I&#39;m curious if I should just use one or multiple.

My whole thinking process was &quot;What if I have a thread pool with 4 working threads and dispatch 4 tasks that all use some sort of mutex that possibly blocks each task for some period of time? Then let&#39;s say I dispatch 4 more tasks while the original 4 are still working that perform an algorithm and would never be blocked. Wouldn&#39;t that waste time waiting for another task to finish that could be spent actually computing something?&quot;

The obvious answer that comes to mind is yes, and I should have at least two specific thread pools for dealing with tasks that are entirely exclusive and others that are mutually exclusive. But from what I&#39;m reading this isn&#39;t a common practice. For example, with the .NET framework there is only one thread pool to be used and to have more would require you to write your own. Of course, I could just increase the amount of threads I have in my thread pool to 8 in the above example and everything would be just fine, but maybe it would be smarter to limit the amount of specific tasks being performed simultaneously and be sure to always leave room for the independent ones.

I&#39;m probably thinking way outside the box and just a simple thread pool would be sufficient for what I&#39;m doing. But it did get me thinking. What is your take on the subject?

~Lin</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2014 02:31:31 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>General Programming</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/multiple-thread-pools/538632.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Multiple Thread Pools</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@lothy Lothy]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/lothy">@lothy</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Locking is something that you <em>always</em> have to do unless you’ve chosen to use volatile fields or atomic values instead.<br>
Basically you need the resulting bytecode to emit a memory fence instruction at runtime, otherwise you’re going to have cache consistency issues (i.e., one cpu core sees true even though the value was set to false a moment ago by another).</p>
<p>It’s no secret that the vast majority of things don’t endlessly gain performance when scaling to more cores. That’s why I’ve said that tasks to be execute on the thread pool need to be discrete and independent, rather than interdependent on too many other things. When this is the case you would reasonably expect a performance increase for most of the tasks being execute (again, though, you’ll find that some highly contended pieces of code will be a bottleneck).</p>
<p>The trick is to know when to favour atomic operations instead of locks. You’ll find that parts of code which are either lightly or not at all contentious benefit substantially from atomic operations; there’s no spurious failure when writing to the memory.<br>
However when you use atomics in highly contended code then they can fail to be updated as many as n times (n being the number of threads).</p>
<p>You’re right. I probably am oversimplifying it for anyone reading that isn’t a bit practiced with the APIs in question. But it’s not rocket science either.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/multiple-thread-pools/538632/12">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/multiple-thread-pools/538632/12</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2014 02:31:31 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-538632-12</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/multiple-thread-pools/538632.rss">Multiple Thread Pools</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Multiple Thread Pools</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@mod_taharok Taharok]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/mod_taharok">@mod_taharok</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“Lothy, post:10, topic:538632”]The overhead of locking is very low unless something is actually under contention. In practice the 80/20 rule will come into play and proper profiling would identify the most contention-prone sections.</p>
<p>Anyway, with the executor and concurrency API in Java it’s actually relatively easy to get it right. I don’t know how C/C++ are coming along (they do have a specification for memory access within the context of concurrency now) but I suspect it’s much harder in those languages.[/quote]</p>
<p>Performance is not just useful in engine architecture, it’s necessary. I still think you’re oversimplifying a rather complicated problem. Even with the 80/20 or even 90/10 rule, just “throwing more threads at the problem” won’t actually guarantee it will be faster. Locking becomes rather expensive if you have to do it a lot, which you will without very careful design. Any time not doing engine-related tasks is time wasted, which includes waiting on another thread to finish mutex access to some area of memory.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/multiple-thread-pools/538632/11">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/multiple-thread-pools/538632/11</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 18 Jan 2014 23:16:30 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-538632-11</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/multiple-thread-pools/538632.rss">Multiple Thread Pools</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Multiple Thread Pools</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@lothy Lothy]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/lothy">@lothy</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>The overhead of locking is very low unless something is actually under contention. In practice the 80/20 rule will come into play and proper profiling would identify the most contention-prone sections.</p>
<p>Anyway, with the executor and concurrency API in Java it’s actually relatively easy to get it right. I don’t know how C/C++ are coming along (they do have a specification for memory access within the context of concurrency now) but I suspect it’s much harder in those languages.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/multiple-thread-pools/538632/10">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/multiple-thread-pools/538632/10</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2014 11:22:54 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-538632-10</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/multiple-thread-pools/538632.rss">Multiple Thread Pools</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Multiple Thread Pools</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@mod_taharok Taharok]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/mod_taharok">@mod_taharok</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“Lothy, post:8, topic:538632”][quote author=Taharok link=topic=657463.msg4398478#msg4398478 date=1389849387]<br>
Are you sure you actually want to go multi-threaded?<br>
[/quote]<br>
It’s 2014. Processors are now designed with power consumption as the primary focus, and concurrent capability is only growing.<br>
Anyone who chooses to write single-threaded applications (besides trivial applications without substantial workload) in 2014 deserves to be shot.[/quote]</p>
<p>Forgive me, but I consider your reply to be oversimplifying the matter. <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=5" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"> Game engines do not work like most other applications. You can’t just throw extra threads at it and expect it to get better performance. You have a complex network of inter-system dependencies to deal with and it takes a very experienced concurrency programmer to reduce race conditions to publicly shared data (especially thinking of game content scripts here) to the point of not causing huge performance loss when multiple threads are communicating with one another. Honestly, it is very difficult to program a multi-threaded game engine that actually increases performance. You can use <span class="bbcode-i">threading</span> to separate tasks (such as graphics for one, a main thread for everything else), but this situation is not multi-threading and it does not scale to n threads.</p>
<p>[quote=“0xCAFEBABE, post:7, topic:538632”]Here are a few links to a website containing useful information about game engines (both multithreading and in general). The multithreading articles are in four parts.</p>
<p><a href="http://blog.slapware.eu/" class="onebox" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">http://blog.slapware.eu/</a><br>
<a href="http://blog.slapware.eu/game-engine/review-and-refacturing/multithreaded-game-engine-discussion/" class="onebox" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">http://blog.slapware.eu/game-engine/review-and-refacturing/multithreaded-game-engine-discussion/</a></p>
<p>As a side note, if you aren’t already, set the Processor Affinity for your threads. That “might” speed things up, as it results in fewer cache misses.[/quote]</p>
<p>It might reduce cache misses, but that’s due to what affinity actually does. Affinity asks the operating system to try and schedule the application on the same thread for every time slice. It’s not guaranteed to be granted and it may not actually increase performance benefits. A lower amount of cache misses is possible, but definitely not guaranteed. As far as I understand it, affinity also does not describe what to do with any other processes. Even if your application has affinity to core <span class="hashtag">#2</span>, for example, even though it may always execute on core <span class="hashtag">#2</span>, other applications may still be scheduled to run on core <span class="hashtag">#2</span> as well. I see cache misses being just as liking in that case, since you can’t actually completely dedicate a core to your application.</p>
<p>[quote=“Lin, post:6, topic:538632”][quote author=Taharok link=topic=657463.msg4398478#msg4398478 date=1389849387]<br>
If this is for a game engine, I can’t begin to start because the top is simply too large to say in one message. I was just talking with one of my professors today about threading in a multi-threaded game engine and the topic is both very complex and difficult in a lot of ways. There’s many things to consider and, overall, there are soooooooooo many problems that can happen. Also, bear in mind there is a difference between multi-threaded and threading approaches to architecture. Are you sure you actually want to go multi-threaded? If this isn’t related directly to the game engine, then I will be happy to post something irt to that.<br>
[/quote]</p>
<p>It is indeed for a game engine. With how my game is going to function, it would do better on a multi-core processor. Or it should with my current designs. In a nutshell, I planned on splitting the world up into fixed-sized containers, or “chunks” if you want to use the Minecraft term. Each chunk would contain a vertex buffer for the mesh that would get drawn. When you begin to edit the terrain, if the changes were big enough, all chunks involved would be switched to GPU-generated mesh rendering, where a geometry shader would be used to generate the mesh for that chunk instead of re-generating the mesh on the CPU over and over again. After the user has stopped editing the terrain for a certain amount of time, a different thread would start regenerating the mesh for that chunk. Once finished the chunk would switch back to the cached version. Since chunks would be independent of each other and the chunk’s terrain values wouldn’t be modified on the generator thread, I don’t see any immediate issues.</p>
<p>However the I wish to run a lot of other procedures on other threads as well. I’d like a lot of the in-game “hardware” (it’s a mechanic I’m currently designing. Video <a href="http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=1MP7j8_7YdE" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">here</a> for clarification) processing to be on separate threads since it all can probably be run in parallel. It’s difficult to explain this situation because I don’t want to give away too many of the ideas I have.</p>
<p>I’m assuming what you mean between multi-threaded and threading approaches to architecture are basically running multiple tasks on one core so the procedures aren’t blocking others from running vs using multiple cores so the tasks run completely in parallel. The latter is what I’m trying to achieve, as I stated in the second sentence of this post. Also I’m aware of the memory conflicts I might have to deal with if I’m not careful with how I set things up.</p>
<p>However, it would appear there is no general answer to this topic. It would make sense to have a thread pool dedicated to rebuilding a chunk’s mesh, since nothing ever depends on the chunk’s mesh itself - its strictly for rendering only. But then there would be empty threads spending most of their time idling. Perhaps I’ll finish designing how everything will be processed and figure out how the tasks can be split up and go from there instead of making making early assumptions. Thank you for the input.[/quote]</p>
<p>Threading means you’re using a few threads to handle different aspects of the engine that are independent (which sounds a lot like how you want to approach this), whereas multithreaded indicates an architecture that operates on n threads and multithreads EVERYTHING in the engine. There are many approaches to this, but a lot of them are not very good. My own opinion is limited because despite any concurrency programming I’ve done, I have done very little when it comes to game engines. The problem becomes much more complex. It’s naive to assume adding threads to a game engine will increase performance–it’s not even close to that simple. I’m sure you understand that some portions of the engine’s update procedure have to wait on other things (synchronous tasks), but sub-parts of those other parts can be run in parallel (asynchronous tasks). This is a good start to doing multi-threading, though be wary that actually creating a task scheduler that works with n threads has its own complications:</p>
<p>-Ideally, you want to be able to schedule and execute tasks without locking (lockless queues, for example) or you want to reduce locking, because it eats up ridiculous amounts of time<br>
-You want to reduce race conditions; if you multi-thread game logic, any time you access a variable that’s outside of local function scope its access has to be monitored for fear of concurrent modification, or you can switch to a pure-functional language or use an event-driven language with strict rules and use messaging systems to try and reduce the need for global variables, thus eliminating race conditions and a ton of locks</p>
<p>Things like this will help the multi-threaded architecture be better, but you will need to write this engine in various single-threaded and multi-threaded architectures and profile to figure out which is best. In the very least, using a threading approach to optimize graphics is probably a huge performance boost for you. You might not even need to use multi-threading elsewhere. If it’s pure academic, go for it. If it’s to actually optimize things, profile more of your game engine and figure out if you actually have bottlenecks in locations that can be executed in parallel. If your bottlenecks are in places that have to be done synchronously or can’t be optimized with multiple threads, doing a multi-threaded arch won’t improve performance. And, without a lot of experience doing multi-threaded programming, you may even ruin your performance a bit or even hugely.</p>
<p>I had something else to add, but I seem to have forgotten it. There are plenty of resources for multi-threaded architectures, but be skeptical (as you always should in software engineering).</p>
<p>2c</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/multiple-thread-pools/538632/9">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/multiple-thread-pools/538632/9</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2014 05:24:35 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-538632-9</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/multiple-thread-pools/538632.rss">Multiple Thread Pools</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Multiple Thread Pools</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@lothy Lothy]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/lothy">@lothy</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote" data-post="5" data-topic="538632">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 Taharok:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Are you sure you actually want to go multi-threaded?</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>It’s 2014. Processors are now designed with power consumption as the primary focus, and concurrent capability is only growing.<br>
Anyone who chooses to write single-threaded applications (besides trivial applications without substantial workload) in 2014 deserves to be shot.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/multiple-thread-pools/538632/8">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/multiple-thread-pools/538632/8</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2014 10:50:49 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-538632-8</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/multiple-thread-pools/538632.rss">Multiple Thread Pools</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Multiple Thread Pools</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@0xCAFEBABE 0xCAFEBABE]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/0xcafebabe">@0xCAFEBABE</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Here are a few links to a website containing useful information about game engines (both multithreading and in general). The multithreading articles are in four parts.</p>
<p><a href="http://blog.slapware.eu/" class="onebox" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">http://blog.slapware.eu/</a><br>
<a href="http://blog.slapware.eu/game-engine/review-and-refacturing/multithreaded-game-engine-discussion/" class="onebox" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">http://blog.slapware.eu/game-engine/review-and-refacturing/multithreaded-game-engine-discussion/</a></p>
<p>As a side note, if you aren’t already, set the Processor Affinity for your threads. That “might” speed things up, as it results in fewer cache misses.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/multiple-thread-pools/538632/7">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/multiple-thread-pools/538632/7</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2014 10:18:35 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-538632-7</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/multiple-thread-pools/538632.rss">Multiple Thread Pools</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Multiple Thread Pools</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Lin Lin]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/lin">@Lin</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote" data-post="5" data-topic="538632">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 Taharok:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>If this is for a game engine, I can’t begin to start because the top is simply too large to say in one message. I was just talking with one of my professors today about threading in a multi-threaded game engine and the topic is both very complex and difficult in a lot of ways. There’s many things to consider and, overall, there are soooooooooo many problems that can happen. Also, bear in mind there is a difference between multi-threaded and threading approaches to architecture. Are you sure you actually want to go multi-threaded? If this isn’t related directly to the game engine, then I will be happy to post something irt to that.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>It is indeed for a game engine. With how my game is going to function, it would do better on a multi-core processor. Or it should with my current designs. In a nutshell, I planned on splitting the world up into fixed-sized containers, or “chunks” if you want to use the Minecraft term. Each chunk would contain a vertex buffer for the mesh that would get drawn. When you begin to edit the terrain, if the changes were big enough, all chunks involved would be switched to GPU-generated mesh rendering, where a geometry shader would be used to generate the mesh for that chunk instead of re-generating the mesh on the CPU over and over again. After the user has stopped editing the terrain for a certain amount of time, a different thread would start regenerating the mesh for that chunk. Once finished the chunk would switch back to the cached version. Since chunks would be independent of each other and the chunk’s terrain values wouldn’t be modified on the generator thread, I don’t see any immediate issues.</p>
<p>However the I wish to run a lot of other procedures on other threads as well. I’d like a lot of the in-game “hardware” (it’s a mechanic I’m currently designing. Video <a href="http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=1MP7j8_7YdE" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">here</a> for clarification) processing to be on separate threads since it all can probably be run in parallel. It’s difficult to explain this situation because I don’t want to give away too many of the ideas I have.</p>
<p>I’m assuming what you mean between multi-threaded and threading approaches to architecture are basically running multiple tasks on one core so the procedures aren’t blocking others from running vs using multiple cores so the tasks run completely in parallel. The latter is what I’m trying to achieve, as I stated in the second sentence of this post. Also I’m aware of the memory conflicts I might have to deal with if I’m not careful with how I set things up.</p>
<p>However, it would appear there is no general answer to this topic. It would make sense to have a thread pool dedicated to rebuilding a chunk’s mesh, since nothing ever depends on the chunk’s mesh itself - its strictly for rendering only. But then there would be empty threads spending most of their time idling. Perhaps I’ll finish designing how everything will be processed and figure out how the tasks can be split up and go from there instead of making making early assumptions. Thank you for the input.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/multiple-thread-pools/538632/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/multiple-thread-pools/538632/6</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2014 09:26:06 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-538632-6</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/multiple-thread-pools/538632.rss">Multiple Thread Pools</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Multiple Thread Pools</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@mod_taharok Taharok]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/mod_taharok">@mod_taharok</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>If this is for a game engine, I can’t begin to start because the top is simply too large to say in one message. I was just talking with one of my professors today about threading in a multi-threaded game engine and the topic is both very complex and difficult in a lot of ways. There’s many things to consider and, overall, there are soooooooooo many problems that can happen. Also, bear in mind there is a difference between multi-threaded and threading approaches to architecture. Are you sure you actually want to go multi-threaded? If this isn’t related directly to the game engine, then I will be happy to post something irt to that.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/multiple-thread-pools/538632/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/multiple-thread-pools/538632/5</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2014 05:16:27 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-538632-5</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/multiple-thread-pools/538632.rss">Multiple Thread Pools</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Multiple Thread Pools</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@lothy Lothy]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/lothy">@lothy</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>You want two thread pools. One for queueing non-IO tasks, and one bounded thread pool (i.e., one or two threads max) for IO tasks.<br>
And then you need to make sure each task submitted for processing is discrete and independent of other tasks.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/multiple-thread-pools/538632/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/multiple-thread-pools/538632/4</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2014 10:36:52 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-538632-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/multiple-thread-pools/538632.rss">Multiple Thread Pools</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Multiple Thread Pools</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Lin Lin]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/lin">@Lin</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Asynchronous callbacks still require a thread pool if you don’t want to deal with the expense of creating and destroying a thread every function call. You’re thinking one level ahead.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/multiple-thread-pools/538632/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/multiple-thread-pools/538632/3</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2014 10:33:10 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-538632-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/multiple-thread-pools/538632.rss">Multiple Thread Pools</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Multiple Thread Pools</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@DefLegende DefLegende]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/deflegende">@DefLegende</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Have you tried using async callbacks?</p>
<p>I think they could be the way to go as they allow the code to be run without blocking the caller and returns a callback when it’s done.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/multiple-thread-pools/538632/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/multiple-thread-pools/538632/2</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2014 08:23:46 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-538632-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/multiple-thread-pools/538632.rss">Multiple Thread Pools</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Multiple Thread Pools</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Lin Lin]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/lin">@Lin</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I’ve been designing how the threading will work in my game to allow the best usage of multiple cores. Clearly a thread pool is the best way to go, but I’m curious if I should just use one or multiple.</p>
<p>My whole thinking process was “What if I have a thread pool with 4 working threads and dispatch 4 tasks that all use some sort of mutex that possibly blocks each task for some period of time? Then let’s say I dispatch 4 more tasks while the original 4 are still working that perform an algorithm and would never be blocked. Wouldn’t that waste time waiting for another task to finish that could be spent actually computing something?”</p>
<p>The obvious answer that comes to mind is yes, and I should have at least two specific thread pools for dealing with tasks that are entirely exclusive and others that are mutually exclusive. But from what I’m reading this isn’t a common practice. For example, with the .NET framework there is only one thread pool to be used and to have more would require you to write your own. Of course, I could just increase the amount of threads I have in my thread pool to 8 in the above example and everything would be just fine, but maybe it would be smarter to limit the amount of specific tasks being performed simultaneously and be sure to always leave room for the independent ones.</p>
<p>I’m probably thinking way outside the box and just a simple thread pool would be sufficient for what I’m doing. But it did get me thinking. What is your take on the subject?</p>
<p>~Lin</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/multiple-thread-pools/538632/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/multiple-thread-pools/538632/1</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2014 02:12:42 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-538632-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/multiple-thread-pools/538632.rss">Multiple Thread Pools</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
