<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Help me plz</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/help-me-plz/237854</link>
    <description>hello, i have a small problem. I cannot find out where to download [b]java 6 update 7[/b]. I can find out where to download all the other ones... but sadly, not the one im looking for. I can do everything else but i need to find out where to download java because i have the wrong one, therefore, i cannot set the correct classpath and path, so if someone could help me and give me the link where i can get java 6 update 7 that would be greeeeat.
TYVFM
Jimmy
P.S. Plz dont send me http://java.sun.com/javase/downloads/index.jsp  or tell me to go into the server tutorial becuase its no help..... TYVFM
It seams as though there is noone to help me create a server, so.... If anyone has a server, that they dont use or dont want, i can host 4u, plzzzz</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2008 18:03:56 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/help-me-plz/237854.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Help me plz</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Jimmy88 Jimmy88]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/jimmy88">@Jimmy88</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>hello, i have a small problem. I cannot find out where to download <span class="bbcode-b">java 6 update 7</span>. I can find out where to download all the other ones… but sadly, not the one im looking for. I can do everything else but i need to find out where to download java because i have the wrong one, therefore, i cannot set the correct classpath and path, so if someone could help me and give me the link where i can get java 6 update 7 that would be greeeeat.<br>
TYVFM<br>
Jimmy<br>
P.S. Plz dont send me <a href="http://java.sun.com/javase/downloads/index.jsp" rel="nofollow noopener">http://java.sun.com/javase/downloads/index.jsp</a>  or tell me to go into the server tutorial becuase its no help… TYVFM<br>
It seams as though there is noone to help me create a server, so… If anyone has a server, that they dont use or dont want, i can host 4u, plzzzz</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/help-me-plz/237854/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/help-me-plz/237854/1</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2008 18:03:56 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-237854-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/help-me-plz/237854.rss">Help me plz</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
