<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Html &amp; css [updated]</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/html-css-updated/399467</link>
    <description>This guide will take you step by step in coding a HTML page. Love it, hate it, but no flaming. I&#39;m going to try to make this the biggest tutorial in MoparScape! So if you have anything to add or want to see anything you want to learn, please post and I will try to post it! 

[b]Table of Contents[/b]
&lt;blockquote&gt;Prologue
Chapter 1 - Learning the Ropes
~HTML
~~Step 1: Setting up a structure for your HTML page
~~Step 2: Adding content to your page
~CSS

Chapter 2 - Making our site sexy
~Graphics
~CSS
~HTML

Chapter 3 - Adding detail to the site (Coming today)&lt;/blockquote&gt;

[b][i][u]PROLOGUE[/u][/i][/b]
Thank-you for looking at this step by step guide to learning HTML. While doing this guide, you should be able to learn how to make a proper HTML and CSS pages, be able to do a lot with CSS and be able to make pro websites without using a pre-made site. This is for LEARNING PURPOSES ONLY and should only posted on MoparScape. I do NOT give permission for this to be re-posted on any other site. Thank-you for looking.

[b][i][u]CHAPTER 1 - LEARNING THE ROPES[/u][/i][/b]

[b][u]HTML[/u][/b]
[b][u]Step 1: Setting up a structure for your HTML page[/u][/b]
The basic structure of a HTML page consists of 3 main codes:

[ul][li]&lt;head&gt;[/li]
[li]&lt;body&gt;[/li]
[li]&lt;footer&gt;[/li][/ul]

These all have their specific meaning to them. &lt;head&gt; being the head of it all. This holds codes for the title, favorite icon, styles and other imports such as style sheets. The &lt;body&gt; holds everything that&#39;s in your page, the text, images and other boxes. The &lt;footer&gt; holds everything you want down below such as the credits and other miscellaneous links. This is one of the most important things to know about coding HTML.
[code=Example]&lt;head&gt;
CONTENT
&lt;/head&gt;

&lt;body&gt;
CONTENT
&lt;/body&gt;

&lt;footer&gt;
CONTENT
&lt;/footer&gt;[/code]

When coding with HTML, once your done with a certain section you should put an end code on it: &lt;/CODE TO END&gt;. Sometimes, you do not put an end code on it, this is the case with some dividing codes. Now that we know the basics of setting up an HTML page, lets move on.

[b][u]Step 2: Adding content to your page[/u][/b]
We will start by doing the Header and working our way down.

As I said above, the header isn&#39;t really used to hold content that will be shown. We will be using codes such as &lt;title&gt; in it. &lt;title&gt; makes it so that the page has a title. We will also want a favorite icon, for this we will be using the code &lt;link href=&quot;PIC URL&quot; rel=&quot;icon&quot;&gt;. Now lets put this in our HTML code! As you see below, we will be using the end code for &lt;title&gt;.
[code]&lt;head&gt;
&lt;title&gt;My first page!&lt;/title&gt;
&lt;link href=&quot;PIC URL&quot; rel=&quot;icon&quot;&gt;
&lt;/head&gt;

&lt;body&gt;
CONTENT
&lt;/body&gt;

&lt;footer&gt;
CONTENT
&lt;/footer&gt;[/code]
There will be more to put into this, but for now, lets just leave it at this.

So, now we want to add content to our page! We should probably put in dividers so we can keep track of all this. To use a dividing, we will use the code &quot;&lt;div&gt;&quot;. We really will only use the dividing code in the Body of the page, sometimes the footer if we have more than one thing down there. We can also put more than text in here, we can put buttons and images too. To make a basic text button, we will use this code: &lt;a href=&quot;URL&quot;&gt;NAME&lt;/a&gt;. The code href will take you to the link that is in the quotations. If the page is inside your site, you don&#39;t have to put the full link, you may put something as simple as &quot;home.html&quot; or &quot;playnow.html&quot;. To put an image in we will be using the code &lt;img src=&quot;PIC URL&quot;&gt;. This will go and fetch the image from the url you put in. If you don&#39;t want your things all pushed to the left or right, we can put in a code that centers them. This code is &lt;center&gt;. Pretty self explanatory. If we only want something like the text or buttons centered, we may put the code &lt;center&gt; and then put the end code &lt;/center&gt; right after it, making the area inside those 2 codes centered. But if you want something aligned to the right, we should do something like this: &lt;align=&quot;right&quot;&gt;. That will put all the code to the right. If you just want it to go to the left, put &lt;align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;, or if you do not have any code that&#39;s aligning the page, just leave it blank since a HTML page automatically aligns to the left.
[code=Example]&lt;head&gt;
&lt;title&gt;My first page!&lt;/title&gt;
&lt;link href=&quot;PIC URL&quot; rel=&quot;icon&quot;&gt;
&lt;/head&gt;

&lt;body&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
&lt;center&gt;
&lt;a href=&quot;URL&quot;&gt;NAME&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/center&gt;
&lt;align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;PIC URL&quot;&gt;
&lt;/align&gt;
&lt;align=&quot;right&quot;&gt;
Welcome to the site!
&lt;/align&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/body&gt;

&lt;footer&gt;
CONTENT
&lt;/footer&gt;[/code]

Now, no one wants a plain old boring site with no color... So to put a color the the background, we will but this: &lt;style&gt;body { background-color:COLOR CODE; } &lt;style&gt;. This will make the background what ever color coder you put in. What if my text color clashes with my background color? No worries! Just put this: &lt;font color=&quot;COLOR CODE&quot;&gt;MESSAGE&lt;/font&gt;. That will change the color of the font inside those codes. If you want to have all the text on the page a certain color, we will replace your style code with this one: &lt;style&gt;body { background-color:COLOR CODE; color:COLOR CODE } &lt;style&gt;. To get color codes, I suggest using this site: [url=http://html-color-codes.info/]http://html-color-codes.info/[/url].
[code]&lt;head&gt;
&lt;title&gt;My first page!&lt;/title&gt;
&lt;link href=&quot;PIC URL&quot; rel=&quot;icon&quot;&gt;
&lt;/head&gt;

&lt;body&gt;
&lt;style&gt;body { background-color:#FF8000; color:#000000; } &lt;/style&gt;
&lt;div name=&quot;NAME&quot;&gt;
&lt;center&gt;
&lt;a href=&quot;URL&quot;&gt;NAME&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/center&gt;
&lt;align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;PIC URL&quot;&gt;
&lt;/align&gt;
&lt;align=&quot;right&quot;&gt;
Welcome to the site!
&lt;/align&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/body&gt;

&lt;footer&gt;
CONTENT
&lt;/footer&gt;[/code]

The style code can also be implemented in a different way. We can use it in another document called a CSS file. I will get into this at the end.

If you feel your text button is too boring and you want a cooler font, we can always change it. We can do this by putting &lt;font face=&quot;Arial&quot;&gt; in front of the button (it will also work for any text). We can also enlarge the text by putting in this code: &lt;font face=&quot;Arial&quot; size=&quot;20&quot;&gt; (again, goes for any text). What If you want a picture for a link? Great! We&#39;ll just put this: &lt;a href=&quot;URL&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;PIC URL&quot;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;. This will make the image inside of the &lt;a&gt; codes a button. 

Now, if you want certain things inside a box, you can put this code: &lt;fieldset&gt;. This will make it so that it puts a box around whatever is inside the &lt;fieldset&gt; code. We can also put a little message at the top by using &lt;legend&gt;. 
[code]&lt;head&gt;
&lt;title&gt;My first page!&lt;/title&gt;
&lt;link href=&quot;PIC URL&quot; rel=&quot;icon&quot;&gt;
&lt;/head&gt;

&lt;body&gt;
&lt;style&gt;body { background-color:#FF8000; color:#000000; } &lt;/style&gt;
&lt;div name=&quot;NAME&quot;&gt;
&lt;center&gt;
&lt;a href=&quot;URL&quot;&gt;NAME&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/center&gt;
&lt;fieldset&gt;
&lt;legend&gt;Body&lt;/legend&gt;
&lt;align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;PIC URL&quot;&gt;
&lt;/align&gt;
&lt;align=&quot;right&quot;&gt;
Welcome to the site!
&lt;/align&gt;
&lt;/fieldset&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/body&gt;

&lt;footer&gt;
CONTENT
&lt;/footer&gt;[/code]

Now, lets look at the footer. Usually, we see credits and links to Terms of service and development teams (stuff like that) in the footer. So I&#39;m going to make this part clean and fast. You will want to put something like this: &amp;copy;2011 My Site. You may also want to put links and stuff, in text regular size is the best way to go (for how to make a button, look above). 
[code]&lt;head&gt;
&lt;title&gt;My first page!&lt;/title&gt;
&lt;link href=&quot;PIC URL&quot; rel=&quot;icon&quot;&gt;
&lt;/head&gt;

&lt;body&gt;
&lt;style&gt;body { background-color:#FF8000; color:#000000; } &lt;/style&gt;
&lt;div name=&quot;NAME&quot;&gt;
&lt;center&gt;
&lt;a href=&quot;URL&quot;&gt;NAME&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/center&gt;
&lt;fieldset&gt;
&lt;legend&gt;Body&lt;/legend&gt;
&lt;align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;PIC URL&quot;&gt;
&lt;/align&gt;
&lt;align=&quot;right&quot;&gt;
Welcome to the site!
&lt;/align&gt;
&lt;/fieldset&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/body&gt;

&lt;footer&gt;
&lt;center&gt;
&amp;copy;2011 My Site || &lt;a href=&quot;URL&quot;&gt;TEXT&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/footer&gt;[/code]

So there you have it folks! A basic site! I put in some random images but to see what your site will turn out to look like, go here: http://darkproductions.comze.com/basicexample.html

[b][u]CSS[/u][/b]
Ok, so CSS is actually a lot like Java. We can have a file somewhere else, and then have it imported into the page you want. So lets start out by making a CSS page. We&#39;re going to call it &quot;style.css&quot; (since a CSS is a style sheet). This is only the basics at the moment, so we&#39;re only going to make what I put up in the HTML part. So we&#39;re going to throw this into your .css document:
[code]body { background-color:#FF8000; color:#000000; } [/code]

CSS is more like Java than HTML in the way that it uses the brackets the same way. For example, the work body would be like a method (public void body()) in java and anything inside the brackets pertains to that method, body. Since the body pertains to mainly everything inside the page, it can also hold the background images/colors (images in chapter 2). That&#39;s how we use this basically. 

You may now get rid of that in your HTML file (it would be the &lt;style&gt;). Now, we have to import this into your HTML file, so to do that we&#39;re going to put this in your header: &lt;link rel=&quot;stylesheet&quot; href=&quot;style.css&quot;&gt;. That will make everything in your CSS be displayed on your site. 

=====================================================================================

[b][i][u]CHAPTER 2 - MAKING OUR SITE SEXY[/u][/i][/b]
[b][u]Graphics[/u][/b]
Here is a tutorial I put together (request):
http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Rw78HTTonTs

As we all know, a regular site can be quite boring without pictures and banners and what not. So we&#39;re going to do some Graphics Designing to start out with. I suggest using Photoshop for this, if you do not have this you can always torrent it or go to your local store and pick one up. They might be pretty expensive, but their worth getting. Next we&#39;re going to need some awesome fonts. We will get some new fonts from [url=http://www.dafont.com]dafont.com[/url]. They have a wide selection of cool fonts that can easily grab people attentions. If you are using Photoshop, I suggest you download a style package, their are tons of results on Google. You should also probably design some buttons before we move on (ones in cooler text) and a favorite icon. You should also maybe search Google for some background unless your already pro a graphics design and can make your own background. Here are some that might interest you:
[url=http://images2.layoutsparks.com/1/146822/awesome-fire-dragon-ablaze.jpg]http://images2.layoutsparks.com/1/146822/awesome-fire-dragon-ablaze.jpg[/url]
[url=http://www.awesomebackgrounds.com/templates/FromAwesomeBackgroundsDotCom-Etched.JPG]http://www.awesomebackgrounds.com/templates/FromAwesomeBackgroundsDotCom-Etched.JPG[/url]

When getting an image, I would suggest one that will look fine repeating itself so it can make it all go together smoothly. Once you have all those graphics together we will move on to the next step with implementing them.

[b][u]CSS[/u][/b]
If you didn&#39;t make a CSS file with the last one, you will be making one now (if you didn&#39;t make one before follow the CSS step in Chapter 1). So first of all, lets put in our background. We will want to add this to our body code: background-image:url(&#39;URL TO PIC&#39;);. That will import the background image. Now, there are many things that we can do with this, we can make it so it doesn&#39;t repeat and so it does repeat. For this I&#39;m going to make it repeat down the Y axis of my page (I will be using the first background posted above). Repeat code: background-repeat:repeat;. No repeat code: background-repeat:no-repeat;. If your doing something like mine, you should do it like this: background-repeat:repeat y;. That will make the image repeat only going down. If you are doing that, your probably going to want it centered. So we should add this: background-position:top-center;. Are CSS should now look something like this:
[code]body { background-color:#000000; color:#FF8000; background-image:url(&#39;LINK&#39;); background-repeat:repeat y; background-size:100%; } [/code]

Your probably wondering, &quot;Why, if we&#39;re putting in a background image, are we keeping in a background color too?&quot;. The answer to that is clean and simple. Sometimes the image takes a little longer to load, and its the fire image like I&#39;m using, its going to look a bit we&#39;re looking white (default HTML background color). 

Now that we have our background, sometimes we don&#39;t want the text getting in the way of out pictures on the site (such as the flames). So we&#39;re going to give a certain area that the text will fit in. This goes by the width of the page. So I&#39;m going to make it so all my text has to fit into 550 pixel width. To make it fit into a certain width, we&#39;re going to make a new divide ID called width: div#width {width: 550px; margin: 10px auto 10px auto; position: relative;}, (we will put this into action in the HTML in the next part). Now that we have our basic site down, lets get to work on putting in images, and other awesome material.

[b][u]HTML[/u][/b]
Lets start out with importing our CSS (I&#39;m going over this again). We will be editing our heading by adding this: &lt;link href=&quot;LINK TO CSS&quot; rel=&quot;stylesheet&quot;&gt;. Once that is added, we&#39;re going to add our banner. You should upload the image you made to a image hosting site or if you know how to, upload it to your site. We will then put this: &lt;img src=&quot;LINK&quot;&gt;. Now we will upload our buttons like we did the banner and then add this code to make them work: &lt;a href=&quot;LINK&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;IMG LINK&quot;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;. You might want to put a space between your banner and your buttons to put a space in there, we&#39;re going to use the code &lt;br&gt;. &lt;br&gt; stands for a space, and it will make 1 space every time you put that down. So now our site will look something like this:
[code]&lt;head&gt;
&lt;title&gt;Basic Example 2&lt;/title&gt;
&lt;link href=&quot;&quot; type=&quot;icon&quot;&gt;
&lt;link href=&quot;&quot; rel=&quot;stylesheet&quot;&gt;
&lt;/head&gt;
&lt;body&gt;
&lt;div id=&quot;body&quot;&gt;
&lt;center&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;&quot;&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;a href=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;[/code]

Now, lets make some new fieldsets. We&#39;ll be using the same code, but we&#39;re going to add some stuff to it. Like the size of it and the color. So lets start out with the code: &lt;fieldset style=&quot;border-color:COLOR CODE; width:WIDTH;&quot;&gt;. Fill those in then add it to the body of your site. Now we&#39;re going to put our message in there like always then put in our ending code, &lt;/fieldset&gt;. Now, lets make the font something else, something cooler! I&#39;m going to make my font Tubular, which is the font of the buttons and the banner. If you don&#39;t remember the font code to change the style of the font, its this: &lt;font face=&quot;NAME&quot;&gt;. Now, if we want an image next to the font, we&#39;re going to put this code in: &lt;img src=&quot;LINK&quot; align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;. This way, we can have an image and the font right next to each other! If you want to add anything you learned from the first chapter, go right ahead. 

Heres what a basic site, from this chapter, should look somewhat like: http://darkproductions.comze.com/basic2.html

You&#39;r just going to do what you did with the footer of the last site and use that again. That&#39;s it for this chapter! If you would like to use my site base, you can rip it off yourself (since this community is full of pro leachers, MoparScape should make a new reward title for that, PRO LEACHER and have a pokemon that leaches health from you on it... That would be epic).

[b][i][u]Chapter 3 - Adding detail to the site[/u][/i][/b]
This chapter is coming today! After this chapter you will be able to make hover images, side by side boxes, and better graphics design.

Free Web Hosting - [url=http://000webhost.com]000webhost.com[/url]
Paid Web Hosting - [url=http://mi-webs.com]mi-webs.com[/url]

Whats to come?
A Lot More CSS coding
More HTML coding
(Specifics):
Hover Images
Making more boxes

Like to thank for contributing to the thread:
I vain I
ollie123

If you have any questions about the things I have posted so far, please leave a comment and I will better explain them to you. Thanks for looking!</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 18 Jun 2011 15:40:18 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>General Programming</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/html-css-updated/399467.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Html &amp; css [updated]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@m1lkman m1lkman]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/m1lkman">@m1lkman</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“runewings317, post:11, topic:399467”][quote author=m1lkman link=topic=496598.msg3633249#msg3633249 date=1308411205]<br>
Is this really needed?<br>
[/quote]Mmhm. I’m going to be getting into more detailed web design (java script) as we go along/I start learning it xD[/quote]</p>
<p>Alright, goodluck.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/html-css-updated/399467/12">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/html-css-updated/399467/12</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 18 Jun 2011 15:40:18 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-399467-12</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/html-css-updated/399467.rss">Html &amp; css [updated]</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Html &amp; css [updated]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@runewings317 runewings317]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/runewings317">@runewings317</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“m1lkman, post:10, topic:399467”]Is this really needed?[/quote]Mmhm. I’m going to be getting into more detailed web design (java script) as we go along/I start learning it xD</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/html-css-updated/399467/11">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/html-css-updated/399467/11</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 18 Jun 2011 15:38:52 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-399467-11</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/html-css-updated/399467.rss">Html &amp; css [updated]</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Html &amp; css [updated]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@m1lkman m1lkman]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/m1lkman">@m1lkman</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Is this really needed?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/html-css-updated/399467/10">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/html-css-updated/399467/10</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 18 Jun 2011 15:33:25 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-399467-10</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/html-css-updated/399467.rss">Html &amp; css [updated]</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Html &amp; css [updated]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@runewings317 runewings317]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/runewings317">@runewings317</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“ollie123, post:8, topic:399467”]CSS is nothing like Java</p>
<p> is deprecated; you should use CSS instead</p>
<p>© is the proper way to put a copyright symbol in</p>
<p>Needs some refining but otherwise good work.[/quote]In the way it uses brackets it is and thanks for the © code, I forgot what it was… And I’ll put the aligning via CSS in in chapter 3. Thanks for you support! Appreciated.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/html-css-updated/399467/9">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/html-css-updated/399467/9</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 17 Jun 2011 15:50:26 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-399467-9</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/html-css-updated/399467.rss">Html &amp; css [updated]</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Html &amp; css [updated]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@ollie123 Ollie123]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/ollie123">@ollie123</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>CSS is nothing like Java</p>
<p> is deprecated; you should use CSS instead</p>
<p>© is the proper way to put a copyright symbol in</p>
<p>Needs some refining but otherwise good work.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/html-css-updated/399467/8">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/html-css-updated/399467/8</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 17 Jun 2011 06:53:25 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-399467-8</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/html-css-updated/399467.rss">Html &amp; css [updated]</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Html &amp; css [updated]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@runewings317 runewings317]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/runewings317">@runewings317</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“I Vain I”]<a href="http://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php/topic,363483.0.html" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">The Biggest Tutorial In Moparscape, All About Modeling. [Adding models video up]</a></p>
<p>plus, this won’t get to be very big if you don’t have the right info.[/quote]Working on getting the right info. Trying my best and hardest. And trust me, I’ll get it. [quote=“Tu, post:6, topic:399467”][quote author=runewings317 link=topic=496598.msg3630795#msg3630795 date=1308189853]<br>
Ok, so CSS is actually a lot like Java.<br>
[/quote]</p>
<p>?[/quote]You obviously didn’t read. I put a whole explanation of how its similar to Java.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/html-css-updated/399467/7">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/html-css-updated/399467/7</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 16 Jun 2011 23:23:41 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-399467-7</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/html-css-updated/399467.rss">Html &amp; css [updated]</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Html &amp; css [updated]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Tu1 Tu]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/tu1">@Tu1</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote" data-post="1" data-topic="399467">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/runewings317/40/5_e05bb34c421432ee4d40de30c10af3e5.png" class="avatar"> runewings317:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Ok, so CSS is actually a lot like Java.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/html-css-updated/399467/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/html-css-updated/399467/6</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 16 Jun 2011 22:38:51 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-399467-6</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/html-css-updated/399467.rss">Html &amp; css [updated]</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Html &amp; css [updated]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@runewings317 runewings317]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/runewings317">@runewings317</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“owner nitro, post:4, topic:399467”]Sexy Jon Nice Work![/quote]TY! I’m going to make this the biggest tutorial in MoparScape!</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/html-css-updated/399467/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/html-css-updated/399467/5</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 16 Jun 2011 21:47:27 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-399467-5</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/html-css-updated/399467.rss">Html &amp; css [updated]</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Html &amp; css [updated]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@owner_nitro owner nitro]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/owner_nitro">@owner_nitro</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Sexy Jon Nice Work!</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/html-css-updated/399467/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/html-css-updated/399467/4</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 16 Jun 2011 21:19:21 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-399467-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/html-css-updated/399467.rss">Html &amp; css [updated]</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Html &amp; css [updated]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@runewings317 runewings317]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/runewings317">@runewings317</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“I Vain I”]well the global attributes don’t include ‘name’ so why not just follow the global standards?[/quote]Its so they can find something easier… But if it makes you happy I’ll remove them. When I do more advanced HTML tomorrow I’ll include the DTD. This right here is for beginners and their layout (nothing huge, nothing fancy)</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/html-css-updated/399467/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/html-css-updated/399467/3</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 16 Jun 2011 03:59:23 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-399467-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/html-css-updated/399467.rss">Html &amp; css [updated]</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Html &amp; css [updated]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@runewings317 runewings317]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/runewings317">@runewings317</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“I Vain I”][quote author=runewings317 link=topic=496598.msg3630795#msg3630795 date=1308189853]<br>
The basic structure of a HTML page consists of 3 main codes:</p>
<p>[ul][li][/li]<br>
[li][/li]<br>
[li][/li][/ul]</p>
<p>[/quote]the global structure of an html document consists of the:<br>
dtd (document type declaration)<br>
header<br>
body</p>
<aside class="quote">
<blockquote>
<p></p>
<div>


<p>html5 doesn’t support a ‘name’ attribute for dividers it only supports:<br>
accesskey, draggable, style, class, hidden, tabindex, contenteditable, id, title, contextmenu, lang, dir, spellcheck<br>
(not including the eventhandler-attributes.)[/quote]name has always worked for me, plus its only to point on what you want to call it for an easy find. DTD I rarely ever see and yes I know what it is…</p>
</div>
</blockquote></aside>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/html-css-updated/399467/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/html-css-updated/399467/2</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 16 Jun 2011 03:19:55 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-399467-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/html-css-updated/399467.rss">Html &amp; css [updated]</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Html &amp; css [updated]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@runewings317 runewings317]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/runewings317">@runewings317</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>This guide will take you step by step in coding a HTML page. Love it, hate it, but no flaming. I’m going to try to make this the biggest tutorial in MoparScape! So if you have anything to add or want to see anything you want to learn, please post and I will try to post it!</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Table of Contents</span></p>
<blockquote>Prologue
Chapter 1 - Learning the Ropes
~HTML
~~Step 1: Setting up a structure for your HTML page
~~Step 2: Adding content to your page
~CSS
<p>Chapter 2 - Making our site sexy<br>
~Graphics<br>
~CSS<br>
~HTML</p>
<p>Chapter 3 - Adding detail to the site (Coming today)</p>
</blockquote>
<p><span class="bbcode-b"><span class="bbcode-i"><span class="bbcode-u">PROLOGUE</span></span></span><br>
Thank-you for looking at this step by step guide to learning HTML. While doing this guide, you should be able to learn how to make a proper HTML and CSS pages, be able to do a lot with CSS and be able to make pro websites without using a pre-made site. This is for LEARNING PURPOSES ONLY and should only posted on MoparScape. I do NOT give permission for this to be re-posted on any other site. Thank-you for looking.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b"><span class="bbcode-i"><span class="bbcode-u">CHAPTER 1 - LEARNING THE ROPES</span></span></span></p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b"><span class="bbcode-u">HTML</span></span><br>
<span class="bbcode-b"><span class="bbcode-u">Step 1: Setting up a structure for your HTML page</span></span><br>
The basic structure of a HTML page consists of 3 main codes:</p>
<p>[ul][li][/li]<br>
[li][/li]<br>
[li][/li][/ul]</p>
<p>These all have their specific meaning to them.  being the head of it all. This holds codes for the title, favorite icon, styles and other imports such as style sheets. The  holds everything that’s in your page, the text, images and other boxes. The  holds everything you want down below such as the credits and other miscellaneous links. This is one of the most important things to know about coding HTML.</p>
<p>[code=Example]<br>
CONTENT</p>


CONTENT


CONTENT
[/code]
<p>When coding with HTML, once your done with a certain section you should put an end code on it: &lt;/CODE TO END&gt;. Sometimes, you do not put an end code on it, this is the case with some dividing codes. Now that we know the basics of setting up an HTML page, lets move on.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b"><span class="bbcode-u">Step 2: Adding content to your page</span></span><br>
We will start by doing the Header and working our way down.</p>
<p>As I said above, the header isn’t really used to hold content that will be shown. We will be using codes such as  in it.  makes it so that the page has a title. We will also want a favorite icon, for this we will be using the code . Now lets put this in our HTML code! As you see below, we will be using the end code for .</p>
<p>[code]</p>
My first page!



CONTENT


CONTENT
[/code]
There will be more to put into this, but for now, lets just leave it at this.
<p>So, now we want to add content to our page! We should probably put in dividers so we can keep track of all this. To use a dividing, we will use the code “</p><div>”. We really will only use the dividing code in the Body of the page, sometimes the footer if we have more than one thing down there. We can also put more than text in here, we can put buttons and images too. To make a basic text button, we will use this code: <a>NAME</a>. The code href will take you to the link that is in the quotations. If the page is inside your site, you don’t have to put the full link, you may put something as simple as “home.html” or “playnow.html”. To put an image in we will be using the code <img>. This will go and fetch the image from the url you put in. If you don’t want your things all pushed to the left or right, we can put in a code that centers them. This code is . Pretty self explanatory. If we only want something like the text or buttons centered, we may put the code  and then put the end code  right after it, making the area inside those 2 codes centered. But if you want something aligned to the right, we should do something like this: &lt;align=“right”&gt;. That will put all the code to the right. If you just want it to go to the left, put &lt;align=“left”&gt;, or if you do not have any code that’s aligning the page, just leave it blank since a HTML page automatically aligns to the left.
<p>[code=Example]</p>
My first page!



<div>

<a>NAME</a>


<img>


Welcome to the site!

</div>


CONTENT
[/code]
<p>Now, no one wants a plain old boring site with no color… So to put a color the the background, we will but this: body { background-color:COLOR CODE; } . This will make the background what ever color coder you put in. What if my text color clashes with my background color? No worries! Just put this: MESSAGE. That will change the color of the font inside those codes. If you want to have all the text on the page a certain color, we will replace your style code with this one: body { background-color:COLOR CODE; color:COLOR CODE } . To get color codes, I suggest using this site: <a href="http://html-color-codes.info/" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">http://html-color-codes.info/</a>.</p>
<p>[code]</p>
My first page!



body { background-color:#FF8000; color:#000000; } 
<div>

<a>NAME</a>


<img>


Welcome to the site!

</div>


CONTENT
[/code]
<p>The style code can also be implemented in a different way. We can use it in another document called a CSS file. I will get into this at the end.</p>
<p>If you feel your text button is too boring and you want a cooler font, we can always change it. We can do this by putting  in front of the button (it will also work for any text). We can also enlarge the text by putting in this code:  (again, goes for any text). What If you want a picture for a link? Great! We’ll just put this: <a><img></a>. This will make the image inside of the <a> codes a button.</a></p>
<p>Now, if you want certain things inside a box, you can put this code: . This will make it so that it puts a box around whatever is inside the  code. We can also put a little message at the top by using .</p>
<p>[code]</p>
My first page!



body { background-color:#FF8000; color:#000000; } 
<div>

<a>NAME</a>


Body

<img>


Welcome to the site!


</div>


CONTENT
[/code]
<p>Now, lets look at the footer. Usually, we see credits and links to Terms of service and development teams (stuff like that) in the footer. So I’m going to make this part clean and fast. You will want to put something like this: ©2011 My Site. You may also want to put links and stuff, in text regular size is the best way to go (for how to make a button, look above).</p>
<p>[code]</p>
My first page!



body { background-color:#FF8000; color:#000000; } 
<div>

<a>NAME</a>


Body

<img>


Welcome to the site!


</div>



©2011 My Site || <a>TEXT</a>
[/code]
<p>So there you have it folks! A basic site! I put in some random images but to see what your site will turn out to look like, go here: <a href="http://darkproductions.comze.com/basicexample.html" rel="nofollow noopener">http://darkproductions.comze.com/basicexample.html</a></p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b"><span class="bbcode-u">CSS</span></span><br>
Ok, so CSS is actually a lot like Java. We can have a file somewhere else, and then have it imported into the page you want. So lets start out by making a CSS page. We’re going to call it “style.css” (since a CSS is a style sheet). This is only the basics at the moment, so we’re only going to make what I put up in the HTML part. So we’re going to throw this into your .css document:</p>
<pre><code class="lang-auto"></code></pre>
<p>CSS is more like Java than HTML in the way that it uses the brackets the same way. For example, the work body would be like a method (public void body()) in java and anything inside the brackets pertains to that method, body. Since the body pertains to mainly everything inside the page, it can also hold the background images/colors (images in chapter 2). That’s how we use this basically.</p>
<p>You may now get rid of that in your HTML file (it would be the ). Now, we have to import this into your HTML file, so to do that we’re going to put this in your header: . That will make everything in your CSS be displayed on your site.</p>
<p>=====================================================================================</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b"><span class="bbcode-i"><span class="bbcode-u">CHAPTER 2 - MAKING OUR SITE SEXY</span></span></span><br>
<span class="bbcode-b"><span class="bbcode-u">Graphics</span></span><br>
Here is a tutorial I put together (request):<br>
<div class="lazyYT" data-youtube-id="Rw78HTTonTs" data-youtube-title="" data-width="480" data-height="270" data-parameters="feature=oembed&amp;wmode=opaque"></div></p>
<p>As we all know, a regular site can be quite boring without pictures and banners and what not. So we’re going to do some Graphics Designing to start out with. I suggest using Photoshop for this, if you do not have this you can always torrent it or go to your local store and pick one up. They might be pretty expensive, but their worth getting. Next we’re going to need some awesome fonts. We will get some new fonts from <a href="http://www.dafont.com" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">dafont.com</a>. They have a wide selection of cool fonts that can easily grab people attentions. If you are using Photoshop, I suggest you download a style package, their are tons of results on Google. You should also probably design some buttons before we move on (ones in cooler text) and a favorite icon. You should also maybe search Google for some background unless your already pro a graphics design and can make your own background. Here are some that might interest you:<br>
<a href="http://images2.layoutsparks.com/1/146822/awesome-fire-dragon-ablaze.jpg" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">http://images2.layoutsparks.com/1/146822/awesome-fire-dragon-ablaze.jpg</a><br>
<a href="http://www.awesomebackgrounds.com/templates/FromAwesomeBackgroundsDotCom-Etched.JPG" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">http://www.awesomebackgrounds.com/templates/FromAwesomeBackgroundsDotCom-Etched.JPG</a></p>
<p>When getting an image, I would suggest one that will look fine repeating itself so it can make it all go together smoothly. Once you have all those graphics together we will move on to the next step with implementing them.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b"><span class="bbcode-u">CSS</span></span><br>
If you didn’t make a CSS file with the last one, you will be making one now (if you didn’t make one before follow the CSS step in Chapter 1). So first of all, lets put in our background. We will want to add this to our body code: background-image:url(‘URL TO PIC’);. That will import the background image. Now, there are many things that we can do with this, we can make it so it doesn’t repeat and so it does repeat. For this I’m going to make it repeat down the Y axis of my page (I will be using the first background posted above). Repeat code: background-repeat:repeat;. No repeat code: background-repeat:no-repeat;. If your doing something like mine, you should do it like this: background-repeat:repeat y;. That will make the image repeat only going down. If you are doing that, your probably going to want it centered. So we should add this: background-position:top-center;. Are CSS should now look something like this:</p>
<pre><code class="lang-auto"></code></pre>
<p>Your probably wondering, “Why, if we’re putting in a background image, are we keeping in a background color too?”. The answer to that is clean and simple. Sometimes the image takes a little longer to load, and its the fire image like I’m using, its going to look a bit we’re looking white (default HTML background color).</p>
<p>Now that we have our background, sometimes we don’t want the text getting in the way of out pictures on the site (such as the flames). So we’re going to give a certain area that the text will fit in. This goes by the width of the page. So I’m going to make it so all my text has to fit into 550 pixel width. To make it fit into a certain width, we’re going to make a new divide ID called width: div#width {width: 550px; margin: 10px auto 10px auto; position: relative;}, (we will put this into action in the HTML in the next part). Now that we have our basic site down, lets get to work on putting in images, and other awesome material.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b"><span class="bbcode-u">HTML</span></span><br>
Lets start out with importing our CSS (I’m going over this again). We will be editing our heading by adding this: . Once that is added, we’re going to add our banner. You should upload the image you made to a image hosting site or if you know how to, upload it to your site. We will then put this: <img>. Now we will upload our buttons like we did the banner and then add this code to make them work: <a><img></a>. You might want to put a space between your banner and your buttons to put a space in there, we’re going to use the code <br>. <br> stands for a space, and it will make 1 space every time you put that down. So now our site will look something like this:</p>
<p>[code]</p>
Basic Example 2




<div>

<img>
<br>
<a><img></a>[/code]
<p>Now, lets make some new fieldsets. We’ll be using the same code, but we’re going to add some stuff to it. Like the size of it and the color. So lets start out with the code: . Fill those in then add it to the body of your site. Now we’re going to put our message in there like always then put in our ending code, . Now, lets make the font something else, something cooler! I’m going to make my font Tubular, which is the font of the buttons and the banner. If you don’t remember the font code to change the style of the font, its this: . Now, if we want an image next to the font, we’re going to put this code in: <img>. This way, we can have an image and the font right next to each other! If you want to add anything you learned from the first chapter, go right ahead.</p>
<p>Heres what a basic site, from this chapter, should look somewhat like: <a href="http://darkproductions.comze.com/basic2.html" rel="nofollow noopener">http://darkproductions.comze.com/basic2.html</a></p>
<p>You’r just going to do what you did with the footer of the last site and use that again. That’s it for this chapter! If you would like to use my site base, you can rip it off yourself (since this community is full of pro leachers, MoparScape should make a new reward title for that, PRO LEACHER and have a pokemon that leaches health from you on it… That would be epic).</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b"><span class="bbcode-i"><span class="bbcode-u">Chapter 3 - Adding detail to the site</span></span></span><br>
This chapter is coming today! After this chapter you will be able to make hover images, side by side boxes, and better graphics design.</p>
<p>Free Web Hosting - <a href="http://000webhost.com" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">000webhost.com</a><br>
Paid Web Hosting - <a href="http://mi-webs.com" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">mi-webs.com</a></p>
<p>Whats to come?<br>
A Lot More CSS coding<br>
More HTML coding<br>
(Specifics):<br>
Hover Images<br>
Making more boxes</p>
<p>Like to thank for contributing to the thread:<br>
I vain I<br>
ollie123</p>
<p>If you have any questions about the things I have posted so far, please leave a comment and I will better explain them to you. Thanks for looking!</p>
</div>
</div>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/html-css-updated/399467/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/html-css-updated/399467/1</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 16 Jun 2011 02:04:13 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-399467-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/html-css-updated/399467.rss">Html &amp; css [updated]</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
