<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Pest Control Guide!</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/pest-control-guide/192385</link>
    <description>This is another one of my creations! I made this all by myself, and I did not leach it. Everything is by me and only me.


[size=24pt][b]PEST CONTROL[/b][/size]
[U]
[b]Getting There[/b][/U]

First of all, to get to pest control, go to Port Sarim and then go to the 2nd to last dock and you&#39;ll
see &#39;Squire&#39; Talk to him and say &#39;I would like to go to your outpost&#39; and you&#39;ll be taken there. 
Then go to world 144, which is the most popular pest control world. Then head south and
you&#39;ll see different docks. The first one you&#39;ll see is for 40+, the one next to it is 70+ and the one next to that 
is 100+. All of these are different because the portals have different HP and the monsters are stronger.

Here is equipment I recommend for pest control:

[U][B]Melee [(All portals!)(recommended to have 60+ attack, 60+ strength)][/B][/U]
Wear your [b]highest[/b] attack and strength bonus armor. For a weapon, I suggest an Abbysal Whip or Dragon Scimitar.
For the shield slot, a Rune Defender, God Book, Obsidian Shield, or the shield to that armor set. For the armor, it doesn&#39;t matter, but I recommend a fighter torso for the body. For the amulet, a suggest an Amulet of Fury, Amulet of Glory, Amulet of Power, or Amulet of Accuracy. 
For gloves, I suggest armor gloves (Mithril or higher) or the best dragon hide vambraces. For capes, I suggest a Fire Cape, Obsidian Cape, God Cape, or Fremnik Cloak. For boots, I suggest armor boots (Mithril or higher), nothing else would really be effective. For the helmet slot, I suggest a Helm of Neitznot, Berserker Helm, Warrior Helm, or the helmet that goes with your armor set. Last, for the ring slot, although this isn&#39;t needed, a Berserker or Warrior ring would help.
[U]
[B]Range [(Most effective on Red and Purple portals)(Optional: 60+ Ranged is a must!)][/b][/U]
Wear the highest Ranged attack bonus, nothing else matters. A bow of chose would be a Magic Bow, Dorgeshu&#39;un  C&#39;Bow, or Crystal Bow. Remember, in Pest Control, you do NOT get your arrows back. So for your bank&#39;s sake, use inexpensive arrows/bolts for your weapon (Magic Bow: Iron or below, Dorgeshu&#39;un C&#39;Bow: Bone Bolts, Crystal Bow: Lucky you, you don&#39;t need arrows!). For a helmet, a robin hood hat would be best, then an Archer Helmet, then followed by the helmet of your ranged set. For body and legs, I suggest Full Dragon Hide of your range level (Red or above), Full Karils, or 3rd Age range armor. For an amulet, an Amulet of Glory or Amulet of Fury would be best. For boots, anything would do, but Ranger Boots are recommended. For the Cape Slot, if using steel arrows, wear Ava&#39;s Accumulator, otherwise, wear any cape that doesn&#39;t bring down range attack bonus. Then for the ring slot, an archer ring would do, but if not available, just leave it with nothing.

[U][b]Mage [(Only effective in highly populated monster areas! Do not use anything BUT Ancient Magiks and you must have 88+ magic!)(Not recommended unless you have Ancient Magik&#39;s unlocked)][/b][/U]
Wear the highest possible mage bonus! You do not want to waste runes! Remember, only use this method if you have completed Desert Treasure and are using Ancient Magiks! For a helmet, I recommend Farseer helmet, or the helmet of your set. For body and legs, I recommend a set such as full Ahrims, full Mystic, full Ghostly, full infinity, or full 3rd Aged mage. For the weapon slot, an Ancients staff is best, otherwise a staff that supplies unlimited runes for that spell (Air, fire, earth, etc.). For boots, the boots of that set would be best, then followed by Infinity, Mystic, Ghostly, or Desert Boots. For gloves, the gloves of that set are recommended, followed by ones from other sets such as Infinity, Mystic, 
Ghostly, or normal gloves. For shield, I would leave this slot empty, unless you can get your hands on a God Book (Holy, Unholy, Balance) or Mage book. For cape, I recommend a God Cape, a God Cloak, or Obsidian Cape, all other capes will be fine. For rings, I recommend a Seers rings, but it isn&#39;t required. Remember to bring a plentiful amount of runes with you for your trip!

[U][b]Playing Pest Control[/b][/U]

Now time to play! Now, pick the appropriate dock for your level (40+,70+,100+) and click &#39;Climb Ladder&#39;.
Now you&#39;ll be on the ship! It takes 25 people or a couple of minutes for the boat to leave. And when you get there 
you&#39;ll see this:
[img]http://img233.imageshack.us/img233/1884/main1mh7.png[/img]

Now, the best place to go is the West, Purple portal, which is my best of choice.
So head West through the gates and go to the portal. Now you&#39;ll probably see this:

[img]http://img213.imageshack.us/img213/3306/main2un2.png[/img]

You&#39;ll see a portal (with a shield) and some strange creatures. Now, don&#39;t worry about any of these except
spinners. These you NEED to kill because they heal portals, making it very difficult to kill. Also, don&#39;t worry
about dying, this is a [url=http://www.tip.it/runescape/?page=mini_games.htm]Low Risk[/url] game.

Eventually, the portal will drop it&#39;s shield, making it attackable. Now click &#39;Attack Portal&#39; and wait.
The portal will soon die unless there are some left over spinners. This is where you need to make a choice:

A)Kill spinners and let others kill portal
B)Keep on attacking portal and let other kill spinners.

Well, I recommend if your a low-level (40-79) to choose choice A.
If your a high-level (80+) choose choice B.
[U]
[b]Strategies:[/b][/U]
If you are a low level, I suggest you don&#39;t attack the portals, and kill everything besides a splatter. Why?
Because splatters explode hitting in the low 20&#39;s. If you are a ranger or a mager, attack the portal. Why?
Because all portals have a very good weakness to magic and range. My recommendation for rangers is a
Dorgeshuun C&#39;Bow with as many bone bolts as you can afford. I state that because the Dorgeshuun C&#39;bow (AKA Bone
X bow) is very cheap and bolts are only 4gp ea. For magers I recommend ancients because of the high density of
creatures you will get well over 1k xp per cast.

[b]Armor/Weapon[/b] -Melee: I recommend at least rune with a decent weapon (Dragon Wep or whip) with your highest attack prayer on.
                               Magers: I recommend you have any set of full mystic and a good supply of runes.
                               Rangers: I recommend the Dorgeshuun C&#39;Bow (like I stated above) and armor that gives the best range bonus.
                               If you&#39;re using C&#39;Bow, wield a god book (Book of Balance, Unholy Book, Holy Book) and put on best range prayer.

[b]For Magers![/b]
Wait until a lot of monsters spawn, then cast your barrage spell so you get the most out of the spell! This gives TONS of exp!

[img]http://img136.imageshack.us/img136/6158/main3ox8.png[/img]

Now you&#39;ll (eventually) kill the portal. Once the portal is dead, go to other portals and attack
(and choose between choice A and choice B).

Game has ended? You should see this:

[img]http://img219.imageshack.us/img219/8436/main4ot8.png[/img]

You didn&#39;t see that? That means you didn&#39;t hit at least 50 damage during the game.


Well, once you save up your points, or if you&#39;re impatient and would like to spend
your 1 point right away, you can exchange them for items or xp. Items include farming
mining sets and Void Knight armory. Time to find the Void Knight, which looks like this:

[img]http://img233.imageshack.us/img233/3847/main5ll0.png[/img]

Now right click and click &#39;Exchange points&#39;

[img]http://img213.imageshack.us/img213/8657/main6ma1.png[/img]

Then you&#39;ll see the variety of XP exchange and items I was talking about:

[img]http://img219.imageshack.us/img219/3789/main7yf0.png[/img]

[img]http://img136.imageshack.us/img136/9148/main8mh6.png[/img]

Now, according to how much points you have, you can choose between XP,
By spending 1,10, or 100 points, or items.

To get your items simply click (for xp click amount of points to spend) it and press &#39;Confirm&#39;.
As shown below:

[img]http://img136.imageshack.us/img136/7294/main9sn2.png[/img]


[b]I hope you liked my guide and hope for more! Please post feedback![/b]</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2008 01:08:56 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/pest-control-guide/192385.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Pest Control Guide!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@ninja_nub ninja nub]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/ninja_nub">@ninja_nub</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I did make it… I’ve posted it on Silabsoft, RuneLocus, and RsEdge…</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/pest-control-guide/192385/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/pest-control-guide/192385/6</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2008 01:08:56 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-192385-6</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/pest-control-guide/192385.rss">Pest Control Guide!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Pest Control Guide!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@bootnecklad bootnecklad]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/bootnecklad">@bootnecklad</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I like proof to prove things…</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/pest-control-guide/192385/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/pest-control-guide/192385/5</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2008 20:31:02 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-192385-5</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/pest-control-guide/192385.rss">Pest Control Guide!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Pest Control Guide!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@exe626 exe626]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/exe626">@exe626</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>So I heard you didn’t make this.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/pest-control-guide/192385/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/pest-control-guide/192385/4</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2008 20:08:57 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-192385-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/pest-control-guide/192385.rss">Pest Control Guide!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Pest Control Guide!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@ninja_nub ninja nub]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/ninja_nub">@ninja_nub</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Well, I heard a lot of people, including my friends, asking how to play… So I made a guide.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/pest-control-guide/192385/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/pest-control-guide/192385/3</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2008 07:43:51 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-192385-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/pest-control-guide/192385.rss">Pest Control Guide!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Pest Control Guide!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@pk4pk pk4pk]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/pk4pk">@pk4pk</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Nice one. All though I think every one does no how to</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/pest-control-guide/192385/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/pest-control-guide/192385/2</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2008 07:40:10 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-192385-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/pest-control-guide/192385.rss">Pest Control Guide!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Pest Control Guide!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@ninja_nub ninja nub]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/ninja_nub">@ninja_nub</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>This is another one of my creations! I made this all by myself, and I did not leach it. Everything is by me and only me.</p>
<p>[size=24pt]<span class="bbcode-b">PEST CONTROL</span>[/size]<br>
<span class="bbcode-u"><br>
<span class="bbcode-b">Getting There</span></span></p>
<p>First of all, to get to pest control, go to Port Sarim and then go to the 2nd to last dock and you’ll<br>
see ‘Squire’ Talk to him and say ‘I would like to go to your outpost’ and you’ll be taken there.<br>
Then go to world 144, which is the most popular pest control world. Then head south and<br>
you’ll see different docks. The first one you’ll see is for 40+, the one next to it is 70+ and the one next to that<br>
is 100+. All of these are different because the portals have different HP and the monsters are stronger.</p>
<p>Here is equipment I recommend for pest control:</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-u"><span class="bbcode-b">Melee [(All portals!)(recommended to have 60+ attack, 60+ strength)]</span></span><br>
Wear your <span class="bbcode-b">highest</span> attack and strength bonus armor. For a weapon, I suggest an Abbysal Whip or Dragon Scimitar.<br>
For the shield slot, a Rune Defender, God Book, Obsidian Shield, or the shield to that armor set. For the armor, it doesn’t matter, but I recommend a fighter torso for the body. For the amulet, a suggest an Amulet of Fury, Amulet of Glory, Amulet of Power, or Amulet of Accuracy.<br>
For gloves, I suggest armor gloves (Mithril or higher) or the best dragon hide vambraces. For capes, I suggest a Fire Cape, Obsidian Cape, God Cape, or Fremnik Cloak. For boots, I suggest armor boots (Mithril or higher), nothing else would really be effective. For the helmet slot, I suggest a Helm of Neitznot, Berserker Helm, Warrior Helm, or the helmet that goes with your armor set. Last, for the ring slot, although this isn’t needed, a Berserker or Warrior ring would help.<br>
<span class="bbcode-u"><br>
<span class="bbcode-b">Range [(Most effective on Red and Purple portals)(Optional: 60+ Ranged is a must!)]</span></span><br>
Wear the highest Ranged attack bonus, nothing else matters. A bow of chose would be a Magic Bow, Dorgeshu’un  C’Bow, or Crystal Bow. Remember, in Pest Control, you do NOT get your arrows back. So for your bank’s sake, use inexpensive arrows/bolts for your weapon (Magic Bow: Iron or below, Dorgeshu’un C’Bow: Bone Bolts, Crystal Bow: Lucky you, you don’t need arrows!). For a helmet, a robin hood hat would be best, then an Archer Helmet, then followed by the helmet of your ranged set. For body and legs, I suggest Full Dragon Hide of your range level (Red or above), Full Karils, or 3rd Age range armor. For an amulet, an Amulet of Glory or Amulet of Fury would be best. For boots, anything would do, but Ranger Boots are recommended. For the Cape Slot, if using steel arrows, wear Ava’s Accumulator, otherwise, wear any cape that doesn’t bring down range attack bonus. Then for the ring slot, an archer ring would do, but if not available, just leave it with nothing.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-u"><span class="bbcode-b">Mage [(Only effective in highly populated monster areas! Do not use anything BUT Ancient Magiks and you must have 88+ magic!)(Not recommended unless you have Ancient Magik’s unlocked)]</span></span><br>
Wear the highest possible mage bonus! You do not want to waste runes! Remember, only use this method if you have completed Desert Treasure and are using Ancient Magiks! For a helmet, I recommend Farseer helmet, or the helmet of your set. For body and legs, I recommend a set such as full Ahrims, full Mystic, full Ghostly, full infinity, or full 3rd Aged mage. For the weapon slot, an Ancients staff is best, otherwise a staff that supplies unlimited runes for that spell (Air, fire, earth, etc.). For boots, the boots of that set would be best, then followed by Infinity, Mystic, Ghostly, or Desert Boots. For gloves, the gloves of that set are recommended, followed by ones from other sets such as Infinity, Mystic,<br>
Ghostly, or normal gloves. For shield, I would leave this slot empty, unless you can get your hands on a God Book (Holy, Unholy, Balance) or Mage book. For cape, I recommend a God Cape, a God Cloak, or Obsidian Cape, all other capes will be fine. For rings, I recommend a Seers rings, but it isn’t required. Remember to bring a plentiful amount of runes with you for your trip!</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-u"><span class="bbcode-b">Playing Pest Control</span></span></p>
<p>Now time to play! Now, pick the appropriate dock for your level (40+,70+,100+) and click ‘Climb Ladder’.<br>
Now you’ll be on the ship! It takes 25 people or a couple of minutes for the boat to leave. And when you get there<br>
you’ll see this:<br>
<img src="http://img233.imageshack.us/img233/1884/main1mh7.png" alt width="" height=""></p>
<p>Now, the best place to go is the West, Purple portal, which is my best of choice.<br>
So head West through the gates and go to the portal. Now you’ll probably see this:</p>
<p><img src="http://img213.imageshack.us/img213/3306/main2un2.png" alt width="" height=""></p>
<p>You’ll see a portal (with a shield) and some strange creatures. Now, don’t worry about any of these except<br>
spinners. These you NEED to kill because they heal portals, making it very difficult to kill. Also, don’t worry<br>
about dying, this is a <a href="http://www.tip.it/runescape/?page=mini_games.htm" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">Low Risk</a> game.</p>
<p>Eventually, the portal will drop it’s shield, making it attackable. Now click ‘Attack Portal’ and wait.<br>
The portal will soon die unless there are some left over spinners. This is where you need to make a choice:</p>
<p>A)Kill spinners and let others kill portal<br>
B)Keep on attacking portal and let other kill spinners.</p>
<p>Well, I recommend if your a low-level (40-79) to choose choice A.<br>
If your a high-level (80+) choose choice B.<br>
<span class="bbcode-u"><br>
<span class="bbcode-b">Strategies:</span></span><br>
If you are a low level, I suggest you don’t attack the portals, and kill everything besides a splatter. Why?<br>
Because splatters explode hitting in the low 20’s. If you are a ranger or a mager, attack the portal. Why?<br>
Because all portals have a very good weakness to magic and range. My recommendation for rangers is a<br>
Dorgeshuun C’Bow with as many bone bolts as you can afford. I state that because the Dorgeshuun C’bow (AKA Bone<br>
X bow) is very cheap and bolts are only 4gp ea. For magers I recommend ancients because of the high density of<br>
creatures you will get well over 1k xp per cast.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Armor/Weapon</span> -Melee: I recommend at least rune with a decent weapon (Dragon Wep or whip) with your highest attack prayer on.<br>
Magers: I recommend you have any set of full mystic and a good supply of runes.<br>
Rangers: I recommend the Dorgeshuun C’Bow (like I stated above) and armor that gives the best range bonus.<br>
If you’re using C’Bow, wield a god book (Book of Balance, Unholy Book, Holy Book) and put on best range prayer.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">For Magers!</span><br>
Wait until a lot of monsters spawn, then cast your barrage spell so you get the most out of the spell! This gives TONS of exp!</p>
<p><img src="http://img136.imageshack.us/img136/6158/main3ox8.png" alt width="" height=""></p>
<p>Now you’ll (eventually) kill the portal. Once the portal is dead, go to other portals and attack<br>
(and choose between choice A and choice B).</p>
<p>Game has ended? You should see this:</p>
<p><img src="http://img219.imageshack.us/img219/8436/main4ot8.png" alt width="" height=""></p>
<p>You didn’t see that? That means you didn’t hit at least 50 damage during the game.</p>
<p>Well, once you save up your points, or if you’re impatient and would like to spend<br>
your 1 point right away, you can exchange them for items or xp. Items include farming<br>
mining sets and Void Knight armory. Time to find the Void Knight, which looks like this:</p>
<p><img src="http://img233.imageshack.us/img233/3847/main5ll0.png" alt width="" height=""></p>
<p>Now right click and click ‘Exchange points’</p>
<p><img src="http://img213.imageshack.us/img213/8657/main6ma1.png" alt width="" height=""></p>
<p>Then you’ll see the variety of XP exchange and items I was talking about:</p>
<p><img src="http://img219.imageshack.us/img219/3789/main7yf0.png" alt width="" height=""></p>
<p><img src="http://img136.imageshack.us/img136/9148/main8mh6.png" alt width="" height=""></p>
<p>Now, according to how much points you have, you can choose between XP,<br>
By spending 1,10, or 100 points, or items.</p>
<p>To get your items simply click (for xp click amount of points to spend) it and press ‘Confirm’.<br>
As shown below:</p>
<p><img src="http://img136.imageshack.us/img136/7294/main9sn2.png" alt width="" height=""></p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">I hope you liked my guide and hope for more! Please post feedback!</span></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/pest-control-guide/192385/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/pest-control-guide/192385/1</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2008 06:46:44 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-192385-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/pest-control-guide/192385.rss">Pest Control Guide!</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
