<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Hamachi Guide</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/hamachi-guide/109281</link>
    <description>                [center][b]Guide To Getting and Learning How To Use Hamachi![/b][/center]

I&#39;ve seen many questions how to use hamachi and where to get it. I&#39;ve decided to make a simple guide.

               Rules:
               -No flamming
               -No spamming
               -Feel free to ask any questions!!

  

  [b]Section 1[/b]: Getting Hamachi and Learning How To Use It

  [b]Chapter 1[/b]: Getting hamachi

 Firstly before anything else, download hamachi. To do this, simply go to www.hamachi.cc/download if it doesn&#39;t work just open up a internet window and put it in the adress bar. Fill out the information and select the option you want to choose. There&#39;s three options. Select anyone by clicking &quot;Download&quot; after you finish downloading hamachi onto your computer, go find hamachi on your computer wherever you saved it and install it. If it says a newer version of hamachi is available, would you like to update? Click yes and if it says it again, re-download it. After you finish installing it on your computer, you have hamachi!!
  
  [b]Chapter 2[/b]: Learning How To Use Hamachi

 Using hamachi is pretty simple. If you want to join a network, e.g a server, on the bottom right you should see a triangle, click it and click &quot;Join network&quot; type in the network name and password and you have joined. Just open up moparscape and put in the IP of the server and the port and you have connected to a server. If it says servers down, well then it&#39;s down. If you want to make a network for e.g to make your own server using hamachi, just click the triangle and click &quot;Create a network&quot; make a username and password and you have made an network. The circle kind of symbol is just options for hamachi. I&#39;d leave em for now.

  [b]Chapter 3[/b]: How To Make A Hamachi server

 To make a hamachi server just follow this link. http://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php/topic,134771.0.html
Follow what it says, after you finished what it says open up hamachi and make a network. After you made the network go to control panel, security center, windows firewall and make sure the firewall is off. Then go to the exceptions tab and click &quot;Add port&quot; and type in hamachi for the name and for the port just put the port of your server and click TCP and click add port. Then just go to your server folder and click runserver.bat and it&#39;s online!

 Hope I helped people confused with hamachi.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 12 Jun 2007 01:40:46 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/hamachi-guide/109281.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Hamachi Guide</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@zezi111 zezi111]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/zezi111">@zezi111</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Try restarting it or redownloading it.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/hamachi-guide/109281/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/hamachi-guide/109281/3</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 12 Jun 2007 01:40:46 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-109281-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/hamachi-guide/109281.rss">Hamachi Guide</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Hamachi Guide</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Threatening Threatening]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/threatening">@Threatening</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>What do you do if your hamachi will not turn on?..My hamachi says its turning on then “error connecting…”<br>
sorry if this is spam <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=6" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/hamachi-guide/109281/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/hamachi-guide/109281/2</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 12 Jun 2007 01:20:23 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-109281-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/hamachi-guide/109281.rss">Hamachi Guide</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Hamachi Guide</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@zezi111 zezi111]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/zezi111">@zezi111</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <pre><code>            [center][b]Guide To Getting and Learning How To Use Hamachi![/b][/center]
</code></pre>
<p>I’ve seen many questions how to use hamachi and where to get it. I’ve decided to make a simple guide.</p>
<pre><code>           Rules:
           -No flamming
           -No spamming
           -Feel free to ask any questions!!
</code></pre>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Section 1</span>: Getting Hamachi and Learning How To Use It</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Chapter 1</span>: Getting hamachi</p>
<p>Firstly before anything else, download hamachi. To do this, simply go to www.hamachi.cc/download if it doesn’t work just open up a internet window and put it in the adress bar. Fill out the information and select the option you want to choose. There’s three options. Select anyone by clicking “Download” after you finish downloading hamachi onto your computer, go find hamachi on your computer wherever you saved it and install it. If it says a newer version of hamachi is available, would you like to update? Click yes and if it says it again, re-download it. After you finish installing it on your computer, you have hamachi!!</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Chapter 2</span>: Learning How To Use Hamachi</p>
<p>Using hamachi is pretty simple. If you want to join a network, e.g a server, on the bottom right you should see a triangle, click it and click “Join network” type in the network name and password and you have joined. Just open up moparscape and put in the IP of the server and the port and you have connected to a server. If it says servers down, well then it’s down. If you want to make a network for e.g to make your own server using hamachi, just click the triangle and click “Create a network” make a username and password and you have made an network. The circle kind of symbol is just options for hamachi. I’d leave em for now.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Chapter 3</span>: How To Make A Hamachi server</p>
<p>To make a hamachi server just follow this link. <a href="http://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php/topic,134771.0.html" rel="nofollow noopener">http://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php/topic,134771.0.html</a><br>
Follow what it says, after you finished what it says open up hamachi and make a network. After you made the network go to control panel, security center, windows firewall and make sure the firewall is off. Then go to the exceptions tab and click “Add port” and type in hamachi for the name and for the port just put the port of your server and click TCP and click add port. Then just go to your server folder and click runserver.bat and it’s online!</p>
<p>Hope I helped people confused with hamachi.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/hamachi-guide/109281/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/hamachi-guide/109281/1</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 12 Jun 2007 00:40:46 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-109281-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/hamachi-guide/109281.rss">Hamachi Guide</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
