<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>TERA Online</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/tera-online/520842</link>
    <description>Does anyone else here play? From what I hear, it&#39;s a really fun game. It&#39;s f2p now, so no more having to buy it. I made a lancer, I forget the name, but I&#39;m pretty new. From the start, it looks excellent. The graphics are great from the start, it&#39;s got good gameplay, it&#39;s pretty unique, has a great pve (not sure about pvp yet), but I&#39;m really excited to get going in this game. I&#39;ve got a few levels, but nothing too much. Can&#39;t wait to see some of the bosses in the game.

The starting quests are quite generic. Run here - talk to this guy - run back and talk to the same person. Next quest is the same thing, except more people. I think(?) eventually you run into a quest where it tells you to slay this many monsters and return to the quest missioner. Though, if you want to be a ranged class, it makes you actually have to aim your spells and attacks to hit the target, which makes it more difficult. I find that pretty unique. So, if you&#39;re a priest or some-sort of healing class, you can&#39;t just focus on health bars.

The physics to the game, from which I&#39;ve seen so far, are quite nice. There&#39;s a good feel of realism to the game, which makes it more enjoyable for me. I don&#39;t lag too much, but I get some lag spikes when I run into a large amount of players. Other than that, I&#39;m really enjoying the game. Some of the features in it are unoriginal and overused, but there&#39;s some unique content in it. Overall, I do say that it&#39;s worth playing, you all should check it out if you haven&#39;t already.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 21 Jun 2013 18:37:02 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Games</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/tera-online/520842.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>TERA Online</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@ArmorCroc ArmorCroc]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/armorcroc">@ArmorCroc</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p><a class="mention" href="/u/lilxcj">@LilXCj</a>, yes there are political-kind-of things, but it isn’t necessary in the game to be involved here. However, if you like to play by yourself MMOs are not maybe the thing for you.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/tera-online/520842/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/tera-online/520842/6</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 21 Jun 2013 18:37:02 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-520842-6</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/tera-online/520842.rss">TERA Online</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>TERA Online</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@LilXCj LilXCj]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/lilxcj">@LilXCj</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>From what I’ve gleamed, it’s a pretty player intensive universe since you can even run campaigns for what seems to be political positions.</p>
<p>For someone like me who doesn’t really talk to people in online games (i like to keep to myself), it doesn’t seem my type of game.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/tera-online/520842/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/tera-online/520842/5</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 19 Jun 2013 07:28:26 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-520842-5</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/tera-online/520842.rss">TERA Online</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>TERA Online</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@ArmorCroc ArmorCroc]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/armorcroc">@ArmorCroc</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Oh wow! Thanks Uncalled for reminding me of this game! I bought it 16 days before the open beta and thought at first like “Awww, crap! I bought a game which will be free to play in just weeks!” The fun part is, I got the senior status or w/e it’s called! 8 character slots, 4 bank tabs, the second fastest mount in the game, which is the lovely frostlion. What I absolutely love about the mounts is: Have anyone tried to press space a few thousand times while standing still in a crowded area? The sound is deafening if using headphones and not ready for this noise terrorism! What other special features did I get…? Some necklaces I think… What ever you do, PLEASE DO NOT pick ELIN as your race!! I would much rather see Popori’s everywhere even the male Castanics are a more pleasant choice! (Castanics are fabulous as f*ck!)<br>
One very common thing in MMORPGs is the armors of female characters. High-end gear are like thongs and something to barely cover the nipples while the low to mid gear are much more armor-looking. I like the fact in this game that if you just stand still in combat you end up very vulnerable while blocking and evading can be used to kill pretty much the same level BAMs as you or at low levels, with good timing I’ve killed a 7 level higher than me BAM with a friend of 10 levels lower than the monster. BAM = short of Big Ass Monsters, the name the developers have given these boss monsters. Which in turn is very suitable for the mighty Kumas leader, Kadas. The BAM title fits this guy very well, just Google “Kadas Tera”. <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/smiley.png?v=5" title=":smiley:" class="emoji" alt=":smiley:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/tera-online/520842/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/tera-online/520842/4</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 19 Jun 2013 02:17:06 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-520842-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/tera-online/520842.rss">TERA Online</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>TERA Online</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Uncalled Uncalled]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/uncalled">@Uncalled</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Yeah, I pretty much do the main questline and move on. I do enjoy doing the side-quests here and there, but I never do them too often. So I wouldn’t know. I could imagine them being tedious and annoying, as most MMO’s make their side-quests like that.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/tera-online/520842/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/tera-online/520842/3</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2013 06:53:53 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-520842-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/tera-online/520842.rss">TERA Online</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>TERA Online</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@xxx123xxx xxx123xxx]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/xxx123xxx">@xxx123xxx</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I’ve played it till level 13 or so, quests were annoying and the intro was even worse. Side quests took forever to complete, e.g there was one your supposed to find these fragments and they were global too so everybody was after them, took me 2 hours to do that stupid quest. That’s just me tho, I have to do all the side quests in an area to move on <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=5" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/tera-online/520842/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/tera-online/520842/2</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2013 03:03:09 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-520842-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/tera-online/520842.rss">TERA Online</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>TERA Online</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Uncalled Uncalled]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/uncalled">@Uncalled</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Does anyone else here play? From what I hear, it’s a really fun game. It’s f2p now, so no more having to buy it. I made a lancer, I forget the name, but I’m pretty new. From the start, it looks excellent. The graphics are great from the start, it’s got good gameplay, it’s pretty unique, has a great pve (not sure about pvp yet), but I’m really excited to get going in this game. I’ve got a few levels, but nothing too much. Can’t wait to see some of the bosses in the game.</p>
<p>The starting quests are quite generic. Run here - talk to this guy - run back and talk to the same person. Next quest is the same thing, except more people. I think(?) eventually you run into a quest where it tells you to slay this many monsters and return to the quest missioner. Though, if you want to be a ranged class, it makes you actually have to aim your spells and attacks to hit the target, which makes it more difficult. I find that pretty unique. So, if you’re a priest or some-sort of healing class, you can’t just focus on health bars.</p>
<p>The physics to the game, from which I’ve seen so far, are quite nice. There’s a good feel of realism to the game, which makes it more enjoyable for me. I don’t lag too much, but I get some lag spikes when I run into a large amount of players. Other than that, I’m really enjoying the game. Some of the features in it are unoriginal and overused, but there’s some unique content in it. Overall, I do say that it’s worth playing, you all should check it out if you haven’t already.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/tera-online/520842/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/tera-online/520842/1</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2013 00:26:18 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-520842-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/tera-online/520842.rss">TERA Online</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
