<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Buttons stopped working</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/buttons-stopped-working/548796</link>
    <description>I don&#39;t know why. I haven&#39;t touched my files in a long time and I never changed anything but suddenly now many buttons don&#39;t work anymore.

The only thing that&#39;s happened is when I imported the project to Eclipse because I had to redownload it, it was at first giving me a bunch of errors and I had to clean the project. But the original source that I literally didn&#39;t touch works fine and before my server was working fine too until what happened with Eclipse, all the files are almost identical, I didn&#39;t change the code, but for some reason when I build with Eclipse my server gets a bunch of unresolved errors and the original source gets none.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2014 18:24:31 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/buttons-stopped-working/548796.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Buttons stopped working</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@winK winK]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/wink">@winK</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I don’t know why. I haven’t touched my files in a long time and I never changed anything but suddenly now many buttons don’t work anymore.</p>
<p>The only thing that’s happened is when I imported the project to Eclipse because I had to redownload it, it was at first giving me a bunch of errors and I had to clean the project. But the original source that I literally didn’t touch works fine and before my server was working fine too until what happened with Eclipse, all the files are almost identical, I didn’t change the code, but for some reason when I build with Eclipse my server gets a bunch of unresolved errors and the original source gets none.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/buttons-stopped-working/548796/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/buttons-stopped-working/548796/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2014 18:24:31 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-548796-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/buttons-stopped-working/548796.rss">Buttons stopped working</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
