<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>~My RS2 Guides~</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-rs2-guides/102226</link>
    <description>Hey these are some of my guides there sort but helpful and 100% made by me and all tested by me and my real life freinds :D. You must rember these are guides for people who are members only because i was a member from day 1 :D

1. My guide to 43 runecraft where you can make nats witch is a very good way to make money.

First you must get to 16 runecraft just run airs it should take you 100 normal ess. then buy around 8k normal ess and 20 duel rings (may need more) or you can make them witch i recomend.
OK now we have our ess and duel rings first get a fire tira and a duel ring. Get a full invo of ess and telly to duel area run up the fire telly make your fire&#39;s than telly to castle wars and bank the fires and get a full invo of ess and so on.

I raised my runecraft from 16 to 43 in 1 night doing this it is very effictive. Now once you have 43 runecraft buy a few glorys and complete the abyss mini game and run nats thro there you can make 300k a hour if you have 10 glorys. info on abyss mini game is here [url=http://www.runehq.com]www.runehq.com[/url]

2. My Fast 1-70 range guide

First get 250 bronze and maybe 2k iron arrows and your chaps/vambs/bow. From lvl 1-20 i recomend cows some people use chickens but there lower exp again. Once you hit 20-40 move onto the Guards in Varrok. At 40 You should travel to castle wars and just near there are some orges if you look on the map there sould be a little island right infront of castle wars thats them :P. there good untill 60. i got to 50 in 2 hours on them. now for 60-70 you can keept going with orges witch i did or move onto Pest Control.

3. My Free-World Pure

Stats we are aiming for 
60 str
40 attack
1 def
1 pray
40 range
40-60 mage depends on your budget

Now first i get 20 str 20 attack then 40 range for hit points. After that get 40 attack and 40 str. Then you should raise mage to 41  rember 41 not 40. After that you can pk if you wanted wouldnt be very good tho. now get 60 str and you could raise to 60 mage. 
These stats rule because With 60 mage you can own any one who isnt a pure. 40 Range gives you green d hide good mage defense. And with 60 str well you just own with a scim and 2hand for ko&#39;s.



There&#39;s my first 3 guides i will add more later on and more in detail with pics. Now there is alot of people who will know these things but for people who this will help you i hope.

~Ca1LuM</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 29 May 2007 17:14:52 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-rs2-guides/102226.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>~My RS2 Guides~</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Ca1lum Ca1lum]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/ca1lum">@Ca1lum</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Hey these are some of my guides there sort but helpful and 100% made by me and all tested by me and my real life freinds :D. You must rember these are guides for people who are members only because i was a member from day 1 <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/smiley.png?v=6" title=":smiley:" class="emoji" alt=":smiley:"></p>
<ol>
<li>My guide to 43 runecraft where you can make nats witch is a very good way to make money.</li>
</ol>
<p>First you must get to 16 runecraft just run airs it should take you 100 normal ess. then buy around 8k normal ess and 20 duel rings (may need more) or you can make them witch i recomend.<br>
OK now we have our ess and duel rings first get a fire tira and a duel ring. Get a full invo of ess and telly to duel area run up the fire telly make your fire’s than telly to castle wars and bank the fires and get a full invo of ess and so on.</p>
<p>I raised my runecraft from 16 to 43 in 1 night doing this it is very effictive. Now once you have 43 runecraft buy a few glorys and complete the abyss mini game and run nats thro there you can make 300k a hour if you have 10 glorys. info on abyss mini game is here <a href="http://www.runehq.com" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">www.runehq.com</a></p>
<ol start="2">
<li>My Fast 1-70 range guide</li>
</ol>
<p>First get 250 bronze and maybe 2k iron arrows and your chaps/vambs/bow. From lvl 1-20 i recomend cows some people use chickens but there lower exp again. Once you hit 20-40 move onto the Guards in Varrok. At 40 You should travel to castle wars and just near there are some orges if you look on the map there sould be a little island right infront of castle wars thats them :P. there good untill 60. i got to 50 in 2 hours on them. now for 60-70 you can keept going with orges witch i did or move onto Pest Control.</p>
<ol start="3">
<li>My Free-World Pure</li>
</ol>
<p>Stats we are aiming for<br>
60 str<br>
40 attack<br>
1 def<br>
1 pray<br>
40 range<br>
40-60 mage depends on your budget</p>
<p>Now first i get 20 str 20 attack then 40 range for hit points. After that get 40 attack and 40 str. Then you should raise mage to 41  rember 41 not 40. After that you can pk if you wanted wouldnt be very good tho. now get 60 str and you could raise to 60 mage.<br>
These stats rule because With 60 mage you can own any one who isnt a pure. 40 Range gives you green d hide good mage defense. And with 60 str well you just own with a scim and 2hand for ko’s.</p>
<p>There’s my first 3 guides i will add more later on and more in detail with pics. Now there is alot of people who will know these things but for people who this will help you i hope.</p>
<p>~Ca1LuM</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-rs2-guides/102226/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-rs2-guides/102226/1</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 29 May 2007 17:14:52 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-102226-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-rs2-guides/102226.rss">~My RS2 Guides~</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
