<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>SageScape[718]</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/sagescape-718/517815</link>
    <description>[b]SageScape![/b]
Well thanks for your time of looking at this server! I have one picture for now im very sorry but our graphics are pretty good! It&#39;s a 718 like i said in the subject and has beautiful combat! Im an owner my name is reesepuff in game and other owners name is satvir1 hes the coder and the maker! Very experinced staff team and have a vps, Our staff consult players instead of using the bann feature, there are no dupes! The Eco is great! We dont like punishment but we will inforce rules for the players who obey should have a great time and meet bunches of people,! Both owners are on a lot so no worries on staff not being on! We are looking for staff but if you come in the server and ask for staff then We probally will never look at you for staff! :) but overall we would love for you to check us out! Thanks

-reesepuff
Forums- http://godz4hire.nstars.org/
Download- https://www.dropbox.com/s/67pqlzqfaa030bo/godz4Hire.jar
[img]http://puu.sh/2G1re.jpg[/img]</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2013 12:29:01 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/sagescape-718/517815.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>SageScape[718]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Cruel_Truth Cruel Truth]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/cruel_truth">@Cruel_Truth</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I’ve seen a lot of advertisement media before…but what the hell dude?</p>
<p>No offence but that media just hollers immaturity.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/sagescape-718/517815/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/sagescape-718/517815/4</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2013 12:29:01 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-517815-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/sagescape-718/517815.rss">SageScape[718]</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>SageScape[718]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Potzon Potzon]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/potzon">@Potzon</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Add some more pictures.<br>
Sorry, but I don’t think this is a very good server, because the advertisement is really bad… ;/</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/sagescape-718/517815/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/sagescape-718/517815/3</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2013 12:27:13 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-517815-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/sagescape-718/517815.rss">SageScape[718]</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>SageScape[718]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Ix_Soulcist_xI Soulcist]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/ix_soulcist_xi">@Ix_Soulcist_xI</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Well, after looking at the website I noticed the banner that is huge as Hell, I’d probably change that to something smaller or of the same thing that is smaller.</p>
<p>I also noticed that the staff rules were of public view, how about adding a section for the staff team to allow themselves to see the staff rules in their own board considering staff rules aren’t REALLY for public view.</p>
<p>I’d work on getting an actual website (paid hosting with SMF, vB, IPB etc., one of the many softwares out there).</p>
<p>You could take better pictures of the server, and loose the editing with paint because it looks horrible and the picture itself looks too pixelated. Also include more pictures that would explain more of this server (without using so many words because I don’t even read the text, only look at the pictures for my part so I’m sure there are others like that as well), not using one will explain not much of anything.</p>
<p>Good luck with the server.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/sagescape-718/517815/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/sagescape-718/517815/2</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2013 05:12:21 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-517815-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/sagescape-718/517815.rss">SageScape[718]</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>SageScape[718]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@deloria deloria]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/deloria">@deloria</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p><span class="bbcode-b">SageScape!</span><br>
Well thanks for your time of looking at this server! I have one picture for now im very sorry but our graphics are pretty good! It’s a 718 like i said in the subject and has beautiful combat! Im an owner my name is reesepuff in game and other owners name is satvir1 hes the coder and the maker! Very experinced staff team and have a vps, Our staff consult players instead of using the bann feature, there are no dupes! The Eco is great! We dont like punishment but we will inforce rules for the players who obey should have a great time and meet bunches of people,! Both owners are on a lot so no worries on staff not being on! We are looking for staff but if you come in the server and ask for staff then We probally will never look at you for staff! <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=5" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"> but overall we would love for you to check us out! Thanks</p>
<p>-reesepuff<br>
Forums- <a href="http://godz4hire.nstars.org/" rel="nofollow noopener">http://godz4hire.nstars.org/</a><br>
Download- <a href="https://www.dropbox.com/s/67pqlzqfaa030bo/godz4Hire.jar" rel="nofollow noopener">https://www.dropbox.com/s/67pqlzqfaa030bo/godz4Hire.jar</a><br>
<img src="http://puu.sh/2G1re.jpg" alt width="" height=""></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/sagescape-718/517815/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/sagescape-718/517815/1</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2013 05:07:20 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-517815-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/sagescape-718/517815.rss">SageScape[718]</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
