<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>WTF is wrong with archlinux....?!</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/wtf-is-wrong-with-archlinux/270682</link>
    <description>WTF is wrong with archlinux....?!!!!


Ok, here&#39;s how it went:

I decided to format one of my partitions for arch today (using windows disk manager or whatever...) and for some reason, it deleted 2 partitions instead of one and I was like &quot;fuck, a year and a half work lost!&quot; so I restarted my comp to install arch(x86_64). It installed fine. Booted up, no x or window manager so I downloaded and installed Kde and xorg.... Here is where the fun starts:

Now when I boot up it won&#39;t let me log in even though I know that I have the correct password for the root account. It seems to have lost my password. 

And I am really annoyed cause it took an hour and a half to download and install kde (I have slow connection) and the only computer I can use to burn cds is the one with arch on it. But it hasn&#39;t got windows or any other usable OS on it. Is there any way to reset the arch password without needing to download any new OS or anything?


Never mind. After a few hours of screwing around I got it working.....</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 02 Apr 2009 18:22:25 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Technology</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/wtf-is-wrong-with-archlinux/270682.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>WTF is wrong with archlinux....?!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@runescape3dude runescape3dude]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/runescape3dude">@runescape3dude</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Tried that it had the same outcome.</p>
<p>In the end I had just found a windows hard disk, shoved it in. Booted it and burned a “core” disk so it wouldn’t take as long to install. Then after that I reinstalled xorg, xfce4 instead of kde and hal so the mouse and keyboard would work. Now it is running nicely.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/wtf-is-wrong-with-archlinux/270682/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/wtf-is-wrong-with-archlinux/270682/3</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 02 Apr 2009 18:22:25 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-270682-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/wtf-is-wrong-with-archlinux/270682.rss">WTF is wrong with archlinux....?!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>WTF is wrong with archlinux....?!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Speljohan Speljohan]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/speljohan">@Speljohan</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I see you have already solved it, but l2fallback</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/wtf-is-wrong-with-archlinux/270682/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/wtf-is-wrong-with-archlinux/270682/2</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 02 Apr 2009 10:47:26 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-270682-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/wtf-is-wrong-with-archlinux/270682.rss">WTF is wrong with archlinux....?!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>WTF is wrong with archlinux....?!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@runescape3dude runescape3dude]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/runescape3dude">@runescape3dude</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>WTF is wrong with archlinux…!!!</p>
<p>Ok, here’s how it went:</p>
<p>I decided to format one of my partitions for arch today (using windows disk manager or whatever…) and for some reason, it deleted 2 partitions instead of one and I was like “fuck, a year and a half work lost!” so I restarted my comp to install arch(x86_64). It installed fine. Booted up, no x or window manager so I downloaded and installed Kde and xorg… Here is where the fun starts:</p>
<p>Now when I boot up it won’t let me log in even though I know that I have the correct password for the root account. It seems to have lost my password.</p>
<p>And I am really annoyed cause it took an hour and a half to download and install kde (I have slow connection) and the only computer I can use to burn cds is the one with arch on it. But it hasn’t got windows or any other usable OS on it. Is there any way to reset the arch password without needing to download any new OS or anything?</p>
<p>Never mind. After a few hours of screwing around I got it working…</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/wtf-is-wrong-with-archlinux/270682/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/wtf-is-wrong-with-archlinux/270682/1</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 02 Apr 2009 06:25:46 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-270682-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/wtf-is-wrong-with-archlinux/270682.rss">WTF is wrong with archlinux....?!</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
