<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>[READ] Need Help?</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/read-need-help/551733</link>
    <description>   I&#39;m helping anyone who needs any servers help, with any source / client / cache developement.
Aswell with any GFX, and web developement, I have gathered a group of really experienced programmers.
The purpose of this is to help anyone who needs help with issues there having, and to also help people get on the right path to programming, if they already aren&#39;t. Alot of people have been needing help lately, and there&#39;s not alot of people getting good either. Everything is the same, all the methods, content, etc. We&#39;re just really trying to improve the RSPS and MoparScape Community, and help strengthen as many people as we can skills and talents with programming overall. 

Contact me on skype if you need help;

im2high2behere</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 01 Jun 2015 23:20:47 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/read-need-help/551733.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>[READ] Need Help?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@zyle1992 Zymus]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/zyle1992">@zyle1992</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I don’t think that you’re permitted to do this. I don’t think you can create a topic for people to post in. I think a more productive way of accomplishing this is looking into the Server Help section and seeing what you can do, or going into the Development section.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/read-need-help/551733/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/read-need-help/551733/2</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jun 2015 23:20:47 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-551733-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/read-need-help/551733.rss">[READ] Need Help?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[READ] Need Help?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@FoHammer FoHammer]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/fohammer">@FoHammer</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I’m helping anyone who needs any servers help, with any source / client / cache developement.<br>
Aswell with any GFX, and web developement, I have gathered a group of really experienced programmers.<br>
The purpose of this is to help anyone who needs help with issues there having, and to also help people get on the right path to programming, if they already aren’t. Alot of people have been needing help lately, and there’s not alot of people getting good either. Everything is the same, all the methods, content, etc. We’re just really trying to improve the RSPS and MoparScape Community, and help strengthen as many people as we can skills and talents with programming overall.</p>
<p>Contact me on skype if you need help;</p>
<p>im2high2behere</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/read-need-help/551733/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/read-need-help/551733/1</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 29 May 2015 23:41:17 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-551733-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/read-need-help/551733.rss">[READ] Need Help?</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
