<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>BlizzardRSPS - The new, the fresh, the old. [Hiring]</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/blizzardrsps-the-new-the-fresh-the-old-hiring/527810</link>
    <description>[CENTER]
BlizzardRSPS
[URL=http://&quot;http://blizzardrsps.com/&quot;]Home[/URL]
[URL=http://&quot;http://blizzardrsps.com/play.php&quot;]Play[/url]
[URL=http://&quot;http://rswebclients.com/play/BlizzardRSPS&quot;]External Play[/url]
[URL=http://&quot;http://blizzardrsps.com/forums/&quot;]Forums[/url]
_________________________________________________________
Although we do not have a logo at this minute, we are working more on the server than our site and mini-features.
BlizzardRSPS is a mixed type of a RSPS, we offer a bit of old, a bit of fresh and most of all a bit of new. Attempting to make a multi-genre RSPS for your sakes, hate? Throw it at us, we&#39;ll only improve! love? Throw it towards us, we&#39;ll take that love into consideration in updates.

Pictures:
[img]http://img856.imageshack.us/img856/4250/8nn0.png[/img]
-Working Random Events, can be triggered by random objects around the game also. (Rewarded with 50,000 Coins and 2 Crystal Keys)
[img]http://img850.imageshack.us/img850/9096/lp1y.png[/img]
-Fully operational Castle Wars, and 7 other mini-games available to play.
[img]http://img10.imageshack.us/img10/5716/hn0p.png[/img]
-Our home, we&#39;ve worked hard to create what it is now. And we are still only 60% finished with it. Expanding it through-out the castle very soon!
[img]http://i39.tinypic.com/6qh5og.png[/img]
-We have 13 fully working bosses, mixture of easy-to-hard. Custom,new and old! Most rare drops come from them!
[img]http://i.imgur.com/aO3OsPt.png[/img]
-Crazy skin colours for your characters!

Not only this , but we have more? You&#39;ve seen all this kind of stuff before? You&#39;ll be surprised to what changes we&#39;ve made to some most-known and played features.

[b]So lets put into a short list what else we have to offer[/b]:
We don&#39;t want to hide half of our community away from rares, so we&#39;ve given everyone a chance of winning Seasonal Items from Penguins which can be located at Rock crabs. They will drop on a very rare scale, White Party-hats and Crystal Keys.

-A community which will mostly support you, have a laugh with you.
-A chance to be noticed, veterans will be needed.
-Advanced dicing for Donators
-Item upgrades
-Fully working upgraded Dungeoneering, we hope it&#39;s better than any other servers
-Lag issue,memory issues and other server hazards have been fixed for excellent up-time and performance.
-NPCs are scattered around the game, most shops are at home but some are elsewhere :O
-We&#39;ve got over 96% of our items, perfectly statisticed. (Some customs are excluded)
-Not a vast amount of customized items
-Perfect RS Chaotic Crossbow
-Real RS Dung Teleport /w Kinship Ring
-Fixed Slayer NPC Perfectly Animated and Updated
-Player Owned Shops, with most dupes fixed. Reported dupes will be rewarded :)
-As seen above, working random events(triggered in-fact).
-Mystery boxes, in events shall be given out.
Not only this, but as you&#39;ve hopefully heard before, various activities and events go on. 

We&#39;re hiring, applications to be sent to Jay via the site, we&#39;re expecting quality and strength in leadership and commitment, It&#39;s a RSPS? We need professionals in the matter of moderating, we will give trials out to those who may not seem like they are enough for others, but in-fact they are suitable for the job. 

Give us a chance, there&#39;s nothing to loose, For the last time..

[URL=http://&quot;http://blizzardrsps.com/&quot;]Home[/URL]
[URL=http://&quot;http://blizzardrsps.com/play.php&quot;]Play[/url]
[URL=http://&quot;http://rswebclients.com/play/BlizzardRSPS&quot;]External Play[/url]
[URL=http://&quot;http://blizzardrsps.com/forums/&quot;]Forums[/url]
[/CENTER]</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 11 Aug 2013 13:58:22 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/blizzardrsps-the-new-the-fresh-the-old-hiring/527810.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>BlizzardRSPS - The new, the fresh, the old. [Hiring]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@3owl 3owl]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/3owl">@3owl</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[CENTER]<br>
BlizzardRSPS<br>
<a data-bbcode="true">Home</a><br>
<a data-bbcode="true">Play</a><br>
<a data-bbcode="true">External Play</a><br>
<a data-bbcode="true">Forums</a></p>
<hr>
<p>Although we do not have a logo at this minute, we are working more on the server than our site and mini-features.<br>
BlizzardRSPS is a mixed type of a RSPS, we offer a bit of old, a bit of fresh and most of all a bit of new. Attempting to make a multi-genre RSPS for your sakes, hate? Throw it at us, we’ll only improve! love? Throw it towards us, we’ll take that love into consideration in updates.</p>
<p>Pictures:<br>
<img src="http://img856.imageshack.us/img856/4250/8nn0.png" alt width="" height=""><br>
-Working Random Events, can be triggered by random objects around the game also. (Rewarded with 50,000 Coins and 2 Crystal Keys)<br>
<img src="http://img850.imageshack.us/img850/9096/lp1y.png" alt width="" height=""><br>
-Fully operational Castle Wars, and 7 other mini-games available to play.<br>
<img src="http://img10.imageshack.us/img10/5716/hn0p.png" alt width="" height=""><br>
-Our home, we’ve worked hard to create what it is now. And we are still only 60% finished with it. Expanding it through-out the castle very soon!<br>
<img src="http://i39.tinypic.com/6qh5og.png" alt width="241" height="254"><br>
-We have 13 fully working bosses, mixture of easy-to-hard. Custom,new and old! Most rare drops come from them!<br>
<div class="lightbox-wrapper"><a class="lightbox" href="http://i.imgur.com/aO3OsPt.png" title="aO3OsPt.png" rel="nofollow noopener"><img src="http://i.imgur.com/aO3OsPt.png" alt width="690" height="434"><div class="meta">
<svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-far-image svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#far-image"></use></svg><span class="filename">aO3OsPt.png</span><span class="informations">869×547</span><svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-discourse-expand svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#discourse-expand"></use></svg>
</div></a></div><br>
-Crazy skin colours for your characters!</p>
<p>Not only this , but we have more? You’ve seen all this kind of stuff before? You’ll be surprised to what changes we’ve made to some most-known and played features.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">So lets put into a short list what else we have to offer</span>:<br>
We don’t want to hide half of our community away from rares, so we’ve given everyone a chance of winning Seasonal Items from Penguins which can be located at Rock crabs. They will drop on a very rare scale, White Party-hats and Crystal Keys.</p>
<p>-A community which will mostly support you, have a laugh with you.<br>
-A chance to be noticed, veterans will be needed.<br>
-Advanced dicing for Donators<br>
-Item upgrades<br>
-Fully working upgraded Dungeoneering, we hope it’s better than any other servers<br>
-Lag issue,memory issues and other server hazards have been fixed for excellent up-time and performance.<br>
-NPCs are scattered around the game, most shops are at home but some are elsewhere <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/open_mouth.png?v=9" title=":open_mouth:" class="emoji" alt=":open_mouth:"><br>
-We’ve got over 96% of our items, perfectly statisticed. (Some customs are excluded)<br>
-Not a vast amount of customized items<br>
-Perfect RS Chaotic Crossbow<br>
-Real RS Dung Teleport /w Kinship Ring<br>
-Fixed Slayer NPC Perfectly Animated and Updated<br>
-Player Owned Shops, with most dupes fixed. Reported dupes will be rewarded <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=9" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"><br>
-As seen above, working random events(triggered in-fact).<br>
-Mystery boxes, in events shall be given out.<br>
Not only this, but as you’ve hopefully heard before, various activities and events go on.</p>
<p>We’re hiring, applications to be sent to Jay via the site, we’re expecting quality and strength in leadership and commitment, It’s a RSPS? We need professionals in the matter of moderating, we will give trials out to those who may not seem like they are enough for others, but in-fact they are suitable for the job.</p>
<p>Give us a chance, there’s nothing to loose, For the last time…</p>
<p><a data-bbcode="true">Home</a><br>
<a data-bbcode="true">Play</a><br>
<a data-bbcode="true">External Play</a><br>
<a data-bbcode="true">Forums</a><br>
[/CENTER]</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/blizzardrsps-the-new-the-fresh-the-old-hiring/527810/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/blizzardrsps-the-new-the-fresh-the-old-hiring/527810/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 11 Aug 2013 13:58:22 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-527810-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/blizzardrsps-the-new-the-fresh-the-old-hiring/527810.rss">BlizzardRSPS - The new, the fresh, the old. [Hiring]</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
