<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Advertising</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/advertising/235340</link>
    <description>It seems that an immense amount of you seem to think it is alright to advertise both your servers and forums in your server download topics.  This is unacceptable, and will not be tolerated.  If you are caught doing it, you will be [b]punished severely, no questions asked[/b].  You are all aware that this should not happen, and it&#39;s going to stop right now.

Please also take into account that this does not only go for the downloads section, but for the [b]whole[/b] site.  The only exception for this is the RSC section, which [b]Server[/b] advertisements will be acceptable for RSC servers.

I&#39;ve been receiving personal messages asking if this rules goes for signatures as well, it [b]does not[/b].</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 06 Oct 2008 21:30:53 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Community Suggestions</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/advertising/235340.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Advertising</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Tico135 Tico]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/tico135">@Tico135</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>It seems that an immense amount of you seem to think it is alright to advertise both your servers and forums in your server download topics.  This is unacceptable, and will not be tolerated.  If you are caught doing it, you will be <span class="bbcode-b">punished severely, no questions asked</span>.  You are all aware that this should not happen, and it’s going to stop right now.</p>
<p>Please also take into account that this does not only go for the downloads section, but for the <span class="bbcode-b">whole</span> site.  The only exception for this is the RSC section, which <span class="bbcode-b">Server</span> advertisements will be acceptable for RSC servers.</p>
<p>I’ve been receiving personal messages asking if this rules goes for signatures as well, it <span class="bbcode-b">does not</span>.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/advertising/235340/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/advertising/235340/1</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 06 Oct 2008 21:30:53 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-235340-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/advertising/235340.rss">Advertising</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
