<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Insecurity, Laziness, Solutions</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/insecurity-laziness-solutions/261621</link>
    <description>Hello and thank you for reading, don&#39;t skim whatever you do.

It has come to my attention recently after visiting a few user made forums/sites, not to name any, people just don&#39;t care about web security. A single line of code can ruin your life believe me.

First and primary problem, echoing/using direct user input. Have you found yourself doing this? $variable1 = $_post[&#39;1&#39;]? How about fopen($_post[&#39;1&#39;])? How about we get smart and client side filter with maybe a maxlength? I won&#39;t even get into database credentials and log.txt. mail()?

Worst solution: &quot;You could have brought it to my attention instad of letting me find out. You have been banned! Sorry!&quot;. You know who you are, this just pisses me off. You ban me and say oh, no one else will find that vulnerability, ill fix it tomorrow. Lets see, I have 100 proxies I can use, 10+ vpns, 1000+ unsecured wireless networks in my area. Overall, banning someone does you no good. At all. Also to add to this, &quot;you tried to steal my passes!&quot;, your information is useless to me, you should be happy.

Significant solution: FILTER EVERYTHING. NOTHING CLIENTSIDE. When I say filter everything, filter that little menu deep inside the usercp that asks my gender. The best way to go about doing this is htmlentities or similiar, mysqlescape, as well as strreplace any known attacks. Basically google it, I wont go into detail here, but remember if it comes from a user at all, whether it be variables, anything intercepted, etc. Cookies should be random junk, if you must use them at all. To name a few.

Best solution: None :) I was once told there is no such thing as network security. Your main goal is to be less vulnerable than the other guy, and keep out noobs like me. The actual best thing to do is ask someone to pen test or look up every common hacking technique known and use it on your site and use it on all your friends sites.

Important note: Users uploading anything is usually a bad idea. If possible LIMIT everything, whether it be connections, uploads, flooding. My friend told me to test his upload script, I said ok, let me curl 2000 files per minute.

Memorable Examples:
-Idiot on these forums invents a &quot;proxy&quot; that file_get_contents($_post), I put in index.php and boom! To this day I have full access to his database, I just dont care.

-Friend found an XSS hole in an old version of vbulliten. Linked us to a php file on his server which posted a topic in the forum saying &quot;im a noob&quot; or something.

-Fool hit the news with sqlinjection to a popular site but instead of admin passwords, he went right to spitting out the 300k emails. Ching.

-Someone in this forum allowed PHP files to be uploaded and accessed. lol..

-Someone is DDOSing me! Oh no! Maybe if I cry and whine it&#39;ll stop.

Thanks, any additions please post, any errors if important please post. I can try hacking a few sites if you wish to let us. I would advise someone more professional. Last note: When someone hacks you and you find out or someone tells you have a vulnerability, please thank them. I am sick of being called a noob when I save you reinstalling your operating system.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2009 18:07:43 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>General Programming</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/insecurity-laziness-solutions/261621.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Insecurity, Laziness, Solutions</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@runescape3dude runescape3dude]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/runescape3dude">@runescape3dude</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <pre><code class="lang-auto">-Idiot on these forums invents a "proxy" that file_get_contents($_post), I put in index.php and boom! To this day I have full access to his database, I just dont care.</code></pre>
<p>No you don’t. + The server hasn’t been plugged in for the last 3 months.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/insecurity-laziness-solutions/261621/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/insecurity-laziness-solutions/261621/5</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2009 18:07:43 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-261621-5</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/insecurity-laziness-solutions/261621.rss">Insecurity, Laziness, Solutions</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Insecurity, Laziness, Solutions</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@moparisthebest Moparisthebest]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/moparisthebest">@moparisthebest</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote no-group quote-modified" data-post="1" data-topic="261635">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/onlyonerule/40/5_6bca9977b612b7aeef77ba1ec1cd67b3.png" class="avatar"><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/261635/1">On another topic</a>
</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Something I would like to add is md5 hashing isn’t as safe as some people say it is. websites like <a href="http://www.md5.rednoize.com/" rel="nofollow noopener">http://www.md5.rednoize.com/</a> are becoming more popular and before we know it we will be able too look up any password hash and unhash it. To anyone who really wants to make a secure site. Make your own unique encyption so even if your code has a flaw. It will be difficult for anyone to unhash a unique encryption.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>If you don’t trust md5, then use something more secure, like sha1.  I would never recommend someone to ‘write their own encryption algorithm’, to do so would be to assume you are smarter than a group of research scientists with doctorates in cryptology, 9.99999999 times out of 10, you are wrong.  An alternative would be to salt your hashes.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group quote-modified" data-post="1" data-topic="261635">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/onlyonerule/40/5_6bca9977b612b7aeef77ba1ec1cd67b3.png" class="avatar"><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/261635/1">On another topic</a>
</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Another thing. Some people like trying to go as far as they can without using a secure database like MySQL. I’m not saying MySQL is all that secure, but it is made for a purpous. But instead people try using .txt files or XML to save information. But don’t realise how easy it can be accessed through a remote user Even if it is in a secured folder or in a completely different hard drive on your server. As long as it can be read by the server it can be accessed by a remote computer. Never save anyones personal information in open files.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I would say you have just as much risk of someone remotely opening your file as you do of someone remotely opening your MySQL database, don’t be lulled into a false sense of security using tools that seem secure, when they all really just rely on a password (and can be configured to not even do that!)  In the end MySQL stores it’s information in ‘open files’ as well.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/insecurity-laziness-solutions/261621/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/insecurity-laziness-solutions/261621/4</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2009 01:35:25 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-261621-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/insecurity-laziness-solutions/261621.rss">Insecurity, Laziness, Solutions</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Insecurity, Laziness, Solutions</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@belbn belbn]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/belbn">@belbn</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>This is my point. Fags advertise their “professional” sites, wouldn’t call it production, yet they still have shit code. How many of you right in this forum can be called this?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/insecurity-laziness-solutions/261621/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/insecurity-laziness-solutions/261621/3</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2009 20:02:55 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-261621-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/insecurity-laziness-solutions/261621.rss">Insecurity, Laziness, Solutions</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Insecurity, Laziness, Solutions</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Unhandled Unhandled]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/unhandled">@Unhandled</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Go tell it to moparscape. If you don’t know this already you probably shouldn’t be putting code on production servers.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/insecurity-laziness-solutions/261621/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/insecurity-laziness-solutions/261621/2</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2009 19:58:55 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-261621-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/insecurity-laziness-solutions/261621.rss">Insecurity, Laziness, Solutions</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Insecurity, Laziness, Solutions</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@belbn belbn]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/belbn">@belbn</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Hello and thank you for reading, don’t skim whatever you do.</p>
<p>It has come to my attention recently after visiting a few user made forums/sites, not to name any, people just don’t care about web security. A single line of code can ruin your life believe me.</p>
<p>First and primary problem, echoing/using direct user input. Have you found yourself doing this? $variable1 = $_post[‘1’]? How about fopen($_post[‘1’])? How about we get smart and client side filter with maybe a maxlength? I won’t even get into database credentials and log.txt. mail()?</p>
<p>Worst solution: “You could have brought it to my attention instad of letting me find out. You have been banned! Sorry!”. You know who you are, this just pisses me off. You ban me and say oh, no one else will find that vulnerability, ill fix it tomorrow. Lets see, I have 100 proxies I can use, 10+ vpns, 1000+ unsecured wireless networks in my area. Overall, banning someone does you no good. At all. Also to add to this, “you tried to steal my passes!”, your information is useless to me, you should be happy.</p>
<p>Significant solution: FILTER EVERYTHING. NOTHING CLIENTSIDE. When I say filter everything, filter that little menu deep inside the usercp that asks my gender. The best way to go about doing this is htmlentities or similiar, mysqlescape, as well as strreplace any known attacks. Basically google it, I wont go into detail here, but remember if it comes from a user at all, whether it be variables, anything intercepted, etc. Cookies should be random junk, if you must use them at all. To name a few.</p>
<p>Best solution: None <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=6" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"> I was once told there is no such thing as network security. Your main goal is to be less vulnerable than the other guy, and keep out noobs like me. The actual best thing to do is ask someone to pen test or look up every common hacking technique known and use it on your site and use it on all your friends sites.</p>
<p>Important note: Users uploading anything is usually a bad idea. If possible LIMIT everything, whether it be connections, uploads, flooding. My friend told me to test his upload script, I said ok, let me curl 2000 files per minute.</p>
<p>Memorable Examples:<br>
-Idiot on these forums invents a “proxy” that file_get_contents($_post), I put in index.php and boom! To this day I have full access to his database, I just dont care.</p>
<p>-Friend found an XSS hole in an old version of vbulliten. Linked us to a php file on his server which posted a topic in the forum saying “im a noob” or something.</p>
<p>-Fool hit the news with sqlinjection to a popular site but instead of admin passwords, he went right to spitting out the 300k emails. Ching.</p>
<p>-Someone in this forum allowed PHP files to be uploaded and accessed. lol…</p>
<p>-Someone is DDOSing me! Oh no! Maybe if I cry and whine it’ll stop.</p>
<p>Thanks, any additions please post, any errors if important please post. I can try hacking a few sites if you wish to let us. I would advise someone more professional. Last note: When someone hacks you and you find out or someone tells you have a vulnerability, please thank them. I am sick of being called a noob when I save you reinstalling your operating system.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/insecurity-laziness-solutions/261621/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/insecurity-laziness-solutions/261621/1</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2009 19:44:42 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-261621-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/insecurity-laziness-solutions/261621.rss">Insecurity, Laziness, Solutions</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
