<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Client Programming (worth your time)</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/client-programming-worth-your-time/420739</link>
    <description>Hello, and thank you for viewing my thread. First and foremost, I&#39;d like to say. Please ignore the sprite positioning and poor Client work. It was done by me, and Client-sided programming is not a strong point of mine.

I&#39;d also like to say, I&#39;ve just begun working on this project, and it has under 24 hours of programming time invested in it, so please be gentle with me. I&#39;m looking for a mature (preferably adult) programmer, who can program Clients very well. The programmer should be very familiar with Clients, and should be able to do anything ranging from moving sprites, to removing and editing entire parts of the Client. If you add my AIM and listen to what I have to say, once you log-in, I know you&#39;ll want to be my partner. In closing I&#39;d like to say, my MoparScape account does NOT represent my programming experience or abilities. Thank you for your valuable time, please take a look at the pictures below if you&#39;re interested.

**I&#39;ve removed all of the RuneScape Map Icons from the minimap, and started adding my own, to show that I have a general idea of Clients, but like I said. They&#39;re not my strong suit.**

*I can promise you, that this server will be a one-of-a-kind. You&#39;ll never see a server like it, and we intend to be 100% original and unique.*


My AIM is: Abmassator1@yahoo
My Skype is: buysomedrugsyo



Reward System and Skill Icons:
http://img196.imageshack.us/img196/1886/rewards0skills.jpg

Custom Map Icons and Clan Chat:
http://img600.imageshack.us/img600/7450/cc0customicons.jpg

Achievement Diary, 474+ Content, and NPC edits:
http://img20.imageshack.us/img20/1600/diary0port0npcs.jpg


Additional information:

- My source is based on Shard Revolutions (not project no-doze).

- My Client is a cleaned 317 with a 474 cache. Hard-coding won&#39;t corrupt the cache.

- You will be given access to the Dedicated host once the server is out of Alpha stage testing and in open Beta.

- You will be given Administrative rights, and be a Developer with power equal to me.

- I have started writing the first server mandate, which you can ask to view once we begin chatting. I have very strict rules and expectations from Staff, Players, and Programmers that must be adhered to.

DOUBLE EDIT:
- The Game-Frame will remain a 317, this is non-negotiable.

- I&#39;m 19 years old, don&#39;t think you&#39;ll be working with a silly child or anything.

- I don&#39;t have a mic to use with Skype, but I can speak with you over Xbox Live if need-be.

If you have any questions, please feel free to post. You can flame me and say bad things about me, I don&#39;t mind. Also you can contact me without posting here.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 06 Nov 2011 02:23:05 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Game Development</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/client-programming-worth-your-time/420739.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Client Programming (worth your time)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Jack_Bower Jack Bower]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/jack_bower">@Jack_Bower</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“Ags Rush, post:2, topic:420739”]inb4mopar</p>
<p>I can’t tell if this is a well thought out thread, or a Troll.[/quote]</p>
<p>What do you mean?</p>
<p>EDIT: The pictures are now fixed.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/client-programming-worth-your-time/420739/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/client-programming-worth-your-time/420739/3</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 06 Nov 2011 02:23:05 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-420739-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/client-programming-worth-your-time/420739.rss">Client Programming (worth your time)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Client Programming (worth your time)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Ags_Rush Ags Rush]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/ags_rush">@Ags_Rush</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>inb4mopar</p>
<p>I can’t tell if this is a well thought out thread, or a Troll.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/client-programming-worth-your-time/420739/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/client-programming-worth-your-time/420739/2</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 06 Nov 2011 02:09:51 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-420739-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/client-programming-worth-your-time/420739.rss">Client Programming (worth your time)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Client Programming (worth your time)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Jack_Bower Jack Bower]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/jack_bower">@Jack_Bower</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Hello, and thank you for viewing my thread. First and foremost, I’d like to say. Please ignore the sprite positioning and poor Client work. It was done by me, and Client-sided programming is not a strong point of mine.</p>
<p>I’d also like to say, I’ve just begun working on this project, and it has under 24 hours of programming time invested in it, so please be gentle with me. I’m looking for a mature (preferably adult) programmer, who can program Clients very well. The programmer should be very familiar with Clients, and should be able to do anything ranging from moving sprites, to removing and editing entire parts of the Client. If you add my AIM and listen to what I have to say, once you log-in, I know you’ll want to be my partner. In closing I’d like to say, my MoparScape account does NOT represent my programming experience or abilities. Thank you for your valuable time, please take a look at the pictures below if you’re interested.</p>
<p><strong>I’ve removed all of the RuneScape Map Icons from the minimap, and started adding my own, to show that I have a general idea of Clients, but like I said. They’re not my strong suit.</strong></p>
<p><em>I can promise you, that this server will be a one-of-a-kind. You’ll never see a server like it, and we intend to be 100% original and unique.</em></p>
<p>My AIM is: Abmassator1@yahoo<br>
My Skype is: buysomedrugsyo</p>
<p>Reward System and Skill Icons:<br>
<a href="http://img196.imageshack.us/img196/1886/rewards0skills.jpg" class="onebox" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">http://img196.imageshack.us/img196/1886/rewards0skills.jpg</a></p>
<p>Custom Map Icons and Clan Chat:<br>
<a href="http://img600.imageshack.us/img600/7450/cc0customicons.jpg" class="onebox" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">http://img600.imageshack.us/img600/7450/cc0customicons.jpg</a></p>
<p>Achievement Diary, 474+ Content, and NPC edits:<br>
<a href="http://img20.imageshack.us/img20/1600/diary0port0npcs.jpg" class="onebox" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">http://img20.imageshack.us/img20/1600/diary0port0npcs.jpg</a></p>
<p>Additional information:</p>
<ul>
<li>
<p>My source is based on Shard Revolutions (not project no-doze).</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>My Client is a cleaned 317 with a 474 cache. Hard-coding won’t corrupt the cache.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>You will be given access to the Dedicated host once the server is out of Alpha stage testing and in open Beta.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>You will be given Administrative rights, and be a Developer with power equal to me.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>I have started writing the first server mandate, which you can ask to view once we begin chatting. I have very strict rules and expectations from Staff, Players, and Programmers that must be adhered to.</p>
</li>
</ul>
<p>DOUBLE EDIT:</p>
<ul>
<li>
<p>The Game-Frame will remain a 317, this is non-negotiable.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>I’m 19 years old, don’t think you’ll be working with a silly child or anything.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>I don’t have a mic to use with Skype, but I can speak with you over Xbox Live if need-be.</p>
</li>
</ul>
<p>If you have any questions, please feel free to post. You can flame me and say bad things about me, I don’t mind. Also you can contact me without posting here.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/client-programming-worth-your-time/420739/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/client-programming-worth-your-time/420739/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 06 Nov 2011 01:41:55 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-420739-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/client-programming-worth-your-time/420739.rss">Client Programming (worth your time)</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
