<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Overall help</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/overall-help/259074</link>
    <description>Okay, hello everyone, i&#39;m having a few problems due to me not doing this for a long time, so please any reminding would be great. My main issue is that on my old pc&#39;s i used to have this &#39;&#39;perfect compiler&#39;&#39; which worked for many different sources, i was hoping somebody could either link download or give me info on how to get. now the only source that seems to work for me without the perfect compiler is Figmentscape. the only problem with this is that any user that logs on seems to be invisible, ive never edited this and was thinking only a whole restart could help this. please give any info, even if you dont know it will help, will appreciate it loads, thanks everyone. :)</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2009 07:33:50 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/overall-help/259074.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Overall help</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@killoplish killoplish]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/killoplish">@killoplish</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Okay, hello everyone, i’m having a few problems due to me not doing this for a long time, so please any reminding would be great. My main issue is that on my old pc’s i used to have this ‘‘perfect compiler’’ which worked for many different sources, i was hoping somebody could either link download or give me info on how to get. now the only source that seems to work for me without the perfect compiler is Figmentscape. the only problem with this is that any user that logs on seems to be invisible, ive never edited this and was thinking only a whole restart could help this. please give any info, even if you dont know it will help, will appreciate it loads, thanks everyone. <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=6" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/overall-help/259074/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/overall-help/259074/1</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2009 07:33:50 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-259074-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/overall-help/259074.rss">Overall help</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
