<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Item, Object, and NPC Viewers</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/item-object-and-npc-viewers/548470</link>
    <description>Hi. I&#39;ve been spending the past couple of days adding onto my cache editor API and writing plugins for it. Now granted, none of this was really all [i]that[/i] hard, and it only views (for now), but I wanted to make a topic separate from the suite&#39;s topic to allow people to comment directly on these plugins. One way of thinking of it is these are 3 separate tools, so please don&#39;t hurt me for wanting to flood this section with my contributions. :D

[B]NOTE: These plugins require [u]API 1.3[/u] to properly work. If you are just downloading these and adding onto a pre-1.3 suite download, you must make sure the 4 Tao library files (Tao.OpenGl.DLL, Tao.OpenGl.XML, Tao.Platform.Windows.DLL, and Tao.Platform.Windows.XML) are in the same directory as the Cache Editor API.DLL 1.3 file![/B] If this is too confusing, just download the latest suite with all of the plugins and whatnot situated [url=https://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php/topic,662853.0.html]Here[/url].

[b]Overall Features[/b]
Every plugin comes with a property editor and model viewer. Modifying the model-editing properties will cause the model to update, so although you cannot save any of your modifications, this can come in handy. Some of the properties in the items and objects are unnamed.

[b]Item Viewer[/b]
This plugin allows you to view all of the items by selecting &quot;obj.dat&quot; in the &quot;Config&quot; sub-archive. It features the item&#39;s sprite, its model that&#39;s automatically rotated as the sprite is, and locking the sprite to the model viewer. This can be useful if you&#39;re trying to get the best sprite for your item. Modifying the properties will update the sprite and/or model as necessary. The unnamed variables in here are all related to equipment. I didn&#39;t take the time to figure out exactly what was what and rather than give them lame names like &quot;male_0&quot;, I left them as-is.

[img]http://i.imgur.com/69a4KJh.png[/img]

[b]Object Viewer[/b]
This plugin allows you to view all of the objects by selecting &quot;loc.dat&quot; in the &quot;config&quot; sub-archive. Unique to this besides property and model viewing is a simple feature that finds the object type for you. For example, 10 is the most common, but some objects use 0, or 22, and rather than guess, it goes ahead and loops to 23 to try and find the correct type that displays a model.

[img]http://i.imgur.com/bCpfyBd.png[/img]

[b]NPC Viewer[/b]
Everything is (hopefully) properly named in terms of the properties, although &quot;SettingsID&quot; and &quot;VarBitIndex&quot; are unclear. It&#39;s worth noting the SubNPCIDs is ignored for the model, due to the children requiring &quot;VarBit&quot; data. I haven&#39;t looked into this enough to implement it properly. This can be useful for getting the animations for an NPC (as if dumps didn&#39;t exist).

[img]http://i.imgur.com/qjlmhb8.png[/img]

[url=http://www.mediafire.com/download/h0bwgqjtqbzle80/ion_plugins.zip][b]Download[/b][/url]
[url=https://github.com/Lin20/cachesuite]Source on GitHub[/url]

~Lin</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2014 01:31:03 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/item-object-and-npc-viewers/548470.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Item, Object, and NPC Viewers</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@imthenull imthenull]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/imthenull">@imthenull</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“Miss Silabsoft, post:5, topic:548470”]It would be useful to see you go the extra step on the animations and have them actually display, You can take a look at bentski’s animation viewer.[/quote]bitch speaks the truth</p>
<p>(sorry silab, ily)</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/item-object-and-npc-viewers/548470/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/item-object-and-npc-viewers/548470/6</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2014 01:31:03 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-548470-6</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/item-object-and-npc-viewers/548470.rss">Item, Object, and NPC Viewers</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Item, Object, and NPC Viewers</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@silabsoft RuneAgent]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/silabsoft">@silabsoft</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>It would be useful to see you go the extra step on the animations and have them actually display, You can take a look at bentski’s animation viewer.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/item-object-and-npc-viewers/548470/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/item-object-and-npc-viewers/548470/5</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2014 00:44:34 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-548470-5</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/item-object-and-npc-viewers/548470.rss">Item, Object, and NPC Viewers</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Item, Object, and NPC Viewers</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@imthenull imthenull]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/imthenull">@imthenull</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>this is awesome, great job Lin</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/item-object-and-npc-viewers/548470/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/item-object-and-npc-viewers/548470/4</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2014 17:04:22 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-548470-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/item-object-and-npc-viewers/548470.rss">Item, Object, and NPC Viewers</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Item, Object, and NPC Viewers</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Lin Lin]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/lin">@Lin</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>It looks like one of your subarchives was either repacked or compressed improperly. The project is open-source, so you’re more than welcome to download and debug the cache loading procedure to see just where it messed up. If I spent more time putting in exception handlers and safety code, you’d be able to browse everything that functioned properly. But I didn’t, because I live in a pretend world where there’s no such thing as people wanting more items than there were originally intended, or images in a sub-archive that the index file would allow. Maybe one day I’ll add those in, but until then, I’m sorry but your corrupted cache is unusable with my editor.</p>
<p>Also, thank you for the feedback.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/item-object-and-npc-viewers/548470/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/item-object-and-npc-viewers/548470/3</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2014 21:34:39 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-548470-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/item-object-and-npc-viewers/548470.rss">Item, Object, and NPC Viewers</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Item, Object, and NPC Viewers</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@sk8rdude461 sk8rdude461]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/sk8rdude461">@sk8rdude461</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Dude, awesome. I’ve been waiting for your new cache editor to get some tools <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=5" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"><br>
Do you know how to “repair” a cache that has errors? I.E, I cannot open some parts of the cache in Tom’s editor… It’d probably cause issues on your editor too…<br>
Edit:<br>
It does, in fact, error on your editor too… But with toms I at least have access to some features.</p>
<p><img src="http://puu.sh/dvmgv/06f588e807.png" alt width="" height=""></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/item-object-and-npc-viewers/548470/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/item-object-and-npc-viewers/548470/2</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2014 06:16:58 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-548470-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/item-object-and-npc-viewers/548470.rss">Item, Object, and NPC Viewers</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Item, Object, and NPC Viewers</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Lin Lin]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/lin">@Lin</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Hi. I’ve been spending the past couple of days adding onto my cache editor API and writing plugins for it. Now granted, none of this was really all <span class="bbcode-i">that</span> hard, and it only views (for now), but I wanted to make a topic separate from the suite’s topic to allow people to comment directly on these plugins. One way of thinking of it is these are 3 separate tools, so please don’t hurt me for wanting to flood this section with my contributions. <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/smiley.png?v=5" title=":smiley:" class="emoji" alt=":smiley:"></p>
<p>[B]NOTE: These plugins require <span class="bbcode-u">API 1.3</span> to properly work. If you are just downloading these and adding onto a pre-1.3 suite download, you must make sure the 4 Tao library files (Tao.OpenGl.DLL, Tao.OpenGl.XML, Tao.Platform.Windows.DLL, and Tao.Platform.Windows.XML) are in the same directory as the Cache Editor API.DLL 1.3 file![/B] If this is too confusing, just download the latest suite with all of the plugins and whatnot situated <a href="https://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php/topic,662853.0.html" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">Here</a>.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Overall Features</span><br>
Every plugin comes with a property editor and model viewer. Modifying the model-editing properties will cause the model to update, so although you cannot save any of your modifications, this can come in handy. Some of the properties in the items and objects are unnamed.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Item Viewer</span><br>
This plugin allows you to view all of the items by selecting “obj.dat” in the “Config” sub-archive. It features the item’s sprite, its model that’s automatically rotated as the sprite is, and locking the sprite to the model viewer. This can be useful if you’re trying to get the best sprite for your item. Modifying the properties will update the sprite and/or model as necessary. The unnamed variables in here are all related to equipment. I didn’t take the time to figure out exactly what was what and rather than give them lame names like “male_0”, I left them as-is.</p>
<p><img src="http://i.imgur.com/69a4KJh.png" alt width="" height=""></p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Object Viewer</span><br>
This plugin allows you to view all of the objects by selecting “loc.dat” in the “config” sub-archive. Unique to this besides property and model viewing is a simple feature that finds the object type for you. For example, 10 is the most common, but some objects use 0, or 22, and rather than guess, it goes ahead and loops to 23 to try and find the correct type that displays a model.</p>
<p><img src="http://i.imgur.com/bCpfyBd.png" alt width="" height=""></p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">NPC Viewer</span><br>
Everything is (hopefully) properly named in terms of the properties, although “SettingsID” and “VarBitIndex” are unclear. It’s worth noting the SubNPCIDs is ignored for the model, due to the children requiring “VarBit” data. I haven’t looked into this enough to implement it properly. This can be useful for getting the animations for an NPC (as if dumps didn’t exist).</p>
<p><img src="http://i.imgur.com/qjlmhb8.png" alt width="" height=""></p>
<p><a href="http://www.mediafire.com/download/h0bwgqjtqbzle80/ion_plugins.zip" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener"><span class="bbcode-b">Download</span></a><br>
<a href="https://github.com/Lin20/cachesuite" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">Source on GitHub</a></p>
<p>~Lin</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/item-object-and-npc-viewers/548470/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/item-object-and-npc-viewers/548470/1</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2014 06:11:57 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-548470-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/item-object-and-npc-viewers/548470.rss">Item, Object, and NPC Viewers</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
