<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Help with srl please</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/help-with-srl-please/279174</link>
    <description>can some one help me besides telling me what they think i am... i click on files (in scar) then go to srl download and nothing happens. I CAN NOT FIND A LINK ON THE INTERNET. please help me before i go rageing nuts on my computer and throw it off my balcony into my pool of DEATH!!!

thank you for looking at this post and hopefully you&#39;ll help me before i go ape shit on my computer... thank you..
 oh and if anyone makes a good search engine in the future...do not tell me your name.. because i will never be able to find anything on it. thanks again.

-zac
[center][img]http://moparisthebest.com/smf/Themes/default/images/warnmute.gif[/img] You really didn&#39;t need to make 4 topics to get somebodys attention. Enjoy your weeks mute to rethink what you did.[/center]
[center][img]http://moparisthebest.com/smf/Themes/default/images/warnmute.gif[/img] P.S. stop bumping old topics.[/center]</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 19 May 2009 04:42:35 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/help-with-srl-please/279174.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Help with srl please</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@grayfoxx grayfoxx]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/grayfoxx">@grayfoxx</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>can some one help me besides telling me what they think i am… i click on files (in scar) then go to srl download and nothing happens. I CAN NOT FIND A LINK ON THE INTERNET. please help me before i go rageing nuts on my computer and throw it off my balcony into my pool of DEATH!!!</p>
<p>thank you for looking at this post and hopefully you’ll help me before i go ape shit on my computer… thank you…<br>
oh and if anyone makes a good search engine in the future…do not tell me your name… because i will never be able to find anything on it. thanks again.</p>
<p>-zac<br>
[center]<img src="http://moparisthebest.com/smf/Themes/default/images/warnmute.gif" alt width="" height=""> You really didn’t need to make 4 topics to get somebodys attention. Enjoy your weeks mute to rethink what you did.[/center]<br>
[center]<img src="http://moparisthebest.com/smf/Themes/default/images/warnmute.gif" alt width="" height=""> P.S. stop bumping old topics.[/center]</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/help-with-srl-please/279174/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/help-with-srl-please/279174/1</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 19 May 2009 04:42:35 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-279174-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/help-with-srl-please/279174.rss">Help with srl please</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
