<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>I Cannot connect to my own Server!?!</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/i-cannot-connect-to-my-own-server/470758</link>
    <description>I have a server named &#39;SkaarjPK&#39; I ran it for a while without any problems, then I stopped running it and stopped port forwarding. Then after about 3 or 4 months I wanted to connect to my server and fix it up. but when I run the source and the client and try to connect. I get an error that said &#39;Error connecting to server&#39; so then I uninstalled MySQL and it worked, I connected and played around a bit, but then when I logged out and tried another account I got the same problem, and yes, I cannot log back in with any other account.

I have no clue how this is possible, but any suggestions would help. Thanks everyone &lt;3</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 02 Dec 2012 11:02:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/i-cannot-connect-to-my-own-server/470758.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>I Cannot connect to my own Server!?!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Krajix Krajix]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/krajix">@Krajix</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I have a server named ‘SkaarjPK’ I ran it for a while without any problems, then I stopped running it and stopped port forwarding. Then after about 3 or 4 months I wanted to connect to my server and fix it up. but when I run the source and the client and try to connect. I get an error that said ‘Error connecting to server’ so then I uninstalled MySQL and it worked, I connected and played around a bit, but then when I logged out and tried another account I got the same problem, and yes, I cannot log back in with any other account.</p>
<p>I have no clue how this is possible, but any suggestions would help. Thanks everyone &lt;3</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/i-cannot-connect-to-my-own-server/470758/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/i-cannot-connect-to-my-own-server/470758/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 02 Dec 2012 11:02:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-470758-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/i-cannot-connect-to-my-own-server/470758.rss">I Cannot connect to my own Server!?!</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
