<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>[PI] Insanity-X Debugging</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/pi-insanity-x-debugging/452732</link>
    <description>As you know, all RSPS servers have a lot bugs and problems. I have already fixed A LOT of bugs on my server, ShadowPk, I&#39;ve fixed all dupes that I know of. I use a PI base. My direct base is InsanityX. I&#39;ve fixed all popular bugs, such as the ones people you can find with google, and the ones that my players find easily. I&#39;m sure there are still hundreds of bugs left and I need to know a list of commonly passed up Insanity X bugs that way I can find the bug and terminate it. I will repp+ you for listing a bunch of Insanity X bugs that I may or may have not noticed yet. If you think you may know a way to fix the bug, please tell me how. If you want to help me look for bugs on my server, please do so and you won&#39;t go unrewarded.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 03 Aug 2012 23:47:13 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/pi-insanity-x-debugging/452732.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>[PI] Insanity-X Debugging</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@belhelmiel belhelmiel]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/belhelmiel">@belhelmiel</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>As you know, all RSPS servers have a lot bugs and problems. I have already fixed A LOT of bugs on my server, ShadowPk, I’ve fixed all dupes that I know of. I use a PI base. My direct base is InsanityX. I’ve fixed all popular bugs, such as the ones people you can find with google, and the ones that my players find easily. I’m sure there are still hundreds of bugs left and I need to know a list of commonly passed up Insanity X bugs that way I can find the bug and terminate it. I will repp+ you for listing a bunch of Insanity X bugs that I may or may have not noticed yet. If you think you may know a way to fix the bug, please tell me how. If you want to help me look for bugs on my server, please do so and you won’t go unrewarded.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/pi-insanity-x-debugging/452732/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/pi-insanity-x-debugging/452732/1</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 03 Aug 2012 23:47:13 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-452732-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/pi-insanity-x-debugging/452732.rss">[PI] Insanity-X Debugging</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
