<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>How to answer a question in a helpful way</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-answer-a-question-in-a-helpful-way/48150</link>
    <description>Didn&#39;t know where to post this! Figured I would post it in programming general. This goes for other forum-questions aswell ;)

It&#39;s my impression that many answers to questions as of late have sounded a bit... well... [i]retarded[/i] (for lack of a better word). While there might be a few folks out there genuinely in need of a good roasting, most people just want some help. There&#39;s no need to make it more painful than it already may be.

Here are some excellent suggestions from ESR&#39;s oft-quoted essay, [URL=http://www.catb.org/~esr/faqs/smart-questions.html#id266392]How To Ask Questions The Smart Way[/URL]:

[URL=http://www.catb.org/~esr/faqs/smart-questions.html#id266392][b]How To Answer Questions in a Helpful Way[/b][/URL]

[b]Be gentle.[/b] Problem-related stress can make people seem rude or stupid even when they&#39;re not.

[b]Reply to a first offender off-line.[/b] There is no need of public humiliation for someone who may have made an honest mistake. A real newbie may not know how to search archives or where the FAQ is stored or posted.

[b]If you don&#39;t know for sure, say so![/b] A wrong but authoritative-sounding answer is worse than none at all. Don&#39;t point anyone down a wrong path simply because it&#39;s fun to sound like an expert. Be humble and honest; set a good example for both the querent and your peers.

[b]If you can&#39;t help, don&#39;t hinder.[/b] Don&#39;t make jokes about procedures that could trash the user&#39;s setup — the poor sap might interpret these as instructions.

[b]Ask probing questions to elicit more details.[/b] If you&#39;re good at this, the querent will learn something — and so might you. Try to turn the bad question into a good one; remember we were all newbies once.

While just muttering RTFM is sometimes justified when replying to someone who is just a lazy slob, a pointer to documentation (even if it&#39;s just a suggestion to google for a key phrase) is better.

[b]If you&#39;re going to answer the question at all, give good value.[/b] Don&#39;t suggest kludgy workarounds when somebody is using the wrong tool or approach. Suggest good tools. Reframe the question.

[b]Help your community learn from the question.[/b] When you field a good question, ask yourself “How would the relevant documentation or FAQ have to change so that nobody has to answer this again?” Then send a patch to the document maintainer.

If you did research to answer the question, [b]demonstrate your skills rather than writing as though you pulled the answer out of your ass.[/b] Answering one good question is like feeding a hungry person one meal, but teaching them research skills by example is teaching them to grow food for a lifetime.

Thanks! Hopefully this will eliminate some of the retardation going around the place.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 16 Jan 2007 21:08:12 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>General Programming</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-answer-a-question-in-a-helpful-way/48150.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>How to answer a question in a helpful way</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Tree Tree]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/tree">@Tree</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <blockquote>Reply to a first offender off-line. There is no need of public humiliation for someone who may have made an honest mistake. A real newbie may not know how to search archives or where the FAQ is stored or posted.</blockquote>
<p>I laughed at this, but the rest makes perfect sence.</p>
<p>Nice.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-answer-a-question-in-a-helpful-way/48150/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-answer-a-question-in-a-helpful-way/48150/4</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jan 2007 21:08:12 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-48150-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-answer-a-question-in-a-helpful-way/48150.rss">How to answer a question in a helpful way</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>How to answer a question in a helpful way</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@93dcthugs93 93dcthugs93]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/93dcthugs93">@93dcthugs93</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Yeah neither do I. wow i don’t fully agree with myself <em>slap</em></p>
<p>Anyways, some people are fun to bake aren’t they <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/smiley.png?v=6" title=":smiley:" class="emoji" alt=":smiley:"></p>
<p>Just don’t do it all the time.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-answer-a-question-in-a-helpful-way/48150/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-answer-a-question-in-a-helpful-way/48150/3</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jan 2007 16:33:07 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-48150-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-answer-a-question-in-a-helpful-way/48150.rss">How to answer a question in a helpful way</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>How to answer a question in a helpful way</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@bullzeye95 bullzeye]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/bullzeye95">@bullzeye95</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>God man, you’re on overdrive!  This is your 3rd very helpful thread since you’ve gotten back!</p>
<blockquote>[b]Reply to a first offender off-line.[/b] There is no need of public humiliation for someone who may have made an honest mistake. A real newbie may not know how to search archives or where the FAQ is stored or posted.</blockquote>
I don't fully agree with that though.  I always make sure I've tried everything I can think of before making a thread.  And take, for example, those dumb noobs that come here asking about moparscape.  It says not to post here about it on the rules, in the caption below the questions forum, and in the "News" box.
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-answer-a-question-in-a-helpful-way/48150/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-answer-a-question-in-a-helpful-way/48150/2</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jan 2007 05:33:16 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-48150-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-answer-a-question-in-a-helpful-way/48150.rss">How to answer a question in a helpful way</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>How to answer a question in a helpful way</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@93dcthugs93 93dcthugs93]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/93dcthugs93">@93dcthugs93</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Didn’t know where to post this! Figured I would post it in programming general. This goes for other forum-questions aswell <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/wink.png?v=6" title=":wink:" class="emoji" alt=":wink:"></p>
<p>It’s my impression that many answers to questions as of late have sounded a bit… well… <span class="bbcode-i">retarded</span> (for lack of a better word). While there might be a few folks out there genuinely in need of a good roasting, most people just want some help. There’s no need to make it more painful than it already may be.</p>
<p>Here are some excellent suggestions from ESR’s oft-quoted essay, <a href="http://www.catb.org/~esr/faqs/smart-questions.html#id266392" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">How To Ask Questions The Smart Way</a>:</p>
<p><a href="http://www.catb.org/~esr/faqs/smart-questions.html#id266392" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener"><span class="bbcode-b">How To Answer Questions in a Helpful Way</span></a></p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Be gentle.</span> Problem-related stress can make people seem rude or stupid even when they’re not.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Reply to a first offender off-line.</span> There is no need of public humiliation for someone who may have made an honest mistake. A real newbie may not know how to search archives or where the FAQ is stored or posted.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">If you don’t know for sure, say so!</span> A wrong but authoritative-sounding answer is worse than none at all. Don’t point anyone down a wrong path simply because it’s fun to sound like an expert. Be humble and honest; set a good example for both the querent and your peers.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">If you can’t help, don’t hinder.</span> Don’t make jokes about procedures that could trash the user’s setup — the poor sap might interpret these as instructions.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Ask probing questions to elicit more details.</span> If you’re good at this, the querent will learn something — and so might you. Try to turn the bad question into a good one; remember we were all newbies once.</p>
<p>While just muttering RTFM is sometimes justified when replying to someone who is just a lazy slob, a pointer to documentation (even if it’s just a suggestion to google for a key phrase) is better.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">If you’re going to answer the question at all, give good value.</span> Don’t suggest kludgy workarounds when somebody is using the wrong tool or approach. Suggest good tools. Reframe the question.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Help your community learn from the question.</span> When you field a good question, ask yourself “How would the relevant documentation or FAQ have to change so that nobody has to answer this again?” Then send a patch to the document maintainer.</p>
<p>If you did research to answer the question, <span class="bbcode-b">demonstrate your skills rather than writing as though you pulled the answer out of your ass.</span> Answering one good question is like feeding a hungry person one meal, but teaching them research skills by example is teaching them to grow food for a lifetime.</p>
<p>Thanks! Hopefully this will eliminate some of the retardation going around the place.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-answer-a-question-in-a-helpful-way/48150/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-answer-a-question-in-a-helpful-way/48150/1</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jan 2007 05:18:15 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-48150-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-answer-a-question-in-a-helpful-way/48150.rss">How to answer a question in a helpful way</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
