<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Server Hosting ~~~ Need Help</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/server-hosting-need-help/471244</link>
    <description>I&#39;m using Project Annihilation. My purpose is to work with this project between home computers, see myself and ect. I have setup no-ip, and I have use uturrent for port forwarding. I open the PJA_user client, and change the 127.0.0.1 ip to my no-ip address. I then sent that same client to my second computer. On my host computer, I open up no-ip, then use eclipse to run the server. Then go on my second computer, open up client.. then nothing happens, I get a connection error.

[b]What I&#39;m I doing wrong here? Do I need to add something to the server file? Or add something to Client? Or something with eclipse?[/b]</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2012 02:27:03 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/server-hosting-need-help/471244.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Server Hosting ~~~ Need Help</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Maximu Maximu]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/maximu">@Maximu</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I’m using Project Annihilation. My purpose is to work with this project between home computers, see myself and ect. I have setup no-ip, and I have use uturrent for port forwarding. I open the PJA_user client, and change the 127.0.0.1 ip to my no-ip address. I then sent that same client to my second computer. On my host computer, I open up no-ip, then use eclipse to run the server. Then go on my second computer, open up client… then nothing happens, I get a connection error.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">What I’m I doing wrong here? Do I need to add something to the server file? Or add something to Client? Or something with eclipse?</span></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/server-hosting-need-help/471244/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/server-hosting-need-help/471244/1</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2012 02:27:03 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-471244-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/server-hosting-need-help/471244.rss">Server Hosting ~~~ Need Help</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
