<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Is FindRoadColor currently broken?</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/is-findroadcolor-currently-broken/307208</link>
    <description>Hi all,

I&#39;ve searched the forums and google and found a post on another forum stating that SCAR 3.20 broke the FindRoadColor function.  That doesn&#39;t make too much sense to me~ I&#39;d expect a RS update to break it, not a SCAR update.  But I was hoping for confirmation if updates have, in fact, broken the FindRoadColor function.

Background: I leeched a script for mining ore that worked pretty darn well.  Based on tutorials and my dated c++ knowledge, I then wrote a separate routine for testing purposes which based on bitmaps, once near a statue in north Falador, allow me to flawlessly (so far) find the smelter and smelt.  That might sound miniscule, but for me it was a big step! :)
   I then started a test script using radial walks to transit from the furnace to the mining site, just to see if I could do it... but using FindRoadColor never works.  By manually eyedropping the color I brought success to around 5-10% per roadwalk, but still nothing near what&#39;s needed for the long transit.  I was hoping that by using FindRoadColor or FindFaladorRoadColor I could make a more reliable script.  I could, I suppose, use bitmaps at road intersections, but I&#39;m afraid that would be more predictable, and therefore more detectable by Jagex.
   I can post my scripts, but they are not properly credited yet.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 09 Oct 2009 18:16:17 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/is-findroadcolor-currently-broken/307208.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Is FindRoadColor currently broken?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@yimboli yimboli]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/yimboli">@yimboli</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Thanks.  I found the post (saying FindRoadColor was broken) on a cached google page of villavu, since the forums were not accessible the last couple days.  Looks like they’re back up now <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=5" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/is-findroadcolor-currently-broken/307208/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/is-findroadcolor-currently-broken/307208/3</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Oct 2009 18:16:17 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-307208-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/is-findroadcolor-currently-broken/307208.rss">Is FindRoadColor currently broken?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Is FindRoadColor currently broken?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Mopman Mopman]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/mopman">@Mopman</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>You might wanna repost this over on the SRL Forum (<a href="http://villavu.com">villavu.com</a>) if you didn’t already, the SCAR headz are way more active over there than they are here.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/is-findroadcolor-currently-broken/307208/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/is-findroadcolor-currently-broken/307208/2</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Oct 2009 17:56:03 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-307208-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/is-findroadcolor-currently-broken/307208.rss">Is FindRoadColor currently broken?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Is FindRoadColor currently broken?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@yimboli yimboli]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/yimboli">@yimboli</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Hi all,</p>
<p>I’ve searched the forums and google and found a post on another forum stating that SCAR 3.20 broke the FindRoadColor function.  That doesn’t make too much sense to me~ I’d expect a RS update to break it, not a SCAR update.  But I was hoping for confirmation if updates have, in fact, broken the FindRoadColor function.</p>
<p>Background: I leeched a script for mining ore that worked pretty darn well.  Based on tutorials and my dated c++ knowledge, I then wrote a separate routine for testing purposes which based on bitmaps, once near a statue in north Falador, allow me to flawlessly (so far) find the smelter and smelt.  That might sound miniscule, but for me it was a big step! <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=5" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"><br>
I then started a test script using radial walks to transit from the furnace to the mining site, just to see if I could do it… but using FindRoadColor never works.  By manually eyedropping the color I brought success to around 5-10% per roadwalk, but still nothing near what’s needed for the long transit.  I was hoping that by using FindRoadColor or FindFaladorRoadColor I could make a more reliable script.  I could, I suppose, use bitmaps at road intersections, but I’m afraid that would be more predictable, and therefore more detectable by Jagex.<br>
I can post my scripts, but they are not properly credited yet.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/is-findroadcolor-currently-broken/307208/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/is-findroadcolor-currently-broken/307208/1</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Oct 2009 02:11:19 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-307208-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/is-findroadcolor-currently-broken/307208.rss">Is FindRoadColor currently broken?</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
