<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Website Template</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/website-template/83439</link>
    <description>I need a website template :o
I would make it myself but I don&#39;t got photoshop on this laptop, and it would be hard to make it with no mouse anyways.. If you could make it I would appreciate it ;D

What I want it something like.. 
Banner ontop, height 300 length 600.
I want the main template to be whatever a normal one would be in length and what ever height you think would work, I&#39;m not to sure about sizes atm, I want the navigation to be on the left featuring about 5 buttons, or the space for them, I can make my own later. I want the colors to be black, and neon green as borders, ect. You should know what I&#39;m talking about if you&#39;ve seen alienware. I want a main info section in the center of the template, should be considerably large but not to big. 
I would appreciate it if you atleast try to make something, I don&#39;t expect it to be done right away. Even if you aren&#39;t that good at graphics I would like to see you try to make one, it could help you improve your graphic abilitys.
 
Many thanks
Exe626</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 22 Apr 2007 21:24:13 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Graphics</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/website-template/83439.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Website Template</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@exe626 exe626]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/exe626">@exe626</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Well then, looks like it wont be to high quality since I lost 1 graphic master</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/website-template/83439/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/website-template/83439/3</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 22 Apr 2007 21:24:13 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-83439-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/website-template/83439.rss">Website Template</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Website Template</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@FastBallz FastBawlz]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/fastballz">@FastBallz</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I’m to fucking lazy for large pieces of work</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/website-template/83439/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/website-template/83439/2</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 22 Apr 2007 21:06:36 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-83439-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/website-template/83439.rss">Website Template</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Website Template</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@exe626 exe626]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/exe626">@exe626</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I need a website template :o<br>
I would make it myself but I don’t got photoshop on this laptop, and it would be hard to make it with no mouse anyways… If you could make it I would appreciate it ;D</p>
<p>What I want it something like…<br>
Banner ontop, height 300 length 600.<br>
I want the main template to be whatever a normal one would be in length and what ever height you think would work, I’m not to sure about sizes atm, I want the navigation to be on the left featuring about 5 buttons, or the space for them, I can make my own later. I want the colors to be black, and neon green as borders, ect. You should know what I’m talking about if you’ve seen alienware. I want a main info section in the center of the template, should be considerably large but not to big.<br>
I would appreciate it if you atleast try to make something, I don’t expect it to be done right away. Even if you aren’t that good at graphics I would like to see you try to make one, it could help you improve your graphic abilitys.</p>
<p>Many thanks<br>
Exe626</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/website-template/83439/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/website-template/83439/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 22 Apr 2007 21:00:26 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-83439-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/website-template/83439.rss">Website Template</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
