<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Help with commonly asked questions...(not sure if already been done)</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/help-with-commonly-asked-questions-not-sure-if-already-been-done/397402</link>
    <description>Q) How to portforward/allow others onto my server?

A) Go onto &quot;cmd&quot; and type ipconfig, scroll around until you find your default gateway, type this into your address bar and type admin as a username, admin as a password, or your changed user and pass if you changed. its quite simple from there. (What you do after you log in varies depending on your router.

Q) File Path Not Specified! HELP!!!

A) Right click the run.bat file and click edit, Change the number to 25, or your latest version of JDK.

Q) Error connecting to server

A) Go into Source and find run.bat, wait for it to say something along the lines of &quot;Online!&quot; then do not exit this, minimize it and open client and use run, this should solve the problem!

Q)Can i get others to play w/o portforwarding?

A) No.

Q)Is there any other way to portforward?

A)Yes, but the forum that helps with this is another rsps, i will make a thread showing this method, (100% free of viruses).

Q) HELP, I﻿ FORGOT MY USER AND PASS FOR PORTFORWARDING! HELP!

A) If your using a bthomehub, there should be a &quot;hidden&quot; button which you&#39;ll have to use a small object to push, this should reset the homehub to factory settings, meaning you may have to prepare to reset it, but if your desperate for your server to go on the web, its reccomended.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 01 Jun 2011 18:04:51 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/help-with-commonly-asked-questions-not-sure-if-already-been-done/397402.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Help with commonly asked questions...(not sure if already been done)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@ThatsTheGSpot ThatsTheGSpot]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/thatsthegspot">@ThatsTheGSpot</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Q) How to portforward/allow others onto my server?</p>
<p>A) Go onto “cmd” and type ipconfig, scroll around until you find your default gateway, type this into your address bar and type admin as a username, admin as a password, or your changed user and pass if you changed. its quite simple from there. (What you do after you log in varies depending on your router.</p>
<p>Q) File Path Not Specified! HELP!!!</p>
<p>A) Right click the run.bat file and click edit, Change the number to 25, or your latest version of JDK.</p>
<p>Q) Error connecting to server</p>
<p>A) Go into Source and find run.bat, wait for it to say something along the lines of “Online!” then do not exit this, minimize it and open client and use run, this should solve the problem!</p>
<p>Q)Can i get others to play w/o portforwarding?</p>
<p>A) No.</p>
<p>Q)Is there any other way to portforward?</p>
<p>A)Yes, but the forum that helps with this is another rsps, i will make a thread showing this method, (100% free of viruses).</p>
<p>Q) HELP, I﻿ FORGOT MY USER AND PASS FOR PORTFORWARDING! HELP!</p>
<p>A) If your using a bthomehub, there should be a “hidden” button which you’ll have to use a small object to push, this should reset the homehub to factory settings, meaning you may have to prepare to reset it, but if your desperate for your server to go on the web, its reccomended.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/help-with-commonly-asked-questions-not-sure-if-already-been-done/397402/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/help-with-commonly-asked-questions-not-sure-if-already-been-done/397402/1</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jun 2011 18:04:51 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-397402-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/help-with-commonly-asked-questions-not-sure-if-already-been-done/397402.rss">Help with commonly asked questions...(not sure if already been done)</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
