<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Looking for some help returning to Private Servers</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/looking-for-some-help-returning-to-private-servers/359698</link>
    <description>Hello everyone, It&#39;s been quite awhile since I&#39;ve been using Java code and private servers.
I&#39;m hoping to find a person who has enough experience to help me out, 1 on 1, and see if I can relearn it faster than usual.

My main goal is to find a completely empty base and bring it up into a very interactive server, much like those today.
Most of the coding will become more clearer as we discuss back and forth about it, since I&#39;ve led plenty of servers back
in the day.(Back when it was.. DK 6 and Update 10 or so :P)

Just send me a message or reply on here, I&#39;d love to get a tutor to help me out return into Private servers.

Thanks.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 11 Sep 2010 16:46:48 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/looking-for-some-help-returning-to-private-servers/359698.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Looking for some help returning to Private Servers</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Warsham Warsham]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/warsham">@Warsham</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Hello everyone, It’s been quite awhile since I’ve been using Java code and private servers.<br>
I’m hoping to find a person who has enough experience to help me out, 1 on 1, and see if I can relearn it faster than usual.</p>
<p>My main goal is to find a completely empty base and bring it up into a very interactive server, much like those today.<br>
Most of the coding will become more clearer as we discuss back and forth about it, since I’ve led plenty of servers back<br>
in the day.(Back when it was… DK 6 and Update 10 or so :P)</p>
<p>Just send me a message or reply on here, I’d love to get a tutor to help me out return into Private servers.</p>
<p>Thanks.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/looking-for-some-help-returning-to-private-servers/359698/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/looking-for-some-help-returning-to-private-servers/359698/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 11 Sep 2010 16:46:48 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-359698-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/looking-for-some-help-returning-to-private-servers/359698.rss">Looking for some help returning to Private Servers</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
