<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Map blanks out when increasing height level on jarred client?</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/map-blanks-out-when-increasing-height-level-on-jarred-client/547440</link>
    <description>Hi, so on a normal client loading through the class files and using the bat starter everything works fine and there&#39;s no issues. However when I jar my client (I have tried with and without compression) and login (everything works fine with the client itself through the jar), It will have two things missing: 1.) Water texture is missing. Water is just a blank blue color. And 2.) When height level is increased, the new height level objects and all data is not loaded resulting in a blank floor, and when the height level is decreased again, everything turns black as shown in the pictures below. When you teleport to a different area however, everything seems to go back to normal. But textures are missing everywhere. Not just for water. Even grass and sand look incredibly plain so i&#39;m assuming no textures are being loaded?

Increasing height level:
[img]http://i.imgur.com/Qtm9HPj.png[/img]

Decreasing height level back to original after already increasing.
[img]http://i.imgur.com/mgUy1zQ.png[/img] (ignore mith dragon our models are just a mess.)


Does anyone have a fix for both of these issues? We really want the jar client to work.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Oct 2014 05:30:04 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/map-blanks-out-when-increasing-height-level-on-jarred-client/547440.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Map blanks out when increasing height level on jarred client?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Paradox68 Paradox68]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/paradox68">@Paradox68</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Hi, so on a normal client loading through the class files and using the bat starter everything works fine and there’s no issues. However when I jar my client (I have tried with and without compression) and login (everything works fine with the client itself through the jar), It will have two things missing: 1.) Water texture is missing. Water is just a blank blue color. And 2.) When height level is increased, the new height level objects and all data is not loaded resulting in a blank floor, and when the height level is decreased again, everything turns black as shown in the pictures below. When you teleport to a different area however, everything seems to go back to normal. But textures are missing everywhere. Not just for water. Even grass and sand look incredibly plain so i’m assuming no textures are being loaded?</p>
<p>Increasing height level:<br>
<img src="http://i.imgur.com/Qtm9HPj.png" alt width="" height=""></p>
<p>Decreasing height level back to original after already increasing.<br>
<img src="http://i.imgur.com/mgUy1zQ.png" alt width="" height=""> (ignore mith dragon our models are just a mess.)</p>
<p>Does anyone have a fix for both of these issues? We really want the jar client to work.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/map-blanks-out-when-increasing-height-level-on-jarred-client/547440/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/map-blanks-out-when-increasing-height-level-on-jarred-client/547440/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 25 Oct 2014 05:30:04 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-547440-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/map-blanks-out-when-increasing-height-level-on-jarred-client/547440.rss">Map blanks out when increasing height level on jarred client?</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
