<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>639 Dementhium, a few questions</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/639-dementhium-a-few-questions/449551</link>
    <description>Alright, I&#39;m pretty new to Dementhium sources, or any 600+ sources for that matter, these are the only things I have had troubles with.

1. I&#39;m having some trouble with NPC attack area, they&#39;ll attack outside of their room, or if it&#39;s a multi-combat zone you&#39;ll have any NPC spawned in that area attacking you. If someone could maybe point my in the right direction on what I should be looking for to change this, that would be great, I&#39;m not looking to remove the multi-combat zone or make the NPC not aggressive, just reduce the distance that it will attack.

2. How does this Tick system work, when I last tried to use it I would get an error saying, something like Class name is not abstract does not override abstract method execute(); and does not override or implement a method from a supertype. Any thoughts? Never seen this before, and I sort of understand what it&#39;s telling me, I just can&#39;t figure out how I would fix it.

Thanks in advance.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 13 Jul 2012 23:54:09 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/639-dementhium-a-few-questions/449551.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>639 Dementhium, a few questions</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@musicmasta musicmasta]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/musicmasta">@musicmasta</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Alright, I’m pretty new to Dementhium sources, or any 600+ sources for that matter, these are the only things I have had troubles with.</p>
<ol>
<li>
<p>I’m having some trouble with NPC attack area, they’ll attack outside of their room, or if it’s a multi-combat zone you’ll have any NPC spawned in that area attacking you. If someone could maybe point my in the right direction on what I should be looking for to change this, that would be great, I’m not looking to remove the multi-combat zone or make the NPC not aggressive, just reduce the distance that it will attack.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>How does this Tick system work, when I last tried to use it I would get an error saying, something like Class name is not abstract does not override abstract method execute(); and does not override or implement a method from a supertype. Any thoughts? Never seen this before, and I sort of understand what it’s telling me, I just can’t figure out how I would fix it.</p>
</li>
</ol>
<p>Thanks in advance.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/639-dementhium-a-few-questions/449551/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/639-dementhium-a-few-questions/449551/1</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 13 Jul 2012 23:54:09 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-449551-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/639-dementhium-a-few-questions/449551.rss">639 Dementhium, a few questions</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
