<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>I need Javascript + Mootools help</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/i-need-javascript-mootools-help/105923</link>
    <description>Okay is there anyone thats willing to help me implement some [url=http://www.mootools.net]Mootools[/url] script onto a webpage. I just need to know how to place it on a blank page then i can go from there.

Incase you didnt know, Mootools is this VERY amazing javascript stuff, and it&#39;s free. I&#39;m just a noob and i can&#39;t figure out how to find the scripts. 

I only need to know how to get one script from the Mootools script thing then put it on a blank HTML page (I can do this with my own javascript it&#39;s just I don&#39;t understand Mootools).

I&#39;ve blabbered on a bit but please help me!</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 04 Jun 2007 22:31:36 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>General Programming</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/i-need-javascript-mootools-help/105923.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>I need Javascript + Mootools help</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@goatee goatee]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/goatee">@goatee</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Okay is there anyone thats willing to help me implement some <a href="http://www.mootools.net" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">Mootools</a> script onto a webpage. I just need to know how to place it on a blank page then i can go from there.</p>
<p>Incase you didnt know, Mootools is this VERY amazing javascript stuff, and it’s free. I’m just a noob and i can’t figure out how to find the scripts.</p>
<p>I only need to know how to get one script from the Mootools script thing then put it on a blank HTML page (I can do this with my own javascript it’s just I don’t understand Mootools).</p>
<p>I’ve blabbered on a bit but please help me!</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/i-need-javascript-mootools-help/105923/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/i-need-javascript-mootools-help/105923/1</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 04 Jun 2007 22:31:36 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-105923-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/i-need-javascript-mootools-help/105923.rss">I need Javascript + Mootools help</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
