<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>[525]Some bosses make my server crash</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/525-some-bosses-make-my-server-crash/347845</link>
    <description>Alright, well the title basically states what i need help with. Moved on to 525 a little while ago, getting used to the code. One thing that&#39;s annoying and has pretty much stopped my project is whenever i place a god wars boss in it&#39;s lair the server crashes. I assumed the npc was too big for it&#39;s area, so i put one of them (kree&#39;arra) in a big open, no limits field, and it still crashes. Kinda stumped right now, as i&#39;m trying to add god wars, but every time i go near the npc itself the server crashes. I would be standing outside the boss lair, and i can see the boss inside, then i go into the lair, and boom, server crashes. Thanks to anyone who can help, if you need a picture of the error to further help, i&#39;d be happy to post one.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 08 Jul 2010 00:24:46 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/525-some-bosses-make-my-server-crash/347845.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>[525]Some bosses make my server crash</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@r34p4g3pk r34p4g3pk]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/r34p4g3pk">@r34p4g3pk</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Alright, well the title basically states what i need help with. Moved on to 525 a little while ago, getting used to the code. One thing that’s annoying and has pretty much stopped my project is whenever i place a god wars boss in it’s lair the server crashes. I assumed the npc was too big for it’s area, so i put one of them (kree’arra) in a big open, no limits field, and it still crashes. Kinda stumped right now, as i’m trying to add god wars, but every time i go near the npc itself the server crashes. I would be standing outside the boss lair, and i can see the boss inside, then i go into the lair, and boom, server crashes. Thanks to anyone who can help, if you need a picture of the error to further help, i’d be happy to post one.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/525-some-bosses-make-my-server-crash/347845/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/525-some-bosses-make-my-server-crash/347845/1</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jul 2010 00:24:46 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-347845-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/525-some-bosses-make-my-server-crash/347845.rss">[525]Some bosses make my server crash</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
