<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>16 Rules For Getting Bitches</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/16-rules-for-getting-bitches/438069</link>
    <description>I loved this so much. I know each and every one is accurate because it&#39;s how i pull birds anyway:
&lt;blockquote&gt;I. Never say ‘I Love You’ first

Women want to feel like they have to overcome obstacles to win a man’s heart. They crave the challenge of capturing the interest of a man who has other women competing for his attention, and eventually prevailing over his grudging reluctance to award his committed exclusivity. The man who gives his emotional world away too easily robs women of the satisfaction of earning his love. Though you may be in love with her, don’t say it before she has said it. Show compassionate restraint for her need to struggle toward yin fulfillment. Inspire her to take the leap for you, and she’ll return the favor a thousandfold.

II. Make her jealous

Flirt with other women in front of her. Do not dissuade other women from flirting with you. Women will never admit this but jealousy excites them. The thought of you turning on another woman will arouse her sexually. No girl wants a man that no other woman wants. The partner who harnesses the gale storm of jealousy controls the direction of the relationship.

III. You shall make your mission, not your woman, your priority

Forget all those romantic cliches of the leading man proclaiming his undying love for the woman who completes him. Despite whatever protestations to the contrary, women do not want to be “The One” or the center of a man’s existence. They in fact want to subordinate themselves to a worthy man’s life purpose, to help him achieve that purpose with their feminine support, and to follow the path he lays out. You must respect a woman’s integrity and not lie to her that she is “your everything”. She is not your everything, and if she is, she will soon not be anymore.

IV. Don’t play by her rules

If you allow a woman to make the rules she will resent you with a seething contempt even a rapist cannot inspire. The strongest woman and the most strident feminist wants to be led by, and to submit to, a more powerful man. Polarity is the core of a healthy loving relationship. She does not want the prerogative to walk all over you with her capricious demands and mercurial moods. Her emotions are a hurricane, her soul a saboteur. Think of yourself as a bulwark against her tempest. When she grasps for a pillar to steady herself against the whipping winds or yearns for an authority figure to foil her worst instincts, it is you who has to be there… strong, solid, unshakeable and immovable.

V. Adhere to the golden ratio

Give your woman 2/3 of everything she gives you. For every three calls or texts, give her two back. Three declarations of love earn two in return. Three gifts; two nights out. Give her two displays of affection and stop until she has answered with three more. When she speaks, you reply with fewer words. When she emotes, you emote less. The idea behind the golden ratio is twofold — it establishes your greater value by making her chase you, and it demonstrates that you have the self-restraint to avoid getting swept up in her personal dramas. Refraining from reciprocating everything she does for you in equal measure instills in her the proper attitude of belief in your higher status. In her deepest loins it is what she truly wants.

VI. Keep her guessing

True to their inscrutable natures, women ask questions they don’t really want direct answers to. Woe be the man who plays it straight — his fate is the suffering of the beta. Evade, tease, obfuscate. She thrives when she has to imagine what you’re thinking about her, and withers when she knows exactly how you feel. A woman may want financial and family security, but she does not want passion security. In the same manner, when she has displeased you, punish swiftly, but when she has done you right, reward slowly. Reward her good behavior intermittently and unpredictably and she will never tire of working hard to please you.

VII. Always keep two in the kitty

Never allow yourself to be a “kept man”. A man with options is a man without need. It builds confidence and encourages boldness with women if there is another woman, a safety net, to catch you in case you slip and risk a breakup, divorce, or a lost prospect, leading to loneliness and a grinding dry spell. A woman knows once she has slept with a man she has abdicated a measure of her power; when she has fallen in love with him she has surrendered nearly all of it. But love is ephemeral and with time she may rediscover her power and threaten to leave you. It is her final trump card. Withdrawing all her love and all her body in an instant will rend your soul if you are faced with contemplating the empty abyss alone. Knowing there is another you can turn to for affection will fortify your will and satisfy your manhood.

VIII. Say you’re sorry only when absolutely necessary

Do not say you’re sorry for every wrong thing you do. It is a posture of submission that no man should reflexively adopt, no matter how alpha he is. Apologizing increases the demand for more apologies. She will come to expect your contrition, like a cat expects its meal at a set time each day. And then your value will lower in her eyes. Instead, if you have done something wrong, you should acknowledge your guilt in a glancing way without resorting to the actual words “I’m sorry.” Pull the Bill Clinton maneuver and say “Mistakes were made” or tell her you “feel bad” about what you did. You are granted two freebie “I’m sorry”s for the life of your relationship; use them wisely.

IX. Connect with her emotions

Set yourself apart from other men and connect with a woman’s emotional landscape. Her mind is an alien world that requires deft navigation to reach your rendevous. Frolic in the surf of emotions rather than the arid desert of logic. Be playful. Employ all your senses. Describe in lush detail scenarios to set her heart afire. Give your feelings freedom to roam. ROAM. Yes, that is a good word. You’re not on a linear path with her. You are ROAMING all over, taking her on an adventure. In this world, there is no need to finish thoughts or draw conclusions. There is only need to EXPERIENCE. You’re grabbing her hand and running with her down an infinite, labyrinthine alleyway with no end, laughing and letting your fingers glide on the cobblestone walls along the way.

X. Ignore her beauty

The man who trains his mind to subdue the reward centers of his brain when reflecting upon a beautiful female face will magically transform his interactions with women. His apprehension and self-consciousness will melt away, paving the path for more honest and self-possessed interactions with the objects of his desire. This is one reason why the greatest lotharios drown in more love than they can handle — through positive experiences with so many beautiful women they lose their awe of beauty and, in turn, their powerlessness under its spell. It will help you acquire the right frame of mind to stop using the words hot, cute, gorgeous, or beautiful to describe girls who turn you on. Instead, say to yourself “she’s interesting” or “she might be worth getting to know”. Never compliment a girl on her looks, especially not a girl you aren’t fucking. Turn off that part of your brain that wants to put them on pedestals. Further advanced training to reach this state of unawed Zen transcendence is to sleep with many MANY attractive women (try to avoid sleeping with a lot of ugly women if you don’t want to regress). Soon, a Jedi lover you will be.

XI.  Be irrationally self-confident

No matter what your station in life, stride through the world without apology or excuse. It does not matter if objectively you are not the best man a woman can get; what matters is that you think and act like you are. Women have a dog’s instinct for uncovering weakness in men; don’t make it easy for them. Self-confidence, warranted or not, triggers submissive emotional responses in women. Irrational self-confidence will get you more pussy than rational defeatism.

XII.  Maximize your strengths, minimize your weaknesses

In the betterment of ourselves as men we attract women into our orbit. To accomplish this gravitational pull as painlessly and efficiently as possible, you must identify your natural talents and shortcomings and parcel your efforts accordingly. If you are a gifted jokester, don’t waste time and energy trying to raise your status in philosophical debate. If you write well but dance poorly, don’t kill yourself trying to expand your manly influence on the dancefloor. Your goal should be to attract women effortlessly, so play to your strengths no matter what they are; there is a groupie for every male endeavor. Except World of Warcraft.

XIII. Err on the side of too much boldness, rather than too little

Touching a woman inappropriately on the first date will get you further with her than not touching her at all. Don’t let a woman’s faux indignation at your boldness sway you; they secretly love it when a man aggressively pursues what he wants and makes his sexual intentions known. You don’t have to be an asshole, but if you have no choice, being an inconsiderate asshole beats being a polite beta, every time.

XIV. Fuck her good

Fuck her like it’s your last fuck. And hers. Fuck her so good, so hard, so wantonly, so profligately that she is left a quivering, sparking mass of shaking flesh and sex fluids. Drain her of everything, then drain her some more. Kiss her all over, make love to her all night, and hold her close in the morning. Own her body, own her gratitude, own her love. If you don’t know how, learn to give her squirting orgasms.

XV. Maintain your state control

You are an oak tree. You will not be manipulated by crying, yelling, lying, head games, sexual withdrawal, jealousy ploys, pity plays, shit tests, hot/cold/hot/cold, disappearing acts, or guilt trips. She will rain and thunder all around you and you will shelter her until her storm passes. She will not drag you into her chaos or uproot you. When you have mastery over yourself, you will have mastery over her.

XVI.  Never be afraid to lose her

You must not fear. Fear is the love-killer. Fear is the ego-triumph that brings abject loneliness. You will face your fear. You will permit it to pass over and through you. And when your ego-fear is gone you will turn and face your lover, and only your heart will remain. You will walk away from her when she has violated your integrity, and you will let her walk when her heart is closed to you. She who can destroy you, controls you. Don’t give her that power over yourself. Love yourself before you love her.&lt;/blockquote&gt;
SOURCE: http://heartiste.wordpress.com/the-sixteen-commandments-of-poon/</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 02 Apr 2012 07:19:22 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>General Discussion</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/16-rules-for-getting-bitches/438069.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>16 Rules For Getting Bitches</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@sinisoul sini]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/sinisoul">@sinisoul</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I follow rules I, II and V. I don’t really need to have a lecture on why. Woman are strange creatures put on the earth to perplex man and make children. I am in no way a sexist.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/16-rules-for-getting-bitches/438069/20">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/16-rules-for-getting-bitches/438069/20</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 02 Apr 2012 07:19:22 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-438069-20</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/16-rules-for-getting-bitches/438069.rss">16 Rules For Getting Bitches</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>16 Rules For Getting Bitches</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@bowserjr2 Bowser jr]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/bowserjr2">@bowserjr2</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“Frell, post:18, topic:438069”][quote author=jme link=topic=540789.msg3961027#msg3961027 date=1333293742]<br>
Every woman wants a real man.<br>
[/quote]<br>
Then why do they dye their hair, have fake nails, and wear makeup?[/quote]<br>
Because men wants fake women.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/16-rules-for-getting-bitches/438069/19">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/16-rules-for-getting-bitches/438069/19</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 01 Apr 2012 20:53:20 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-438069-19</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/16-rules-for-getting-bitches/438069.rss">16 Rules For Getting Bitches</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>16 Rules For Getting Bitches</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Frell Frell]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/frell">@Frell</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote" data-post="16" data-topic="438069">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/user_avatar/forum.moparisthebest.com/jme/40/55_1.png" class="avatar"> jme:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Every woman wants a real man.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Then why do they dye their hair, have fake nails, and wear makeup?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/16-rules-for-getting-bitches/438069/18">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/16-rules-for-getting-bitches/438069/18</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 01 Apr 2012 20:45:11 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-438069-18</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/16-rules-for-getting-bitches/438069.rss">16 Rules For Getting Bitches</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>16 Rules For Getting Bitches</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Aftermath_961 Aftermath]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/aftermath_961">@Aftermath_961</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="onebox xkcd">
  <header class="source">
      <a href="https://xkcd.com/1027/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">xkcd.com</a>
  </header>
  <article class="onebox-body">
    <h3><a href="https://xkcd.com/1027/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Pickup Artist</a></h3>

<div class="aspect-image" style="--aspect-ratio:290/500;"><img src="https://imgs.xkcd.com/comics/pickup_artist.png"></div>

<p>Son, don't try to play 'make you feel bad' with the Michael Jordan of making you feel bad.</p>

  </article>
  <div class="onebox-metadata">
    
    
  </div>
  <div style="clear: both"></div>
</aside>

          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/16-rules-for-getting-bitches/438069/17">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/16-rules-for-getting-bitches/438069/17</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 01 Apr 2012 15:29:40 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-438069-17</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/16-rules-for-getting-bitches/438069.rss">16 Rules For Getting Bitches</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>16 Rules For Getting Bitches</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@jme jme]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/jme">@jme</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Every woman wants a real man. These are basically accurate, but also common sense (maybe not common sense to some people?)</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/16-rules-for-getting-bitches/438069/16">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/16-rules-for-getting-bitches/438069/16</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 01 Apr 2012 15:22:22 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-438069-16</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/16-rules-for-getting-bitches/438069.rss">16 Rules For Getting Bitches</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>16 Rules For Getting Bitches</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Aftermath_961 Aftermath]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/aftermath_961">@Aftermath_961</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“Tree, post:10, topic:438069”][quote author=Aftermath link=topic=540789.msg3960646#msg3960646 date=1333246495]<br>
Disagree with almost all. I suppose it depends on your target demographic and what you’re looking for.<br>
[/quote]</p>
<p>The list above simply shows men how to adopt positive traits. Confidence, social intellect and the ability to hold their values when the opposite sex tries to compromise them. These traits are universally attractive to females. The exception being women who are above the age of 30ish.[/quote]</p>
<p>Yes, except I can do all of that without mind games. This is more of a guide to “how to fake it”.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/16-rules-for-getting-bitches/438069/15">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/16-rules-for-getting-bitches/438069/15</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 01 Apr 2012 15:21:39 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-438069-15</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/16-rules-for-getting-bitches/438069.rss">16 Rules For Getting Bitches</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>16 Rules For Getting Bitches</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@MujaheD Radeon]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/mujahed">@MujaheD</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote quote-modified" data-post="12" data-topic="438069">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 R.I.P RSC:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>I guess if you are into bitches, than this comes in handy. If you’re aiming for women who are more than nice dolls, most of these tactics will get you nowhere.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>If you’re going to class it like that, then 90% of women are bitches. It has been so with 100% of my encounters.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/16-rules-for-getting-bitches/438069/14">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/16-rules-for-getting-bitches/438069/14</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 01 Apr 2012 12:41:43 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-438069-14</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/16-rules-for-getting-bitches/438069.rss">16 Rules For Getting Bitches</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>16 Rules For Getting Bitches</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Mopman Mopman]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/mopman">@Mopman</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Meh, I agree with like 3/4 of them whatever “type” of woman you are looking for. Then a few of them are retarded.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/16-rules-for-getting-bitches/438069/13">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/16-rules-for-getting-bitches/438069/13</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 01 Apr 2012 11:55:29 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-438069-13</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/16-rules-for-getting-bitches/438069.rss">16 Rules For Getting Bitches</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>16 Rules For Getting Bitches</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@R.I.P_RSC R.I.P RSC]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/r.i.p_rsc">@R.I.P_RSC</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I guess if you are into bitches, than this comes in handy. If you’re aiming for women who are more than nice dolls, most of these tactics will get you nowhere.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/16-rules-for-getting-bitches/438069/12">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/16-rules-for-getting-bitches/438069/12</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 01 Apr 2012 09:11:37 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-438069-12</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/16-rules-for-getting-bitches/438069.rss">16 Rules For Getting Bitches</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>16 Rules For Getting Bitches</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@bowserjr2 Bowser jr]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/bowserjr2">@bowserjr2</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Any relationship without mutual respect, isn’t anything that should been seen upon as a goal.</p>
<p>The first thing I need to do, is to make people stop thinking that I’m gay, after that I could see if i want to use any of these sexist tips.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/16-rules-for-getting-bitches/438069/11">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/16-rules-for-getting-bitches/438069/11</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 01 Apr 2012 09:10:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-438069-11</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/16-rules-for-getting-bitches/438069.rss">16 Rules For Getting Bitches</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>16 Rules For Getting Bitches</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Tree Tree]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/tree">@Tree</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote quote-modified" data-post="2" data-topic="438069">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 Aftermath:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Disagree with almost all. I suppose it depends on your target demographic and what you’re looking for.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>The list above simply shows men how to adopt positive traits. Confidence, social intellect and the ability to hold their values when the opposite sex tries to compromise them. These traits are universally attractive to females. The exception being women who are above the age of 30ish.</p>
<p>[quote=“t4, post:7, topic:438069”]sounds like some good rules to get in an unstable relationship and/or attract the wrong type of woman.</p>
<p>why do you think the <span class="bbcode-s">majority</span>many of women are shallow whores? i’d like to bet it’s because most of the time they’re treated like objects: where only their looks or how far they can deep throat defines their value to the world - and they accept it, thus becoming said individual.[/quote]</p>
<p>You can’t pinpoint one reason as to why females are so selective. You could say it comes from tribal days, when picking a suitable mate was a way to survival and protection for their offspring. You could say they’re selective because they are worried about the opinion of their surrounding friends. Ever approached an attractive girl and her friend pulls her away, even though she seems interested? Exactly.</p>
<p>Like i said above, the traits are just the way a man should be. Probably throw in a bit of vulnerability. If you’re in a relationship and you’re letting someone of the opposite sex have control over your boundaries, values, limits and needs then you’re just a shadow of a man. You become a doormat.</p>
<aside class="quote" data-post="9" data-topic="438069">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/defet/40/5_e05bb34c421432ee4d40de30c10af3e5.png" class="avatar"> DEFET:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>now make some rules on how to get <span class="bbcode-u">women</span></p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>The list was created mostly for just sex. However, what it preaches would actually be beneficial in a relationship a lot more than you would think. I know it’s hard to accept that it all sucks. That relationships are about power. That the disney movies where the nice guy gets the girl, are wrong. That what your mum told you on how to treat women, is actually the opposite to what attracts them.</p>
<p>Girls love the jerk. They never admit it because it makes them feel bad about themselves. Even still, they like the jerk. I’ve had plenty of experience with all sorts of women. Some insecure, some amazingly independent. These work. Not to mention, girls don’t even know what they want. There’s loads of times that probably each of you has heard the, ‘I just want a nice guy’ line before she rejects 5  or 6 really friendly people at a club.</p>
<p>The nice guy finishes last.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/16-rules-for-getting-bitches/438069/10">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/16-rules-for-getting-bitches/438069/10</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 01 Apr 2012 08:14:33 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-438069-10</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/16-rules-for-getting-bitches/438069.rss">16 Rules For Getting Bitches</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>16 Rules For Getting Bitches</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@DEFET DEFET]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/defet">@DEFET</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>now make some rules on how to get <span class="bbcode-u">women</span></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/16-rules-for-getting-bitches/438069/9">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/16-rules-for-getting-bitches/438069/9</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 01 Apr 2012 06:18:30 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-438069-9</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/16-rules-for-getting-bitches/438069.rss">16 Rules For Getting Bitches</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>16 Rules For Getting Bitches</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Rodgerwilco Rodgerwilco]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/rodgerwilco">@Rodgerwilco</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>This is dumb.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/16-rules-for-getting-bitches/438069/8">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/16-rules-for-getting-bitches/438069/8</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 01 Apr 2012 04:29:41 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-438069-8</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/16-rules-for-getting-bitches/438069.rss">16 Rules For Getting Bitches</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>16 Rules For Getting Bitches</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@T41 t4]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/t41">@T41</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>sounds like some good rules to get in an unstable relationship and/or attract the wrong type of woman.</p>
<p>why do you think the <span class="bbcode-s">majority</span>many of women are shallow whores? i’d like to bet it’s because most of the time they’re treated like objects: where only their looks or how far they can deep throat defines their value to the world - and they accept it, thus becoming said individual.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/16-rules-for-getting-bitches/438069/7">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/16-rules-for-getting-bitches/438069/7</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 01 Apr 2012 03:35:12 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-438069-7</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/16-rules-for-getting-bitches/438069.rss">16 Rules For Getting Bitches</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>16 Rules For Getting Bitches</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Tree Tree]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/tree">@Tree</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote" data-post="5" data-topic="438069">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/frell/40/5_e05bb34c421432ee4d40de30c10af3e5.png" class="avatar"> Frell:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>sounds like a set of rules created for middle school girls but the genders were swapped</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>There’s nothing wrong with a bit of help. All males have difficulties with females at some point. It’s something most of our gender all share in common. What’s wrong with working together for once, instead of against?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/16-rules-for-getting-bitches/438069/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/16-rules-for-getting-bitches/438069/6</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 01 Apr 2012 02:45:56 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-438069-6</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/16-rules-for-getting-bitches/438069.rss">16 Rules For Getting Bitches</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>16 Rules For Getting Bitches</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Frell Frell]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/frell">@Frell</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>sounds like a set of rules created for middle school girls but the genders were swapped</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/16-rules-for-getting-bitches/438069/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/16-rules-for-getting-bitches/438069/5</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 01 Apr 2012 02:39:33 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-438069-5</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/16-rules-for-getting-bitches/438069.rss">16 Rules For Getting Bitches</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>16 Rules For Getting Bitches</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Tree Tree]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/tree">@Tree</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I’d disagree. The rules basically give a rundown on how to maintain your masculinity and boundaries, when emotionally attached to a female. It’s more a guide to manhood.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/16-rules-for-getting-bitches/438069/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/16-rules-for-getting-bitches/438069/4</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 01 Apr 2012 02:34:59 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-438069-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/16-rules-for-getting-bitches/438069.rss">16 Rules For Getting Bitches</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>16 Rules For Getting Bitches</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@davidi2 Davidi2]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/davidi2">@davidi2</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>ask any long married man what he thinks of these rules and be prepared to get a stern talking to</p>
<p>ask any divorced or single man and you’ll probably find someone that agrees</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/16-rules-for-getting-bitches/438069/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/16-rules-for-getting-bitches/438069/3</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 01 Apr 2012 02:30:14 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-438069-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/16-rules-for-getting-bitches/438069.rss">16 Rules For Getting Bitches</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>16 Rules For Getting Bitches</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Aftermath_961 Aftermath]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/aftermath_961">@Aftermath_961</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Disagree with almost all. I suppose it depends on your target demographic and what you’re looking for.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/16-rules-for-getting-bitches/438069/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/16-rules-for-getting-bitches/438069/2</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 01 Apr 2012 02:14:55 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-438069-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/16-rules-for-getting-bitches/438069.rss">16 Rules For Getting Bitches</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>16 Rules For Getting Bitches</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Tree Tree]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/tree">@Tree</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I loved this so much. I know each and every one is accurate because it’s how i pull birds anyway:</p>
<blockquote>I. Never say ‘I Love You’ first
<p>Women want to feel like they have to overcome obstacles to win a man’s heart. They crave the challenge of capturing the interest of a man who has other women competing for his attention, and eventually prevailing over his grudging reluctance to award his committed exclusivity. The man who gives his emotional world away too easily robs women of the satisfaction of earning his love. Though you may be in love with her, don’t say it before she has said it. Show compassionate restraint for her need to struggle toward yin fulfillment. Inspire her to take the leap for you, and she’ll return the favor a thousandfold.</p>
<p>II. Make her jealous</p>
<p>Flirt with other women in front of her. Do not dissuade other women from flirting with you. Women will never admit this but jealousy excites them. The thought of you turning on another woman will arouse her sexually. No girl wants a man that no other woman wants. The partner who harnesses the gale storm of jealousy controls the direction of the relationship.</p>
<p>III. You shall make your mission, not your woman, your priority</p>
<p>Forget all those romantic cliches of the leading man proclaiming his undying love for the woman who completes him. Despite whatever protestations to the contrary, women do not want to be “The One” or the center of a man’s existence. They in fact want to subordinate themselves to a worthy man’s life purpose, to help him achieve that purpose with their feminine support, and to follow the path he lays out. You must respect a woman’s integrity and not lie to her that she is “your everything”. She is not your everything, and if she is, she will soon not be anymore.</p>
<p>IV. Don’t play by her rules</p>
<p>If you allow a woman to make the rules she will resent you with a seething contempt even a rapist cannot inspire. The strongest woman and the most strident feminist wants to be led by, and to submit to, a more powerful man. Polarity is the core of a healthy loving relationship. She does not want the prerogative to walk all over you with her capricious demands and mercurial moods. Her emotions are a hurricane, her soul a saboteur. Think of yourself as a bulwark against her tempest. When she grasps for a pillar to steady herself against the whipping winds or yearns for an authority figure to foil her worst instincts, it is you who has to be there… strong, solid, unshakeable and immovable.</p>
<p>V. Adhere to the golden ratio</p>
<p>Give your woman 2/3 of everything she gives you. For every three calls or texts, give her two back. Three declarations of love earn two in return. Three gifts; two nights out. Give her two displays of affection and stop until she has answered with three more. When she speaks, you reply with fewer words. When she emotes, you emote less. The idea behind the golden ratio is twofold — it establishes your greater value by making her chase you, and it demonstrates that you have the self-restraint to avoid getting swept up in her personal dramas. Refraining from reciprocating everything she does for you in equal measure instills in her the proper attitude of belief in your higher status. In her deepest loins it is what she truly wants.</p>
<p>VI. Keep her guessing</p>
<p>True to their inscrutable natures, women ask questions they don’t really want direct answers to. Woe be the man who plays it straight — his fate is the suffering of the beta. Evade, tease, obfuscate. She thrives when she has to imagine what you’re thinking about her, and withers when she knows exactly how you feel. A woman may want financial and family security, but she does not want passion security. In the same manner, when she has displeased you, punish swiftly, but when she has done you right, reward slowly. Reward her good behavior intermittently and unpredictably and she will never tire of working hard to please you.</p>
<p>VII. Always keep two in the kitty</p>
<p>Never allow yourself to be a “kept man”. A man with options is a man without need. It builds confidence and encourages boldness with women if there is another woman, a safety net, to catch you in case you slip and risk a breakup, divorce, or a lost prospect, leading to loneliness and a grinding dry spell. A woman knows once she has slept with a man she has abdicated a measure of her power; when she has fallen in love with him she has surrendered nearly all of it. But love is ephemeral and with time she may rediscover her power and threaten to leave you. It is her final trump card. Withdrawing all her love and all her body in an instant will rend your soul if you are faced with contemplating the empty abyss alone. Knowing there is another you can turn to for affection will fortify your will and satisfy your manhood.</p>
<p>VIII. Say you’re sorry only when absolutely necessary</p>
<p>Do not say you’re sorry for every wrong thing you do. It is a posture of submission that no man should reflexively adopt, no matter how alpha he is. Apologizing increases the demand for more apologies. She will come to expect your contrition, like a cat expects its meal at a set time each day. And then your value will lower in her eyes. Instead, if you have done something wrong, you should acknowledge your guilt in a glancing way without resorting to the actual words “I’m sorry.” Pull the Bill Clinton maneuver and say “Mistakes were made” or tell her you “feel bad” about what you did. You are granted two freebie “I’m sorry”s for the life of your relationship; use them wisely.</p>
<p>IX. Connect with her emotions</p>
<p>Set yourself apart from other men and connect with a woman’s emotional landscape. Her mind is an alien world that requires deft navigation to reach your rendevous. Frolic in the surf of emotions rather than the arid desert of logic. Be playful. Employ all your senses. Describe in lush detail scenarios to set her heart afire. Give your feelings freedom to roam. ROAM. Yes, that is a good word. You’re not on a linear path with her. You are ROAMING all over, taking her on an adventure. In this world, there is no need to finish thoughts or draw conclusions. There is only need to EXPERIENCE. You’re grabbing her hand and running with her down an infinite, labyrinthine alleyway with no end, laughing and letting your fingers glide on the cobblestone walls along the way.</p>
<p>X. Ignore her beauty</p>
<p>The man who trains his mind to subdue the reward centers of his brain when reflecting upon a beautiful female face will magically transform his interactions with women. His apprehension and self-consciousness will melt away, paving the path for more honest and self-possessed interactions with the objects of his desire. This is one reason why the greatest lotharios drown in more love than they can handle — through positive experiences with so many beautiful women they lose their awe of beauty and, in turn, their powerlessness under its spell. It will help you acquire the right frame of mind to stop using the words hot, cute, gorgeous, or beautiful to describe girls who turn you on. Instead, say to yourself “she’s interesting” or “she might be worth getting to know”. Never compliment a girl on her looks, especially not a girl you aren’t fucking. Turn off that part of your brain that wants to put them on pedestals. Further advanced training to reach this state of unawed Zen transcendence is to sleep with many MANY attractive women (try to avoid sleeping with a lot of ugly women if you don’t want to regress). Soon, a Jedi lover you will be.</p>
<p>XI.  Be irrationally self-confident</p>
<p>No matter what your station in life, stride through the world without apology or excuse. It does not matter if objectively you are not the best man a woman can get; what matters is that you think and act like you are. Women have a dog’s instinct for uncovering weakness in men; don’t make it easy for them. Self-confidence, warranted or not, triggers submissive emotional responses in women. Irrational self-confidence will get you more pussy than rational defeatism.</p>
<p>XII.  Maximize your strengths, minimize your weaknesses</p>
<p>In the betterment of ourselves as men we attract women into our orbit. To accomplish this gravitational pull as painlessly and efficiently as possible, you must identify your natural talents and shortcomings and parcel your efforts accordingly. If you are a gifted jokester, don’t waste time and energy trying to raise your status in philosophical debate. If you write well but dance poorly, don’t kill yourself trying to expand your manly influence on the dancefloor. Your goal should be to attract women effortlessly, so play to your strengths no matter what they are; there is a groupie for every male endeavor. Except World of Warcraft.</p>
<p>XIII. Err on the side of too much boldness, rather than too little</p>
<p>Touching a woman inappropriately on the first date will get you further with her than not touching her at all. Don’t let a woman’s faux indignation at your boldness sway you; they secretly love it when a man aggressively pursues what he wants and makes his sexual intentions known. You don’t have to be an asshole, but if you have no choice, being an inconsiderate asshole beats being a polite beta, every time.</p>
<p>XIV. Fuck her good</p>
<p>Fuck her like it’s your last fuck. And hers. Fuck her so good, so hard, so wantonly, so profligately that she is left a quivering, sparking mass of shaking flesh and sex fluids. Drain her of everything, then drain her some more. Kiss her all over, make love to her all night, and hold her close in the morning. Own her body, own her gratitude, own her love. If you don’t know how, learn to give her squirting orgasms.</p>
<p>XV. Maintain your state control</p>
<p>You are an oak tree. You will not be manipulated by crying, yelling, lying, head games, sexual withdrawal, jealousy ploys, pity plays, shit tests, hot/cold/hot/cold, disappearing acts, or guilt trips. She will rain and thunder all around you and you will shelter her until her storm passes. She will not drag you into her chaos or uproot you. When you have mastery over yourself, you will have mastery over her.</p>
<p>XVI.  Never be afraid to lose her</p>
<p>You must not fear. Fear is the love-killer. Fear is the ego-triumph that brings abject loneliness. You will face your fear. You will permit it to pass over and through you. And when your ego-fear is gone you will turn and face your lover, and only your heart will remain. You will walk away from her when she has violated your integrity, and you will let her walk when her heart is closed to you. She who can destroy you, controls you. Don’t give her that power over yourself. Love yourself before you love her.</p>
</blockquote><br>
SOURCE: <a href="http://heartiste.wordpress.com/the-sixteen-commandments-of-poon/" rel="nofollow noopener">http://heartiste.wordpress.com/the-sixteen-commandments-of-poon/</a>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/16-rules-for-getting-bitches/438069/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/16-rules-for-getting-bitches/438069/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 01 Apr 2012 02:08:06 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-438069-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/16-rules-for-getting-bitches/438069.rss">16 Rules For Getting Bitches</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
