<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>ChatBack History not loading properly</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/chatback-history-not-loading-properly/326027</link>
    <description>Well, since I made my client full screen, the chat back history isn&#39;t set up properly and I&#39;m having some trouble positioning it correctly. Here&#39;s a pic:

[img]http://img687.imageshack.us/img687/1523/transkp.png[/img]

It&#39;s circled in red and that&#39;s the chat history. Does anybody know how to position it so that it goes into the chat back and isn&#39;t so small in the corner? Along with the mapScenes, I think that&#39;s what they are called. The little mini map icons, such as the bank icon, water fountain icon and such on the mini map. I&#39;m having trouble positioning that as well. I&#39;d greatly appreciate it.

Thanks.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 17 Jan 2010 04:32:01 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Game Development</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/chatback-history-not-loading-properly/326027.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>ChatBack History not loading properly</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Continue Continue]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/continue">@Continue</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Well, since I made my client full screen, the chat back history isn’t set up properly and I’m having some trouble positioning it correctly. Here’s a pic:</p>
<p><img src="http://img687.imageshack.us/img687/1523/transkp.png" alt width="" height=""></p>
<p>It’s circled in red and that’s the chat history. Does anybody know how to position it so that it goes into the chat back and isn’t so small in the corner? Along with the mapScenes, I think that’s what they are called. The little mini map icons, such as the bank icon, water fountain icon and such on the mini map. I’m having trouble positioning that as well. I’d greatly appreciate it.</p>
<p>Thanks.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/chatback-history-not-loading-properly/326027/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/chatback-history-not-loading-properly/326027/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 17 Jan 2010 04:32:01 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-326027-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/chatback-history-not-loading-properly/326027.rss">ChatBack History not loading properly</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
