<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>[Project Help] Cape and animations ;o Need PRO People :)</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/project-help-cape-and-animations-o-need-pro-people/291618</link>
    <description>Ok, well assuming  the title, you hopefully understand the topic. I am posting here for help on a project im creating and it involves A cape and it&#39;s animation, the Fire cape.

Ok well, i&#39;ve honestly gone brain dead trying to get this working, but I know what im doing wrong.
So my plan is to make the fire cape into a &quot;snow cape&quot; or &quot;water cape&quot; making the gfx of lava change to the gfx of snow falling or the gfx of water moving. i tried just a simple recolour through ints, and obviously it didn&#39;t look like snow or water. I realized ( i hope) that while looking at the ints in through the cache, there was a &quot;action&quot; there with a line involving some file idk cbb to remember it atm, ill post a pic later. And i was thinking, maybe, &quot;action&quot; would be the gfx for the cape. So i was assuming i&#39;d need to find out what the water or snow fall gfx is and simply replace that with the lava codes. WELL, tbh, i don&#39;t know what the water/snow fall gfx are (if there even is snow fall) so i couldn&#39;t really go any further.

SO my question is, is anyone good enough up to spoonfeeding me on how to change the lava to water or snow gfx( if there is a snow gfx than fawk try your hardest to get it)
if you need any more information, int example what ever, just tell me and ill get you it asap.
(if this is allowed)- I&#39;ll rep++ for anyone who can help meh get the cape :)</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 29 Jul 2009 15:35:31 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/project-help-cape-and-animations-o-need-pro-people/291618.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>[Project Help] Cape and animations ;o Need PRO People :)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@the1337legend the1337legend]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/the1337legend">@the1337legend</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Hmmmm ok, i’ll give it a go in a lil bit, gotta finish questing on rs first ;o<br>
Thanks a ton for the help. <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=5" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/project-help-cape-and-animations-o-need-pro-people/291618/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/project-help-cape-and-animations-o-need-pro-people/291618/3</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 29 Jul 2009 15:35:31 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-291618-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/project-help-cape-and-animations-o-need-pro-people/291618.rss">[Project Help] Cape and animations ;o Need PRO People :)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Project Help] Cape and animations ;o Need PRO People :)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@system system]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/system">@system</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>The texture is set in the cape model. Textures are just colour numbers in the range 1-50. (or is it 0-49, never remember which)<br>
So you can do one or more of these.<br>
Change the color number in the model file, re-colour with ints, swap the texture IDs in the palette or change one of the textures for a custom one.</p>
<p>Ints is your best method atm.</p>
<p>Don’t think there is a snow texture, magic logs/tree is about closest.<br>
There are 2 or 3 water textures. A marble texture.<br>
There is the fountain droplets texture as well. (jagex screwed up with this once, to make water capes - google search)</p>
<p>Most textures aren’t animated, but if you figured out how they are animated, you could replace one of the little used textures (portraits) with a custom one. Would make the portaits animated snow fall as well, if you do that.<br>
I beleive that if a texture is animated it animates it on everything that has that texture.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/project-help-cape-and-animations-o-need-pro-people/291618/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/project-help-cape-and-animations-o-need-pro-people/291618/2</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 29 Jul 2009 07:11:57 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-291618-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/project-help-cape-and-animations-o-need-pro-people/291618.rss">[Project Help] Cape and animations ;o Need PRO People :)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Project Help] Cape and animations ;o Need PRO People :)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@the1337legend the1337legend]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/the1337legend">@the1337legend</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Ok, well assuming  the title, you hopefully understand the topic. I am posting here for help on a project im creating and it involves A cape and it’s animation, the Fire cape.</p>
<p>Ok well, i’ve honestly gone brain dead trying to get this working, but I know what im doing wrong.<br>
So my plan is to make the fire cape into a “snow cape” or “water cape” making the gfx of lava change to the gfx of snow falling or the gfx of water moving. i tried just a simple recolour through ints, and obviously it didn’t look like snow or water. I realized ( i hope) that while looking at the ints in through the cache, there was a “action” there with a line involving some file idk cbb to remember it atm, ill post a pic later. And i was thinking, maybe, “action” would be the gfx for the cape. So i was assuming i’d need to find out what the water or snow fall gfx is and simply replace that with the lava codes. WELL, tbh, i don’t know what the water/snow fall gfx are (if there even is snow fall) so i couldn’t really go any further.</p>
<p>SO my question is, is anyone good enough up to spoonfeeding me on how to change the lava to water or snow gfx( if there is a snow gfx than fawk try your hardest to get it)<br>
if you need any more information, int example what ever, just tell me and ill get you it asap.<br>
(if this is allowed)- I’ll rep++ for anyone who can help meh get the cape <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=5" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/project-help-cape-and-animations-o-need-pro-people/291618/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/project-help-cape-and-animations-o-need-pro-people/291618/1</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 29 Jul 2009 00:50:40 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-291618-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/project-help-cape-and-animations-o-need-pro-people/291618.rss">[Project Help] Cape and animations ;o Need PRO People :)</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
