<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Ok wth ip problem?</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/ok-wth-ip-problem/241018</link>
    <description>alrite so im over here minding my own business trying to get my server started. i do the no-ip thing. blah blah blah i get to moparscape server status page enter it all in with the RIGHT ip adress and it keeps saying server needs to be online so i check to see what the hell is going on if this page is on crack and look what i find.. something HELLA wierd..

i go to whatismyip.com and it says the ip that i originally know of that i used. so then just to make sure i use the command box and type in ipconfig and my ip is totally different... i know it wouldnt be the safest idea to use my actual ip so im just going to use cross it all out and put an example of what im talking about..

[IMG]http://i37.tinypic.com/6g8rvd.jpg[/img]

SO THERE IT IS

any help at all with just the example?..</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2008 19:30:47 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/ok-wth-ip-problem/241018.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Ok wth ip problem?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Varmisher5150 Varmisher5150]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/varmisher5150">@Varmisher5150</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>alrite so im over here minding my own business trying to get my server started. i do the no-ip thing. blah blah blah i get to moparscape server status page enter it all in with the RIGHT ip adress and it keeps saying server needs to be online so i check to see what the hell is going on if this page is on crack and look what i find… something HELLA wierd…</p>
<p>i go to <a href="http://whatismyip.com" rel="nofollow noopener">whatismyip.com</a> and it says the ip that i originally know of that i used. so then just to make sure i use the command box and type in ipconfig and my ip is totally different… i know it wouldnt be the safest idea to use my actual ip so im just going to use cross it all out and put an example of what im talking about…</p>
<p><img src="http://i37.tinypic.com/6g8rvd.jpg" alt width="140" height="120"></p>
<p>SO THERE IT IS</p>
<p>any help at all with just the example?..</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/ok-wth-ip-problem/241018/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/ok-wth-ip-problem/241018/1</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2008 19:30:47 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-241018-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/ok-wth-ip-problem/241018.rss">Ok wth ip problem?</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
