<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Best source/client for my purpose?</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/best-source-client-for-my-purpose/448846</link>
    <description>Hello!  This is my first post here and i&#39;m also really new to this server stuff so I&#39;m asking for help, wasn&#39;t sure what section to post in so I chose Server Help.  So basically I want a source for me and a few of my friends just to mess around in, with skills, some mini games, and just lots of world and commands.  And also a web client because I have a website and my friends would rather use that than a client.  Before you ask Yes I did look I spent 4 hours yesturday searching and I couldn&#39;t find any, I only found one that I could get to work.  So thanks for any suggestions!</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 08 Jul 2012 19:45:03 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/best-source-client-for-my-purpose/448846.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Best source/client for my purpose?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@NardCake NardCake]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/nardcake">@NardCake</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Hello!  This is my first post here and i’m also really new to this server stuff so I’m asking for help, wasn’t sure what section to post in so I chose Server Help.  So basically I want a source for me and a few of my friends just to mess around in, with skills, some mini games, and just lots of world and commands.  And also a web client because I have a website and my friends would rather use that than a client.  Before you ask Yes I did look I spent 4 hours yesturday searching and I couldn’t find any, I only found one that I could get to work.  So thanks for any suggestions!</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/best-source-client-for-my-purpose/448846/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/best-source-client-for-my-purpose/448846/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 08 Jul 2012 19:45:03 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-448846-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/best-source-client-for-my-purpose/448846.rss">Best source/client for my purpose?</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
