<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Lycx</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/lycx/392625</link>
    <description>[center][i]I am watching howl&#39;s moving castle as I type this thread, so please excuse any spelling errors as my eyes are on the video and my fingers are typing :|[/i]
[IMG]http://lycx.org/Themes/SimplePRO/images/theme/mylogo.png[/img]

I started with an old favourate for my server, a particular revision winterlove now called [i]blakescape[/i]. I had noticed a lot of popular servers had created something from this, or had created something entirely from scratch. Because I am uncapable to create networking, then do whatever comes after I&#39;ve decided just to use something I have been somewhat successful before by created several servers that have reached aprox. 30 player at 90% of the time but back then this was common for a silabsoft server so this isn&#39;t a big accomplishment for me personally but I can&#39;t say it didn&#39;t feel good running a community and creating a game for the first time. I started by cleaning up every file to ensure that it was easier for me to look through and edit - this was something I did for myself not for a release to the downloads section, I did however create a thread for my development on cleaning it. People supported my progress and as Tatemo explained to me:[/center]

[quote=&quot;Tatemo, post:6, topic:361848&quot;]Looks nice enough. But you are doing conventions wrong. Read some java tutorials :)

The files need to be indented by the brackets and generally in Java it goes:

public class blah { (Bracket on same line now next Palidino was just a moron)
[Tab] void blarg() {
[tab][tab]
[tab]}
}
 

Other than that pretty good I guess :)[/quote][center]
Because what I was changing as I cleaned is I moved the [b]{[/b] onto a new line,
[/center][code=java]private int burntFish(int i)
{
	switch (i)
	{
		case 317:
		case 321:
			return 323;
	};
};[/code][center]
But personally what&#39;s wrong with being a little different, players wont even notice as long as it&#39;s efficient and or provides some decent content to keep them active currently I&#39;m working on skills then focusing on combat aspects like weapon specials, prayer bonuses aswell as prayer playing a part in combat, potions &amp; food .etc. A stated below I am only focusing on 19 skills, I plan on editing the skill menu on a 377 deob to a 289 skill menu, the revision before slayer was released. I personally don&#39;t hate Farming but it is a difficult skill for me to add at the moment, once I become more skilled I hope to make my own version of it where it doesn&#39;t take hours to get a herb or something like a potatoe.[/center]

[b]Development[/b]

[ul][li][i]Skill Development[/i]
http://lycx.org/index.php?topic=3.0[list][li]This is a link to my website mentioned in my signature, I use it to update my information of the development and ideas of my server and the thread is a bit large, and I would dislike having to edit it in two, possibly three locations so I&#39;m going to use an external link.[/li][/list][/li][/ul]</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 26 Apr 2011 03:03:13 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/lycx/392625.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Lycx</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Wintercanon Wintercanon]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/wintercanon">@Wintercanon</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>If you want to use NIO in this I suggest you wait until <a href="http://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php/topic,489526.0.html" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">OrathanAPI</a> has its NIO reactor design added. It will apply a simple TCP NIO server, which Runescape’s codec can easily be applied to. There isn’t need for a massive library like MINA or Netty in a Runescape Private Server.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/lycx/392625/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/lycx/392625/5</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 26 Apr 2011 03:03:13 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-392625-5</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/lycx/392625.rss">Lycx</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Lycx</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@doom_j doom_j]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/doom_j">@doom_j</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Please add more information in your topic, like goals, credits to other members who’s code was used, features your planning on adding, and just a summary of what the server is going to be about. <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=5" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/lycx/392625/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/lycx/392625/4</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 26 Apr 2011 02:20:29 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-392625-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/lycx/392625.rss">Lycx</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Lycx</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Andrew_Ferguson The317Guy]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/andrew_ferguson">@Andrew_Ferguson</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>This is an ad, you have to learn that there is way way to much text for anyone with the intention span of an average moparscape user wouldn’t be able to read it all right?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/lycx/392625/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/lycx/392625/3</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 26 Apr 2011 02:19:33 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-392625-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/lycx/392625.rss">Lycx</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Lycx</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@gnomez gnomez]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/gnomez">@gnomez</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>what is this? is this a advertisement i cant even tell</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/lycx/392625/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/lycx/392625/2</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 26 Apr 2011 02:11:48 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-392625-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/lycx/392625.rss">Lycx</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Lycx</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@WW1 WW]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/ww1">@WW1</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[center]<span class="bbcode-i">I am watching howl’s moving castle as I type this thread, so please excuse any spelling errors as my eyes are on the video and my fingers are typing <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/expressionless.png?v=5" title=":expressionless:" class="emoji" alt=":expressionless:"></span><br>
<img src="http://lycx.org/Themes/SimplePRO/images/theme/mylogo.png" alt width="" height=""></p>
<p>I started with an old favourate for my server, a particular revision winterlove now called <span class="bbcode-i">blakescape</span>. I had noticed a lot of popular servers had created something from this, or had created something entirely from scratch. Because I am uncapable to create networking, then do whatever comes after I’ve decided just to use something I have been somewhat successful before by created several servers that have reached aprox. 30 player at 90% of the time but back then this was common for a silabsoft server so this isn’t a big accomplishment for me personally but I can’t say it didn’t feel good running a community and creating a game for the first time. I started by cleaning up every file to ensure that it was easier for me to look through and edit - this was something I did for myself not for a release to the downloads section, I did however create a thread for my development on cleaning it. People supported my progress and as Tatemo explained to me:[/center]</p>
<p>[quote=“Tatemo, post:6, topic:361848”]Looks nice enough. But you are doing conventions wrong. Read some java tutorials <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=5" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
<p>The files need to be indented by the brackets and generally in Java it goes:</p>
<p>public class blah { (Bracket on same line now next Palidino was just a moron)<br>
[Tab] void blarg() {<br>
[tab][tab]<br>
[tab]}<br>
}</p>
<p>Other than that pretty good I guess :)[/quote][center]<br>
Because what I was changing as I cleaned is I moved the <span class="bbcode-b">{</span> onto a new line,<br>
[/center]<code>private int burntFish(int i)
{
	switch (i)
	{
		case 317:
		case 321:
			return 323;
	};
};</code>[center]<br>
But personally what’s wrong with being a little different, players wont even notice as long as it’s efficient and or provides some decent content to keep them active currently I’m working on skills then focusing on combat aspects like weapon specials, prayer bonuses aswell as prayer playing a part in combat, potions &amp; food .etc. A stated below I am only focusing on 19 skills, I plan on editing the skill menu on a 377 deob to a 289 skill menu, the revision before slayer was released. I personally don’t hate Farming but it is a difficult skill for me to add at the moment, once I become more skilled I hope to make my own version of it where it doesn’t take hours to get a herb or something like a potatoe.[/center]</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Development</span></p>
<p>[ul][li]<span class="bbcode-i">Skill Development</span><br>
<a href="http://lycx.org/index.php?topic=3.0%5Blist%5D%5Bli%5DThis" rel="nofollow noopener">http://lycx.org/index.php?topic=3.0[list][li]This</a> is a link to my website mentioned in my signature, I use it to update my information of the development and ideas of my server and the thread is a bit large, and I would dislike having to edit it in two, possibly three locations so I’m going to use an external link.[/li][/list][/li][/ul]</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/lycx/392625/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/lycx/392625/1</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 26 Apr 2011 02:09:55 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-392625-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/lycx/392625.rss">Lycx</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
