<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>What to do?</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/what-to-do/387860</link>
    <description>I just received these comments out of the blue and they are one of the most hateful thing&#39;s I&#39;ve ever read :( I&#39;ve done so many things to try and make up with him for something that happened nearly a year ago and he just doesn&#39;t care :(. I never said anything about me and thomas being friends either.

[quote=&quot;krackkid&quot;]Troller
Spammer
and
Flamer

All in which you are.[/quote]

[quote=&quot;h1 sk1ller&quot;]Please just stop, do whatever you want I honestly don&#39;t care, hate me if you want. I am not a troller flamer or spammer so just get over that! I am really nice and you seem to forget about everything nice we have done just because of something that happened in the past, even me and lilcjx have accepted eachother now so why can&#39;t you? I am none of those except partially spammer, and I have yet to still work on that.[/quote]

[quote=&quot;krackkid&quot;]If you say so.[/quote]

[quote=&quot;h1 sk1ller&quot;]Everyone else in the whole moparscape forum has accepted me, except you and missilabsoft.[/quote]

[quote=&quot;krackkid&quot;]again if you say so lol.[/quote]

[quote=&quot;h1 sk1ller&quot;]I&#39;m serious :mad: EVERYONE has accepted me again except you and missilabsoft... Please just stop bringing up what happened in the past, god it&#39;s nearly been a year.. If you want I can post up shit in the forum of what you&#39;ve done to me in the past, but do I? No! Trolls do that and if I&#39;m such a &#39;troll&#39; then why haven&#39;t I done that? I honestly don&#39;t care if you hate me, I would like to be friends again but you will probably reply again with &#39;whatever if you say so lololol&#39; I&#39;m even good friends with moparisthebest now and he is really cool, and why would he be friends with a troll?[/quote]

[quote=&quot;krackkid&quot;]lol you don&#39;t even know everyone on moparscape, so thats not true and I can get people to hate you :3 It&#39;s not hard. 


Also I don&#39;t dislike or hate you, I just have fun annoying you some times when I am sad or upset. It brings my spirits up, honestly you&#39;re nothing to me, nothing that worries me thats why I ignore you in minecraft.[/quote]

[quote=&quot;h1 sk1ller&quot;]That&#39;s the second most hateful thing I have EVER fucking heard from anyone!!!!!!! Honestly I don&#39;t give  FUCK ABOUT YOU ANYMORE! I have tried so much to be fucking kind to you but it doesn&#39;t do shit!! All I get is fucking hate back from you and now you threaten to get people to hate me!!!! And I&#39;m depressed enough to have to deal with your fucking bullshit of getting your hopes up, I think about killing myself every day! And I&#39;ve even tried 3 times this year, do you fucking think I need to deal with the shit you hand me aswell? I am one of the fucking nicest people, but when you don&#39;t forgive and forget then it becomes fucking hard! I don&#39;t give a fuck if I&#39;m nothing to you, I considered you as a &#39;friend&#39; and you just say that to me! &#39;you&#39;re nothing to me.&#39; well guess what, I don&#39;t give a fuck about anything you do anymore, go on kick me out of lapis city I&#39;ll just make my own server. And you actually called me the troller.. :([/quote]

[quote=&quot;krackkid&quot;][quote]
Thomas H
Blahh.
Thomas H says:
i started using photoshop
;D
and imma start learning how to model
Krack kid says:
I heard
Thomas H says:

Krack kid says:
I also heard you and H1 sk1ller are friends
D:
Thomas H says:
lolwut
who said that
Krack kid says:
he said 
Thomas H says:
h1 did?
i cant stand him
Krack kid says:
he said everyone but me and silab like him
and are friends with him
Thomas H says:
lol
i dont[/quote][/quote]

[quote=&quot;krackkid&quot;]I don&#39;t care about you being there, I don&#39;t care about you at all. I am sorry but thats all I can say. My heart is to a lone to care.[/quote]</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 25 Mar 2011 01:17:28 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>General Discussion</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/what-to-do/387860.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>What to do?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Scape-JAVA Scape-JAVA]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/scape-java">@Scape-JAVA</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Really guys, try sorting your differences out else where. Nobody wants to be involved in drama between you and others.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/what-to-do/387860/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/what-to-do/387860/2</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 25 Mar 2011 01:17:28 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-387860-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/what-to-do/387860.rss">What to do?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>What to do?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@h1_sk1ller h1 sk1ller]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/h1_sk1ller">@h1_sk1ller</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I just received these comments out of the blue and they are one of the most hateful thing’s I’ve ever read <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/frowning.png?v=5" title=":frowning:" class="emoji" alt=":frowning:"> I’ve done so many things to try and make up with him for something that happened nearly a year ago and he just doesn’t care :(. I never said anything about me and thomas being friends either.</p>
<p>[quote=“krackkid”]Troller<br>
Spammer<br>
and<br>
Flamer</p>
<p>All in which you are.[/quote]</p>
<aside class="quote">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 h1 sk1ller:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Please just stop, do whatever you want I honestly don’t care, hate me if you want. I am not a troller flamer or spammer so just get over that! I am really nice and you seem to forget about everything nice we have done just because of something that happened in the past, even me and lilcjx have accepted eachother now so why can’t you? I am none of those except partially spammer, and I have yet to still work on that.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<aside class="quote">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/krackkid/40/5_e05bb34c421432ee4d40de30c10af3e5.png" class="avatar"> krackkid:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>If you say so.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<aside class="quote">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 h1 sk1ller:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Everyone else in the whole moparscape forum has accepted me, except you and missilabsoft.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<aside class="quote">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/krackkid/40/5_e05bb34c421432ee4d40de30c10af3e5.png" class="avatar"> krackkid:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>again if you say so lol.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<aside class="quote">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 h1 sk1ller:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>I’m serious :mad: EVERYONE has accepted me again except you and missilabsoft… Please just stop bringing up what happened in the past, god it’s nearly been a year… If you want I can post up shit in the forum of what you’ve done to me in the past, but do I? No! Trolls do that and if I’m such a ‘troll’ then why haven’t I done that? I honestly don’t care if you hate me, I would like to be friends again but you will probably reply again with ‘whatever if you say so lololol’ I’m even good friends with moparisthebest now and he is really cool, and why would he be friends with a troll?</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>[quote=“krackkid”]lol you don’t even know everyone on moparscape, so thats not true and I can get people to hate you :3 It’s not hard.</p>
<p>Also I don’t dislike or hate you, I just have fun annoying you some times when I am sad or upset. It brings my spirits up, honestly you’re nothing to me, nothing that worries me thats why I ignore you in minecraft.[/quote]</p>
<aside class="quote">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 h1 sk1ller:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>That’s the second most hateful thing I have EVER fucking heard from anyone!!! Honestly I don’t give  FUCK ABOUT YOU ANYMORE! I have tried so much to be fucking kind to you but it doesn’t do shit!! All I get is fucking hate back from you and now you threaten to get people to hate me!!! And I’m depressed enough to have to deal with your fucking bullshit of getting your hopes up, I think about killing myself every day! And I’ve even tried 3 times this year, do you fucking think I need to deal with the shit you hand me aswell? I am one of the fucking nicest people, but when you don’t forgive and forget then it becomes fucking hard! I don’t give a fuck if I’m nothing to you, I considered you as a ‘friend’ and you just say that to me! ‘you’re nothing to me.’ well guess what, I don’t give a fuck about anything you do anymore, go on kick me out of lapis city I’ll just make my own server. And you actually called me the troller… <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/frowning.png?v=5" title=":frowning:" class="emoji" alt=":frowning:"></p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>[quote=“krackkid”][quote]<br>
Thomas H<br>
Blahh.<br>
Thomas H says:<br>
i started using photoshop<br>
;D<br>
and imma start learning how to model<br>
Krack kid says:<br>
I heard<br>
Thomas H says:</p>
<p>Krack kid says:<br>
I also heard you and H1 sk1ller are friends<br>
D:<br>
Thomas H says:<br>
lolwut<br>
who said that<br>
Krack kid says:<br>
he said<br>
Thomas H says:<br>
h1 did?<br>
i cant stand him<br>
Krack kid says:<br>
he said everyone but me and silab like him<br>
and are friends with him<br>
Thomas H says:<br>
lol<br>
i dont[/quote][/quote]</p>
<aside class="quote">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/krackkid/40/5_e05bb34c421432ee4d40de30c10af3e5.png" class="avatar"> krackkid:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>I don’t care about you being there, I don’t care about you at all. I am sorry but thats all I can say. My heart is to a lone to care.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/what-to-do/387860/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/what-to-do/387860/1</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 25 Mar 2011 01:11:17 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-387860-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/what-to-do/387860.rss">What to do?</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
