<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>READ THIS FIRST! - Tutorial Rules</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/read-this-first-tutorial-rules/2665</link>
    <description>This forum is for all the tutorials you want to share with the rest of the world, or for any cool tutorial you&#39;ve found, provided that you credit the person who wrote the tutorial in the beginning of your topic. 

[b]TUTORIAL RULES: [/b]

[ul][*] No requests of anything. Requests belong in any some other forum, but not here.
[*] No asking for Rep. This is one of Mopar&#39;s All Forum Rules.
[*] A title explaining what your tutorial is about.  None of this &quot;OMG AMAZING TUT HERE!&quot;
[*] Pictures. To take a screen shot of something on your computer, press the Print Screen (Prt Scrn) button and then open up paint and click on Edit &gt; Paste.
[*] Make sure your tutorials have a good description so we don&#39;t have to go to 3rd party websites
[*] Make sure your tutorials DO NOT CONTAIN ILLEGAL MATERIAL. If you have to have illegal material on your tutorial, please link to it from another website. Do not attach it to your post.
[*] Do not put TUT or [TUT] or whatever in the thread title. This is the tutorial section, it&#39;s implied.
[*] Do not contain &quot;coming soon&quot;s for the entire tutorial, or any of the tutorial for that matter. It&#39;s aggravating. When you&#39;re done with the tutorial then post it.
[*] [b]No stupid or not useful tutorials.[/b] If you think it is stupid, you&#39;re probably right, so don&#39;t post it.
[*] Always list your sources.
[*] If a tutorial has already been posted, then the duplicate of that tutorial will be locked/removed. [b]Use the search button![/b]
[*] Titles can&#39;t be in all caps. If so, or close to all caps, then it will be edited.
[*] [b]Bumping is allowed here![/b] People are here to learn! Follow the rules and don&#39;t make spam posts letting people know that they have bumped an old thread. No one cares! Bumping once again, IS ALLOWED!
[*] No tutorials advocating your own &quot;referral&quot; link.[/ul]

.

IMPORTANT! Make sure your Tutorials, Tips, etc are as fully described as can be.  I will read them all, and I want to be able to follow every single one without having to look up anything further, without having problem, and seeing some pictures. No pictures means not as many people will view them or lose interest very fast. If I can&#39;t follow it, it isn&#39;t detailed enough, if I generally think its not that great, or whatever else, I&#39;ll lock or move it. 

[blue][b]Warning[/b] - Always use a clear title or you will get your thread locked![/blue]

Please list your sources or like I said above, I&#39;ll lock or move it. 

Thanks, and have fun!</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 14 Dec 2007 19:06:33 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>General Discussion</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/read-this-first-tutorial-rules/2665.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>READ THIS FIRST! - Tutorial Rules</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@therealjdb JDB`]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/therealjdb">@therealjdb</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Woah, what? I didn’t modify any bumping rule, all I did was fix a few spelling errors lol.  <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/confused.png?v=6" title=":confused:" class="emoji" alt=":confused:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/read-this-first-tutorial-rules/2665/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/read-this-first-tutorial-rules/2665/3</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 14 Dec 2007 19:06:33 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-2665-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/read-this-first-tutorial-rules/2665.rss">READ THIS FIRST! - Tutorial Rules</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>READ THIS FIRST! - Tutorial Rules</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Ron Ron]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/ron">@Ron</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p><span class="bbcode-b">Note for therealdjb:</span> Please do not change the bumping rule. Bumping is allowed in this section because it is a tutorial section. Read my topic in the moderators’ section. Thank you.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/read-this-first-tutorial-rules/2665/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/read-this-first-tutorial-rules/2665/2</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2007 04:58:19 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-2665-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/read-this-first-tutorial-rules/2665.rss">READ THIS FIRST! - Tutorial Rules</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>READ THIS FIRST! - Tutorial Rules</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Starblaster100 Starblaster100]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/starblaster100">@Starblaster100</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>This forum is for all the tutorials you want to share with the rest of the world, or for any cool tutorial you’ve found, provided that you credit the person who wrote the tutorial in the beginning of your topic.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">TUTORIAL RULES: </span></p>
<p>[ul][<em>] No requests of anything. Requests belong in any some other forum, but not here.<br>
[</em>] No asking for Rep. This is one of Mopar’s All Forum Rules.<br>
[<em>] A title explaining what your tutorial is about.  None of this “OMG AMAZING TUT HERE!”<br>
[</em>] Pictures. To take a screen shot of something on your computer, press the Print Screen (Prt Scrn) button and then open up paint and click on Edit &gt; Paste.<br>
[<em>] Make sure your tutorials have a good description so we don’t have to go to 3rd party websites<br>
[</em>] Make sure your tutorials DO NOT CONTAIN ILLEGAL MATERIAL. If you have to have illegal material on your tutorial, please link to it from another website. Do not attach it to your post.<br>
[<em>] Do not put TUT or [TUT] or whatever in the thread title. This is the tutorial section, it’s implied.<br>
[</em>] Do not contain "coming soon"s for the entire tutorial, or any of the tutorial for that matter. It’s aggravating. When you’re done with the tutorial then post it.<br>
[<em>] <span class="bbcode-b">No stupid or not useful tutorials.</span> If you think it is stupid, you’re probably right, so don’t post it.<br>
[</em>] Always list your sources.<br>
[<em>] If a tutorial has already been posted, then the duplicate of that tutorial will be locked/removed. <span class="bbcode-b">Use the search button!</span><br>
[</em>] Titles can’t be in all caps. If so, or close to all caps, then it will be edited.<br>
[<em>] <span class="bbcode-b">Bumping is allowed here!</span> People are here to learn! Follow the rules and don’t make spam posts letting people know that they have bumped an old thread. No one cares! Bumping once again, IS ALLOWED!<br>
[</em>] No tutorials advocating your own “referral” link.[/ul]</p>
<p>.</p>
<p>IMPORTANT! Make sure your Tutorials, Tips, etc are as fully described as can be.  I will read them all, and I want to be able to follow every single one without having to look up anything further, without having problem, and seeing some pictures. No pictures means not as many people will view them or lose interest very fast. If I can’t follow it, it isn’t detailed enough, if I generally think its not that great, or whatever else, I’ll lock or move it.</p>
<p>[blue]<span class="bbcode-b">Warning</span> - Always use a clear title or you will get your thread locked![/blue]</p>
<p>Please list your sources or like I said above, I’ll lock or move it.</p>
<p>Thanks, and have fun!</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/read-this-first-tutorial-rules/2665/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/read-this-first-tutorial-rules/2665/1</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 11 May 2006 17:57:19 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-2665-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/read-this-first-tutorial-rules/2665.rss">READ THIS FIRST! - Tutorial Rules</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
