<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Someone please close this</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/someone-please-close-this/309375</link>
    <description>OK I&#39;ve figured out how to add money into my new client since it started out with none. I added 940m, but it showed up as coins in general. By that I mean If I wanted to take out 500m it would literally try to take out 500m in coins and it wouldn&#39;t show it like: 500m. Instead you would have one set of coins filling up your inventory. I would like to know how I can change so it would show normally. I&#39;m new at Java and I&#39;m still looking around and learning, but I&#39;ve got this far so help would be gladly appreciated, thanks in advance.


EDIT: I figured it out, thank you for reading my post anyway. Could someone please lock or delete this post.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 18 Oct 2009 18:29:30 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/someone-please-close-this/309375.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Someone please close this</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@PureEpics PureEpics]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/pureepics">@PureEpics</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>OK I’ve figured out how to add money into my new client since it started out with none. I added 940m, but it showed up as coins in general. By that I mean If I wanted to take out 500m it would literally try to take out 500m in coins and it wouldn’t show it like: 500m. Instead you would have one set of coins filling up your inventory. I would like to know how I can change so it would show normally. I’m new at Java and I’m still looking around and learning, but I’ve got this far so help would be gladly appreciated, thanks in advance.</p>
<p>EDIT: I figured it out, thank you for reading my post anyway. Could someone please lock or delete this post.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/someone-please-close-this/309375/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/someone-please-close-this/309375/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 18 Oct 2009 18:29:30 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-309375-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/someone-please-close-this/309375.rss">Someone please close this</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
