<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>New server needed</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-server-needed/547011</link>
    <description>There needs to be a new, well built stable server built, obviously profitable income is an advantage but there needs to be no corruption, A team of people who actually know how to code properly and the right staff from day 1. Advertisement which is done properly and maybe advance the game a little this is 2014 now we are playing a game from 2001 so the love of the game is clearly still there, Only thing is what&#39;s wrong with a few new things added as well?</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2014 16:23:58 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-server-needed/547011.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>New server needed</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@malikz malikz]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/malikz">@malikz</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>You guys can make custom quests to add incentive to actually DO quests. Quests, for the most part, aren’t rewarding EXP wise. I was thinking maybe making bounties (kill people in the wild x amount of times), or (do this quest twice). Let me try to explain a little more in detail.</p>
<p>As I’ve been playing Destiny, I like the setup they have. They have a really nice PvE setup, and then a decent PvP setup. You have bounties to kill PvE bosses on different modes, and then doing certain things while in PvP.</p>
<p>Make custom bosses (could be minigames), and when beating those minigames (within a certain time frame or difficulty), your rewards will vary, but you have a higher chance of getting something rewarding from completing the minigame. Within those minigames, you can make “bounties” to complete by doing minigames a certain way. It can give exp incentives, or item incentives (or both) depending on the level of difficulty, and the time it took to complete it.</p>
<p>For PvP, you guys should make it so that the ONLY way to complete PvP bounties is if you’re in a clan (this is where you implement clan capes). To enter a clan, the clan leader should be able to create a quest to get INTO the clan (could be whatever they want…for example, kill black dragon 5 times). Once in the clan, you’re enabled to complete PvP bounties, but can ONLY complete the bounties when wearing your respective clan cape.</p>
<p>Bounties for PvP could include killing “opposing clan” members in different ways. You can kill enemies by getting the kill through range, or kill clan leader, killing all enemy clan members once, etc.</p>
<p>The bounties can reset daily, and then you can have WEEKLY bounties to complete. You can make various bounties, but cycle them and don’t have the same ones active, every day. Cycle the quests to switch it up.</p>
<p>Also, when completing raids, or especially difficult mini games, you guys could make it that you can upgrade your armor or weapons through items that enable you to upgrade your armor and weapons. In destiny, they’re called ascent shards (or something like that)…maybe you can create a rainbow shaded bead (modeled after the ones you get from killing imps), and when used against armor, or a weapon, you can +1 that equipment (ONLY ONCE) of a state you choose, or add 1 more additional hit when in combat (happens at random), or range slightly faster than normal if you upgrade a bow. For instance, if I get the rainbow bead (should be named something else), I can add +1 permanent strength to my chest plate, or add +1 defense to my plate. For other bonuses, inside combat, you have a random chance of hitting 1 more time within those 3 rounds (after hitting once, you can hit another time (rare chance) so instead of 3 hits, you have a chance of hitting 4 times. Also, when you get pked, just like regular items, you have a chance of losing that item, and whoever loots it and is able to use it, can use the bonus. For range, you can range slightly faster, or have a higher chance than normal of hitting critically (higher chance of hitting your highest hit with range). I could come up with more ideas if you guys would like.</p>
<p>Between stat bonuses, and other (more rewarding) bonuses, you can adjust the amount of rainbow beads needed to receive low tier, mid tier, or top tier bonuses for that item, and receive them at random (cannot personally select the bonus you wish to have). For instance, a stat bonus (depending on the stat) can require 1 rainbow bead, or two. Since attack and strength are slightly more important than defense, you can require defense and hp to just need 1 bead, and 2 beads for str or attk (but it will select attack or str randomly). For top tier stuff like random 4th hit, or ranging slightly quicker, you can make it so that you need 3-5 beads (respectively) to select bonuses within their respective tiers.</p>
<p>Also, make it so that you can ONLY receive these beads through weekly bounties, or raids (which would need to be extremely difficult…like spawning 3-5 black dragons on an island and having to kill them within 20 minutes), and THEN you MAY have a chance to receive the bead.</p>
<p>I could see this getting abused down the line, so I guess there needs to be road blocks to prevent that. It was just an idea.</p>
<p>Basically, make an rsc that models Destiny. As I think about it, I really think it could work. Raids in rsc could be real fun if done right.</p>
<p>If anyone is confused, I can try to explain even further (if you seriously want to try this idea out). It really could work, but would require a legit coder.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-server-needed/547011/21">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-server-needed/547011/21</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2014 16:23:58 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-547011-21</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-server-needed/547011.rss">New server needed</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>New server needed</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@da_real_hype da real hype]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/da_real_hype">@da_real_hype</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“Lothy, post:19, topic:547011”]My solution doesn’t involve that many game modes.<br>
There would be two.</p>
<ol>
<li>Regular mode, with the ability to enter the wilderness for f2p or p2p pking.</li>
<li>PVP mode (where you can set your stats and use items of your choosing), with the ability to enter the wilderness for f2p or p2p pking.</li>
</ol>
<p>It’s not rocket science.</p>
<p>As for stopping botting, you could always implement ‘quests’ like those in WoW where you perform some task that rewards reasonable experience. The tasks are dynamic and may require travelling around the world to complete. The experience is generous enough that doing the is more effective than grinding, but harder to bot.[/quote][quote=“Lothy, post:6, topic:547011”][quote author=waj link=topic=665910.msg4451959#msg4451959 date=1412183483]</p>
<aside class="quote">
<blockquote>
<p>Do you know if RSCRevolution has a good foundation? I was thinking about sending them my resume. I play there sometimes when I take breaks from my project. I think it would be great to work with them.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Stay away from that team at all costs, they are a bunch of retards the only person who can truly do anything worth while on there is N0m(Nothing on here).</p>
<p>They also lie about who they are for some odd reason, but anyone who’s been around for the last couple of years knows exactly who they all are.<br>
[/quote]<br>
You’ve piqued my curiosity. Who are they, and why would they hide their identities?[/quote]</p>
<p><span class="hashtag">#1</span>. Something similar to what i been thinking of.</p>
<p><span class="hashtag">#2</span>. Crooks(from scam servers with snoopy back in the day) and a couple others</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-server-needed/547011/20">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-server-needed/547011/20</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2014 02:58:34 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-547011-20</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-server-needed/547011.rss">New server needed</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>New server needed</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@lothy Lothy]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/lothy">@lothy</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>My solution doesn’t involve that many game modes.<br>
There would be two.</p>
<ol>
<li>Regular mode, with the ability to enter the wilderness for f2p or p2p pking.</li>
<li>PVP mode (where you can set your stats and use items of your choosing), with the ability to enter the wilderness for f2p or p2p pking.</li>
</ol>
<p>It’s not rocket science.</p>
<p>As for stopping botting, you could always implement ‘quests’ like those in WoW where you perform some task that rewards reasonable experience. The tasks are dynamic and may require travelling around the world to complete. The experience is generous enough that doing the is more effective than grinding, but harder to bot.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-server-needed/547011/19">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-server-needed/547011/19</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 02 Oct 2014 22:27:18 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-547011-19</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-server-needed/547011.rss">New server needed</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>New server needed</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Fabrice_L Fabrice L]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/fabrice_l">@Fabrice_L</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote" data-post="13" data-topic="547011">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/rodgerwilco/40/5_e05bb34c421432ee4d40de30c10af3e5.png" class="avatar"> Rodgerwilco:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Is that all? Or is there some bonuses for playing legend or extreme?</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I haven’t really worked it out yet, depends on what people want</p>
<aside class="quote" data-post="17" data-topic="547011">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/rscshadow/40/5_e05bb34c421432ee4d40de30c10af3e5.png" class="avatar"> RSCShadow:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>That is way too much to grok all at once. Players don’t want to read up on game rules and mechanics, they want to jump in and play right away. Having a bunch of options, modes, character attributes and settings makes things really confusing for the programmer and the player. How does a “legendary” player trade with an “easy” player? How can you share a world between every one?</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>That’s pretty easy actually, just by adding in simple things.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-u"><span class="bbcode-b">How to keep easy/normal items away from hard/extreme/legendary?</span></span><br>
To do this, you could simply add one single definition to the item named difficulty (0 = easy, 1 = normal, 2 = hard, 3 = extreme, 4 = legendary).<br>
By adding a little check here and there, you can make sure the easy and normal items cannot be picked up by hard/extreme and legendary players or even being offered in trade with them. Can be done whatever way you want it to be tbh.</p>
<p>An easy player can take legendary items though, but when he creates something else out of it, it’ll become an item aqcuired in easy mode though.</p>
<p>There won’t be anything confusing to it, it’ll just sent the owner of that item a message like this “You can’t trade items you gathered in easy mode with this player” or something like it.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-server-needed/547011/18">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-server-needed/547011/18</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 02 Oct 2014 21:37:05 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-547011-18</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-server-needed/547011.rss">New server needed</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>New server needed</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@RSCShadow RSCShadow]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/rscshadow">@RSCShadow</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“Lothy, post:14, topic:547011”]Another thing, there should be a way (in my opinion) to launch right into PVP if you’re that way inclined. To achieve this users should have two sets of stats, two banks, and two inventories. In the PVP context they use their PVP stats/bank/inventory, and are free to generate items and make stat changes as they see fit. In the regular game context they have their regular stats/bank/inventory and are subject to the usual levelling up process.[/quote]That is way too much to grok all at once. Players don’t want to read up on game rules and mechanics, they want to jump in and play right away. Having a bunch of options, modes, character attributes and settings makes things really confusing for the programmer and the player. How does a “legendary” player trade with an “easy” player? How can you share a world between every one? How can you distinguish different leagues? There’s bound to be better solutions.</p>
<p>Instead of having two copies of a player for PvP, why not just introduce more entertaining PvP minigames for points? People already understand the concept of minigames that don’t permanently alter your character and it would be a lot easier to code.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-server-needed/547011/17">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-server-needed/547011/17</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 02 Oct 2014 21:08:40 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-547011-17</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-server-needed/547011.rss">New server needed</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>New server needed</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@lothy Lothy]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/lothy">@lothy</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Well regular gameplay allows you to do all of the non-PVP stuff. The idea is more or less to allow people to do what they want, when they want. It also makes the fun parts of the game immediately accessible to people who are time-poor (this is a common problem for some players who aren’t unemployed or otherwise able to engage in grinding on low-experience servers).</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-server-needed/547011/16">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-server-needed/547011/16</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 02 Oct 2014 21:06:41 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-547011-16</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-server-needed/547011.rss">New server needed</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>New server needed</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Rodgerwilco Rodgerwilco]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/rodgerwilco">@Rodgerwilco</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Then there is no benefit of playing the “regular” game.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-server-needed/547011/15">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-server-needed/547011/15</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 02 Oct 2014 21:04:22 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-547011-15</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-server-needed/547011.rss">New server needed</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>New server needed</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@lothy Lothy]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/lothy">@lothy</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Another thing, there should be a way (in my opinion) to launch right into PVP if you’re that way inclined. To achieve this users should have two sets of stats, two banks, and two inventories. In the PVP context they use their PVP stats/bank/inventory, and are free to generate items and make stat changes as they see fit. In the regular game context they have their regular stats/bank/inventory and are subject to the usual levelling up process.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-server-needed/547011/14">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-server-needed/547011/14</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 02 Oct 2014 21:03:06 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-547011-14</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-server-needed/547011.rss">New server needed</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>New server needed</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Rodgerwilco Rodgerwilco]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/rodgerwilco">@Rodgerwilco</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Is that all? Or is there some bonuses for playing legend or extreme?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-server-needed/547011/13">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-server-needed/547011/13</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 02 Oct 2014 20:14:40 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-547011-13</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-server-needed/547011.rss">New server needed</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>New server needed</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Fabrice_L Fabrice L]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/fabrice_l">@Fabrice_L</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote" data-post="11" data-topic="547011">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/user_avatar/forum.moparisthebest.com/lothy/40/51_1.png" class="avatar"> Lothy:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>I think the key is to allow for both grind and non-grind gameplay in the same world. Different game contexts within the same server, different experience rates, whatever. A server that, within reason, offers something for everybody.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Sounds like something I’m implementing already, a choice between 5 difficulties on login:</p>
<ul>
<li>Easy: RSC * 20</li>
<li>Normal: RSC * 10</li>
<li>Hard: RSC * 5</li>
<li>Extreme: RSC * 2</li>
<li>Legend: RSC * 1</li>
</ul>
<p>Might figure out a way for trading and stuff too, so easy and normal can trade with eachother and same with hard/extreme/legend</p>
<p><img src="http://i.imgur.com/7U8xXgu.png" alt width="" height=""></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-server-needed/547011/12">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-server-needed/547011/12</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 02 Oct 2014 12:44:14 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-547011-12</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-server-needed/547011.rss">New server needed</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>New server needed</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@lothy Lothy]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/lothy">@lothy</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I think the key is to allow for both grind and non-grind gameplay in the same world. Different game contexts within the same server, different experience rates, whatever. A server that, within reason, offers something for everybody.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-server-needed/547011/11">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-server-needed/547011/11</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2014 23:49:16 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-547011-11</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-server-needed/547011.rss">New server needed</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>New server needed</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@nacional nacional]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/nacional">@nacional</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote" data-post="9" data-topic="547011">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/rodgerwilco/40/5_e05bb34c421432ee4d40de30c10af3e5.png" class="avatar"> Rodgerwilco:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Maybe the focus should be new ways of training rather than grind and afking. Which would turn into an active community rather than 100 online with 10 people actually communicating. Lets make the game more active.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-server-needed/547011/10">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-server-needed/547011/10</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2014 23:01:13 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-547011-10</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-server-needed/547011.rss">New server needed</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>New server needed</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Rodgerwilco Rodgerwilco]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/rodgerwilco">@Rodgerwilco</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Maybe the focus should be new ways of training rather than grind and afking. Which would turn into an active community rather than 100 online with 10 people actually communicating. Lets make the game more active.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-server-needed/547011/9">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-server-needed/547011/9</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2014 21:55:12 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-547011-9</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-server-needed/547011.rss">New server needed</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>New server needed</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Aleka Aleka]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/aleka">@Aleka</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I’ve been hearing there should be this kind of server talk all the time. Just make the server. Why have someone else make it for you?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-server-needed/547011/8">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-server-needed/547011/8</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2014 21:12:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-547011-8</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-server-needed/547011.rss">New server needed</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>New server needed</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@hulkamaanio hulkamaanio]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/hulkamaanio">@hulkamaanio</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>would love to see basic point based pk server with red drag farming for rune/dragon and pirates for bloods <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/smiley.png?v=5" title=":smiley:" class="emoji" alt=":smiley:"> like royalpk used to be <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=5" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-server-needed/547011/7">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-server-needed/547011/7</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2014 20:59:36 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-547011-7</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-server-needed/547011.rss">New server needed</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>New server needed</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@lothy Lothy]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/lothy">@lothy</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“waj, post:5, topic:547011”][quote author=TechN9ne link=topic=665910.msg4451912#msg4451912 date=1412142158]<br>
Do you know if RSCRevolution has a good foundation? I was thinking about sending them my resume. I play there sometimes when I take breaks from my project. I think it would be great to work with them.<br>
[/quote]<br>
Stay away from that team at all costs, they are a bunch of retards the only person who can truly do anything worth while on there is N0m(Nothing on here).</p>
<p>They also lie about who they are for some odd reason, but anyone who’s been around for the last couple of years knows exactly who they all are.[/quote]<br>
You’ve piqued my curiosity. Who are they, and why would they hide their identities?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-server-needed/547011/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-server-needed/547011/6</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2014 20:43:19 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-547011-6</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-server-needed/547011.rss">New server needed</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>New server needed</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@waj waj]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/waj">@waj</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote" data-post="4" data-topic="547011">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/techn9ne/40/5_e05bb34c421432ee4d40de30c10af3e5.png" class="avatar"> TechN9ne:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Do you know if RSCRevolution has a good foundation? I was thinking about sending them my resume. I play there sometimes when I take breaks from my project. I think it would be great to work with them.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Stay away from that team at all costs, they are a bunch of retards the only person who can truly do anything worth while on there is N0m(Nothing on here).</p>
<p>They also lie about who they are for some odd reason, but anyone who’s been around for the last couple of years knows exactly who they all are.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-server-needed/547011/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-server-needed/547011/5</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2014 17:11:23 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-547011-5</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-server-needed/547011.rss">New server needed</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>New server needed</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@TechN9ne TechN9ne]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/techn9ne">@TechN9ne</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Do you know if RSCRevolution has a good foundation? I was thinking about sending them my resume. I play there sometimes when I take breaks from my project. I think it would be great to work with them.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-server-needed/547011/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-server-needed/547011/4</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2014 05:42:38 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-547011-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-server-needed/547011.rss">New server needed</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>New server needed</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@l0w_archer l0w archer]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/l0w_archer">@l0w_archer</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>i do understand what you mean mate, i admit i have no actual coding experience as far as it goes for the ability to re write a server</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-server-needed/547011/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-server-needed/547011/3</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2014 10:35:17 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-547011-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-server-needed/547011.rss">New server needed</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>New server needed</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Everyonedies Everyonedies]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/everyonedies">@Everyonedies</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Go for it then.  Thats if your not one of these QQ kids who are never happy with whats on offer but lack the ability to code themselves.  The love is still there yes, but what ALL these servers lack is real rsc players… By that, i dont mean the drones of noobs who pk’ed low level.  I mean the big guns of high end pking.  There is not enough of them left.  If you cant do it yourself why bother trying to spur other people to do it when the end result is just noobs from real rsc thinking they qualify as serious pkers of old.  You do not.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-server-needed/547011/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-server-needed/547011/2</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2014 23:59:18 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-547011-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-server-needed/547011.rss">New server needed</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>New server needed</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@l0w_archer l0w archer]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/l0w_archer">@l0w_archer</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>There needs to be a new, well built stable server built, obviously profitable income is an advantage but there needs to be no corruption, A team of people who actually know how to code properly and the right staff from day 1. Advertisement which is done properly and maybe advance the game a little this is 2014 now we are playing a game from 2001 so the love of the game is clearly still there, Only thing is what’s wrong with a few new things added as well?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-server-needed/547011/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-server-needed/547011/1</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2014 19:45:03 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-547011-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-server-needed/547011.rss">New server needed</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
