<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Explaining Java Tools (And how to use them)</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/explaining-java-tools-and-how-to-use-them/322240</link>
    <description>- For Mods: I think this is a tutorial; although I&#39;m not 100% sure. If you think it isn&#39;t, please message me and I will put it in general discussion. I&#39;ll apply this with RuneScape P Servers so that I don&#39;t have to post it in MITB :P -

[b]Difficulty: N/A
Things needed: Willingness to listen and read, at least beginner knowledge of java[/b]

[b]Chapters:[/b]
1: Decompilers, and how they are helpful in the &quot;RSPS World&quot;.
2: Obfuscators and Deobfuscators
3: Eclipse
4: Notepad++
5: MITB Deob Page


[b]Chapter 1: Decompilers[/b]
Imagine this: You come across an amazing 317 client, the best you&#39;ve ever seen! You quickly press the blue &quot;Download Now!&quot; button and you pray as your computer downloads it. You extract the file, put it into a folder and open it up. To your surprise, all the files are .class extensions! What is this?? You lose all your interest in the client as it is basically useless because you cannot modify it in any way. So, what do you do now?

Head over to the decompilers, of course! Go to www.google.com and search for &quot;DJ Java Decompiler&quot;. It&#39;s a good decompiler and it works. Download the decompiler.

Now open it up and do the easy as hell + fun process!

Go up to the file menu, and press &quot;open&quot;.
[IMG]http://i50.tinypic.com/91mght.jpg[/img]

Now you want to locate the class file you want to open. (I believe it&#39;s only 1 at a time, sadly.)
Then, click open and BAM! You got your class file! WOOT WOOT. Now, you should only edit from that window, or else you might have some complications. Once you&#39;re done editing, you go up to &quot;File&quot; and click &quot;Save As...&quot;. The default setting is the java extension, but you should always click &quot;Save As...&quot; so that you&#39;re 100%. You can also save it as different files like text documents or .js (javascript docs).

[b]Chapter 2: Deobfuscators and Obfuscators[/b]

You can easily find one or the other (or both) on Google. What a deobfuscator does is it turns a runescape client that you downloaded from their website, into a deob, and with a little bit of modifying you can make the client connect to an rsps. Sadly, deobfuscators don&#39;t work with today&#39;s code though :(

On the other hand, an obfuscator protects code. You might of seen an obfuscated client or file. Deltascape is an example. in the char files, when you look at a players account the player&#39;s password is an example of what is obfuscated. So to sum up obfuscators, they protect Java code. *This can be used to destroy leechers, too*

[b]Chapter 3: Java Eclipse[/b]

*There is a free download for this on Google.com*  Basically, Eclipse is a tool for Java developers. When you get into the higher levels of Java programming, this really will come in handy. For example, if you have Eclipse you can delete that clumsy old compiler, because it does it right for you when you change the source code. 

[b]Chapter 4: Notepad++[/b]

Notepad++ is pretty much a &quot;must-have&quot; for any type of programmer. HTML or Java, XML, CSS, whatever. 

Features:
&lt;blockquote&gt;Notepad++ v5.6.2 new features and fixed bugs (from v5.6.1) :

1.  Fix the Unicode localization file display problem.
2.  Update templat localization file (english.xml) to v5.6.1.
3.  Fix tag highlighting bug while disabling indent guide lines.
4.  Fix the translated sub menu entries applying on the menu item.
5.  Display more information while catching of plugins crash.


Notepad++ v5.6.1 new features and fixed bugs (from v5.6) :

1.  Fix brace highlighting breaking issue and related performance problem.
2.  Add new encodings in the shortcuts map.
3.  Remove annoying encoding issue warning dialogs.
4.  Enhance Html encoding auto-detection.
5.  Fix case-insensitive searching bug for non-ascii characters (for example some characters in French and Cyrillic letters).
6.  Add find result commands in the menu.
7.  Add DOS CodePage : CP437, CP737, CP850, CP852, CP855, CP857, CP858, CP860, CP861, CP863, CP865, CP866 and CP869.
8.  Fix localization combo box unselected in preference dialog bug after startup (when a localization file is in use).


Notepad++ v5.6 new features and fixed bugs (from v5.5.1) :

1.  Add languages encoding - Chinese traditional (BIG5), Chinese Simplified (GB2312), Japanese (Shift JIS), Korean (EUC), Thai (TIS-620), Hebrew (iso-8859-8), Hebrew (1255), Central European (1250), Cyrillic (1251), Cyrillic (KOI8-U), Cyrillic (KOI8-R), Cyrillic (Mac), Western European(1252), Greek (1253), Turkish(1254), Arabic (1256), Baltic (1257), Vietnamese (1258), ISO_8859-1 to ISO_8859-16 and a lot of more.
2.  Add auto-detection of HTML and XML files encodings.
3.  Add COBOL, D, Gui4Cli, PowerShell and R language support.
4.  Add Marker Jumper feature (Jump down/up : Ctrl+Num/Ctrl+Shift+Num).
5.  Add indent guide line highlighting for html/xml tags.
6.  Add system tray context menu and new command argument &quot;-systemtray&quot;.
7.  Fix Unicode to ANSI encoding bug.
8.  Fix last recent file list menu items localization encoding bug.
9.  Fix last recent file number goes to zero issue.
10. Add new command argument &quot;--help&quot;.
11. Fix Calltip hint bug and add a new capacity in it.
12. Add the ability to add the second keyword group for user in both LISP and Scheme languages.
13. Fix the wrap symbol display problem.
14. Add SQL ESC symbol &#39;\&#39;.
15. Fix column editor insert number bug in virtual space mode.
16. Fix status bar displaying &quot;-2 char&quot; issue for a empty document.
17. Fix installation of NppShell64 failed issue in installer.


Included plugins (Unicode):

1.  TextFX v0.26
2.  NppExec v0.3.2
3.  Spell Checker v1.3.3
4.  MIME Tools v1.6
5.  NppExport v0.2.8
6.  NppNetNote v0.1
7.  Compare Plugin 1.5.5
8.  Plugin Manager 0.9.3.0

Included plugins (ANSI):

1.  TextFX v0.25
2.  NppExec v0.3.2
3.  Spell Checker v1.3.3
4.  MIME Tools v1.6
5.  NppExport v0.2.8
6.  Light Explorer v1.5
7.  NppNetNote v0.1
8.  Compare Plugin 1.5.5
9.  Plugin Manager 0.9.3.0&lt;/blockquote&gt;
[IMG]http://i48.tinypic.com/1z3nwx5.jpg[/img]

[b]Chapter 5: MITB deob list[/b]
A little cool list of deobs:
http://www.moparisthebest.com/rs/deob/

You can use some tools to turn this into a working server and release it, making a new popular deob like 508, 525, or 562, etc... (You&#39;ll need more tools than in this tutorial)

[i]
Thank you for reading my tutorial, and I hope you learned something new today. I am sure beginning programmers will also learn from this.[/i]</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 27 Dec 2009 01:48:19 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/explaining-java-tools-and-how-to-use-them/322240.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Explaining Java Tools (And how to use them)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Espeon Espeon]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/espeon">@Espeon</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <ul>
<li>For Mods: I think this is a tutorial; although I’m not 100% sure. If you think it isn’t, please message me and I will put it in general discussion. I’ll apply this with RuneScape P Servers so that I don’t have to post it in MITB <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=5" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"> -</li>
</ul>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Difficulty: N/A<br>
Things needed: Willingness to listen and read, at least beginner knowledge of java</span></p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Chapters:</span><br>
1: Decompilers, and how they are helpful in the “RSPS World”.<br>
2: Obfuscators and Deobfuscators<br>
3: Eclipse<br>
4: Notepad++<br>
5: MITB Deob Page</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Chapter 1: Decompilers</span><br>
Imagine this: You come across an amazing 317 client, the best you’ve ever seen! You quickly press the blue “Download Now!” button and you pray as your computer downloads it. You extract the file, put it into a folder and open it up. To your surprise, all the files are .class extensions! What is this?? You lose all your interest in the client as it is basically useless because you cannot modify it in any way. So, what do you do now?</p>
<p>Head over to the decompilers, of course! Go to <a href="http://www.google.com" rel="nofollow noopener">www.google.com</a> and search for “DJ Java Decompiler”. It’s a good decompiler and it works. Download the decompiler.</p>
<p>Now open it up and do the easy as hell + fun process!</p>
<p>Go up to the file menu, and press “open”.<br>
<img src="http://i50.tinypic.com/91mght.jpg" alt width="140" height="120"></p>
<p>Now you want to locate the class file you want to open. (I believe it’s only 1 at a time, sadly.)<br>
Then, click open and BAM! You got your class file! WOOT WOOT. Now, you should only edit from that window, or else you might have some complications. Once you’re done editing, you go up to “File” and click “Save As…”. The default setting is the java extension, but you should always click “Save As…” so that you’re 100%. You can also save it as different files like text documents or .js (javascript docs).</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Chapter 2: Deobfuscators and Obfuscators</span></p>
<p>You can easily find one or the other (or both) on Google. What a deobfuscator does is it turns a runescape client that you downloaded from their website, into a deob, and with a little bit of modifying you can make the client connect to an rsps. Sadly, deobfuscators don’t work with today’s code though <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/frowning.png?v=5" title=":frowning:" class="emoji" alt=":frowning:"></p>
<p>On the other hand, an obfuscator protects code. You might of seen an obfuscated client or file. Deltascape is an example. in the char files, when you look at a players account the player’s password is an example of what is obfuscated. So to sum up obfuscators, they protect Java code. <em>This can be used to destroy leechers, too</em></p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Chapter 3: Java Eclipse</span></p>
<p><em>There is a free download for this on <a href="http://Google.com" rel="nofollow noopener">Google.com</a></em>  Basically, Eclipse is a tool for Java developers. When you get into the higher levels of Java programming, this really will come in handy. For example, if you have Eclipse you can delete that clumsy old compiler, because it does it right for you when you change the source code.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Chapter 4: Notepad++</span></p>
<p>Notepad++ is pretty much a “must-have” for any type of programmer. HTML or Java, XML, CSS, whatever.</p>
<p>Features:</p>
<blockquote>Notepad++ v5.6.2 new features and fixed bugs (from v5.6.1) :
<ol>
<li>Fix the Unicode localization file display problem.</li>
<li>Update templat localization file (english.xml) to v5.6.1.</li>
<li>Fix tag highlighting bug while disabling indent guide lines.</li>
<li>Fix the translated sub menu entries applying on the menu item.</li>
<li>Display more information while catching of plugins crash.</li>
</ol>
<p>Notepad++ v5.6.1 new features and fixed bugs (from v5.6) :</p>
<ol>
<li>Fix brace highlighting breaking issue and related performance problem.</li>
<li>Add new encodings in the shortcuts map.</li>
<li>Remove annoying encoding issue warning dialogs.</li>
<li>Enhance Html encoding auto-detection.</li>
<li>Fix case-insensitive searching bug for non-ascii characters (for example some characters in French and Cyrillic letters).</li>
<li>Add find result commands in the menu.</li>
<li>Add DOS CodePage : CP437, CP737, CP850, CP852, CP855, CP857, CP858, CP860, CP861, CP863, CP865, CP866 and CP869.</li>
<li>Fix localization combo box unselected in preference dialog bug after startup (when a localization file is in use).</li>
</ol>
<p>Notepad++ v5.6 new features and fixed bugs (from v5.5.1) :</p>
<ol>
<li>Add languages encoding - Chinese traditional (BIG5), Chinese Simplified (GB2312), Japanese (Shift JIS), Korean (EUC), Thai (TIS-620), Hebrew (iso-8859-8), Hebrew (1255), Central European (1250), Cyrillic (1251), Cyrillic (KOI8-U), Cyrillic (KOI8-R), Cyrillic (Mac), Western European(1252), Greek (1253), Turkish(1254), Arabic (1256), Baltic (1257), Vietnamese (1258), ISO_8859-1 to ISO_8859-16 and a lot of more.</li>
<li>Add auto-detection of HTML and XML files encodings.</li>
<li>Add COBOL, D, Gui4Cli, PowerShell and R language support.</li>
<li>Add Marker Jumper feature (Jump down/up : Ctrl+Num/Ctrl+Shift+Num).</li>
<li>Add indent guide line highlighting for html/xml tags.</li>
<li>Add system tray context menu and new command argument “-systemtray”.</li>
<li>Fix Unicode to ANSI encoding bug.</li>
<li>Fix last recent file list menu items localization encoding bug.</li>
<li>Fix last recent file number goes to zero issue.</li>
<li>Add new command argument “–help”.</li>
<li>Fix Calltip hint bug and add a new capacity in it.</li>
<li>Add the ability to add the second keyword group for user in both LISP and Scheme languages.</li>
<li>Fix the wrap symbol display problem.</li>
<li>Add SQL ESC symbol ‘’.</li>
<li>Fix column editor insert number bug in virtual space mode.</li>
<li>Fix status bar displaying “-2 char” issue for a empty document.</li>
<li>Fix installation of NppShell64 failed issue in installer.</li>
</ol>
<p>Included plugins (Unicode):</p>
<ol>
<li>TextFX v0.26</li>
<li>NppExec v0.3.2</li>
<li>Spell Checker v1.3.3</li>
<li>MIME Tools v1.6</li>
<li>NppExport v0.2.8</li>
<li>NppNetNote v0.1</li>
<li>Compare Plugin 1.5.5</li>
<li>Plugin Manager 0.9.3.0</li>
</ol>
<p>Included plugins (ANSI):</p>
<ol>
<li>TextFX v0.25</li>
<li>NppExec v0.3.2</li>
<li>Spell Checker v1.3.3</li>
<li>MIME Tools v1.6</li>
<li>NppExport v0.2.8</li>
<li>Light Explorer v1.5</li>
<li>NppNetNote v0.1</li>
<li>Compare Plugin 1.5.5</li>
<li>Plugin Manager 0.9.3.0</li>
</ol>
</blockquote><br>
<img src="http://i48.tinypic.com/1z3nwx5.jpg" alt width="140" height="120">

<p><span class="bbcode-b">Chapter 5: MITB deob list</span><br>
A little cool list of deobs:<br>
<a href="http://www.moparisthebest.com/rs/deob/" class="onebox" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">http://www.moparisthebest.com/rs/deob/</a></p>
<p>You can use some tools to turn this into a working server and release it, making a new popular deob like 508, 525, or 562, etc… (You’ll need more tools than in this tutorial)</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-i"><br>
Thank you for reading my tutorial, and I hope you learned something new today. I am sure beginning programmers will also learn from this.</span></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/explaining-java-tools-and-how-to-use-them/322240/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/explaining-java-tools-and-how-to-use-them/322240/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 27 Dec 2009 01:48:19 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-322240-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/explaining-java-tools-and-how-to-use-them/322240.rss">Explaining Java Tools (And how to use them)</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
