<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Alter Ego</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/alter-ego/184675</link>
    <description>Picture the Sims. now take away the aspect of being a &quot;God character&quot; and just being one character. Strip away the graphics and replace them with amazing vignettes and a much more interesting and enjoyable game. You now have Alter Ego. It has wit and humour as well as some slightly disturbing yet realistic parts. It was written by a psychologist who wanted to try something new, and succeeded greatly. It comes in male and female. http://www.abandonia.com/en/games/263/Alter+Ego+(Man+and+Woman).html
I do not know (T)opars policy on abandonware, so I will take it down at a staff member&#39;s request.
Please note that there are some [easily fixable] errors in the male game. You should use Dosbox if you want sound to come from your speakers. Also, press CTL + S to save, however you have to fiddle with the male save games to make saving work. Saving is also not necessary. I have had perfect [yet realistic] endings quite a bit and am amazed by the enjoyment [and even experience!] this game gives.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 27 Feb 2008 11:12:57 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Games</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/alter-ego/184675.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Alter Ego</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@cooper cooper]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/cooper">@cooper</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Picture the Sims. now take away the aspect of being a “God character” and just being one character. Strip away the graphics and replace them with amazing vignettes and a much more interesting and enjoyable game. You now have Alter Ego. It has wit and humour as well as some slightly disturbing yet realistic parts. It was written by a psychologist who wanted to try something new, and succeeded greatly. It comes in male and female. <a href="http://www.abandonia.com/en/games/263/Alter+Ego+(Man+and+Woman).html" rel="nofollow noopener">http://www.abandonia.com/en/games/263/Alter+Ego+(Man+and+Woman).html</a><br>
I do not know (T)opars policy on abandonware, so I will take it down at a staff member’s request.<br>
Please note that there are some [easily fixable] errors in the male game. You should use Dosbox if you want sound to come from your speakers. Also, press CTL + S to save, however you have to fiddle with the male save games to make saving work. Saving is also not necessary. I have had perfect [yet realistic] endings quite a bit and am amazed by the enjoyment [and even experience!] this game gives.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/alter-ego/184675/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/alter-ego/184675/1</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 27 Feb 2008 11:12:57 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-184675-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/alter-ego/184675.rss">Alter Ego</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
