<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Looking for someone who can make webclients</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/looking-for-someone-who-can-make-webclients/296068</link>
    <description>Hello people. I am looking for someone who really know what they are doing in converting regular client to webclient. Many people failed to do so including me. I am willing to &quot;donate&quot;(Since I can&#39;t buy things here I will call it donate) 5 dollars to who ever make the webclient working.

Post, private message me here or email me at administrator@ritzscape.net if you are interested.

P.S For prof that I pay, ask the dude Stupit. I hate him now because I gave him 5 bucks in paypal and he won&#39;t even give me the finished webclient...  If this is still illegal, I am sorry I did not know.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 19 Aug 2009 04:08:12 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Game Development</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/looking-for-someone-who-can-make-webclients/296068.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Looking for someone who can make webclients</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@ssolidd ssolidd]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/ssolidd">@ssolidd</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Hello people. I am looking for someone who really know what they are doing in converting regular client to webclient. Many people failed to do so including me. I am willing to “donate”(Since I can’t buy things here I will call it donate) 5 dollars to who ever make the webclient working.</p>
<p>Post, private message me here or email me at <a href="mailto:administrator@ritzscape.net">administrator@ritzscape.net</a> if you are interested.</p>
<p>P.S For prof that I pay, ask the dude Stupit. I hate him now because I gave him 5 bucks in paypal and he won’t even give me the finished webclient…  If this is still illegal, I am sorry I did not know.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/looking-for-someone-who-can-make-webclients/296068/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/looking-for-someone-who-can-make-webclients/296068/1</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 19 Aug 2009 04:08:12 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-296068-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/looking-for-someone-who-can-make-webclients/296068.rss">Looking for someone who can make webclients</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
