<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>[Delta] Talk to NPC and add items to sell?</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/delta-talk-to-npc-and-add-items-to-sell/464129</link>
    <description>Hello Moparscape friends, I usually strive to teach myself Java but I&#39;m just stuck with this problem. I&#39;m working on a system where people talk to an NPC, and give the NPC items and they set the price on how much they&#39;d like to sell it for. I&#39;m going to then have this price displayed on the website, with item pictures, and details, etc. Most of you probably know that I&#39;m pretty well capable of doing all of the stuff website sided, hence my name. Currently I have a players inventory saving to a SQL database, and I&#39;m displaying it on the website, so I&#39;m well capable of doing website sided stuff and a few Java things along those lines.

[size=10pt][b]tl;dr[/b][/size] - How do I have players give an NPC items with a pre-defined amount and have that item logged somewhere?

Thanks anyone who helps, I can&#39;t offer rewards but I&#39;m always here to help with Web Development!</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 14 Oct 2012 16:22:39 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/delta-talk-to-npc-and-add-items-to-sell/464129.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>[Delta] Talk to NPC and add items to sell?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@The_Web_Guy The Web Guy]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/the_web_guy">@The_Web_Guy</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Hello Moparscape friends, I usually strive to teach myself Java but I’m just stuck with this problem. I’m working on a system where people talk to an NPC, and give the NPC items and they set the price on how much they’d like to sell it for. I’m going to then have this price displayed on the website, with item pictures, and details, etc. Most of you probably know that I’m pretty well capable of doing all of the stuff website sided, hence my name. Currently I have a players inventory saving to a SQL database, and I’m displaying it on the website, so I’m well capable of doing website sided stuff and a few Java things along those lines.</p>
<p>[size=10pt]<span class="bbcode-b">tl;dr</span>[/size] - How do I have players give an NPC items with a pre-defined amount and have that item logged somewhere?</p>
<p>Thanks anyone who helps, I can’t offer rewards but I’m always here to help with Web Development!</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/delta-talk-to-npc-and-add-items-to-sell/464129/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/delta-talk-to-npc-and-add-items-to-sell/464129/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 14 Oct 2012 16:22:39 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-464129-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/delta-talk-to-npc-and-add-items-to-sell/464129.rss">[Delta] Talk to NPC and add items to sell?</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
