<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Playing to the best of your ability</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/playing-to-the-best-of-your-ability/551407</link>
    <description>Hello, I have a problem that I could really use a personal motivator/adviser for, so if you read this and decide you want to help, please pm me your skype so we can talk further, or leave suggestions in comments. Thanks.

So I am currently a sophomore in high school and am looking to play high level soccer, D1 in college to be specific. I am a very mental player which is good, and bad at the same time. When I am confident, I can do moves and take shots that I did not even know I was capable of doing in-game. In a game this past weekend I was as confident as I could be and hit an upper 90 from 35 yards out. But the downside to being mental, whenever I am not as confident (which is a major problem) I play soo bad. I am usually in-between my top game and my worst game because I can go into a game with all the confidence and have 1 bad touch and it just plummets. A few months ago I went to a college ID camp where college coaches come to watch and scout players. I played horribly there and looked awful in front of all of these high level college coaches. That is not good since I really want a scholarship for soccer to a D1 college. I am going to 2 more college ID camps this summer where the players will be as good as they get (in the United States lol). I need to look good there and I know I can stand out if my confidence level is high. I am looking for advice on how to take the mental aspect of the game out of my head so I can just play my game. Or if anyone has good advice on how to boost and maintain a high confidence level. I am also looking for some really good solo drills that will improve my first touch as well as my footwork (skill moves). If anyone has any advice on any of these please comment or pm me! Thanks!</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 18 May 2015 01:28:25 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>General Discussion</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/playing-to-the-best-of-your-ability/551407.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Playing to the best of your ability</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@asshole_rule asshole_rule]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/asshole_rule">@asshole_rule</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>well one problem is you’re very very slow. 4.7 is terrible</p>
<p>i don’t know shit about soccer, but you shouldn’t worry as you’re just a sophomore. You’ve got plenty of time to work on whatever you need. I suggest you reach out to coaches yourself though, through e-mails and what not. Don’t wait for them to come to you, you go to them first.</p>
<p>I’m a collegiate track and field athlete, and i speak from experience that my sophomore year in my sport didn’t mean shit. literally didn’t matter at all. NCAA coaches aren’t allowed to start officially recruiting you until after your junior season, so junior year is probably the most important, followed by senior year. Just keep practicing and getting better. I think that your confidence will go up as your skill level goes up.</p>
<p>As for your slow 40 time. Do resistance training and short speed work.</p>
<p>Ex: running as fast as you can up a hill for 30-100 meters/yards<br>
60 meter/yard repeats</p>
<p>I do workouts similar to this, obviously way more in depth though. these are just simple workouts you can do. I probably run around a high 4.2 or 4.3</p>
<p>you can change the distances to whatever you want, but obviously if you’re only timing yourself for 40 meters, running short distances will help the most.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/playing-to-the-best-of-your-ability/551407/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/playing-to-the-best-of-your-ability/551407/6</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 18 May 2015 01:28:25 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-551407-6</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/playing-to-the-best-of-your-ability/551407.rss">Playing to the best of your ability</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Playing to the best of your ability</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Mr.Draconian Mr.Draconian]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/mr.draconian">@Mr.Draconian</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Lets forgot about the difference between the words football and soccer because this isn’t the discussion here.</p>
<p>Being confident is important but being too confident and not taking your opponents seriously might strike you down and might be the reason of you not getting in a college.</p>
<p>I suggest bringing one of your closest friends to the camp to cheer you up and not let you be nervous thats what I most people do in big events.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/playing-to-the-best-of-your-ability/551407/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/playing-to-the-best-of-your-ability/551407/5</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 10 May 2015 15:49:16 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-551407-5</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/playing-to-the-best-of-your-ability/551407.rss">Playing to the best of your ability</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Playing to the best of your ability</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@b00mz1029 b00mz1029]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/b00mz1029">@b00mz1029</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote" data-post="2" data-topic="551411">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/janetfdoss/40/5_e05bb34c421432ee4d40de30c10af3e5.png" class="avatar">
</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Very nice discussion between you and the newbie soccer player. I love football. Once i was a good player too. One thing i noticed that you just guessed with a word soccer. Why is that? Why you can not name it soccer instead of football?</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I am most definitely not a “newbie” lol. I am a very good player but I have in-game confidence issues. I dont like the word “soccer” for the sole reason that American Football stole the name from real football</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/playing-to-the-best-of-your-ability/551407/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/playing-to-the-best-of-your-ability/551407/4</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 May 2015 21:29:19 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-551407-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/playing-to-the-best-of-your-ability/551407.rss">Playing to the best of your ability</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Playing to the best of your ability</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@b00mz1029 b00mz1029]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/b00mz1029">@b00mz1029</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“Welliton_inc, post:2, topic:551407”]The fact you call it “soccer” automatically means you are bad at football!</p>
<p>I kid.</p>
<p>But seriously, what position do you play? Also you don’t need to learn skill moves to be able to dribble. But if I’m going to be honest, and I am not lying, pure elite dribbling you are born with. No joke. It isn’t something you can really be taught. Shooting you can be taught, but dribbling is one of those things you are either born with or you are not. If you are a striker and you can’t dribble, you should rely on your shooting and aggression, having pace will help too. Look at Diego Costa for example, he isn’t the most technical of players but he is world class nonetheless.</p>
<p>Now regarding your mentality. Believe me, being confident helps ALOT. The confidence comes from being around people who believe in you too. You have to have inner strength in order to fight through the tough times. If you don’t believe in yourself how can you expect others to believe in you too? If you lose the ball in a game, don’t be sad just keep trying, play positively and positive things will occur.</p>
<p>Basiclly, you won’t improve your dribbling too much, your shots can improve by practice along with the rest of your game. Watch a lot of the top matches (La liga &amp; champions league) as much as you can and obviously, play as much as you can. If you give me a little more information on your position, age, height etc I can maybe help you further.</p>
<p>Note: my experience comes from being in a football team, and having a pro youth brother.[/quote]</p>
<p>Thanks for your input, and yes, even though I am American I agree “soccer” should be called football like everywhere else in the world names it :P. I am mainly a winger but I play some striker as well. My dribbling skills are just fine in my opinion. I want to better my moves like getting more fluent at stepovers and moving into more advanced moves. I am starting to become more fluent with my maradonas but I still need improvement. I am about 6 foot and I am 16 years old. I am pretty skinny but I can push players off of the ball as well as shield the ball using my body. My biggest physical strength is my speed. I run a 4.7 second 40 and have great endurance. My biggest weakness is my confidence I think :P. Some games I have it and others I do not. I need to find a way to have the same confidence level every game so I am a consistent player. With my club team and High School team my confidence is fairly high because I am sure I am better than most of the players I am up against, but whenever I go to high level college ID camps or other camps, I get nervous that I will not compete with the other players and whenever I think like that, it becomes reality, and I do not know how to stop those thoughts. Thanks for input!</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/playing-to-the-best-of-your-ability/551407/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/playing-to-the-best-of-your-ability/551407/3</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 May 2015 03:24:21 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-551407-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/playing-to-the-best-of-your-ability/551407.rss">Playing to the best of your ability</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Playing to the best of your ability</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Welliton_inc Welliton_inc]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/welliton_inc">@Welliton_inc</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>The fact you call it “soccer” automatically means you are bad at football!</p>
<p>I kid.</p>
<p>But seriously, what position do you play? Also you don’t need to learn skill moves to be able to dribble. But if I’m going to be honest, and I am not lying, pure elite dribbling you are born with. No joke. It isn’t something you can really be taught. Shooting you can be taught, but dribbling is one of those things you are either born with or you are not. If you are a striker and you can’t dribble, you should rely on your shooting and aggression, having pace will help too. Look at Diego Costa for example, he isn’t the most technical of players but he is world class nonetheless.</p>
<p>Now regarding your mentality. Believe me, being confident helps ALOT. The confidence comes from being around people who believe in you too. You have to have inner strength in order to fight through the tough times. If you don’t believe in yourself how can you expect others to believe in you too? If you lose the ball in a game, don’t be sad just keep trying, play positively and positive things will occur.</p>
<p>Basiclly, you won’t improve your dribbling too much, your shots can improve by practice along with the rest of your game. Watch a lot of the top matches (La liga &amp; champions league) as much as you can and obviously, play as much as you can. If you give me a little more information on your position, age, height etc I can maybe help you further.</p>
<p>Note: my experience comes from being in a football team, and having a pro youth brother.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/playing-to-the-best-of-your-ability/551407/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/playing-to-the-best-of-your-ability/551407/2</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 May 2015 00:56:47 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-551407-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/playing-to-the-best-of-your-ability/551407.rss">Playing to the best of your ability</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Playing to the best of your ability</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@b00mz1029 b00mz1029]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/b00mz1029">@b00mz1029</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Hello, I have a problem that I could really use a personal motivator/adviser for, so if you read this and decide you want to help, please pm me your skype so we can talk further, or leave suggestions in comments. Thanks.</p>
<p>So I am currently a sophomore in high school and am looking to play high level soccer, D1 in college to be specific. I am a very mental player which is good, and bad at the same time. When I am confident, I can do moves and take shots that I did not even know I was capable of doing in-game. In a game this past weekend I was as confident as I could be and hit an upper 90 from 35 yards out. But the downside to being mental, whenever I am not as confident (which is a major problem) I play soo bad. I am usually in-between my top game and my worst game because I can go into a game with all the confidence and have 1 bad touch and it just plummets. A few months ago I went to a college ID camp where college coaches come to watch and scout players. I played horribly there and looked awful in front of all of these high level college coaches. That is not good since I really want a scholarship for soccer to a D1 college. I am going to 2 more college ID camps this summer where the players will be as good as they get (in the United States lol). I need to look good there and I know I can stand out if my confidence level is high. I am looking for advice on how to take the mental aspect of the game out of my head so I can just play my game. Or if anyone has good advice on how to boost and maintain a high confidence level. I am also looking for some really good solo drills that will improve my first touch as well as my footwork (skill moves). If anyone has any advice on any of these please comment or pm me! Thanks!</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/playing-to-the-best-of-your-ability/551407/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/playing-to-the-best-of-your-ability/551407/1</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 07 May 2015 23:48:49 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-551407-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/playing-to-the-best-of-your-ability/551407.rss">Playing to the best of your ability</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
