<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>RuneFallen - PI</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/runefallen-pi/552725</link>
    <description>[center][size=24pt][b]RuneFallen[/b][/size][/center]

RuneFallen is a new upcoming server that is in development. The server will be economy with some cool features. There will be some custom easy quests that will be available to do. The quests will be easy to do but you will have to earn the items since I will disable shops. Only shops that will be needed will be accessible while your quest adventures begin. There will be lots more features within the server to bring back oldschool times and try to make it lots of fun. The home is Entrana and there will be some things at home that will make it feel like home.

I currently added a tutorial island where you can speak to a guy and he will teach you a few things. You can then choose whether to teleport to home or training area. You will then receive your starter items and the starter items will be the items you need to start out whether you&#39;re a skiller or want to pvm. I&#39;m also going to remove rock crabs for training and I&#39;m going to be adding a custom training area where you can train between different monsters. I only added this which will make it easier for when you start out. There will be low level custom training area and I might add a high level custom training area. All normal dungeons will stay where they are currently.

While I&#39;m posting this I am working on cleaning some stuff up like the quest tabs and stuff like that. Just to make it feel a lot more cleaner and there won&#39;t be as many things on the quest tab. I&#39;m going to be adding Iron Man feature once the server reaches a good amount of players and I will also be adding an achievement diary so that players will also receive awards for they are achieving on the server.


I will add some more media as soon as I finish cleaning some stuff up.
[spoiler][/spoiler] 

Thank you for taking your time to read this and I hope you have a great time watching this develop.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 31 Jul 2015 18:31:19 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/runefallen-pi/552725.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>RuneFallen - PI</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Just_Creative Just Creative]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/just_creative">@Just_Creative</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[center][size=24pt]<span class="bbcode-b">RuneFallen</span>[/size][/center]</p>
<p>RuneFallen is a new upcoming server that is in development. The server will be economy with some cool features. There will be some custom easy quests that will be available to do. The quests will be easy to do but you will have to earn the items since I will disable shops. Only shops that will be needed will be accessible while your quest adventures begin. There will be lots more features within the server to bring back oldschool times and try to make it lots of fun. The home is Entrana and there will be some things at home that will make it feel like home.</p>
<p>I currently added a tutorial island where you can speak to a guy and he will teach you a few things. You can then choose whether to teleport to home or training area. You will then receive your starter items and the starter items will be the items you need to start out whether you’re a skiller or want to pvm. I’m also going to remove rock crabs for training and I’m going to be adding a custom training area where you can train between different monsters. I only added this which will make it easier for when you start out. There will be low level custom training area and I might add a high level custom training area. All normal dungeons will stay where they are currently.</p>
<p>While I’m posting this I am working on cleaning some stuff up like the quest tabs and stuff like that. Just to make it feel a lot more cleaner and there won’t be as many things on the quest tab. I’m going to be adding Iron Man feature once the server reaches a good amount of players and I will also be adding an achievement diary so that players will also receive awards for they are achieving on the server.</p>
<p>I will add some more media as soon as I finish cleaning some stuff up.<br>
[spoiler][/spoiler]</p>
<p>Thank you for taking your time to read this and I hope you have a great time watching this develop.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/runefallen-pi/552725/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/runefallen-pi/552725/1</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 31 Jul 2015 18:31:19 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-552725-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/runefallen-pi/552725.rss">RuneFallen - PI</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
