<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Mirage Source --Not Rsps!--</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/mirage-source-not-rsps/412060</link>
    <description>                                                                [b]MIRAGE SOURCE - OPEN SOURCE MMORPG MAKER[/b]



Hello. Have you ever wanted to make your own mmorpg? And be able to claim full credits on it? From wanting to create a simple game to play with your friends, to dreams of making a game with real money income. Mirage Source is the place to start.


What is Mirage Source?
Well due to the fact, that another off breed of mirage summoned it up better than i could have explained, ill quote him. ;)
&lt;blockquote&gt;Mirage&#39;s original form was a small game called &#39;Final Fantasy Online&#39; created by a bloke called Consty. Back then it was a simple server and client system with a GDI graphics engine. It had maps, npcs and movement. That was about it. Although it wasn&#39;t very complicated this basic structure stuck and 2 years later Consty came out with a brand-new game - Mirage Online! This little project was built using the much more powerful DirectDraw system which was available in DirectX7. This game enjoyed moderate popularity before eventually being closed and sold to an interested player called Shannara. Shannara continued to develop the game and at the same time licensed a copy of the source code to yet another player called Kael who used this to release a closed-source engine called &#39;Player Worlds&#39;. This was a huge milestone. This engine could be used to create your very own online RPG game with absolutely no prior experience or knowledge. People flocked to it. For a long while Mirage and Player Worlds lived in peace - that is until PC appeared on the scene.

Into the public domain
PC was what you call a &#39;script kiddie&#39; but he identified himself as a &#39;cyber terrorist&#39;. Due to the nature of Player Worlds anyone who used it had a copy of the compiled engine. There were a few decompilers out at the time, however, which allowed you to revert the compiled project back into it&#39;s original state - source code and all! PC released this to everyone around both the Mirage and Player Worlds communities and threw everything into chaos. In the aftermath of this event Shannara decided to clean his hands of the entire thing and released Mirage with a notice that explicitly placed Mirage in the public domain. Anyone and everyone could now grab a copy of the source code and do with it what they pleased. Surprisingly this did not kill Mirage. Although many people took the source code and went off to do their own thing with it, Mirage continued on as a game and Shannara created a new community call Mirage Source which was built around people using the source code to develop their own games and engines.&lt;/blockquote&gt;
And his parting letter can be found here: *
Soo that&#39;s how mirage started, and for about 3-4 years boy did it thrive. Like &quot;Robin&quot; Said, people flocked to it before it was open source, imagine how many extra people came when it was open! Well after the years, Mirage slowly died. And a new mmorpg maker was born from it known as Eclipse Origins. That is where i started. I found eclipse about 3 years ago. While playing runescape xD. I started my major programming there, &quot;I dont consider rs-ps&#39;s real programming.&quot; And after awhile Origins became old. And i wanted to start with the mother &quot;Mirage&quot;. I went back to the forums, and fell in love with mirage. For about a month i fiddled with the engine, and it was pure harmony. Now even though i loved how basic and young the engine felt. I knew that i would never use it for my game engine in the &quot;Youngish&quot; state that it was in, and no one else would. And thats when i found RpgCreation. It started on a mid-day in late summer. I was just playing around on touchofdeathforum&#39;s shoutbox, when one of my friend&#39;s suggested the new open source engine &quot;Mirage Creations&quot;. And i went there straight away. And enjoyed my time for about a week. When i met another young fellow named &quot;Kris&quot;. Me and kris talked, with another Moderator named &quot;Genusis&quot;. And came up with the idea to revive Mirage Source. And we did. We gained permissions from owner to use the source code and name. And headed out from there. After about a week. I had mirage source cleaned up a bit. And was able to release the newest version in over 2 years! Mirage Source 3.9! Or known by some for a strange reason as Mirage Source 4.1! Anyways. This is why i am here. I am inviting you to be a part of a ever growing Open source MMorpg maker! Come join us and start your adventure into Mirage Source!
Simply click the link below, register. And your already there!

*</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 25 Aug 2011 23:41:04 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>General Programming</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/mirage-source-not-rsps/412060.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Mirage Source --Not Rsps!--</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@deathschaos9 DeathsChaos9]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/deathschaos9">@deathschaos9</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote" data-post="3" data-topic="412060">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 noobs are ftw:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>its an advertisement i think</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I agree.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/mirage-source-not-rsps/412060/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/mirage-source-not-rsps/412060/4</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 25 Aug 2011 23:41:04 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-412060-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/mirage-source-not-rsps/412060.rss">Mirage Source --Not Rsps!--</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Mirage Source --Not Rsps!--</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@noobs_are_ftw noobs are ftw]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/noobs_are_ftw">@noobs_are_ftw</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>its an advertisement i think</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/mirage-source-not-rsps/412060/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/mirage-source-not-rsps/412060/3</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 25 Aug 2011 23:30:18 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-412060-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/mirage-source-not-rsps/412060.rss">Mirage Source --Not Rsps!--</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Mirage Source --Not Rsps!--</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@ziplock ziplock]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/ziplock">@ziplock</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Sketchy. What is this? Some shitty mmorpg maker?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/mirage-source-not-rsps/412060/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/mirage-source-not-rsps/412060/2</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 25 Aug 2011 23:21:42 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-412060-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/mirage-source-not-rsps/412060.rss">Mirage Source --Not Rsps!--</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Mirage Source --Not Rsps!--</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@johnl17 johnl17]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/johnl17">@johnl17</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <pre><code>                                                            [b]MIRAGE SOURCE - OPEN SOURCE MMORPG MAKER[/b]
</code></pre>
<p>Hello. Have you ever wanted to make your own mmorpg? And be able to claim full credits on it? From wanting to create a simple game to play with your friends, to dreams of making a game with real money income. Mirage Source is the place to start.</p>
<p>What is Mirage Source?<br>
Well due to the fact, that another off breed of mirage summoned it up better than i could have explained, ill quote him. <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/wink.png?v=5" title=":wink:" class="emoji" alt=":wink:"></p>
<blockquote>Mirage's original form was a small game called 'Final Fantasy Online' created by a bloke called Consty. Back then it was a simple server and client system with a GDI graphics engine. It had maps, npcs and movement. That was about it. Although it wasn't very complicated this basic structure stuck and 2 years later Consty came out with a brand-new game - Mirage Online! This little project was built using the much more powerful DirectDraw system which was available in DirectX7. This game enjoyed moderate popularity before eventually being closed and sold to an interested player called Shannara. Shannara continued to develop the game and at the same time licensed a copy of the source code to yet another player called Kael who used this to release a closed-source engine called 'Player Worlds'. This was a huge milestone. This engine could be used to create your very own online RPG game with absolutely no prior experience or knowledge. People flocked to it. For a long while Mirage and Player Worlds lived in peace - that is until PC appeared on the scene.
<p>Into the public domain<br>
PC was what you call a ‘script kiddie’ but he identified himself as a ‘cyber terrorist’. Due to the nature of Player Worlds anyone who used it had a copy of the compiled engine. There were a few decompilers out at the time, however, which allowed you to revert the compiled project back into it’s original state - source code and all! PC released this to everyone around both the Mirage and Player Worlds communities and threw everything into chaos. In the aftermath of this event Shannara decided to clean his hands of the entire thing and released Mirage with a notice that explicitly placed Mirage in the public domain. Anyone and everyone could now grab a copy of the source code and do with it what they pleased. Surprisingly this did not kill Mirage. Although many people took the source code and went off to do their own thing with it, Mirage continued on as a game and Shannara created a new community call Mirage Source which was built around people using the source code to develop their own games and engines.</p>
</blockquote><br>
And his parting letter can be found here: *<br>
Soo that’s how mirage started, and for about 3-4 years boy did it thrive. Like “Robin” Said, people flocked to it before it was open source, imagine how many extra people came when it was open! Well after the years, Mirage slowly died. And a new mmorpg maker was born from it known as Eclipse Origins. That is where i started. I found eclipse about 3 years ago. While playing runescape xD. I started my major programming there, “I dont consider rs-ps’s real programming.” And after awhile Origins became old. And i wanted to start with the mother “Mirage”. I went back to the forums, and fell in love with mirage. For about a month i fiddled with the engine, and it was pure harmony. Now even though i loved how basic and young the engine felt. I knew that i would never use it for my game engine in the “Youngish” state that it was in, and no one else would. And thats when i found RpgCreation. It started on a mid-day in late summer. I was just playing around on touchofdeathforum’s shoutbox, when one of my friend’s suggested the new open source engine “Mirage Creations”. And i went there straight away. And enjoyed my time for about a week. When i met another young fellow named “Kris”. Me and kris talked, with another Moderator named “Genusis”. And came up with the idea to revive Mirage Source. And we did. We gained permissions from owner to use the source code and name. And headed out from there. After about a week. I had mirage source cleaned up a bit. And was able to release the newest version in over 2 years! Mirage Source 3.9! Or known by some for a strange reason as Mirage Source 4.1! Anyways. This is why i am here. I am inviting you to be a part of a ever growing Open source MMorpg maker! Come join us and start your adventure into Mirage Source!<br>
Simply click the link below, register. And your already there!
<ul>
<li>
</li>
</ul>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/mirage-source-not-rsps/412060/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/mirage-source-not-rsps/412060/1</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 25 Aug 2011 23:16:33 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-412060-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/mirage-source-not-rsps/412060.rss">Mirage Source --Not Rsps!--</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
