<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Near-Blank PI and a 508/525?</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/near-blank-pi-and-a-508-525/519355</link>
    <description>What I want in the PI:
-No NPC&#39;s in the autospawn.cfg
-No Objects spawned via server sided
-Full item.cfg for a 317/377 cache
-Just combat skills added (This isn&#39;t needed, but I&#39;d like to have the least amount of skills in as possible, I don&#39;t know how to write the combat methods so that&#39;s why I want them in still).
-No commands (they can be added by me :P)
-No dialogues
-No Action buttons (aside from logging out)
-No clicking buttons (^)
And Just generally clean. Netty would be a nice touch, and dupe fixes, but hey, I can&#39;t ask for the world right?
On top of that, I&#39;d like to get a 317 client with the 317 or 377 cache that can actually be edited, the cache I normally get is corrupted for some reason.

[hr][hr][hr]

I just want a 508 or 525 that&#39;s completely working. No, I don&#39;t want it to be 100% done. I want one that if I wanted, I could change the IP and some names, jar it, and it&#39;d be online fine.
I&#39;ve tried to download some in the past, but they didn&#39;t like me and I didn&#39;t fix em.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 15 May 2013 22:46:10 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>General Discussion</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/near-blank-pi-and-a-508-525/519355.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Near-Blank PI and a 508/525?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@sk8rdude461 sk8rdude461]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/sk8rdude461">@sk8rdude461</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>What I want in the PI:<br>
-No NPC’s in the autospawn.cfg<br>
-No Objects spawned via server sided<br>
-Full item.cfg for a 317/377 cache<br>
-Just combat skills added (This isn’t needed, but I’d like to have the least amount of skills in as possible, I don’t know how to write the combat methods so that’s why I want them in still).<br>
-No commands (they can be added by me :P)<br>
-No dialogues<br>
-No Action buttons (aside from logging out)<br>
-No clicking buttons (^)<br>
And Just generally clean. Netty would be a nice touch, and dupe fixes, but hey, I can’t ask for the world right?<br>
On top of that, I’d like to get a 317 client with the 317 or 377 cache that can actually be edited, the cache I normally get is corrupted for some reason.</p>
<p>[hr][hr][hr]</p>
<p>I just want a 508 or 525 that’s completely working. No, I don’t want it to be 100% done. I want one that if I wanted, I could change the IP and some names, jar it, and it’d be online fine.<br>
I’ve tried to download some in the past, but they didn’t like me and I didn’t fix em.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/near-blank-pi-and-a-508-525/519355/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/near-blank-pi-and-a-508-525/519355/1</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2013 22:46:10 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-519355-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/near-blank-pi-and-a-508-525/519355.rss">Near-Blank PI and a 508/525?</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
