<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Metal Gear Solid 4: My views *Spoilers*</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/metal-gear-solid-4-my-views-spoilers/212289</link>
    <description>Now, i&#39;ve just finished the game, the final cutscene is well over an hour long in which what you expect, does not happen. Snake does [b]not[/b] die, Big Boss shows up again, explaining how the big boss that was killed and in the other mgs&#39;s was not him, it was solidus the perfect clone of him, snakes brother. Big Boss explains how the new foxdie in his body is stopping the old foxdie which they originally thought would kill snake is now helping him keep alive. 

The end fight between liquid/ocelot and snake is epic, it starts off with a cutscene of them fighting with liquid beating snake, but the two start headbutting each other and allsorts, end up fall against each other holding one another up, they both pick up a syringe of nanobodies which makes them temporily stronger and inject each other with them, basically helping each other. They obviously don&#39;t want to do it, but its something they have to do, from then on you are fighting with just fists on top of a ship in a cutscene type way but you are controlling it, the harder you fight, the more both of you become slow and beat up, it ends in snake ending up beating liquid, blah blah, a few cutscenes go on about the other players, which are all good ones. Then it goes to snake, in a grave yard, he puts the gun in his mouth and seems like he shoots himself. It goes to another cutscene of otacon and sunny talking about snake, sunny asking if snake will come back otacon tells her that he is going away, to get better, the game goes to credits then after a few seconds it and goes to a cutscene with snake sweating and being interupted by big boss which then goes on above as said in the first paragraph. 

It is an epic game, it is better than any film i&#39;ve watched, its better than any game i&#39;ve played. Its more than a game, what makes it even more sad though, is that its the last made by kojima, the guy behind these games. I really hope they leave it at this if they really plan to not make anymore metal gear [b]solid[/b] games, because i don&#39;t want the series being ruined. 

I don&#39;t want to tell you anymore as i really want people to play this game for themselfs, its nothing reading about it, go play it, if not for the gameplay, but for the story.
Newcomers won&#39;t be lost either, the game explains pretty much all the rest of the story for you too.

[b]Plus[/b]
It may seem like i completed it very fast, but listen first. I did play this game [b]none[/b] stop since i got it, the game just sucks you in.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2008 06:05:51 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Games</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/metal-gear-solid-4-my-views-spoilers/212289.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Metal Gear Solid 4: My views *Spoilers*</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@tL tL]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/tl">@tL</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Yeah, but the next one won’t contain raiden in it, theres something that happens at the end with him. (good thing)</p>
<p>Oh my god, seriously i cannot stop playing this game. Its such a shame that this won’t be experienced by more than ps3 users, its such a great game. I know it seems weird a playstation 3 owner saying that the game should be multiplatform because its a fact us ps3 owners like to cling onto our exclusives due to the shortage of them at the moment, (which <em>should</em> change if plans go ahead).</p>
<p>Once you have completed it the first time around you can load your completed game up again to find out you keep all the stuff you have plus some extra unlocked stuff you can buy or already have on the second time around, ie you can change into snakes civilian clothes and loads more stuff. The more you play it the more you find, i started a new game 3 hours after i completed it the first time around, i really am sad that this is the last one developers by Hideo kojima, although lets hope if there is anymore then they won’t loose that same feel mgs has always had.</p>
<p>The final fight between liquid/ocelot and snake, this is after snake has been pretty much microwaved and beated up loads and after everything was over. Liquid found his body and took him to where they are there to fight etc.</p>
<p>Liquid gives him a serious beating in the first half in which if like me at the time thought snake was going to die i thought this is where he died, by liquid beating him to death.<br>
<a href="http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=oQP56mvBrgE&amp;feature=related" class="onebox" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=oQP56mvBrgE&amp;feature=related</a><br>
Where it ends it goes into gameplay/cutscene type thing.<br>
Epic part of the game.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/metal-gear-solid-4-my-views-spoilers/212289/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/metal-gear-solid-4-my-views-spoilers/212289/5</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2008 06:05:51 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-212289-5</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/metal-gear-solid-4-my-views-spoilers/212289.rss">Metal Gear Solid 4: My views *Spoilers*</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Metal Gear Solid 4: My views *Spoilers*</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@sanga282 sanga282]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/sanga282">@sanga282</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote no-group quote-modified" data-post="1" data-topic="212289">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/thug-life/40/5_6bca9977b612b7aeef77ba1ec1cd67b3.png" class="avatar"> Thug-life:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>I really hope they leave it at this if they really plan to not make anymore metal gear <span class="bbcode-b">solid</span> games, because i don’t want the series being ruined.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Well Konami have said that MGS 4 is not the last Metal Gear game but they never said not the MGS game so it probably will be the last MGS but there will be more MG</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/metal-gear-solid-4-my-views-spoilers/212289/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/metal-gear-solid-4-my-views-spoilers/212289/4</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 14 Jun 2008 13:01:30 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-212289-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/metal-gear-solid-4-my-views-spoilers/212289.rss">Metal Gear Solid 4: My views *Spoilers*</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Metal Gear Solid 4: My views *Spoilers*</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@ThAt0n36Uy Elijah]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/that0n36uy">@ThAt0n36Uy</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>It isn’t possible for it to come out on the 360.</p>
<p>It sounds awesome Thug-life. I’m probably going to go out and buy a PS3 in a few days to play this.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/metal-gear-solid-4-my-views-spoilers/212289/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/metal-gear-solid-4-my-views-spoilers/212289/3</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 14 Jun 2008 11:23:29 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-212289-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/metal-gear-solid-4-my-views-spoilers/212289.rss">Metal Gear Solid 4: My views *Spoilers*</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Metal Gear Solid 4: My views *Spoilers*</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@XxKanexX Kane.]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/xxkanexx">@XxKanexX</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“Thug-life, post:1, topic:212289”]<span class="bbcode-b">Plus</span><br>
It may seem like i completed it very fast, but listen first. I did play this game <span class="bbcode-b">none</span> stop since i got it, the game just sucks you in.<br>
<span class="bbcode-b">PlusPlus</span><br>
I’m thinking of getting a small Metal Gear solid tatoo on the top of my bicep, i know someone who can do it for me.<br>
<span class="bbcode-b">PlusPlusPlus</span>I havn’t explained 90% of this game[/quote]<br>
You can right ps, you know.<br>
This game sounds amazing, as you put it.</p>
<p>I’ve never played any on the series, nor do i own a PS3, so i don’t think i’ll be playing it any time soon.<br>
Not coming out on 360?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/metal-gear-solid-4-my-views-spoilers/212289/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/metal-gear-solid-4-my-views-spoilers/212289/2</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 14 Jun 2008 11:06:47 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-212289-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/metal-gear-solid-4-my-views-spoilers/212289.rss">Metal Gear Solid 4: My views *Spoilers*</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Metal Gear Solid 4: My views *Spoilers*</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@tL tL]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/tl">@tL</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Now, i’ve just finished the game, the final cutscene is well over an hour long in which what you expect, does not happen. Snake does <span class="bbcode-b">not</span> die, Big Boss shows up again, explaining how the big boss that was killed and in the other mgs’s was not him, it was solidus the perfect clone of him, snakes brother. Big Boss explains how the new foxdie in his body is stopping the old foxdie which they originally thought would kill snake is now helping him keep alive.</p>
<p>The end fight between liquid/ocelot and snake is epic, it starts off with a cutscene of them fighting with liquid beating snake, but the two start headbutting each other and allsorts, end up fall against each other holding one another up, they both pick up a syringe of nanobodies which makes them temporily stronger and inject each other with them, basically helping each other. They obviously don’t want to do it, but its something they have to do, from then on you are fighting with just fists on top of a ship in a cutscene type way but you are controlling it, the harder you fight, the more both of you become slow and beat up, it ends in snake ending up beating liquid, blah blah, a few cutscenes go on about the other players, which are all good ones. Then it goes to snake, in a grave yard, he puts the gun in his mouth and seems like he shoots himself. It goes to another cutscene of otacon and sunny talking about snake, sunny asking if snake will come back otacon tells her that he is going away, to get better, the game goes to credits then after a few seconds it and goes to a cutscene with snake sweating and being interupted by big boss which then goes on above as said in the first paragraph.</p>
<p>It is an epic game, it is better than any film i’ve watched, its better than any game i’ve played. Its more than a game, what makes it even more sad though, is that its the last made by kojima, the guy behind these games. I really hope they leave it at this if they really plan to not make anymore metal gear <span class="bbcode-b">solid</span> games, because i don’t want the series being ruined.</p>
<p>I don’t want to tell you anymore as i really want people to play this game for themselfs, its nothing reading about it, go play it, if not for the gameplay, but for the story.<br>
Newcomers won’t be lost either, the game explains pretty much all the rest of the story for you too.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Plus</span><br>
It may seem like i completed it very fast, but listen first. I did play this game <span class="bbcode-b">none</span> stop since i got it, the game just sucks you in.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/metal-gear-solid-4-my-views-spoilers/212289/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/metal-gear-solid-4-my-views-spoilers/212289/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 14 Jun 2008 04:48:16 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-212289-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/metal-gear-solid-4-my-views-spoilers/212289.rss">Metal Gear Solid 4: My views *Spoilers*</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
