<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>~*Frosty LTD*~</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/frosty-ltd/320385</link>
    <description>[URL=http://www.mybannermaker.com][IMG]http://mbmfiles.com/Dec2009/091218-JwS9NBj2dy8n.gif[/img][/URL]


Well To began with, my names Goose and I&#39;m trying to create one of the top [317] servers out there. The thing is I can only do so much.

So This is why i decided to get a group of individuals who are good at what they do, and try and help me create this server. I currently have a paypal with money on it for a VPS but im waiting until i have professionals in the fields that i am looking for. I want this server to be one of the servers to talk about online as one of the best. Some of the things that happen to the last server i had was it didn&#39;t work because of the lack of maturity and commitment. Thats why i want to make a team of people that will be commited, mature and pollite.

I havent decided on a source yet but that will be figuered out once i assemble the team, like I said it will be whatever the team favors. We will also have a website and a vps slot and an active donation system.

My experience in servers is Mediocore. I have messed around with a few projects and have also owned a prety successful server known as Hellzpkerz which consisted of atleast 50-60 players a day. Although this server lasted as long as it did, im not satisfied with the outcome.

Ok, enough about me and my past experiences.

As i said before i am looking for Mature Polite and Commited individuals. Don&#39;t bother posting an application if you are not willing to work, have bad manners and have no experience what so ever in any of the team possitions.
							
							Team Possitions


							Coder/Server Programmer
Will be programming the server. You will need to be experienced in programming at least 2 years. Also, you need to be reliable and can work with deadlines. Also you have to be very good at what you do as stated before. You have to be ever to code alot of things, as i plan on added alot of things to server, so be ready to code.

							Website Coder/Maker
Will be incharge of the website. You will need alot of experience in HTML and More. I&#39;m not that experienced in website developmet so i will need to be able to rely on you. And you have to be able to work on daily baisis in the beginning of making it.

							Client Designer/maker
Will be making a client that is suitible for our needs. This person has to be extremely good at what there doing. I want this person to have atleast 2 years of experience as well.


ok well thats about it for now..
here is application print.
Application:

-Name:
-Age:
-Way to contact u preferably Msn?:
-Team Possition:
-Proof of experience:
-A little information about you:
-Why should i chose you?:

looking forward to meeting people for the team thanks 
~Rodney</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 19 Dec 2009 01:51:29 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/frosty-ltd/320385.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>~*Frosty LTD*~</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@str0wnzyou str0wnzyou]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/str0wnzyou">@str0wnzyou</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p><a href="http://www.mybannermaker.com" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener"><img src="http://mbmfiles.com/Dec2009/091218-JwS9NBj2dy8n.gif" alt width="" height=""></a></p>
<p>Well To began with, my names Goose and I’m trying to create one of the top [317] servers out there. The thing is I can only do so much.</p>
<p>So This is why i decided to get a group of individuals who are good at what they do, and try and help me create this server. I currently have a paypal with money on it for a VPS but im waiting until i have professionals in the fields that i am looking for. I want this server to be one of the servers to talk about online as one of the best. Some of the things that happen to the last server i had was it didn’t work because of the lack of maturity and commitment. Thats why i want to make a team of people that will be commited, mature and pollite.</p>
<p>I havent decided on a source yet but that will be figuered out once i assemble the team, like I said it will be whatever the team favors. We will also have a website and a vps slot and an active donation system.</p>
<p>My experience in servers is Mediocore. I have messed around with a few projects and have also owned a prety successful server known as Hellzpkerz which consisted of atleast 50-60 players a day. Although this server lasted as long as it did, im not satisfied with the outcome.</p>
<p>Ok, enough about me and my past experiences.</p>
<p>As i said before i am looking for Mature Polite and Commited individuals. Don’t bother posting an application if you are not willing to work, have bad manners and have no experience what so ever in any of the team possitions.</p>
<pre><code>						Team Possitions


						Coder/Server Programmer
</code></pre>
<p>Will be programming the server. You will need to be experienced in programming at least 2 years. Also, you need to be reliable and can work with deadlines. Also you have to be very good at what you do as stated before. You have to be ever to code alot of things, as i plan on added alot of things to server, so be ready to code.</p>
<pre><code>						Website Coder/Maker
</code></pre>
<p>Will be incharge of the website. You will need alot of experience in HTML and More. I’m not that experienced in website developmet so i will need to be able to rely on you. And you have to be able to work on daily baisis in the beginning of making it.</p>
<pre><code>						Client Designer/maker
</code></pre>
<p>Will be making a client that is suitible for our needs. This person has to be extremely good at what there doing. I want this person to have atleast 2 years of experience as well.</p>
<p>ok well thats about it for now…<br>
here is application print.<br>
Application:</p>
<p>-Name:<br>
-Age:<br>
-Way to contact u preferably Msn?:<br>
-Team Possition:<br>
-Proof of experience:<br>
-A little information about you:<br>
-Why should i chose you?:</p>
<p>looking forward to meeting people for the team thanks<br>
~Rodney</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/frosty-ltd/320385/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/frosty-ltd/320385/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 19 Dec 2009 01:51:29 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-320385-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/frosty-ltd/320385.rss">~*Frosty LTD*~</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
