<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Ultimate SCAR Beginners Guide For Complete Noobs</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/ultimate-scar-beginners-guide-for-complete-noobs/4668</link>
    <description>I made this a while back, and decided I&#39;d contribute here a bit.  I didn&#39;t know where to put it since you can&#39;t make a new topic is the tutorial forum, so I would like it if someone moved it there.  Thanks.

-------------------------

[u][b]Syntax[/b][/u]

Ok, to start off, to make a script, you would make a name, right?  The name HAS to have no spaces, so if you open up scar, you will most likely see this:

[img]http://img328.imageshack.us/img328/717/beginscar0xb.png[/img]

Where it says program New;, you should make it say something relevent to what your doing, so if your making an autominer, go like this:

[code]Program Autominer;[/code]

It has to have a semicolon after it, or else you will get an error.  Moving on.

-------------------------------------

[u][b]Includes[/u][/b]

There are many different includes for SCAR, some of which are very helpful, such as Si.scar, and Squig.txt.  Go to File &gt; Download Includes and get all of them.  Read through a couple of them, they will be in your includes folder which is most likely in C:\Program Files\SCAR 2.03\Includes.   As you read through them you might notice things like:

[code]Function GetStat(stat : String; top : Boolean) : Integer;[/code]

Don&#39;t let how complicated that looks fool you, its actually very simple.  See the Function is nothing, it just tells SCAR what that is, in this case its a function.  The Getstat is what you need to worry about.  Theres most likely instructions on what each function/procedure does and how to use them.  With Getstat this is what it says:

[code]{^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^          GETSTAT         ^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^}
{Opens the stat panel If needed. The variable stat is the name Of the
stat your wanting To retrieve And If top is true it will get the current
stat, If its false it will get the max stat}
{^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^}

Function GetStat(stat : String; top : Boolean) : Integer;[/code]

Followed by a BUNCH of code (Thats a function in Squig.txt).  All you would have to say in YOUR script would be something like this:

[code]Getstat(&lt;the stats name&gt;, true)[/code]

And that will get the current number of the stat you specified.

In other things, their called PROCEDURES.  While looking through an include you might find a procedure something like this for example:

[code]{^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^          OPENSTATS         ^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^}
{Opens the stat panel}
{^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^}

Procedure OpenStats;[/code]

Thats simple.  In your main script just type OpenStats; and that would open the stats tab if you were using this particular include.

Ok, I have explained to you just now what in[u]cludes do and how to understand them, but right now I will teach you how to include them in your script.  Its simple actually, right under your program Autominer; or whatever it is, put this:

[code]{.include &lt;include name&gt;}  (ex. {.include Si.scar} )[/code]

Simple right?  Moving on.

------------------------------

[u][b]Variables[/b][/u]

The next thing you would have to do is declare the variables you are going to use.  I know that sounds confusing, but I just made it sound like that for now.  I will explain it.  Variables like x and y hold numbers, and such.  Example:

[code]Findcolor(x,y,&lt;color&gt;,coordinates)[/code]

The x and y in there will save the coordinates of where it found the color.

You declare variables like this:

[code]Var x,y[/code]

But thats not all.  You can declare certain variables as Booleans, Strings, or Integers.  Booleans meaning true or false.  Strings meaning words.  Integers meaning things like x and y.

To declare x and y as Integers you would have to go like this:

[img]http://img397.imageshack.us/img397/592/var5fj.png[/img]

And that would declare them as integers.  You put all that under your include.  Moving on.

----------------------

[u][b]Constants[/b][/u]

Constants do not NEED to be used, but they are good for giving the user of the script flexability on what they are doing.  Constants are things that stay the same throughout the whole script.  A scripter might do something like this:

[img]http://img328.imageshack.us/img328/5893/const3dh.png[/img]

You get colors by using the dibber in scar and putting it on the color and clicking, that should give you a bunch of numbers in the debug box below the main script.

You declare Constants by going like this:

[code]Const[/code]

And to add things to the Const you would make things related to your script like this:

[code]MonsterColor=453344;[/code]

You have to have a = and then the value (number, string, boolean) and then a semicolon.  Why is this useful in a script you ask?  For a user to put in the color of the monster, it would change the value in the big script itself, example:

[code]Findcolor(x,y,MonsterColor,&lt;coordinates&gt;)[/code]

Moving on.

-------------------

[u][b]Procedures[/u][/b]

In your script you have to name your procedures to something relevant to what your doing.  Since you&#39;ve got your script set up up there, you now need to start scripting the actual script.  This is what you do:

[code]Procedure name;  (ex. Procedure mine; )
Begin[/code]

[img]http://img397.imageshack.us/img397/593/proc7ka.png[/img]

It has to have a semicolon, and after the procedure name, you have to have a Begin because that will tell the script that the procedure will then begin.

A procedure always has to end with this:

[code]End;[/code]

The semicolon tells the script that your ending the PROCEDURE.

Moving on.

-----------------------

[u][b]Making The Script Do What You Want[/b][/u]

There are THOUSANDS of things that you can do, I will only name a couple basic things.

[u][i]FINDCOLOR[/u][/i]

[code]Findcolor(x,y,color,cords,cords,cords,cords)[/code]

This is how that works.  You put Findcolor(x,y, in your script, the x,y will save the coordinates of where it found the color, then the color of the thing your looking for, then you put coordinates searching in a box, so you would put top left corner coordinates, then bottom right, and that would search in a box.  You get coordinates by using the dibber in SCAR then dragging it to the place and left clicking.  That will come up with 2 three to one digit numbers.  YOU HAVE TO ALWAYS HAVE THE SCREEN TARGETTED BY DRAGGING THE CROSSHAIRS TO THE RS SCREEN TO GET COORDINATES.

Example:

[img]http://img397.imageshack.us/img397/3146/findcolor2qn.png[/img]

[u][i]FINDCOLORSPIRAL[/u][/i]

[code]Findcolorspiral(x,y,color,cords,cords)[/code]

Thats a little bit different from Findcolor.  It will search for the color from the coordinates you set outward until it finds it.  Generally faster if your searching for something thats closer to the middle of the screen always.

[img]http://img397.imageshack.us/img397/509/findcolorspiral0eq.png[/img]

[i][u]FINDCOLORTOLERANCE[/i][/u]

[code]Findcolortolerance(x,y,color,cords,cords,cords,cords,tol)[/code]

Thats a little bit different from Findcolor, but exactly the same except theres tolerance.  Tolerance when its referring to color is lets say theres a color (340)  and there was a bunch of similar colors around it such as 350, you would put the tolerance to 10 and it would search for colors 340 + 10, but normally you would set the tolerance to around 30 or 40.

[img]http://img397.imageshack.us/img397/2196/findcolortolerance8lf.png[/img]


[i][u]FINDCOLORSPIRALTOLERANCE[/i][/u]

This uses FindColorSpiral but it has tolerance (read Findcolortolerance).

[img]http://img397.imageshack.us/img397/336/findcolorspiraltolerance4gt.png[/img]

[i]!!PROCEDURES FROM INCLUDES!![/i]

[u][i]MOUSEC[/i][/u]

[code]MouseC(x,y,1)[/code]  -FROM SQUIG-

That will move the mouse human like to the coordinates you set.  You can use x,y after you do a findcolor, for example:

[code]Findcolor(STUFF)
MouseC(x,y,1)[/code]

That will click on the color.  1 is left click, 2 is right click, 0 is no click, meaning it will just move the mouse.

[u][i]GAMETAB[/i][/u]

[code]Gametab(tab number)[/code]  -FROM SI-

Will click on the specified gametab:

Gametab(4) = Inventory
Gametab(5) = Next
Ect.

[i][u]CLICKTEXT[/i][/u]

[code]ClickText(&#39;text&#39;,cords,cords,cords,cords)[/code]  -FROM SQUIG-

That will search for the text you put in on the RS screen in the coordinates you set then click on it.  The coordinates are in a box.  (See Findcolor)  The text is CASE SENSITIVE.

[i][u]MUCH MORE![/u][/i]

There are thousands of procedures, but I won&#39;t name them all, you will have to figure them out yourselves, by looking through the includes and in SCAR help.

Moving on.

---------------

[b][u]The Different Types Of Ends[/b][/u]

There are 3 different types of Ends, but only 1 type of Begin, weird eh?

[code]End - Will end a begin in the middle of a procedure, for example (If (blah) Then Begin)
End; - Will end a procedure.
End. - Will end the script altogether.[/code]

Your ends always have to add up to how many begins you put.

Moving on.

-------------

[b][u]The Main Loop[/b][/u]

This is where you tell your script what exactly to do.

To start the main loop you don&#39;t need a procedure name, all you need is a Begin.

After all your procedures are done and your script does what you want, you need to put this:

[code]Begin
main loop
End.[/code]

Your main loop can consist of ANYTHING.  For example, if you were going to run Squig, you would have to put SetupSquig; in your main loop before anything else.  Also if you wanted to repeat your procedures until a certain time you would do something like this:

[code]Begin
Repeat
procedures
a:=a+1
Until(a=number or constant)
End.[/code]

Sounds complicated?  Its really not!  This is what that up there would do.  It would repeat the procedures you named, and everytime it repeated all of them, it will add an &#39;a&#39;, and it would keep repeating UNTIL a= a number or a constant.  Remember when I taught you wayyy up at the top about constants?  Well yoiu could put something like LoadsToDo=2; in your const, and everytime it repeated the procedure, it would add an &#39;a&#39;, then when a=LoadsToDo, you can make it do what you want.  But of course, if you used A, you would need to declare A as a variable (see Variables).

In most of my scripts, after a= whatever, I use a procedure in most includes called Logout;, that would log your character out of RuneScape.  Then I do something like this:

[code]Writeln(&#39;Loads to do reached, logged out&#39;)
End.[/code]

That would say the text in the dialogue box so the user knows whats going on and End.  would end the script completely, once and for all.

So a pretty good main loop would look like this:

[code]Begin
Repeat
procedures
a:=a+1
Until(a=loadstodo)
Logout;
Writeln(&#39;Loads to do done, logged out&#39;)
End.[/code]

Moving on.

----------------

[b][u]Common Errors[/b][/u]

Since I have taught you alot about scripting so far, you should hopefully know how to script.  Now I will help you with some common frustrating errors of scripting.

[u]Duplicate Identifier[/u]

That means that there is two of the same kind of variables.  You are most likely using an include that already has the variables that you declared, just removed the duplicate variable from your script.

[u]Invalid Parameters[/u]

You didn&#39;t make the procedure right.  For example, MouseC, you need to go Mousec(x,y,1) but you only put MouseC(x,y), thats invalid.

[u]BEGIN Expected In Script[/u]

Your missing a begin, most likely after your procedure name.

[u]Period &#39;.&#39; Expected In Script[/u]

You are missing a period, most likely at the end of your script.

[u]Runtime Error[/u]

You don&#39;t have an updated version of the include, or you didn&#39;t set up the include like your supposed to.

------------------

[b][u]Statements[/b][/u]

There are lots of things in SCAR that help tell about them.  One of them is statements.  Statements are things like and, if, else, then, is, not, to, or, and until.

Until would help you wait until whatever, if (something) then is what if and then is used for.  Or is used for like lets say you wanted to find 2 colors, it can be findcolor and/or, also else means everything else, is means is it there, or something like that, and not means like not there.

================================================================

[b][u]Making The Script[/u][/b]

In this TOTALLY new catagory, I will teach you actually how to make the script using an example.  Hopefully by now you will know how to script, well now you will learn how to implement what you know in a script.

Getting started, ok, well you should already know how to script, open up SCAR, and delete everything thats in there.  You done?  Good.  Now the first thing you should know is you have to make a program name first, right?  We will be making a simple Autominer.  So type something like this in SCAR:

[code]Program Autominer;[/code]

Ok, now lets move on to the next part of scripting.

You will need to use an include, we will be using Si.scar in this script.  You better know how to do this, if you don&#39;t, this is what you do:

[code]{.include Si.scar}[/code]

Your whole script should now look like this:

[code]Program Autominer;
{.include Si.scar}[/code]

If it isn&#39;t, change it.  Moving on.

We will be using the variables x,y in this script, for Findcolor, so please hit enter twice after the include and type this:

[code]Var x,y : Integer;[/code]

That will declare x and y as integer variables (I know, when I was first learning about variables I got lost, it takes a bit of practice).  Your whole script should now look like this:

[code]Program Autominer;
{.include Si.scar}

Var x,y : Integer;[/code]

If it doesn&#39;t, change it.

Moving on, we will now be actually telling the script what to do in procedures.

We are making a procedure that will mine the rock, simple right?  Of course it is.  This procedure is going to contain alot of what you learned, so pay attention.  Press enter twice after the variables and type this:

[code]Procedure minerocks;
Begin[/code]

Your whole script should now look something like this:

[code]Program Autominer;
{.include Si.scar}

Var x,y : Integer;

Procedure minerocks;
Begin[/code]

The Begin after the procedure will tell SCAR that the procedure has begun.

Now we will get to REALLY telling SCAR what to do, this will start using actual procedures from Si.scar and built in ones in SCAR.

Under the begin, we will type this:

[code]Findcolor(x,y,54323,5,5,515,340)
Mouse(x,y,1,1,true)[/code]

Don&#39;t worry, I&#39;m not gonna lose you, I just decided to take two steps ahead this time.  This is an explanation of what that does:  The Findcolor will find the color (the numbers that I put after the x,y NOTE: That is not a real color) of the rock, and the 5,5 is the top left corner of the main screen and the 515 340 is in the bottom right, making the script search in a box for the color.

Mouse (PROCEDURE OF SI) will move the mouse to the color like a human, then left click.  See, on Findcolor we have an x,y, that will save the coordinates that the script found the color of to them, then Mouse(x,y will move the mouse to the coordinates whereever they are.  The 1,1 in Mouse is tolerance, that will either subtract 1 or +1 coordinate to the x,y for randomness, you can put this higher.  The true means left click, false would make it right click.

This is what your whole PROCEDURE should look like:

[code]Procedure minerocks;
Begin
Findcolor(x,y,54323,5,5,515,340)
Mouse(x,y,1,1,true)[/code]

Change it if it doesn&#39;t.  Moving on to the next part.

Now under mouse, you will want it to wait while your mining the rock, right?  I never have showed you this, but theres a function built in SCAR that allows you to set a wait time in MILLISECONDS.  So right under the Mouse put this:

[code]Wait(5000)[/code]

That will make the script wait for 5 seconds while you mine the rock.  There are more accurate and better ways of actually knowing how to make the script know when the rocks gone, but since your most likely a newbie, I won&#39;t say.

Your whole procedure should now look like this:

[code]Procedure minerocks;
Begin
Findcolor(x,y,54323,5,5,515,340)
Mouse(x,y,1,1,true)
Wait(5000)[/code]

Good, now you&#39;ve got a functional autominer, now end this procedure.

That should mine the rocks until you got a full load and then keep going, to make it do something else you would have to add more, but that uses alot of what you know.

Your whole script should now look like this:

[code]Program Powerminer;
{.include Si.scar}

Var x,y : Integer;

Procedure minerocks;
Begin
if(Findcolor(x,y,54323,5,5,515,340))then
begin
Mouse(x,y,1,1,true)
Wait(5000)
end;
End;[/code]

When using procedures that return a value, such as true, you should always use if and then statements!

That won&#39;t work as it doesn&#39;t have a main loop, but you should know how to add one.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 03 May 2007 20:36:46 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/ultimate-scar-beginners-guide-for-complete-noobs/4668.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Ultimate SCAR Beginners Guide For Complete Noobs</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@codx codx]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/codx">@codx</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Nice tutorial, really helpful</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/ultimate-scar-beginners-guide-for-complete-noobs/4668/15">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/ultimate-scar-beginners-guide-for-complete-noobs/4668/15</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 03 May 2007 20:36:46 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-4668-15</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/ultimate-scar-beginners-guide-for-complete-noobs/4668.rss">Ultimate SCAR Beginners Guide For Complete Noobs</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Ultimate SCAR Beginners Guide For Complete Noobs</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Chaos_Shadow Chaos Shadow]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/chaos_shadow">@Chaos_Shadow</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>that made it very simple  for a helpless noob like me  <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=9" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"> thanks!</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/ultimate-scar-beginners-guide-for-complete-noobs/4668/14">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/ultimate-scar-beginners-guide-for-complete-noobs/4668/14</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 29 Jul 2006 11:35:29 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-4668-14</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/ultimate-scar-beginners-guide-for-complete-noobs/4668.rss">Ultimate SCAR Beginners Guide For Complete Noobs</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Ultimate SCAR Beginners Guide For Complete Noobs</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@BlackThursday BlackThursday]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/blackthursday">@BlackThursday</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>All the old includes as well hmm? Cant we get a Beginners guide for the Shitload of SRL functions?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/ultimate-scar-beginners-guide-for-complete-noobs/4668/13">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/ultimate-scar-beginners-guide-for-complete-noobs/4668/13</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 26 Jul 2006 18:52:51 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-4668-13</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/ultimate-scar-beginners-guide-for-complete-noobs/4668.rss">Ultimate SCAR Beginners Guide For Complete Noobs</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Ultimate SCAR Beginners Guide For Complete Noobs</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@MrWicked MrWicked]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/mrwicked">@MrWicked</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Nice tutorial, Its not as scary as it looks lol, to bad STS couldnt come back out and make scripts <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=9" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"> those were so easy to make even the most advanced scripts.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/ultimate-scar-beginners-guide-for-complete-noobs/4668/12">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/ultimate-scar-beginners-guide-for-complete-noobs/4668/12</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 23 Jul 2006 18:45:44 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-4668-12</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/ultimate-scar-beginners-guide-for-complete-noobs/4668.rss">Ultimate SCAR Beginners Guide For Complete Noobs</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Ultimate SCAR Beginners Guide For Complete Noobs</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Bego Bego]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/bego">@Bego</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Dibber, thats what it is =[br][size=1]Posted at: July 20, 2006, 03:26:38 PM[/size][hr]Bump <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/blush.png?v=9" title=":blush:" class="emoji" alt=":blush:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/ultimate-scar-beginners-guide-for-complete-noobs/4668/11">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/ultimate-scar-beginners-guide-for-complete-noobs/4668/11</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 21 Jul 2006 17:19:16 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-4668-11</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/ultimate-scar-beginners-guide-for-complete-noobs/4668.rss">Ultimate SCAR Beginners Guide For Complete Noobs</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Ultimate SCAR Beginners Guide For Complete Noobs</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Ron Ron]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/ron">@Ron</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I think he meant… a dipper, you know, the Color Picker. I am guessing lol. Cause a dibber is something for gardening.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/ultimate-scar-beginners-guide-for-complete-noobs/4668/10">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/ultimate-scar-beginners-guide-for-complete-noobs/4668/10</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jul 2006 19:09:30 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-4668-10</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/ultimate-scar-beginners-guide-for-complete-noobs/4668.rss">Ultimate SCAR Beginners Guide For Complete Noobs</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Ultimate SCAR Beginners Guide For Complete Noobs</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@RdSoxFan618 RdSoxFan618]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/rdsoxfan618">@RdSoxFan618</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Ya know, this did a brilliant job teaching me about FindColor and FindColorSprial and all that, but Wtf is a Dibber?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/ultimate-scar-beginners-guide-for-complete-noobs/4668/9">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/ultimate-scar-beginners-guide-for-complete-noobs/4668/9</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 19 Jul 2006 17:26:22 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-4668-9</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/ultimate-scar-beginners-guide-for-complete-noobs/4668.rss">Ultimate SCAR Beginners Guide For Complete Noobs</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Ultimate SCAR Beginners Guide For Complete Noobs</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Ron Ron]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/ron">@Ron</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I actually see that. <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=9" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"> Congrats man, nice tutorial. I like it when people put other scripts in tutorials, so they teach you and help you make your first script. <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/smiley.png?v=9" title=":smiley:" class="emoji" alt=":smiley:"> Good job man.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/ultimate-scar-beginners-guide-for-complete-noobs/4668/8">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/ultimate-scar-beginners-guide-for-complete-noobs/4668/8</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 12 Jul 2006 05:54:38 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-4668-8</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/ultimate-scar-beginners-guide-for-complete-noobs/4668.rss">Ultimate SCAR Beginners Guide For Complete Noobs</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Ultimate SCAR Beginners Guide For Complete Noobs</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Bego Bego]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/bego">@Bego</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>RS Monkey’s doesn’t explain to a noob, trust me, when I was a noob, and I had no previous programming experience, I wanted a tutorial or someone to talk to me JUST like this one, because even the simplest of tutorials were either perfectly simple but didn’t go in depth so I would read it and forget it the next day, because I had no idea what a program is even, what a variable is, what the hell a value is supposed to mean.</p>
<p>This one talks like your talking to a 2 year old <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/wink.png?v=9" title=":wink:" class="emoji" alt=":wink:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/ultimate-scar-beginners-guide-for-complete-noobs/4668/7">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/ultimate-scar-beginners-guide-for-complete-noobs/4668/7</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 12 Jul 2006 05:36:08 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-4668-7</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/ultimate-scar-beginners-guide-for-complete-noobs/4668.rss">Ultimate SCAR Beginners Guide For Complete Noobs</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Ultimate SCAR Beginners Guide For Complete Noobs</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Ron Ron]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/ron">@Ron</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>You didn’t see The RS Monkey’s? <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/smiley.png?v=9" title=":smiley:" class="emoji" alt=":smiley:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/ultimate-scar-beginners-guide-for-complete-noobs/4668/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/ultimate-scar-beginners-guide-for-complete-noobs/4668/6</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 12 Jul 2006 01:04:27 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-4668-6</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/ultimate-scar-beginners-guide-for-complete-noobs/4668.rss">Ultimate SCAR Beginners Guide For Complete Noobs</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Ultimate SCAR Beginners Guide For Complete Noobs</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Bego Bego]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/bego">@Bego</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Because intermediate people can help themselves, and theres no good noob ones.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/ultimate-scar-beginners-guide-for-complete-noobs/4668/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/ultimate-scar-beginners-guide-for-complete-noobs/4668/5</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 12 Jul 2006 00:59:30 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-4668-5</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/ultimate-scar-beginners-guide-for-complete-noobs/4668.rss">Ultimate SCAR Beginners Guide For Complete Noobs</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Ultimate SCAR Beginners Guide For Complete Noobs</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Xerxes Xerxes]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/xerxes">@Xerxes</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Mine was the best.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/ultimate-scar-beginners-guide-for-complete-noobs/4668/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/ultimate-scar-beginners-guide-for-complete-noobs/4668/4</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jul 2006 22:05:38 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-4668-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/ultimate-scar-beginners-guide-for-complete-noobs/4668.rss">Ultimate SCAR Beginners Guide For Complete Noobs</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Ultimate SCAR Beginners Guide For Complete Noobs</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Ron Ron]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/ron">@Ron</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Another Ultimate SCAR Beginners Guide For Complete Noobs guide? <em>Sigh</em></p>
<p>When will an Ultimate SCAR Advanced Guide for Complete Intermediates guide come out?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/ultimate-scar-beginners-guide-for-complete-noobs/4668/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/ultimate-scar-beginners-guide-for-complete-noobs/4668/3</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jul 2006 21:58:23 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-4668-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/ultimate-scar-beginners-guide-for-complete-noobs/4668.rss">Ultimate SCAR Beginners Guide For Complete Noobs</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Ultimate SCAR Beginners Guide For Complete Noobs</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@DeadBird DeadBird]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/deadbird">@DeadBird</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Helped me alot</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/ultimate-scar-beginners-guide-for-complete-noobs/4668/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/ultimate-scar-beginners-guide-for-complete-noobs/4668/2</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jul 2006 18:41:18 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-4668-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/ultimate-scar-beginners-guide-for-complete-noobs/4668.rss">Ultimate SCAR Beginners Guide For Complete Noobs</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Ultimate SCAR Beginners Guide For Complete Noobs</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Bego Bego]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/bego">@Bego</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I made this a while back, and decided I’d contribute here a bit.  I didn’t know where to put it since you can’t make a new topic is the tutorial forum, so I would like it if someone moved it there.  Thanks.</p>
<hr>
<p><span class="bbcode-u"><span class="bbcode-b">Syntax</span></span></p>
<p>Ok, to start off, to make a script, you would make a name, right?  The name HAS to have no spaces, so if you open up scar, you will most likely see this:</p>
<p><img src="http://img328.imageshack.us/img328/717/beginscar0xb.png" alt width="" height=""></p>
<p>Where it says program New;, you should make it say something relevent to what your doing, so if your making an autominer, go like this:</p>
<pre><code class="lang-auto">Program Autominer;</code></pre>
<p>It has to have a semicolon after it, or else you will get an error.  Moving on.</p>
<hr>
<p><span class="bbcode-u">[b]Includes</span>[/b]</p>
<p>There are many different includes for SCAR, some of which are very helpful, such as Si.scar, and Squig.txt.  Go to File &gt; Download Includes and get all of them.  Read through a couple of them, they will be in your includes folder which is most likely in C:\Program Files\SCAR 2.03\Includes.   As you read through them you might notice things like:</p>
<pre><code class="lang-auto">Function GetStat(stat : String; top : Boolean) : Integer;</code></pre>
<p>Don’t let how complicated that looks fool you, its actually very simple.  See the Function is nothing, it just tells SCAR what that is, in this case its a function.  The Getstat is what you need to worry about.  Theres most likely instructions on what each function/procedure does and how to use them.  With Getstat this is what it says:</p>
<p>[code]{^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^          GETSTAT         ^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^}<br>
{Opens the stat panel If needed. The variable stat is the name Of the<br>
stat your wanting To retrieve And If top is true it will get the current<br>
stat, If its false it will get the max stat}<br>
{^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^}</p>
<p>Function GetStat(stat : String; top : Boolean) : Integer;[/code]</p>
<p>Followed by a BUNCH of code (Thats a function in Squig.txt).  All you would have to say in YOUR script would be something like this:</p>
<pre><code class="lang-auto">Getstat(&lt;the stats name&gt;, true)</code></pre>
<p>And that will get the current number of the stat you specified.</p>
<p>In other things, their called PROCEDURES.  While looking through an include you might find a procedure something like this for example:</p>
<p>[code]{^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^          OPENSTATS         ^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^}<br>
{Opens the stat panel}<br>
{^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^}</p>
<p>Procedure OpenStats;[/code]</p>
<p>Thats simple.  In your main script just type OpenStats; and that would open the stats tab if you were using this particular include.</p>
<p>Ok, I have explained to you just now what in[u]cludes do and how to understand them, but right now I will teach you how to include them in your script.  Its simple actually, right under your program Autominer; or whatever it is, put this:</p>
<pre><code class="lang-auto">{.include &lt;include name&gt;}  (ex. {.include Si.scar} )</code></pre>
<p>Simple right?  Moving on.</p>
<hr>
<p><span class="bbcode-u"><span class="bbcode-b">Variables</span></span></p>
<p>The next thing you would have to do is declare the variables you are going to use.  I know that sounds confusing, but I just made it sound like that for now.  I will explain it.  Variables like x and y hold numbers, and such.  Example:</p>
<pre><code class="lang-auto">Findcolor(x,y,&lt;color&gt;,coordinates)</code></pre>
<p>The x and y in there will save the coordinates of where it found the color.</p>
<p>You declare variables like this:</p>
<pre><code class="lang-auto">Var x,y</code></pre>
<p>But thats not all.  You can declare certain variables as Booleans, Strings, or Integers.  Booleans meaning true or false.  Strings meaning words.  Integers meaning things like x and y.</p>
<p>To declare x and y as Integers you would have to go like this:</p>
<p><img src="http://img397.imageshack.us/img397/592/var5fj.png" alt width="" height=""></p>
<p>And that would declare them as integers.  You put all that under your include.  Moving on.</p>
<hr>
<p><span class="bbcode-u"><span class="bbcode-b">Constants</span></span></p>
<p>Constants do not NEED to be used, but they are good for giving the user of the script flexability on what they are doing.  Constants are things that stay the same throughout the whole script.  A scripter might do something like this:</p>
<p><img src="http://img328.imageshack.us/img328/5893/const3dh.png" alt width="" height=""></p>
<p>You get colors by using the dibber in scar and putting it on the color and clicking, that should give you a bunch of numbers in the debug box below the main script.</p>
<p>You declare Constants by going like this:</p>
<pre><code class="lang-auto">Const</code></pre>
<p>And to add things to the Const you would make things related to your script like this:</p>
<pre><code class="lang-auto">MonsterColor=453344;</code></pre>
<p>You have to have a = and then the value (number, string, boolean) and then a semicolon.  Why is this useful in a script you ask?  For a user to put in the color of the monster, it would change the value in the big script itself, example:</p>
<pre><code class="lang-auto">Findcolor(x,y,MonsterColor,&lt;coordinates&gt;)</code></pre>
<p>Moving on.</p>
<hr>
<p><span class="bbcode-u">[b]Procedures</span>[/b]</p>
<p>In your script you have to name your procedures to something relevant to what your doing.  Since you’ve got your script set up up there, you now need to start scripting the actual script.  This is what you do:</p>
<p><code>Procedure name;  (ex. Procedure mine; )
Begin</code></p>
<p><img src="http://img397.imageshack.us/img397/593/proc7ka.png" alt width="" height=""></p>
<p>It has to have a semicolon, and after the procedure name, you have to have a Begin because that will tell the script that the procedure will then begin.</p>
<p>A procedure always has to end with this:</p>
<pre><code class="lang-auto">End;</code></pre>
<p>The semicolon tells the script that your ending the PROCEDURE.</p>
<p>Moving on.</p>
<hr>
<p><span class="bbcode-u"><span class="bbcode-b">Making The Script Do What You Want</span></span></p>
<p>There are THOUSANDS of things that you can do, I will only name a couple basic things.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-u">[i]FINDCOLOR</span>[/i]</p>
<pre><code class="lang-auto">Findcolor(x,y,color,cords,cords,cords,cords)</code></pre>
<p>This is how that works.  You put Findcolor(x,y, in your script, the x,y will save the coordinates of where it found the color, then the color of the thing your looking for, then you put coordinates searching in a box, so you would put top left corner coordinates, then bottom right, and that would search in a box.  You get coordinates by using the dibber in SCAR then dragging it to the place and left clicking.  That will come up with 2 three to one digit numbers.  YOU HAVE TO ALWAYS HAVE THE SCREEN TARGETTED BY DRAGGING THE CROSSHAIRS TO THE RS SCREEN TO GET COORDINATES.</p>
<p>Example:</p>
<p><img src="http://img397.imageshack.us/img397/3146/findcolor2qn.png" alt width="" height=""></p>
<p><span class="bbcode-u">[i]FINDCOLORSPIRAL</span>[/i]</p>
<pre><code class="lang-auto">Findcolorspiral(x,y,color,cords,cords)</code></pre>
<p>Thats a little bit different from Findcolor.  It will search for the color from the coordinates you set outward until it finds it.  Generally faster if your searching for something thats closer to the middle of the screen always.</p>
<p><img src="http://img397.imageshack.us/img397/509/findcolorspiral0eq.png" alt width="" height=""></p>
<p><span class="bbcode-i">[u]FINDCOLORTOLERANCE</span>[/u]</p>
<pre><code class="lang-auto">Findcolortolerance(x,y,color,cords,cords,cords,cords,tol)</code></pre>
<p>Thats a little bit different from Findcolor, but exactly the same except theres tolerance.  Tolerance when its referring to color is lets say theres a color (340)  and there was a bunch of similar colors around it such as 350, you would put the tolerance to 10 and it would search for colors 340 + 10, but normally you would set the tolerance to around 30 or 40.</p>
<p><img src="http://img397.imageshack.us/img397/2196/findcolortolerance8lf.png" alt width="" height=""></p>
<p><span class="bbcode-i">[u]FINDCOLORSPIRALTOLERANCE</span>[/u]</p>
<p>This uses FindColorSpiral but it has tolerance (read Findcolortolerance).</p>
<p><img src="http://img397.imageshack.us/img397/336/findcolorspiraltolerance4gt.png" alt width="" height=""></p>
<p><span class="bbcode-i">!!PROCEDURES FROM INCLUDES!!</span></p>
<p><span class="bbcode-u"><span class="bbcode-i">MOUSEC</span></span></p>
<p><code>MouseC(x,y,1)</code>  -FROM SQUIG-</p>
<p>That will move the mouse human like to the coordinates you set.  You can use x,y after you do a findcolor, for example:</p>
<p><code>Findcolor(STUFF)
MouseC(x,y,1)</code></p>
<p>That will click on the color.  1 is left click, 2 is right click, 0 is no click, meaning it will just move the mouse.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-u"><span class="bbcode-i">GAMETAB</span></span></p>
<p><code>Gametab(tab number)</code>  -FROM SI-</p>
<p>Will click on the specified gametab:</p>
<p>Gametab(4) = Inventory<br>
Gametab(5) = Next<br>
Ect.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-i">[u]CLICKTEXT</span>[/u]</p>
<p><code>ClickText('text',cords,cords,cords,cords)</code>  -FROM SQUIG-</p>
<p>That will search for the text you put in on the RS screen in the coordinates you set then click on it.  The coordinates are in a box.  (See Findcolor)  The text is CASE SENSITIVE.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-i"><span class="bbcode-u">MUCH MORE!</span></span></p>
<p>There are thousands of procedures, but I won’t name them all, you will have to figure them out yourselves, by looking through the includes and in SCAR help.</p>
<p>Moving on.</p>
<hr>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">[u]The Different Types Of Ends</span>[/u]</p>
<p>There are 3 different types of Ends, but only 1 type of Begin, weird eh?</p>
<p><code>End - Will end a begin in the middle of a procedure, for example (If (blah) Then Begin)
End; - Will end a procedure.
End. - Will end the script altogether.</code></p>
<p>Your ends always have to add up to how many begins you put.</p>
<p>Moving on.</p>
<hr>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">[u]The Main Loop</span>[/u]</p>
<p>This is where you tell your script what exactly to do.</p>
<p>To start the main loop you don’t need a procedure name, all you need is a Begin.</p>
<p>After all your procedures are done and your script does what you want, you need to put this:</p>
<p><code>Begin
main loop
End.</code></p>
<p>Your main loop can consist of ANYTHING.  For example, if you were going to run Squig, you would have to put SetupSquig; in your main loop before anything else.  Also if you wanted to repeat your procedures until a certain time you would do something like this:</p>
<p><code>Begin
Repeat
procedures
a:=a+1
Until(a=number or constant)
End.</code></p>
<p>Sounds complicated?  Its really not!  This is what that up there would do.  It would repeat the procedures you named, and everytime it repeated all of them, it will add an ‘a’, and it would keep repeating UNTIL a= a number or a constant.  Remember when I taught you wayyy up at the top about constants?  Well yoiu could put something like LoadsToDo=2; in your const, and everytime it repeated the procedure, it would add an ‘a’, then when a=LoadsToDo, you can make it do what you want.  But of course, if you used A, you would need to declare A as a variable (see Variables).</p>
<p>In most of my scripts, after a= whatever, I use a procedure in most includes called Logout;, that would log your character out of RuneScape.  Then I do something like this:</p>
<p><code>Writeln('Loads to do reached, logged out')
End.</code></p>
<p>That would say the text in the dialogue box so the user knows whats going on and End.  would end the script completely, once and for all.</p>
<p>So a pretty good main loop would look like this:</p>
<p><code>Begin
Repeat
procedures
a:=a+1
Until(a=loadstodo)
Logout;
Writeln('Loads to do done, logged out')
End.</code></p>
<p>Moving on.</p>
<hr>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">[u]Common Errors</span>[/u]</p>
<p>Since I have taught you alot about scripting so far, you should hopefully know how to script.  Now I will help you with some common frustrating errors of scripting.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-u">Duplicate Identifier</span></p>
<p>That means that there is two of the same kind of variables.  You are most likely using an include that already has the variables that you declared, just removed the duplicate variable from your script.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-u">Invalid Parameters</span></p>
<p>You didn’t make the procedure right.  For example, MouseC, you need to go Mousec(x,y,1) but you only put MouseC(x,y), thats invalid.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-u">BEGIN Expected In Script</span></p>
<p>Your missing a begin, most likely after your procedure name.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-u">Period ‘.’ Expected In Script</span></p>
<p>You are missing a period, most likely at the end of your script.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-u">Runtime Error</span></p>
<p>You don’t have an updated version of the include, or you didn’t set up the include like your supposed to.</p>
<hr>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">[u]Statements</span>[/u]</p>
<p>There are lots of things in SCAR that help tell about them.  One of them is statements.  Statements are things like and, if, else, then, is, not, to, or, and until.</p>
<p>Until would help you wait until whatever, if (something) then is what if and then is used for.  Or is used for like lets say you wanted to find 2 colors, it can be findcolor and/or, also else means everything else, is means is it there, or something like that, and not means like not there.</p>
<p>================================================================</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b"><span class="bbcode-u">Making The Script</span></span></p>
<p>In this TOTALLY new catagory, I will teach you actually how to make the script using an example.  Hopefully by now you will know how to script, well now you will learn how to implement what you know in a script.</p>
<p>Getting started, ok, well you should already know how to script, open up SCAR, and delete everything thats in there.  You done?  Good.  Now the first thing you should know is you have to make a program name first, right?  We will be making a simple Autominer.  So type something like this in SCAR:</p>
<pre><code class="lang-auto">Program Autominer;</code></pre>
<p>Ok, now lets move on to the next part of scripting.</p>
<p>You will need to use an include, we will be using Si.scar in this script.  You better know how to do this, if you don’t, this is what you do:</p>
<pre><code class="lang-auto">{.include Si.scar}</code></pre>
<p>Your whole script should now look like this:</p>
<p><code>Program Autominer;
{.include Si.scar}</code></p>
<p>If it isn’t, change it.  Moving on.</p>
<p>We will be using the variables x,y in this script, for Findcolor, so please hit enter twice after the include and type this:</p>
<pre><code class="lang-auto">Var x,y : Integer;</code></pre>
<p>That will declare x and y as integer variables (I know, when I was first learning about variables I got lost, it takes a bit of practice).  Your whole script should now look like this:</p>
<p>[code]Program Autominer;<br>
{.include Si.scar}</p>
<p>Var x,y : Integer;[/code]</p>
<p>If it doesn’t, change it.</p>
<p>Moving on, we will now be actually telling the script what to do in procedures.</p>
<p>We are making a procedure that will mine the rock, simple right?  Of course it is.  This procedure is going to contain alot of what you learned, so pay attention.  Press enter twice after the variables and type this:</p>
<p><code>Procedure minerocks;
Begin</code></p>
<p>Your whole script should now look something like this:</p>
<p>[code]Program Autominer;<br>
{.include Si.scar}</p>
<p>Var x,y : Integer;</p>
<p>Procedure minerocks;<br>
Begin[/code]</p>
<p>The Begin after the procedure will tell SCAR that the procedure has begun.</p>
<p>Now we will get to REALLY telling SCAR what to do, this will start using actual procedures from Si.scar and built in ones in SCAR.</p>
<p>Under the begin, we will type this:</p>
<p><code>Findcolor(x,y,54323,5,5,515,340)
Mouse(x,y,1,1,true)</code></p>
<p>Don’t worry, I’m not gonna lose you, I just decided to take two steps ahead this time.  This is an explanation of what that does:  The Findcolor will find the color (the numbers that I put after the x,y NOTE: That is not a real color) of the rock, and the 5,5 is the top left corner of the main screen and the 515 340 is in the bottom right, making the script search in a box for the color.</p>
<p>Mouse (PROCEDURE OF SI) will move the mouse to the color like a human, then left click.  See, on Findcolor we have an x,y, that will save the coordinates that the script found the color of to them, then Mouse(x,y will move the mouse to the coordinates whereever they are.  The 1,1 in Mouse is tolerance, that will either subtract 1 or +1 coordinate to the x,y for randomness, you can put this higher.  The true means left click, false would make it right click.</p>
<p>This is what your whole PROCEDURE should look like:</p>
<p><code>Procedure minerocks;
Begin
Findcolor(x,y,54323,5,5,515,340)
Mouse(x,y,1,1,true)</code></p>
<p>Change it if it doesn’t.  Moving on to the next part.</p>
<p>Now under mouse, you will want it to wait while your mining the rock, right?  I never have showed you this, but theres a function built in SCAR that allows you to set a wait time in MILLISECONDS.  So right under the Mouse put this:</p>
<pre><code class="lang-auto">Wait(5000)</code></pre>
<p>That will make the script wait for 5 seconds while you mine the rock.  There are more accurate and better ways of actually knowing how to make the script know when the rocks gone, but since your most likely a newbie, I won’t say.</p>
<p>Your whole procedure should now look like this:</p>
<p><code>Procedure minerocks;
Begin
Findcolor(x,y,54323,5,5,515,340)
Mouse(x,y,1,1,true)
Wait(5000)</code></p>
<p>Good, now you’ve got a functional autominer, now end this procedure.</p>
<p>That should mine the rocks until you got a full load and then keep going, to make it do something else you would have to add more, but that uses alot of what you know.</p>
<p>Your whole script should now look like this:</p>
<p>[code]Program Powerminer;<br>
{.include Si.scar}</p>
<p>Var x,y : Integer;</p>
<p>Procedure minerocks;<br>
Begin<br>
if(Findcolor(x,y,54323,5,5,515,340))then<br>
begin<br>
Mouse(x,y,1,1,true)<br>
Wait(5000)<br>
end;<br>
End;[/code]</p>
<p>When using procedures that return a value, such as true, you should always use if and then statements!</p>
<p>That won’t work as it doesn’t have a main loop, but you should know how to add one.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/ultimate-scar-beginners-guide-for-complete-noobs/4668/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/ultimate-scar-beginners-guide-for-complete-noobs/4668/1</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jul 2006 09:13:54 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-4668-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/ultimate-scar-beginners-guide-for-complete-noobs/4668.rss">Ultimate SCAR Beginners Guide For Complete Noobs</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
