<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>562 Cache Keeps Re-downloading</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/562-cache-keeps-re-downloading/422037</link>
    <description>[s]Hello

I have set up my cache auto-downloader for my 562 server. It&#39;s been working fine for months, but here recently one day, it just decided to fail and I can&#39;t figure it out.

Every time I run my client, it tries and successfully downloads the cache, even if the user already has the client. Once the cache is re-downloaded, the client will run. Once the client is closed and re-opened it will download again and overwrite the cache.

Could this be a server related issue? Maybe an IP tables issue? I disabled it but it seems like more of a client issue. The thing is, I didn&#39;t change a thing with the cache or client. This has be scratching my head. I have noticed that this may be related to Java 7. JDK 7 also seems to cause issues on linux with the server so maybe it is the new java. 

Any help would be greatly appreciated.

-Kizz[/s]

Disregard this, I have fixed the issue by altering the Version check file location to my server. Dumb me.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 18 Nov 2011 04:09:37 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Game Development</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/562-cache-keeps-re-downloading/422037.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>562 Cache Keeps Re-downloading</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@cdoggy cdoggy]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/cdoggy">@cdoggy</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[s]Hello</p>
<p>I have set up my cache auto-downloader for my 562 server. It’s been working fine for months, but here recently one day, it just decided to fail and I can’t figure it out.</p>
<p>Every time I run my client, it tries and successfully downloads the cache, even if the user already has the client. Once the cache is re-downloaded, the client will run. Once the client is closed and re-opened it will download again and overwrite the cache.</p>
<p>Could this be a server related issue? Maybe an IP tables issue? I disabled it but it seems like more of a client issue. The thing is, I didn’t change a thing with the cache or client. This has be scratching my head. I have noticed that this may be related to Java 7. JDK 7 also seems to cause issues on linux with the server so maybe it is the new java.</p>
<p>Any help would be greatly appreciated.</p>
<p>-Kizz[/s]</p>
<p>Disregard this, I have fixed the issue by altering the Version check file location to my server. Dumb me.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/562-cache-keeps-re-downloading/422037/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/562-cache-keeps-re-downloading/422037/1</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 18 Nov 2011 04:09:37 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-422037-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/562-cache-keeps-re-downloading/422037.rss">562 Cache Keeps Re-downloading</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
