<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>&quot;.bat&quot; file coding, [TUT], update 4 (May 18, 2007)</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/bat-file-coding-tut-update-4-may-18-2007/93778</link>
    <description>[b]Tutorial Name: [/b] Batch Files
[b]How hard 1-10: [/b] 0.1
[b]Required Skills: [/b] Do you know how to type? if yes then you&#39;ll be fine
[b]Full Credits: [/b] Me
                                          [center] [b]PLEASE READ THROUGH THIS IF YOU WANT TO KNOW COMMANDS OF THIS TYPE OF STUFF!!!! DONT MISS OUT!!![/b][/center]


[b]Tutorial: [/b]

[b]Step 1:[/b]

Alright, lets get started, go to your desktop and create a new text document.
right click &gt; new &gt; text document

Then, you rename it and make it say &quot;Test.bat&quot; make sure it ends with &quot;.bat&quot; not &quot;.txt&quot;
alright we just got started 

[b]Step 2:[/b]

Now, you right click and click the &quot;edit&quot; option

it opens as a text document, so now we always write one thing before we start: &quot;@echo off&quot;
like this [code] @echo off[/code]
nice isnt it, lol... kk so now, after you did that, we are going to get started with the simple stuff, like titles and how to make stuff display when you open it.

[b]Step 3:[/b]

Okay, now, you type &quot;:menu&quot; or like &quot;:startscreen&quot; or something, i always make my starting place called menu, like this:
[code]
@echo off
:menu
title Test Program
[/code]
so now, you noticed i put &quot;title Test Program&quot; this means that when you open your file, the title will say &quot;Test Program&quot;

[b]Step 4:[/b]

This is a simple step, this is something you should do automatically right after you type the title, you click &quot;enter&quot; and you put &quot;cls&quot; i dont know exactly what that is abbreviating but it makes it so that all the letters from the screen dissappear, for instance, preten you were doing something and then you go back to your main menu, do you want al the words from your previous menu showing? if yes then skip this:
[code]
@echo off
:menu
title Test Program
cls
[/code]

[b]Step 5:[/b]

Now, we have to make it do something, for instance, say something

so you type &quot;echo&quot; and then two spaces and then what you want to say, you could type 1 space but it wouldnt look as good when it is finished, here is what it looks like now:
[code]
@echo off
:menu
title Test Program
cls
echo  Wootage, i made my test program!!!
[/code]

alright, now the last thing.. 

[b]Step 6:[/b]

this is the last step for your program, or at least this one:
you put a &quot;pause&quot;, you know in some programs, it says &quot;press any key to continue&quot;? this is how they do it
[code]
@echo off
:menu
title Test Program
cls
echo  Wootage, i made my test program!!!
pause
[/code]

woo, nice, now if you were to save and then exit out and open ur file, it would look something liek this:

[IMG]http://i119.photobucket.com/albums/o158/Alex_Mirchev/batchfiletut.jpg[/img]

here are the additional stuff you could add:

[b]Variables[/b]

Alright, if you have ever seen the &#39;Perfect Compiler&#39; you would know what a variable is, it is where you can type something and if you type it, it will do a specific action, those are called variables

okay here is the code for a variable:
[code]
set /p option= Option: 

[/code]
just remember, that both of the &quot;options&quot; can be changed, this is the standard format:
[code]
set /p (option name)= (text you want displayed)

[/code]

the part that says &quot;text you want displayed&quot; would be this, for example, preted you wanted the people to chose from different colors, so where it says the second option you would type &quot;Color: &quot; and it would look like this:

[IMG]http://i119.photobucket.com/albums/o158/Alex_Mirchev/batchfiletut2.jpg[/img]

alright, now that we know how to make a variable, lets make it so that if you typed something and clicked enter, it would go somewhere

okay here is the code from the &#39;Perfect Compiler&#39;:
[code]
set /p c=Option: 
if %c%==c goto c
if %c%==C goto c
if %c%==r goto r
if %c%==R goto r
if %c%==jar goto jar
if %c%==Jar goto jar
if %c%==JAR goto jar
if %c%==color goto color
if %c%==Color goto color
if %c%==COLOR goto color
if %c%==reset goto reset
if %c%==Reset goto reset
if %c%==RESET goto reset
if %c%==e goto e
if %c%==E goto e
if %c%==* goto er
goto er
[/code]
okay let me explain, the &quot;set /p c= Option: &quot; is makes option be dispayed, but the variable is actually called &quot;c&quot; 
so,  the &quot;if %c%==c goto c&quot; just means that if the person types &quot;c&quot; the program will to the part of the program that is labeled &quot;:c&quot; or 
[code]
:c
[/code]
 and then it goes on, the last one that says &quot;if %c%==* goto er&quot; means that if the person types anything else, it will take him to the &quot;:er&quot; part of the program, that is short for error.
alright, to make it so that he can go to the error page, you gotta do this, go to the end of your code, press enter and type
[code]:er[/code]
so then if the program is told to goto er, it will look for &quot;:er&quot; and then it will do whatever that part of the program tells it to do, here is what i get when i try to compile without my JDK 1.6:

[IMG]http://i119.photobucket.com/albums/o158/Alex_Mirchev/batchfiletut3.jpg[/img]
like it? rofl
this is the code that makes it do that:
[code]
:je
cls
title Error
echo You do not have JDK 5.0 or JDK 6.0 or any JDK 5.0 and 6.0 updates.
echo Go to Mod Taharok&#39;s tutorial on the Moparscape Tuturoials section
echo for step-by-step instructions to download the newest JDK Update.
pause
cls
goto menu
[/code]

so you get the part about creating the options

[b]Making History files[/b]

Okay, this is the part i had trouble with, but i know how to do it now
this is the guide on how to make another program open if the person does or types something 
okay here we go, pretend you want to show the history of when you opened your program this is what it should look like:
[code]
@echo off
:menu
title Test
cls
echo  Welcome to this test program
echo  Editing history...
echo You have opened the &quot;Test&quot; program at %time% on %date% &gt;&gt; &quot;history.txt&quot;
pause
goto :menu
[/code]

alright, if you have read this guide, you will notice the begginer stuff, such as the title and all the echo stuff.. but check out the part that says &quot;echo You have opened the &quot;Test&quot; program at %time% on %date% &gt;&gt; &quot;history.txt&quot;
that just means that it is going to type in a text document called &quot;history.txt&quot; (if there isnt one, the program automatically creates on by itself)

alright, here is the format for this:
[code]
echo (text here) &gt;&gt; &quot;(name of file).txt&quot;
[/code]

pretty easy...

[b]Opening Programs[/b]

alright, this is what you should do, you find out where the program.exe file is, for istance &quot;iexplore.exe&quot; is the internet explorer program, if you would like to open a website, you would do this:
[code]
&quot;C:\Program Files\Internet Explorer\iexplore.exe&quot; www.hemiscape.com/aarisair
[/code]

that opens this website, try it out if you like
alright this is the standard format for this:
[code]
&quot;C:\Program Files\Internet Explorer\iexplore.exe&quot; (website url)
[/code]

its simple, but to open another program, such as a Microsoft Office Word Document, you would need to do this:

[code]
&quot;C:\Program Files\Microsoft Office\Office10\Shortcut Bar\Office\Microsoft Word.exe&quot;
[/code]

this is mine, but for someone else, it might be different.. so you could do this:
[code]
&quot;%programfiles%(url for .exe file)&quot;
[/code]


[b]Colors[/b]

This is pretty simple, lets say you wanted to change the colors of the text and the background, you would make something like this in the begining, and i really love the way mod taharok does this, so lets use him again:
[code]
:back
cls
echo Please select a color to change the backround to:
echo.
echo black
echo white
echo red
echo yellow
echo green
echo blue
echo purple
echo.
echo.
set /p back=Color: 
if %back%== black (set b=0)
if %back%== white (set b=7)
if %back%== red (set b=4)
if %back%== yellow (set b=6)
if %back%== green (set b=2)
if %back%== blue (set b=1)
if %back%== purple (set b=5)
goto co2
[/code]

let me explain what this does, alright, as u can see, mod taharok gives the choices that you could chose from, those are just the simple colors
okay, so we can see that in the beggining he has the &quot;:back&quot; to indicate that this is a chapter of his program, but, he does not include the &quot;@echo off&quot; because this is just part of his program, well, he made the variable so now if you typed one of the colors, it would change it to that. so this is how he starts off:
[code]
:back
cls
echo Please select a color to change the backround to:
echo.
echo black
echo white
echo red
echo yellow
echo green
echo blue
echo purple
echo.
echo.
set /p back=Color: 
[/code]
this is just the begining, we all know by now how to do this, so then he adds the &quot;if&#39;s&quot;:
[code]
if %back%== black (set b=0)
if %back%== white (set b=7)
if %back%== red (set b=4)
if %back%== yellow (set b=6)
if %back%== green (set b=2)
if %back%== blue (set b=1)
if %back%== purple (set b=5)
goto co2
[/code]
alright, now, we got the if&#39;s, but i cant find in his code where he made the colors change so ill do it for him -.- lol
this is what the complete code shud look like:
[code]
:back
cls
echo Please select a color to change the backround to:
echo.
echo black
echo white
echo red
echo yellow
echo green
echo blue
echo purple
echo.
echo.
set /p back=Color: 
if %back%== black (set b=0)
if %back%== white (set b=7)
if %back%== red (set b=4)
if %back%== yellow (set b=6)
if %back%== green (set b=2)
if %back%== blue (set b=1)
if %back%== purple (set b=5)
goto co2
:co2
title Changed
cls
color %b%%t%
echo Your color has been changed as you requested!
echo.
pause
goto menu
[/code]
ohh sory, i forgot to explain about how the color system works, okay, &quot;b&quot; and &quot;t&quot; are the color modifiers, you change the color by changing &quot;%b%&quot; and &quot;%t%&quot;, then you put the color to change to b and t, like this &quot;color %b%%t%&quot; doesnt matter what order, here is an example:
[code]
@echo off
set (b=5)
set (t=7)
color %b%%t%
pause
[/code]
alright, if you ahve the time, you could add this code to a .bat file, a new one, so that you can see how it works, you can modify it and change the &quot;b&quot; and &quot;t&quot; values in the second and third line of the code, or make a variable so you can easily access it.. i hope you undersand


[b]Shortcuts[/b]

here are a couple shortcuts:
[b]%time%[/b] is for the file to show what time in military style  :cool:
[b]%date%[/b] is for the file to say what the day is atm also  :cool:
[b]%programfiles%[/b] is the shortcut so you dont have to type out the whole url of the place in program files, such as if you wanted to tell the .bat file to open up msn messenger, you would do this: 
[code]&quot;C:\Program Files\Messenger\msnmsgs.exe&quot;[/code] but instead you can put 
[code]&quot;%programfiles%Messenger\msnmsgs.exe&quot;[/code]
get it?
[b]%b%[/b] and [b]%t%[/b] these are both for the color, they are set by default to (t=7) and (b=0). (if you were wondering &quot;b&quot; stands for the number of the background color and &quot;t&quot; stands for the number of the text color. so if you were to write (t=25) it is going to make (t=2) and (b=5). This way, both of the colors change, background and text color. but its confusing so try expirement with only 1 number per variable

[i][u]Alright, i think that this is all that i can teach you, this is just the basic commands of .bat files.. explore it and you will find out a lot about this[/u][/i]

[b]Commands[/b]

did you know that if you were editing your .bat file, you could type this: 
[code]set[/code]
this makes it so the screen fills up with shortcuts that you could type for any part of your computer, for instance, your home drive, its awesome. here is a pic:
[IMG]http://i119.photobucket.com/albums/o158/Alex_Mirchev/batchfiletut4.jpg[/img]

cool isnt it, now if you took the words before the &quot;=&quot;, (like &quot;path&quot;=[trash], you would type %path% and it would display wutever is on the other side) so, if i were to write
[code]
@echo off
:menu
title Test
cls
echo.
echo  %path%
echo.
pause
[/code]
the batch file would show you what &quot;path&quot; is substituted for, here is a pic:
[IMG]http://i119.photobucket.com/albums/o158/Alex_Mirchev/batchfiletut5.jpg[/img]

see what that is? just try it out.. 

[b]Deleting[/b]

Alright, pretend u were trying to make it so that if the person had something like, a file that might contain a virus, such as a .exe file, and u wanted to make it delete that file, u wut do this:
[code]
@echo off
title Virus Deletion
cls
del *.exe
echo  Deleted all possible viruses.
echo.
pause
[/code]
This would make it delete any file that has the extension .exe, now if u wanted to make sure that he has that file before it tries to delete it, lets say the virus name is virus.exe, you would do this:
[code]
@echo off
title Virus Deletion
cls
if exist virus.exe (goto exists) else (goto noexists)
:exists
del virus.exe
echo  Deleted all possible viruses.
echo.
pause
:noexists
echo No virus detected
echo.
pause
[/code]
this will make it so that it checks if the virus.exe exists and will delete it and notify you, but if it doestn exist, it will tell you that there was no virus
alright, now continue to the next part

[b]Pop-up Messages[/b]

lets say you wanted to make a message pop up instead of making it just echo..
you could do this: 
[code]
@echo off
:menu
title Test
cls
echo.
echo  Testing the popup message...
echo.
echo.
msg * YOU GOT TESTED!!
pause
exit
[/code]
it might not work on some older computers.. lol works on my laptop but not on my home computer
if it works, its pretty awesome

so just play around with all the stuff u just learned and enjoy



[b]PLEASE READ[/b]
this is all the time i have so i have to post this, if you want to get the update, it will say &quot;.bat&quot; file coding, TUT 3&quot; not &quot;TUT 2&quot; and then it will say the date it was updated alrighht plz comment</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 12 Jul 2007 13:24:28 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>General Discussion</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/bat-file-coding-tut-update-4-may-18-2007/93778.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>&quot;.bat&quot; file coding, [TUT], update 4 (May 18, 2007)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@MastrChief MastrChief]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/mastrchief">@MastrChief</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>“<a class="mention" href="/u/echo">@echo</a> off<br>
:menu<br>
title Test Program<br>
cls<br>
echo  Wootage, i made my test program!!!”</p>
<p>Why would you have cls there?</p>
<p>EDIT:</p>
<p>Also, You need to explain how to get the files to run.</p>
<p>Just saying “C:\Program Files\Microsoft Office\Office10\Shortcut Bar\Office\Microsoft Word.exe” doesn’t do much…</p>
<p>here’s how I run programs:</p>
<p><code>
START "" /MAX photoshop.exe</code><br>
START “” /MAX photoshop.exe</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/bat-file-coding-tut-update-4-may-18-2007/93778/14">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/bat-file-coding-tut-update-4-may-18-2007/93778/14</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jul 2007 13:24:28 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-93778-14</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/bat-file-coding-tut-update-4-may-18-2007/93778.rss">&quot;.bat&quot; file coding, [TUT], update 4 (May 18, 2007)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>&quot;.bat&quot; file coding, [TUT], update 4 (May 18, 2007)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@pizza_pie pizza pie]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/pizza_pie">@pizza_pie</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“1337h4x, post:12, topic:93778”][quote author=pizza pie link=topic=135963.msg1360841#msg1360841 date=1179890233]<br>
ty for the comment, lol i know it is for noobs that just started this type of stuff… enjoy noobs lol no offense, like a month ago i was like you guys <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=6" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"><br>
[/quote]Stfu noob, you’ll always be a noob and you can’t do anything about it. 'Cept maybe ask MybBob.[/quote]<br>
k</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/bat-file-coding-tut-update-4-may-18-2007/93778/13">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/bat-file-coding-tut-update-4-may-18-2007/93778/13</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jul 2007 13:21:37 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-93778-13</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/bat-file-coding-tut-update-4-may-18-2007/93778.rss">&quot;.bat&quot; file coding, [TUT], update 4 (May 18, 2007)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>&quot;.bat&quot; file coding, [TUT], update 4 (May 18, 2007)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@1337h4x 1337h4x]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/1337h4x">@1337h4x</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“pizza pie, post:11, topic:93778”]ty for the comment, lol i know it is for noobs that just started this type of stuff… enjoy noobs lol no offense, like a month ago i was like you guys :)[/quote]Stfu noob, you’ll always be a noob and you can’t do anything about it. 'Cept maybe ask MybBob.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/bat-file-coding-tut-update-4-may-18-2007/93778/12">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/bat-file-coding-tut-update-4-may-18-2007/93778/12</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 23 May 2007 03:52:05 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-93778-12</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/bat-file-coding-tut-update-4-may-18-2007/93778.rss">&quot;.bat&quot; file coding, [TUT], update 4 (May 18, 2007)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>&quot;.bat&quot; file coding, [TUT], update 4 (May 18, 2007)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@pizza_pie pizza pie]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/pizza_pie">@pizza_pie</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>ty for the comment, lol i know it is for noobs that just started this type of stuff… enjoy noobs lol no offense, like a month ago i was like you guys <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=6" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/bat-file-coding-tut-update-4-may-18-2007/93778/11">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/bat-file-coding-tut-update-4-may-18-2007/93778/11</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 23 May 2007 03:17:13 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-93778-11</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/bat-file-coding-tut-update-4-may-18-2007/93778.rss">&quot;.bat&quot; file coding, [TUT], update 4 (May 18, 2007)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>&quot;.bat&quot; file coding, [TUT], update 4 (May 18, 2007)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@I_Am_Olan14 I Am Olan14]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/i_am_olan14">@I_Am_Olan14</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Ok, good for nubs. I already knew all this though.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/bat-file-coding-tut-update-4-may-18-2007/93778/10">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/bat-file-coding-tut-update-4-may-18-2007/93778/10</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 21 May 2007 21:30:15 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-93778-10</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/bat-file-coding-tut-update-4-may-18-2007/93778.rss">&quot;.bat&quot; file coding, [TUT], update 4 (May 18, 2007)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>&quot;.bat&quot; file coding, [TUT], update 4 (May 18, 2007)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@pizza_pie pizza pie]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/pizza_pie">@pizza_pie</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>alright, adding <span class="bbcode-b">LOTS</span> more stuff, hopefully this gets popular again <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=6" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"> lol[br][size=1]Posted on: May 14, 2007, 05:44:37 PM[/size][hr]added!!!</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/bat-file-coding-tut-update-4-may-18-2007/93778/9">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/bat-file-coding-tut-update-4-may-18-2007/93778/9</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 19 May 2007 08:15:08 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-93778-9</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/bat-file-coding-tut-update-4-may-18-2007/93778.rss">&quot;.bat&quot; file coding, [TUT], update 4 (May 18, 2007)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>&quot;.bat&quot; file coding, [TUT], update 4 (May 18, 2007)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@ghostboy195 ghostboy195]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/ghostboy195">@ghostboy195</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>“cls” stands for Clear Screen. Its also the BASIC command for clearing the screen.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/bat-file-coding-tut-update-4-may-18-2007/93778/8">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/bat-file-coding-tut-update-4-may-18-2007/93778/8</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 14 May 2007 16:53:07 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-93778-8</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/bat-file-coding-tut-update-4-may-18-2007/93778.rss">&quot;.bat&quot; file coding, [TUT], update 4 (May 18, 2007)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>&quot;.bat&quot; file coding, [TUT], update 4 (May 18, 2007)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@pizza_pie pizza pie]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/pizza_pie">@pizza_pie</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>tyvm for the feedback alright, i will be adding on right now[br][size=1]Posted on: May 13, 2007, 10:44:51 PM[/size][hr]alright, added, check it out right now, i added some shortcuts, and if i remember something that i didnt put up there, i’ll make sure to post, please tell me of anything that doesnt make sense or any stuff you might think i didnt tell you about</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/bat-file-coding-tut-update-4-may-18-2007/93778/7">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/bat-file-coding-tut-update-4-may-18-2007/93778/7</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 14 May 2007 10:10:28 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-93778-7</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/bat-file-coding-tut-update-4-may-18-2007/93778.rss">&quot;.bat&quot; file coding, [TUT], update 4 (May 18, 2007)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>&quot;.bat&quot; file coding, [TUT], update 4 (May 18, 2007)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@mvp566 mvp566]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/mvp566">@mvp566</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Yes its definitely worth it. your work in good.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/bat-file-coding-tut-update-4-may-18-2007/93778/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/bat-file-coding-tut-update-4-may-18-2007/93778/6</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 14 May 2007 08:29:32 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-93778-6</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/bat-file-coding-tut-update-4-may-18-2007/93778.rss">&quot;.bat&quot; file coding, [TUT], update 4 (May 18, 2007)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>&quot;.bat&quot; file coding, [TUT], update 4 (May 18, 2007)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@pizza_pie pizza pie]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/pizza_pie">@pizza_pie</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>thanks, in a lil its going to be updated, if i think its worth adding on to</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/bat-file-coding-tut-update-4-may-18-2007/93778/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/bat-file-coding-tut-update-4-may-18-2007/93778/5</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 14 May 2007 03:38:22 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-93778-5</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/bat-file-coding-tut-update-4-may-18-2007/93778.rss">&quot;.bat&quot; file coding, [TUT], update 4 (May 18, 2007)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>&quot;.bat&quot; file coding, [TUT], update 4 (May 18, 2007)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@mvp566 mvp566]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/mvp566">@mvp566</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Nice tutorial, A+, nicely organized, good pictures… well done. and overall helpful</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/bat-file-coding-tut-update-4-may-18-2007/93778/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/bat-file-coding-tut-update-4-may-18-2007/93778/4</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 13 May 2007 22:34:49 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-93778-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/bat-file-coding-tut-update-4-may-18-2007/93778.rss">&quot;.bat&quot; file coding, [TUT], update 4 (May 18, 2007)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>&quot;.bat&quot; file coding, [TUT], update 4 (May 18, 2007)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@billygotshot billygotshot]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/billygotshot">@billygotshot</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>nice lol i shall use it or maybe not…</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/bat-file-coding-tut-update-4-may-18-2007/93778/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/bat-file-coding-tut-update-4-may-18-2007/93778/3</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 13 May 2007 19:34:15 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-93778-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/bat-file-coding-tut-update-4-may-18-2007/93778.rss">&quot;.bat&quot; file coding, [TUT], update 4 (May 18, 2007)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>&quot;.bat&quot; file coding, [TUT], update 4 (May 18, 2007)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@GoldenShard GoldenShard]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/goldenshard">@GoldenShard</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Good for you, nice work. Keep it up.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/bat-file-coding-tut-update-4-may-18-2007/93778/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/bat-file-coding-tut-update-4-may-18-2007/93778/2</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 13 May 2007 10:03:42 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-93778-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/bat-file-coding-tut-update-4-may-18-2007/93778.rss">&quot;.bat&quot; file coding, [TUT], update 4 (May 18, 2007)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>&quot;.bat&quot; file coding, [TUT], update 4 (May 18, 2007)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@pizza_pie pizza pie]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/pizza_pie">@pizza_pie</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p><span class="bbcode-b">Tutorial Name: </span> Batch Files<br>
<span class="bbcode-b">How hard 1-10: </span> 0.1<br>
<span class="bbcode-b">Required Skills: </span> Do you know how to type? if yes then you’ll be fine<br>
<span class="bbcode-b">Full Credits: </span> Me<br>
[center] <span class="bbcode-b">PLEASE READ THROUGH THIS IF YOU WANT TO KNOW COMMANDS OF THIS TYPE OF STUFF!!! DONT MISS OUT!!!</span>[/center]</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Tutorial: </span></p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Step 1:</span></p>
<p>Alright, lets get started, go to your desktop and create a new text document.<br>
right click &gt; new &gt; text document</p>
<p>Then, you rename it and make it say “Test.bat” make sure it ends with “.bat” not “.txt”<br>
alright we just got started</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Step 2:</span></p>
<p>Now, you right click and click the “edit” option</p>
<p>it opens as a text document, so now we always write one thing before we start: “<a class="mention" href="/u/echo">@echo</a> off”<br>
like this <code> @echo off</code><br>
nice isnt it, lol… kk so now, after you did that, we are going to get started with the simple stuff, like titles and how to make stuff display when you open it.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Step 3:</span></p>
<p>Okay, now, you type “:menu” or like “:startscreen” or something, i always make my starting place called menu, like this:</p>
<pre><code class="lang-auto">@echo off
:menu
title Test Program</code></pre>
<p>so now, you noticed i put “title Test Program” this means that when you open your file, the title will say “Test Program”</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Step 4:</span></p>
<p>This is a simple step, this is something you should do automatically right after you type the title, you click “enter” and you put “cls” i dont know exactly what that is abbreviating but it makes it so that all the letters from the screen dissappear, for instance, preten you were doing something and then you go back to your main menu, do you want al the words from your previous menu showing? if yes then skip this:</p>
<pre><code class="lang-auto">@echo off
:menu
title Test Program
cls</code></pre>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Step 5:</span></p>
<p>Now, we have to make it do something, for instance, say something</p>
<p>so you type “echo” and then two spaces and then what you want to say, you could type 1 space but it wouldnt look as good when it is finished, here is what it looks like now:</p>
<pre><code class="lang-auto">@echo off
:menu
title Test Program
cls
echo  Wootage, i made my test program!!!</code></pre>
<p>alright, now the last thing…</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Step 6:</span></p>
<p>this is the last step for your program, or at least this one:<br>
you put a “pause”, you know in some programs, it says “press any key to continue”? this is how they do it</p>
<pre><code class="lang-auto">@echo off
:menu
title Test Program
cls
echo  Wootage, i made my test program!!!
pause</code></pre>
<p>woo, nice, now if you were to save and then exit out and open ur file, it would look something liek this:</p>
<p><img src="http://i119.photobucket.com/albums/o158/Alex_Mirchev/batchfiletut.jpg" alt width="" height=""></p>
<p>here are the additional stuff you could add:</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Variables</span></p>
<p>Alright, if you have ever seen the ‘Perfect Compiler’ you would know what a variable is, it is where you can type something and if you type it, it will do a specific action, those are called variables</p>
<p>okay here is the code for a variable:</p>
<pre><code class="lang-auto">set /p option= Option: 
</code></pre>
<p>just remember, that both of the “options” can be changed, this is the standard format:</p>
<pre><code class="lang-auto">set /p (option name)= (text you want displayed)
</code></pre>
<p>the part that says “text you want displayed” would be this, for example, preted you wanted the people to chose from different colors, so where it says the second option you would type "Color: " and it would look like this:</p>
<p><img src="http://i119.photobucket.com/albums/o158/Alex_Mirchev/batchfiletut2.jpg" alt width="" height=""></p>
<p>alright, now that we know how to make a variable, lets make it so that if you typed something and clicked enter, it would go somewhere</p>
<p>okay here is the code from the ‘Perfect Compiler’:</p>
<pre><code class="lang-auto">set /p c=Option: 
if %c%==c goto c
if %c%==C goto c
if %c%==r goto r
if %c%==R goto r
if %c%==jar goto jar
if %c%==Jar goto jar
if %c%==JAR goto jar
if %c%==color goto color
if %c%==Color goto color
if %c%==COLOR goto color
if %c%==reset goto reset
if %c%==Reset goto reset
if %c%==RESET goto reset
if %c%==e goto e
if %c%==E goto e
if %c%==* goto er
goto er</code></pre>
<p>okay let me explain, the "set /p c= Option: " is makes option be dispayed, but the variable is actually called “c”<br>
so,  the “if %c%==c goto c” just means that if the person types “c” the program will to the part of the program that is labeled “:c” or</p>
<pre><code class="lang-auto">:c</code></pre>
<p>and then it goes on, the last one that says “if %c%==* goto er” means that if the person types anything else, it will take him to the “:er” part of the program, that is short for error.<br>
alright, to make it so that he can go to the error page, you gotta do this, go to the end of your code, press enter and type</p>
<pre><code class="lang-auto">:er</code></pre>
<p>so then if the program is told to goto er, it will look for “:er” and then it will do whatever that part of the program tells it to do, here is what i get when i try to compile without my JDK 1.6:</p>
<p><img src="http://i119.photobucket.com/albums/o158/Alex_Mirchev/batchfiletut3.jpg" alt width="" height=""><br>
like it? rofl<br>
this is the code that makes it do that:</p>
<pre><code class="lang-auto">:je
cls
title Error
echo You do not have JDK 5.0 or JDK 6.0 or any JDK 5.0 and 6.0 updates.
echo Go to Mod Taharok's tutorial on the Moparscape Tuturoials section
echo for step-by-step instructions to download the newest JDK Update.
pause
cls
goto menu</code></pre>
<p>so you get the part about creating the options</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Making History files</span></p>
<p>Okay, this is the part i had trouble with, but i know how to do it now<br>
this is the guide on how to make another program open if the person does or types something<br>
okay here we go, pretend you want to show the history of when you opened your program this is what it should look like:</p>
<pre><code class="lang-auto">@echo off
:menu
title Test
cls
echo  Welcome to this test program
echo  Editing history...
echo You have opened the "Test" program at %time% on %date% &gt;&gt; "history.txt"
pause
goto :menu</code></pre>
<p>alright, if you have read this guide, you will notice the begginer stuff, such as the title and all the echo stuff… but check out the part that says "echo You have opened the “Test” program at %time% on %date% &gt;&gt; “history.txt”<br>
that just means that it is going to type in a text document called “history.txt” (if there isnt one, the program automatically creates on by itself)</p>
<p>alright, here is the format for this:</p>
<pre><code class="lang-auto">echo (text here) &gt;&gt; "(name of file).txt"</code></pre>
<p>pretty easy…</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Opening Programs</span></p>
<p>alright, this is what you should do, you find out where the program.exe file is, for istance “iexplore.exe” is the internet explorer program, if you would like to open a website, you would do this:</p>
<pre><code class="lang-auto">"C:\Program Files\Internet Explorer\iexplore.exe" www.hemiscape.com/aarisair</code></pre>
<p>that opens this website, try it out if you like<br>
alright this is the standard format for this:</p>
<pre><code class="lang-auto">"C:\Program Files\Internet Explorer\iexplore.exe" (website url)</code></pre>
<p>its simple, but to open another program, such as a Microsoft Office Word Document, you would need to do this:</p>
<pre><code class="lang-auto">"C:\Program Files\Microsoft Office\Office10\Shortcut Bar\Office\Microsoft Word.exe"</code></pre>
<p>this is mine, but for someone else, it might be different… so you could do this:</p>
<pre><code class="lang-auto">"%programfiles%(url for .exe file)"</code></pre>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Colors</span></p>
<p>This is pretty simple, lets say you wanted to change the colors of the text and the background, you would make something like this in the begining, and i really love the way mod taharok does this, so lets use him again:</p>
<pre><code class="lang-auto">:back
cls
echo Please select a color to change the backround to:
echo.
echo black
echo white
echo red
echo yellow
echo green
echo blue
echo purple
echo.
echo.
set /p back=Color: 
if %back%== black (set b=0)
if %back%== white (set b=7)
if %back%== red (set b=4)
if %back%== yellow (set b=6)
if %back%== green (set b=2)
if %back%== blue (set b=1)
if %back%== purple (set b=5)
goto co2</code></pre>
<p>let me explain what this does, alright, as u can see, mod taharok gives the choices that you could chose from, those are just the simple colors<br>
okay, so we can see that in the beggining he has the “:back” to indicate that this is a chapter of his program, but, he does not include the “<a class="mention" href="/u/echo">@echo</a> off” because this is just part of his program, well, he made the variable so now if you typed one of the colors, it would change it to that. so this is how he starts off:</p>
<pre><code class="lang-auto">:back
cls
echo Please select a color to change the backround to:
echo.
echo black
echo white
echo red
echo yellow
echo green
echo blue
echo purple
echo.
echo.
set /p back=Color: </code></pre>
<p>this is just the begining, we all know by now how to do this, so then he adds the “if’s”:</p>
<pre><code class="lang-auto">if %back%== black (set b=0)
if %back%== white (set b=7)
if %back%== red (set b=4)
if %back%== yellow (set b=6)
if %back%== green (set b=2)
if %back%== blue (set b=1)
if %back%== purple (set b=5)
goto co2</code></pre>
<p>alright, now, we got the if’s, but i cant find in his code where he made the colors change so ill do it for him -.- lol<br>
this is what the complete code shud look like:</p>
<pre><code class="lang-auto">:back
cls
echo Please select a color to change the backround to:
echo.
echo black
echo white
echo red
echo yellow
echo green
echo blue
echo purple
echo.
echo.
set /p back=Color: 
if %back%== black (set b=0)
if %back%== white (set b=7)
if %back%== red (set b=4)
if %back%== yellow (set b=6)
if %back%== green (set b=2)
if %back%== blue (set b=1)
if %back%== purple (set b=5)
goto co2
:co2
title Changed
cls
color %b%%t%
echo Your color has been changed as you requested!
echo.
pause
goto menu</code></pre>
<p>ohh sory, i forgot to explain about how the color system works, okay, “b” and “t” are the color modifiers, you change the color by changing “%b%” and “%t%”, then you put the color to change to b and t, like this “color %b%%t%” doesnt matter what order, here is an example:</p>
<pre><code class="lang-auto">@echo off
set (b=5)
set (t=7)
color %b%%t%
pause</code></pre>
<p>alright, if you ahve the time, you could add this code to a .bat file, a new one, so that you can see how it works, you can modify it and change the “b” and “t” values in the second and third line of the code, or make a variable so you can easily access it… i hope you undersand</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Shortcuts</span></p>
<p>here are a couple shortcuts:<br>
<span class="bbcode-b">%time%</span> is for the file to show what time in military style  <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/cool.png?v=6" title=":cool:" class="emoji" alt=":cool:"><br>
<span class="bbcode-b">%date%</span> is for the file to say what the day is atm also  <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/cool.png?v=6" title=":cool:" class="emoji" alt=":cool:"><br>
<span class="bbcode-b">%programfiles%</span> is the shortcut so you dont have to type out the whole url of the place in program files, such as if you wanted to tell the .bat file to open up msn messenger, you would do this:</p>
<p><code>"C:\Program Files\Messenger\msnmsgs.exe"</code> but instead you can put</p>
<pre><code class="lang-auto">"%programfiles%Messenger\msnmsgs.exe"</code></pre>
<p>get it?<br>
<span class="bbcode-b">%b%</span> and <span class="bbcode-b">%t%</span> these are both for the color, they are set by default to (t=7) and (b=0). (if you were wondering “b” stands for the number of the background color and “t” stands for the number of the text color. so if you were to write (t=25) it is going to make (t=2) and (b=5). This way, both of the colors change, background and text color. but its confusing so try expirement with only 1 number per variable</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-i"><span class="bbcode-u">Alright, i think that this is all that i can teach you, this is just the basic commands of .bat files… explore it and you will find out a lot about this</span></span></p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Commands</span></p>
<p>did you know that if you were editing your .bat file, you could type this:</p>
<pre><code class="lang-auto">set</code></pre>
<p>this makes it so the screen fills up with shortcuts that you could type for any part of your computer, for instance, your home drive, its awesome. here is a pic:<br>
<img src="http://i119.photobucket.com/albums/o158/Alex_Mirchev/batchfiletut4.jpg" alt width="" height=""></p>
<p>cool isnt it, now if you took the words before the “=”, (like “path”=[trash], you would type %path% and it would display wutever is on the other side) so, if i were to write</p>
<pre><code class="lang-auto">@echo off
:menu
title Test
cls
echo.
echo  %path%
echo.
pause</code></pre>
<p>the batch file would show you what “path” is substituted for, here is a pic:<br>
<img src="http://i119.photobucket.com/albums/o158/Alex_Mirchev/batchfiletut5.jpg" alt width="" height=""></p>
<p>see what that is? just try it out…</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Deleting</span></p>
<p>Alright, pretend u were trying to make it so that if the person had something like, a file that might contain a virus, such as a .exe file, and u wanted to make it delete that file, u wut do this:</p>
<pre><code class="lang-auto">@echo off
title Virus Deletion
cls
del *.exe
echo  Deleted all possible viruses.
echo.
pause</code></pre>
<p>This would make it delete any file that has the extension .exe, now if u wanted to make sure that he has that file before it tries to delete it, lets say the virus name is virus.exe, you would do this:</p>
<pre><code class="lang-auto">@echo off
title Virus Deletion
cls
if exist virus.exe (goto exists) else (goto noexists)
:exists
del virus.exe
echo  Deleted all possible viruses.
echo.
pause
:noexists
echo No virus detected
echo.
pause</code></pre>
<p>this will make it so that it checks if the virus.exe exists and will delete it and notify you, but if it doestn exist, it will tell you that there was no virus<br>
alright, now continue to the next part</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Pop-up Messages</span></p>
<p>lets say you wanted to make a message pop up instead of making it just echo…<br>
you could do this:</p>
<pre><code class="lang-auto">@echo off
:menu
title Test
cls
echo.
echo  Testing the popup message...
echo.
echo.
msg * YOU GOT TESTED!!
pause
exit</code></pre>
<p>it might not work on some older computers… lol works on my laptop but not on my home computer<br>
if it works, its pretty awesome</p>
<p>so just play around with all the stuff u just learned and enjoy</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">PLEASE READ</span><br>
this is all the time i have so i have to post this, if you want to get the update, it will say “.bat” file coding, TUT 3" not “TUT 2” and then it will say the date it was updated alrighht plz comment</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/bat-file-coding-tut-update-4-may-18-2007/93778/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/bat-file-coding-tut-update-4-may-18-2007/93778/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 13 May 2007 08:49:43 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-93778-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/bat-file-coding-tut-update-4-may-18-2007/93778.rss">&quot;.bat&quot; file coding, [TUT], update 4 (May 18, 2007)</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
