<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Quarion - Putting Your Imagination into Perspective</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/quarion-putting-your-imagination-into-perspective/396688</link>
    <description>NOTE: I will not be updating this post, so if you would like to see more updates, head to my update log at [URL=http://quarion.org/smf/index.php]http://quarion.org/smf/index.php[/URL].

I came to a decision of creating a server based out of my original base so people can play. The server will contain many nice features that most current RuneScape games don&#39;t, such as perfect skills and combat effects, numerous details that will make the hair on your back tingle, and countless players that will keep the community going fullspeed into the top server lists. Many of today&#39;s servers contain little to no server features and do everything by ::commands. Here at Quarion, we believe in a no command layout just to give our players more feeling and enjoyment instead of just typing some command.

We also strive for professional work; we don&#39;t make spelling mistakes or .tk domains, nor do we spam servers or DDoS others to get more traffic to ours. We simply believe that our server will get filled with players thanks to our perfection. Currently, we will be gaining players, and soon we will be opening staff applications on our forums. If you would like to see the benefits a staff member can gain, please look on our forums under the &quot;Staff Information&quot; thread located in the &quot;Staff Applications&quot; board.

Now, enough of all this boring text about our server; don&#39;t you want to see some updates and features?





Great details
-Everything you can imagine, from milking cows to producing flour from wheat at the flour mill

All NPCs have dialogues
-Not just random messages, but actual conversations you can have with anyone!

Monsters and Bosses
-All monsters drop their appropriate loot! With all their emotes and effects, you&#39;ll get addicted to killing them!

Skills
-All skills are made to give skillers and pkers a wonderful expierience. No more stupid commands, but realistic interfaces and emotes with their correct graphics!

PKing
-All weapons have correct pricing and effects with specials and graphics perfectly adjointing RuneScape&#39;s specials (in 2007). All combat forms work perfectly, and there is perfect hybriding.

Money gaining
-I have enough of all these servers that thrive on stalls for money. On Quarion, you can gain money through many ways, like pickpocketing, monster drops, pking artifacts (if your in bounty hunter), and many more.

Minigames
-We have many minigames that players love. On Quarion, we don&#39;t half ass anything, especially minigames. We have full castle wars, pest control, clan wars, bounty hunter, and many other options to choose from. 

Suggestions
-Do you have a suggestion? Post a thread under the &quot;Suggestions&quot; board and we will take it under perspective. Too lazy? Well you can simply buy a &quot;Suggestion Form&quot; and fill it out while your playing! 





Combat
-Full melee combat.
-Ranging combat is fully working with all graphics, timers, projectiles and emotes.
-Magic is completely done, it&#39;s simply perfect thanks to Slimdar.
-Defence has a very simple start, with reducing attack hits when it&#39;s levels are higher.

Prayer
-All bones work with correct animations.
-Correct XP rates with each bone.
-Bone on altar works, burying bones in a graveyard gives extra XP.

Thieving
-All objected stalls, turners, safes, etc. work as they should.
-Working on NPC thieving, will be superb once I&#39;m done.
-All stalls and other thieving objects give special items.

Herblore
-Herb identifying works perfectly.
-All potions have correct effects and timings.
-Potion mixing works with all potions to the full extent.
-All formulas work correctly except a few that I can&#39;t find.

Fletching
-All bolts, arrows, shafts, bows, crossbows, etc work perfectly.
-All item makings give correct XP rates.
-All anims and graphics work great with timers.

Crafting
-All gems can get cut, then turned into bolt tips.
-All dragon hides give good interfaces and results.
-All jewelry and other nicknacks work to true full extent.

Mining
-All rocks &quot;lose ore&quot; when mined with correct timing delays.
-Full, flawless object to object conversion.
-All correct animations and graphics, you don&#39;t need to hold pickaxe to use.
-Prospecting rocks is almost complete.

Smithing
-All items on the smithing interface up to Mithril work 100%.
-All anims work fully.
-All different metals work correctly and give the right amount of items for bars.
-interface highlighting due to how many bars you have in your inventory.

Woodcutting
-Worked alot on this, probably my most worked skill.
-Stump creating.
-Correct log givings, random amount of logs given by each type of tree.
-Birds nests ramdomly given, really sexy system.
-Ent changing, you bet it, object to NPC changing works 100%.
-Other little details; too many to give.

Firemaking
-Full firemaking, you better believe it. 
-All logs work, from normal logs to pyre magic logs to colorful logs, etc.
-Every single little detail, from lamps to candles to lanterns.. They all work.
-Other numerous details I won&#39;t list because it would take forever.

Fishing
-Full Harpooning.
-Full lobster caving.
-Full baiting and feather fishing.
-All random events like whirlpools and river trolls work fully.
-Different types of fishing pool spawns, they pick random locations to spawn.

Cooking
-Another skill I worked on slot.
-All foods can be cooked, burning is a possibility depending on your level.
-All foods can be eaten with their correct healings (even sweets).
-Stoves work better than fires.

Runecrafting
-All runes work with their altar.
-Tiara makings work with each altar, and if you wear one, you dont need a talisman.
-All pouches work, took a long time but was pretty easy at the end.

Agility
-Running is perceived and reduced by the level of your agility.
-All courses except a few that are in the wilderness are fully working and done with emotes and graphics.

Farming
-All herb farmings work.
-Every player has their own herbMask updates in their client.
-You can assign someone else to farm your herbs for you.
-Trees, plants, weeds, compost heaps, you name it; they all work.




Castle Wars
-All portals lead to their right place
Middle portal gives a random teleporting.
-If player is wearing cape or hat, cannot enter.
-Once in, player receives hood and cape.
-Once in-game, player cannot attack his own.
-After 5 deaths, players are returned to portals.
-All ladders working.
-Many NPC dialogues all over the arenas.
-Medical tabs are working.
-Kill counts and point rewards.

Pest Control
-All pest control NPCs right by portals
-All NPCs are aggressive
-Multiple attack styles (magic, ranging, melee)
-Void knight in the middle with a chat
-All ladders working and dialogues with NPCs.
-New interfaces with boats, etc.
-NPCs spawning from portals and heading to attack void knight

Bounty Hunter
-Skill will be released on the beginning of June, but so far we have:
-Proper headIcons to distribute how much wealth a player has.
-Teleporting to your bounty working
-New maps integrated into the client for the actual Runescape feeling

Clan Wars
-Clan wars portals working
-You can only enter if your in a clan currently
-You are on the selected team that you are chosen for
-Clan people left/killed numbers of other clan is listed on top
-Capes are optional


[IMG]http://i841.photobucket.com/albums/zz334/CoderNexus/5-27-201110-00-46PM.png[/img]

[IMG]http://i841.photobucket.com/albums/zz334/CoderNexus/5-21-20119-09-39PM-1.png[/img]

[IMG]http://i841.photobucket.com/albums/zz334/CoderNexus/5-26-201110-13-38PM.png[/img]

[IMG]http://i841.photobucket.com/albums/zz334/CoderNexus/5-26-20117-04-35PM.png[/img]

[IMG]http://i841.photobucket.com/albums/zz334/CoderNexus/5-26-20119-01-00PM.png[/img]

[IMG]http://i841.photobucket.com/albums/zz334/CoderNexus/5-26-20119-01-56PM.png[/img]

[IMG]http://i841.photobucket.com/albums/zz334/CoderNexus/5-26-20119-04-00PM.png[/img]

[IMG]http://i841.photobucket.com/albums/zz334/CoderNexus/5-26-20119-04-47PM.png[/img]

[IMG]http://i841.photobucket.com/albums/zz334/CoderNexus/5-26-20119-05-00PM.png[/img]

[IMG]http://i841.photobucket.com/albums/zz334/CoderNexus/5-26-20119-08-27PM.png[/img]

[IMG]http://i841.photobucket.com/albums/zz334/CoderNexus/5-26-20119-09-26PM.png[/img]

[IMG]http://i841.photobucket.com/albums/zz334/CoderNexus/5-26-20119-10-16PM.png[/img]

[IMG]http://i841.photobucket.com/albums/zz334/CoderNexus/5-26-20119-10-29PM.png[/img]

[IMG]http://i841.photobucket.com/albums/zz334/CoderNexus/5-26-20119-11-03PM.png[/img]

[IMG]http://i841.photobucket.com/albums/zz334/CoderNexus/5-26-20119-12-59PM.png[/img]

[IMG]http://i841.photobucket.com/albums/zz334/CoderNexus/5-26-20119-15-18PM.png[/img]

[IMG]http://i841.photobucket.com/albums/zz334/CoderNexus/5-26-20119-17-57PM.png[/img]

[IMG]http://i841.photobucket.com/albums/zz334/CoderNexus/5-26-20119-18-14PM.png[/img]

[size=24pt][b]Supporting pictures: PM me yours if you want to be on here![/b][/size]
[IMG]http://i841.photobucket.com/albums/zz334/CoderNexus/2011-05-2714-01-07769.jpg[/img]
[IMG]http://i841.photobucket.com/albums/zz334/CoderNexus/5ocfvp.jpg[/img]

Thanks for looking at my thread, post some comments. I love criticism.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 28 May 2011 03:58:42 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/quarion-putting-your-imagination-into-perspective/396688.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Quarion - Putting Your Imagination into Perspective</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Loveandpower Loveandpower]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/loveandpower">@Loveandpower</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“zaz278, post:6, topic:396688”]Isn’t this hyperion?[/quote]It is</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/quarion-putting-your-imagination-into-perspective/396688/7">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/quarion-putting-your-imagination-into-perspective/396688/7</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 28 May 2011 03:58:42 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-396688-7</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/quarion-putting-your-imagination-into-perspective/396688.rss">Quarion - Putting Your Imagination into Perspective</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Quarion - Putting Your Imagination into Perspective</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@zaz278 zaz278]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/zaz278">@zaz278</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Isn’t this hyperion?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/quarion-putting-your-imagination-into-perspective/396688/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/quarion-putting-your-imagination-into-perspective/396688/6</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 28 May 2011 03:58:17 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-396688-6</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/quarion-putting-your-imagination-into-perspective/396688.rss">Quarion - Putting Your Imagination into Perspective</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Quarion - Putting Your Imagination into Perspective</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Loveandpower Loveandpower]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/loveandpower">@Loveandpower</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>It’s a very stable server. <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=5" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/quarion-putting-your-imagination-into-perspective/396688/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/quarion-putting-your-imagination-into-perspective/396688/5</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 28 May 2011 03:29:48 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-396688-5</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/quarion-putting-your-imagination-into-perspective/396688.rss">Quarion - Putting Your Imagination into Perspective</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Quarion - Putting Your Imagination into Perspective</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@asshole_rule asshole_rule]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/asshole_rule">@asshole_rule</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“Nexus_, post:3, topic:396688”][quote author=asshole_rule link=topic=493859.msg3610612#msg3610612 date=1306551583]<br>
Looks average, I see nothing unique. Sorry <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/confused.png?v=5" title=":confused:" class="emoji" alt=":confused:"><br>
[/quote]<br>
I dont understand what unique is anymore. What the hell do people want? 3D graphics?[/quote]</p>
<p>That’s the hard part… Once you finally do think of something unique it’ll be appreciated though.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/quarion-putting-your-imagination-into-perspective/396688/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/quarion-putting-your-imagination-into-perspective/396688/4</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 28 May 2011 03:06:27 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-396688-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/quarion-putting-your-imagination-into-perspective/396688.rss">Quarion - Putting Your Imagination into Perspective</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Quarion - Putting Your Imagination into Perspective</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Nexus1 Nexus_]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/nexus1">@Nexus1</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote" data-post="2" data-topic="396688">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/asshole_rule/40/5_e05bb34c421432ee4d40de30c10af3e5.png" class="avatar"> asshole_rule:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Looks average, I see nothing unique. Sorry <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/confused.png?v=5" title=":confused:" class="emoji" alt=":confused:"></p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I dont understand what unique is anymore. What the hell do people want? 3D graphics?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/quarion-putting-your-imagination-into-perspective/396688/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/quarion-putting-your-imagination-into-perspective/396688/3</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 28 May 2011 03:03:12 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-396688-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/quarion-putting-your-imagination-into-perspective/396688.rss">Quarion - Putting Your Imagination into Perspective</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Quarion - Putting Your Imagination into Perspective</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@asshole_rule asshole_rule]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/asshole_rule">@asshole_rule</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Looks average, I see nothing unique. Sorry <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/confused.png?v=5" title=":confused:" class="emoji" alt=":confused:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/quarion-putting-your-imagination-into-perspective/396688/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/quarion-putting-your-imagination-into-perspective/396688/2</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 28 May 2011 02:59:43 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-396688-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/quarion-putting-your-imagination-into-perspective/396688.rss">Quarion - Putting Your Imagination into Perspective</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Quarion - Putting Your Imagination into Perspective</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Nexus1 Nexus_]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/nexus1">@Nexus1</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>NOTE: I will not be updating this post, so if you would like to see more updates, head to my update log at <a href="http://quarion.org/smf/index.php" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">http://quarion.org/smf/index.php</a>.</p>
<p>I came to a decision of creating a server based out of my original base so people can play. The server will contain many nice features that most current RuneScape games don’t, such as perfect skills and combat effects, numerous details that will make the hair on your back tingle, and countless players that will keep the community going fullspeed into the top server lists. Many of today’s servers contain little to no server features and do everything by ::commands. Here at Quarion, we believe in a no command layout just to give our players more feeling and enjoyment instead of just typing some command.</p>
<p>We also strive for professional work; we don’t make spelling mistakes or .tk domains, nor do we spam servers or DDoS others to get more traffic to ours. We simply believe that our server will get filled with players thanks to our perfection. Currently, we will be gaining players, and soon we will be opening staff applications on our forums. If you would like to see the benefits a staff member can gain, please look on our forums under the “Staff Information” thread located in the “Staff Applications” board.</p>
<p>Now, enough of all this boring text about our server; don’t you want to see some updates and features?</p>
<p>Great details<br>
-Everything you can imagine, from milking cows to producing flour from wheat at the flour mill</p>
<p>All NPCs have dialogues<br>
-Not just random messages, but actual conversations you can have with anyone!</p>
<p>Monsters and Bosses<br>
-All monsters drop their appropriate loot! With all their emotes and effects, you’ll get addicted to killing them!</p>
<p>Skills<br>
-All skills are made to give skillers and pkers a wonderful expierience. No more stupid commands, but realistic interfaces and emotes with their correct graphics!</p>
<p>PKing<br>
-All weapons have correct pricing and effects with specials and graphics perfectly adjointing RuneScape’s specials (in 2007). All combat forms work perfectly, and there is perfect hybriding.</p>
<p>Money gaining<br>
-I have enough of all these servers that thrive on stalls for money. On Quarion, you can gain money through many ways, like pickpocketing, monster drops, pking artifacts (if your in bounty hunter), and many more.</p>
<p>Minigames<br>
-We have many minigames that players love. On Quarion, we don’t half ass anything, especially minigames. We have full castle wars, pest control, clan wars, bounty hunter, and many other options to choose from.</p>
<p>Suggestions<br>
-Do you have a suggestion? Post a thread under the “Suggestions” board and we will take it under perspective. Too lazy? Well you can simply buy a “Suggestion Form” and fill it out while your playing!</p>
<p>Combat<br>
-Full melee combat.<br>
-Ranging combat is fully working with all graphics, timers, projectiles and emotes.<br>
-Magic is completely done, it’s simply perfect thanks to Slimdar.<br>
-Defence has a very simple start, with reducing attack hits when it’s levels are higher.</p>
<p>Prayer<br>
-All bones work with correct animations.<br>
-Correct XP rates with each bone.<br>
-Bone on altar works, burying bones in a graveyard gives extra XP.</p>
<p>Thieving<br>
-All objected stalls, turners, safes, etc. work as they should.<br>
-Working on NPC thieving, will be superb once I’m done.<br>
-All stalls and other thieving objects give special items.</p>
<p>Herblore<br>
-Herb identifying works perfectly.<br>
-All potions have correct effects and timings.<br>
-Potion mixing works with all potions to the full extent.<br>
-All formulas work correctly except a few that I can’t find.</p>
<p>Fletching<br>
-All bolts, arrows, shafts, bows, crossbows, etc work perfectly.<br>
-All item makings give correct XP rates.<br>
-All anims and graphics work great with timers.</p>
<p>Crafting<br>
-All gems can get cut, then turned into bolt tips.<br>
-All dragon hides give good interfaces and results.<br>
-All jewelry and other nicknacks work to true full extent.</p>
<p>Mining<br>
-All rocks “lose ore” when mined with correct timing delays.<br>
-Full, flawless object to object conversion.<br>
-All correct animations and graphics, you don’t need to hold pickaxe to use.<br>
-Prospecting rocks is almost complete.</p>
<p>Smithing<br>
-All items on the smithing interface up to Mithril work 100%.<br>
-All anims work fully.<br>
-All different metals work correctly and give the right amount of items for bars.<br>
-interface highlighting due to how many bars you have in your inventory.</p>
<p>Woodcutting<br>
-Worked alot on this, probably my most worked skill.<br>
-Stump creating.<br>
-Correct log givings, random amount of logs given by each type of tree.<br>
-Birds nests ramdomly given, really sexy system.<br>
-Ent changing, you bet it, object to NPC changing works 100%.<br>
-Other little details; too many to give.</p>
<p>Firemaking<br>
-Full firemaking, you better believe it.<br>
-All logs work, from normal logs to pyre magic logs to colorful logs, etc.<br>
-Every single little detail, from lamps to candles to lanterns… They all work.<br>
-Other numerous details I won’t list because it would take forever.</p>
<p>Fishing<br>
-Full Harpooning.<br>
-Full lobster caving.<br>
-Full baiting and feather fishing.<br>
-All random events like whirlpools and river trolls work fully.<br>
-Different types of fishing pool spawns, they pick random locations to spawn.</p>
<p>Cooking<br>
-Another skill I worked on slot.<br>
-All foods can be cooked, burning is a possibility depending on your level.<br>
-All foods can be eaten with their correct healings (even sweets).<br>
-Stoves work better than fires.</p>
<p>Runecrafting<br>
-All runes work with their altar.<br>
-Tiara makings work with each altar, and if you wear one, you dont need a talisman.<br>
-All pouches work, took a long time but was pretty easy at the end.</p>
<p>Agility<br>
-Running is perceived and reduced by the level of your agility.<br>
-All courses except a few that are in the wilderness are fully working and done with emotes and graphics.</p>
<p>Farming<br>
-All herb farmings work.<br>
-Every player has their own herbMask updates in their client.<br>
-You can assign someone else to farm your herbs for you.<br>
-Trees, plants, weeds, compost heaps, you name it; they all work.</p>
<p>Castle Wars<br>
-All portals lead to their right place<br>
Middle portal gives a random teleporting.<br>
-If player is wearing cape or hat, cannot enter.<br>
-Once in, player receives hood and cape.<br>
-Once in-game, player cannot attack his own.<br>
-After 5 deaths, players are returned to portals.<br>
-All ladders working.<br>
-Many NPC dialogues all over the arenas.<br>
-Medical tabs are working.<br>
-Kill counts and point rewards.</p>
<p>Pest Control<br>
-All pest control NPCs right by portals<br>
-All NPCs are aggressive<br>
-Multiple attack styles (magic, ranging, melee)<br>
-Void knight in the middle with a chat<br>
-All ladders working and dialogues with NPCs.<br>
-New interfaces with boats, etc.<br>
-NPCs spawning from portals and heading to attack void knight</p>
<p>Bounty Hunter<br>
-Skill will be released on the beginning of June, but so far we have:<br>
-Proper headIcons to distribute how much wealth a player has.<br>
-Teleporting to your bounty working<br>
-New maps integrated into the client for the actual Runescape feeling</p>
<p>Clan Wars<br>
-Clan wars portals working<br>
-You can only enter if your in a clan currently<br>
-You are on the selected team that you are chosen for<br>
-Clan people left/killed numbers of other clan is listed on top<br>
-Capes are optional</p>
<p><div class="lightbox-wrapper"><a class="lightbox" href="http://i841.photobucket.com/albums/zz334/CoderNexus/5-27-201110-00-46PM.png" title="5-27-201110-00-46PM.png" rel="nofollow noopener"><img src="http://i841.photobucket.com/albums/zz334/CoderNexus/5-27-201110-00-46PM.png" alt width="690" height="200"><div class="meta">
<svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-far-image svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#far-image"></use></svg><span class="filename">5-27-201110-00-46PM.png</span><span class="informations">958×278</span><svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-discourse-expand svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#discourse-expand"></use></svg>
</div></a></div></p>
<p><div class="lightbox-wrapper"><a class="lightbox" href="http://i841.photobucket.com/albums/zz334/CoderNexus/5-21-20119-09-39PM-1.png" title="5-21-20119-09-39PM-1.png" rel="nofollow noopener"><img src="http://i841.photobucket.com/albums/zz334/CoderNexus/5-21-20119-09-39PM-1.png" alt width="532" height="500"><div class="meta">
<svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-far-image svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#far-image"></use></svg><span class="filename">5-21-20119-09-39PM-1.png</span><span class="informations">964×905</span><svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-discourse-expand svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#discourse-expand"></use></svg>
</div></a></div></p>
<p><div class="lightbox-wrapper"><a class="lightbox" href="http://i841.photobucket.com/albums/zz334/CoderNexus/5-26-201110-13-38PM.png" title="5-26-201110-13-38PM.png" rel="nofollow noopener"><img src="http://i841.photobucket.com/albums/zz334/CoderNexus/5-26-201110-13-38PM.png" alt width="690" height="472"><div class="meta">
<svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-far-image svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#far-image"></use></svg><span class="filename">5-26-201110-13-38PM.png</span><span class="informations">771×528</span><svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-discourse-expand svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#discourse-expand"></use></svg>
</div></a></div></p>
<p><img src="http://i841.photobucket.com/albums/zz334/CoderNexus/5-26-20117-04-35PM.png" alt width="244" height="332"></p>
<p><div class="lightbox-wrapper"><a class="lightbox" href="http://i841.photobucket.com/albums/zz334/CoderNexus/5-26-20119-01-00PM.png" title="5-26-20119-01-00PM.png" rel="nofollow noopener"><img src="http://i841.photobucket.com/albums/zz334/CoderNexus/5-26-20119-01-00PM.png" alt width="690" height="472"><div class="meta">
<svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-far-image svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#far-image"></use></svg><span class="filename">5-26-20119-01-00PM.png</span><span class="informations">771×528</span><svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-discourse-expand svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#discourse-expand"></use></svg>
</div></a></div></p>
<p><div class="lightbox-wrapper"><a class="lightbox" href="http://i841.photobucket.com/albums/zz334/CoderNexus/5-26-20119-01-56PM.png" title="5-26-20119-01-56PM.png" rel="nofollow noopener"><img src="http://i841.photobucket.com/albums/zz334/CoderNexus/5-26-20119-01-56PM.png" alt width="690" height="322"><div class="meta">
<svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-far-image svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#far-image"></use></svg><span class="filename">5-26-20119-01-56PM.png</span><span class="informations">1024×479</span><svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-discourse-expand svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#discourse-expand"></use></svg>
</div></a></div></p>
<p><img src="http://i841.photobucket.com/albums/zz334/CoderNexus/5-26-20119-04-00PM.png" alt width="519" height="478"></p>
<p><div class="lightbox-wrapper"><a class="lightbox" href="http://i841.photobucket.com/albums/zz334/CoderNexus/5-26-20119-04-47PM.png" title="5-26-20119-04-47PM.png" rel="nofollow noopener"><img src="http://i841.photobucket.com/albums/zz334/CoderNexus/5-26-20119-04-47PM.png" alt width="690" height="472"><div class="meta">
<svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-far-image svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#far-image"></use></svg><span class="filename">5-26-20119-04-47PM.png</span><span class="informations">771×528</span><svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-discourse-expand svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#discourse-expand"></use></svg>
</div></a></div></p>
<p><div class="lightbox-wrapper"><a class="lightbox" href="http://i841.photobucket.com/albums/zz334/CoderNexus/5-26-20119-05-00PM.png" title="5-26-20119-05-00PM.png" rel="nofollow noopener"><img src="http://i841.photobucket.com/albums/zz334/CoderNexus/5-26-20119-05-00PM.png" alt width="690" height="472"><div class="meta">
<svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-far-image svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#far-image"></use></svg><span class="filename">5-26-20119-05-00PM.png</span><span class="informations">771×528</span><svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-discourse-expand svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#discourse-expand"></use></svg>
</div></a></div></p>
<p><div class="lightbox-wrapper"><a class="lightbox" href="http://i841.photobucket.com/albums/zz334/CoderNexus/5-26-20119-08-27PM.png" title="5-26-20119-08-27PM.png" rel="nofollow noopener"><img src="http://i841.photobucket.com/albums/zz334/CoderNexus/5-26-20119-08-27PM.png" alt width="690" height="452"><div class="meta">
<svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-far-image svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#far-image"></use></svg><span class="filename">5-26-20119-08-27PM.png</span><span class="informations">1021×669</span><svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-discourse-expand svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#discourse-expand"></use></svg>
</div></a></div></p>
<p><div class="lightbox-wrapper"><a class="lightbox" href="http://i841.photobucket.com/albums/zz334/CoderNexus/5-26-20119-09-26PM.png" title="5-26-20119-09-26PM.png" rel="nofollow noopener"><img src="http://i841.photobucket.com/albums/zz334/CoderNexus/5-26-20119-09-26PM.png" alt width="690" height="472"><div class="meta">
<svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-far-image svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#far-image"></use></svg><span class="filename">5-26-20119-09-26PM.png</span><span class="informations">771×528</span><svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-discourse-expand svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#discourse-expand"></use></svg>
</div></a></div></p>
<p><div class="lightbox-wrapper"><a class="lightbox" href="http://i841.photobucket.com/albums/zz334/CoderNexus/5-26-20119-10-16PM.png" title="5-26-20119-10-16PM.png" rel="nofollow noopener"><img src="http://i841.photobucket.com/albums/zz334/CoderNexus/5-26-20119-10-16PM.png" alt width="690" height="472"><div class="meta">
<svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-far-image svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#far-image"></use></svg><span class="filename">5-26-20119-10-16PM.png</span><span class="informations">771×528</span><svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-discourse-expand svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#discourse-expand"></use></svg>
</div></a></div></p>
<p><div class="lightbox-wrapper"><a class="lightbox" href="http://i841.photobucket.com/albums/zz334/CoderNexus/5-26-20119-10-29PM.png" title="5-26-20119-10-29PM.png" rel="nofollow noopener"><img src="http://i841.photobucket.com/albums/zz334/CoderNexus/5-26-20119-10-29PM.png" alt width="690" height="472"><div class="meta">
<svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-far-image svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#far-image"></use></svg><span class="filename">5-26-20119-10-29PM.png</span><span class="informations">771×528</span><svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-discourse-expand svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#discourse-expand"></use></svg>
</div></a></div></p>
<p><div class="lightbox-wrapper"><a class="lightbox" href="http://i841.photobucket.com/albums/zz334/CoderNexus/5-26-20119-11-03PM.png" title="5-26-20119-11-03PM.png" rel="nofollow noopener"><img src="http://i841.photobucket.com/albums/zz334/CoderNexus/5-26-20119-11-03PM.png" alt width="690" height="472"><div class="meta">
<svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-far-image svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#far-image"></use></svg><span class="filename">5-26-20119-11-03PM.png</span><span class="informations">771×528</span><svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-discourse-expand svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#discourse-expand"></use></svg>
</div></a></div></p>
<p><div class="lightbox-wrapper"><a class="lightbox" href="http://i841.photobucket.com/albums/zz334/CoderNexus/5-26-20119-12-59PM.png" title="5-26-20119-12-59PM.png" rel="nofollow noopener"><img src="http://i841.photobucket.com/albums/zz334/CoderNexus/5-26-20119-12-59PM.png" alt width="690" height="472"><div class="meta">
<svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-far-image svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#far-image"></use></svg><span class="filename">5-26-20119-12-59PM.png</span><span class="informations">771×528</span><svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-discourse-expand svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#discourse-expand"></use></svg>
</div></a></div></p>
<p><div class="lightbox-wrapper"><a class="lightbox" href="http://i841.photobucket.com/albums/zz334/CoderNexus/5-26-20119-15-18PM.png" title="5-26-20119-15-18PM.png" rel="nofollow noopener"><img src="http://i841.photobucket.com/albums/zz334/CoderNexus/5-26-20119-15-18PM.png" alt width="690" height="472"><div class="meta">
<svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-far-image svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#far-image"></use></svg><span class="filename">5-26-20119-15-18PM.png</span><span class="informations">771×528</span><svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-discourse-expand svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#discourse-expand"></use></svg>
</div></a></div></p>
<p><img src="http://i841.photobucket.com/albums/zz334/CoderNexus/5-26-20119-17-57PM.png" alt width="511" height="332"></p>
<p><img src="http://i841.photobucket.com/albums/zz334/CoderNexus/5-26-20119-18-14PM.png" alt width="511" height="332"></p>
<p>[size=24pt]<span class="bbcode-b">Supporting pictures: PM me yours if you want to be on here!</span>[/size]<br>
<img src="http://i841.photobucket.com/albums/zz334/CoderNexus/2011-05-2714-01-07769.jpg" alt width="640" height="480"><br>
<img src="http://i841.photobucket.com/albums/zz334/CoderNexus/5ocfvp.jpg" alt width="354" height="480"></p>
<p>Thanks for looking at my thread, post some comments. I love criticism.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/quarion-putting-your-imagination-into-perspective/396688/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/quarion-putting-your-imagination-into-perspective/396688/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 28 May 2011 02:56:32 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-396688-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/quarion-putting-your-imagination-into-perspective/396688.rss">Quarion - Putting Your Imagination into Perspective</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
