<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Lol some joke , *Note* Overrated</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/lol-some-joke-note-overrated/75087</link>
    <description> :rolleyes:

 Ok Well this joke might get a little carried away i might get banned im not sure please tell me i wont do again mods. But heres the first way of the joke.



One day a little boy was walking home fro  school an hears his mom yell &quot;you bitches, you bastards&quot; to the neighbors. he says &quot;mommy what does that mean?&quot; &quot;oh its jus another word for ladies and gentlemen&quot; she says. he gos in the house and hears her say &quot;OH SHIT!&quot; in the bathroom. &quot;mommy what does that mean he says agin. &quot;oh, its another word for putting makeup on your face&quot; she says. then he gos to the kitchen an hears his dad say &quot;oh fuck!!&quot; he said &quot;daddy what does that mean?&quot; &quot;oh, its another word for preparing a lobster&quot; he says. later that night some geusts came for a party and the boy was all like &quot;hey bitches and bastards! my moms in the kitchen wiping shit on her face, and my dads in the kitchen fucking a lobster&quot;.
----------

Second way of joke notice the differences!


A little boy was listening to his parents argue. The mother called the father a bastard and the father called to mother a bitch. Later on the little boy asked his parents what those words meant. &quot;bastard just means gentlemen and bitch just means lady,&quot; they explained to their eager son.

A few days later the son caught them having sex. As he listened on he heard his mother say &quot;DICK! DICK!&quot; and his father say &quot;PUSSY! PUSSY!&quot; When theY realized that he had been standing there, they stopped immediatly.

The son asked what those words meant. &quot;Dick is simply another word for Hat and Pussy is just another word for jacket.&quot; they tried explaining. &quot;OKAY!&quot; the boy said and walked off.

On thanksgiving a while before their party guests began to arrive the boy followed his father around anxiously. As the father was shaving his cut himself and screamed &quot;SHIT!&quot; &quot;daddy, what does shit mean?&quot; the father became quite and said, &quot;oh, its just another word for shaving cream, now go downstairs and help your mom out in the kitchen.&quot;

The boy did as he was told. The mom who was stuffing the turkey got poked with a jagged bone and screamed &quot;FUCK!&quot; The curious boy asked, &quot;Mommy what does Fuck mean?&quot; The mother became embarrased at her inappropriate language and said, &quot;uh...its just another word for stuffing the turkey.&quot; when she said this the doorbell rang. &quot;go and answer that, the guests are here.&quot; &quot;OKAY!&quot; the little boy said excitedly.

As he opened the door he said, &quot;HI ALL YOU BITCHES AND BASTARDS! GIVE ME YOUR DICKS AND PUSSYS AND MY MOM WILL BE OUT AS SOON AS SHES FINISHED FUCKING THE TURKEY AND MY DAD WILL BE OUT AS SOON AS HE GETS THAT WHITE SHIT OFF HIS FACE!&quot;</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 06 Apr 2007 08:24:09 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>General Discussion</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/lol-some-joke-note-overrated/75087.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Lol some joke , *Note* Overrated</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@P3nt P3nt]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/p3nt">@P3nt</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>:rolleyes:</p>
<p>Ok Well this joke might get a little carried away i might get banned im not sure please tell me i wont do again mods. But heres the first way of the joke.</p>
<h2>One day a little boy was walking home fro  school an hears his mom yell “you bitches, you bastards” to the neighbors. he says “mommy what does that mean?” “oh its jus another word for ladies and gentlemen” she says. he gos in the house and hears her say “OH SHIT!” in the bathroom. "mommy what does that mean he says agin. “oh, its another word for putting makeup on your face” she says. then he gos to the kitchen an hears his dad say “oh fuck!!” he said “daddy what does that mean?” “oh, its another word for preparing a lobster” he says. later that night some geusts came for a party and the boy was all like “hey bitches and bastards! my moms in the kitchen wiping shit on her face, and my dads in the kitchen fucking a lobster”.</h2>
<p>Second way of joke notice the differences!</p>
<p>A little boy was listening to his parents argue. The mother called the father a bastard and the father called to mother a bitch. Later on the little boy asked his parents what those words meant. “bastard just means gentlemen and bitch just means lady,” they explained to their eager son.</p>
<p>A few days later the son caught them having sex. As he listened on he heard his mother say “DICK! DICK!” and his father say “PUSSY! PUSSY!” When theY realized that he had been standing there, they stopped immediatly.</p>
<p>The son asked what those words meant. “Dick is simply another word for Hat and Pussy is just another word for jacket.” they tried explaining. “OKAY!” the boy said and walked off.</p>
<p>On thanksgiving a while before their party guests began to arrive the boy followed his father around anxiously. As the father was shaving his cut himself and screamed “SHIT!” “daddy, what does shit mean?” the father became quite and said, “oh, its just another word for shaving cream, now go downstairs and help your mom out in the kitchen.”</p>
<p>The boy did as he was told. The mom who was stuffing the turkey got poked with a jagged bone and screamed “FUCK!” The curious boy asked, “Mommy what does Fuck mean?” The mother became embarrased at her inappropriate language and said, “uh…its just another word for stuffing the turkey.” when she said this the doorbell rang. “go and answer that, the guests are here.” “OKAY!” the little boy said excitedly.</p>
<p>As he opened the door he said, “HI ALL YOU BITCHES AND BASTARDS! GIVE ME YOUR DICKS AND PUSSYS AND MY MOM WILL BE OUT AS SOON AS SHES FINISHED FUCKING THE TURKEY AND MY DAD WILL BE OUT AS SOON AS HE GETS THAT WHITE SHIT OFF HIS FACE!”</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/lol-some-joke-note-overrated/75087/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/lol-some-joke-note-overrated/75087/1</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 06 Apr 2007 08:24:09 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-75087-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/lol-some-joke-note-overrated/75087.rss">Lol some joke , *Note* Overrated</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
