<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Percy Jackson &amp; The Lightning Thief</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/percy-jackson-the-lightning-thief/329257</link>
    <description>I just saw The Lightning Thief, an educational movie about classism. Logan Lerman is a child with ADHD and dyslexia, he is Percy Jackson. While at school he struggles to learn how to read. At home  things are also troublesome. He has an abusive step-father and a passive mother. He appears completely oblivious to the opposite sex and instead hangs out with the only other metro-sexual at his school,  a black kid with crutches. Brandon T. Jackson does a perfect job of portraying an &quot;Ironic&quot; token black friend. He adds a sense of levity and presence to the film while being &quot;Wack&quot; and &quot;Slightly over the top yet still politically correct&quot;. 

Of course with a set up like this you just know that some serious shit has to be coming soon. The main character is a Zac Efron wannabe who can&#39;t read, his life is so lame that if this wasn&#39;t a kids movie you would expect a quick murder-suicide and then roll the credits. However! Percy Jackson, it turns out, is no normal youth. He is actually the son of a Greek god! As Percy goes on a series of increasingly confusing and pointless adventures, which revolve around incredibly poor acting and beautiful computer generated graphics, he doesn&#39;t create any romantic tension between himself and the female lead, fails to become emotional and bond with his long lost father once they are reunited, and doesn&#39;t reveal a sly sense of humor full of pithy witticisms. Fortunately Percy&#39;s token black friend turns out to be a horny Satyr and adds a dramatic flair to an otherwise dull quest to save the world.

Finally it is revealed that everything will be alright because Percy Jackson has saved the world. Much more revelatory is the news that the reason Percy had to live with an abusive alcoholic for a step-father was because the old mans terrible odor masked Percy&#39;s own god like aroma. I&#39;m not kidding, instead of buying perfume or aerosol deodorant his mother decides the best option is to start dating a fat beer guzzling asshole with no sense of personal hygiene. Great plot device! That makes almost as much sense as a horny satyr without a penis or Greek Gods who speak in any accent except Greek. This movies quirks aren&#39;t limited to off-beat and ironic politic correctness; there are also some major continuity errors to break up the unfunny and awkward dialogue and the rushed and uninspired fight scenes. 

The Lightning Thief was a good movie, I give it four stars out of five. It shows that it doesn&#39;t matter who you are or where you come from, as long as your dad is powerful and connected and you have at least one friend who is black and one who is in a wheelchair you can save the world.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 01 Mar 2010 11:47:43 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>General Discussion</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/percy-jackson-the-lightning-thief/329257.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Percy Jackson &amp; The Lightning Thief</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Not_X_A_Alex Not X A Alex]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/not_x_a_alex">@Not_X_A_Alex</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I enjoyed reading this review.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/percy-jackson-the-lightning-thief/329257/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/percy-jackson-the-lightning-thief/329257/6</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 01 Mar 2010 11:47:43 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-329257-6</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/percy-jackson-the-lightning-thief/329257.rss">Percy Jackson &amp; The Lightning Thief</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Percy Jackson &amp; The Lightning Thief</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@R.I.P_RSC R.I.P RSC]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/r.i.p_rsc">@R.I.P_RSC</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>This is quite an odd review. You basically say that the movie sucks, but you conclude that it’s good.</p>
<p>I won’t see it anyways. Can’t they just make a movie based on the ancient stories about the gods?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/percy-jackson-the-lightning-thief/329257/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/percy-jackson-the-lightning-thief/329257/5</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 26 Feb 2010 19:36:33 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-329257-5</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/percy-jackson-the-lightning-thief/329257.rss">Percy Jackson &amp; The Lightning Thief</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Percy Jackson &amp; The Lightning Thief</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Eh_Pretty_Easy Eh Pretty Easy]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/eh_pretty_easy">@Eh_Pretty_Easy</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>It’s a really good movie, I liked it. If you’re a fan of fantasy/HP-like movies, then you should see it.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/percy-jackson-the-lightning-thief/329257/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/percy-jackson-the-lightning-thief/329257/4</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 26 Feb 2010 14:33:58 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-329257-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/percy-jackson-the-lightning-thief/329257.rss">Percy Jackson &amp; The Lightning Thief</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Percy Jackson &amp; The Lightning Thief</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@lothy Lothy]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/lothy">@lothy</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I lol’d. I’m assuming this is a serious outline of the film – will not be seeing it. <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=5" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/percy-jackson-the-lightning-thief/329257/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/percy-jackson-the-lightning-thief/329257/3</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 16 Feb 2010 14:15:58 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-329257-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/percy-jackson-the-lightning-thief/329257.rss">Percy Jackson &amp; The Lightning Thief</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Percy Jackson &amp; The Lightning Thief</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Frell Frell]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/frell">@Frell</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Damn, i wish i took Greek mythology so i could tell the teacher to play this in class.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/percy-jackson-the-lightning-thief/329257/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/percy-jackson-the-lightning-thief/329257/2</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 14 Feb 2010 19:05:18 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-329257-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/percy-jackson-the-lightning-thief/329257.rss">Percy Jackson &amp; The Lightning Thief</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Percy Jackson &amp; The Lightning Thief</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@PaulT PaulT]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/pault">@PaulT</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I just saw The Lightning Thief, an educational movie about classism. Logan Lerman is a child with ADHD and dyslexia, he is Percy Jackson. While at school he struggles to learn how to read. At home  things are also troublesome. He has an abusive step-father and a passive mother. He appears completely oblivious to the opposite sex and instead hangs out with the only other metro-sexual at his school,  a black kid with crutches. Brandon T. Jackson does a perfect job of portraying an “Ironic” token black friend. He adds a sense of levity and presence to the film while being “Wack” and “Slightly over the top yet still politically correct”.</p>
<p>Of course with a set up like this you just know that some serious shit has to be coming soon. The main character is a Zac Efron wannabe who can’t read, his life is so lame that if this wasn’t a kids movie you would expect a quick murder-suicide and then roll the credits. However! Percy Jackson, it turns out, is no normal youth. He is actually the son of a Greek god! As Percy goes on a series of increasingly confusing and pointless adventures, which revolve around incredibly poor acting and beautiful computer generated graphics, he doesn’t create any romantic tension between himself and the female lead, fails to become emotional and bond with his long lost father once they are reunited, and doesn’t reveal a sly sense of humor full of pithy witticisms. Fortunately Percy’s token black friend turns out to be a horny Satyr and adds a dramatic flair to an otherwise dull quest to save the world.</p>
<p>Finally it is revealed that everything will be alright because Percy Jackson has saved the world. Much more revelatory is the news that the reason Percy had to live with an abusive alcoholic for a step-father was because the old mans terrible odor masked Percy’s own god like aroma. I’m not kidding, instead of buying perfume or aerosol deodorant his mother decides the best option is to start dating a fat beer guzzling asshole with no sense of personal hygiene. Great plot device! That makes almost as much sense as a horny satyr without a penis or Greek Gods who speak in any accent except Greek. This movies quirks aren’t limited to off-beat and ironic politic correctness; there are also some major continuity errors to break up the unfunny and awkward dialogue and the rushed and uninspired fight scenes.</p>
<p>The Lightning Thief was a good movie, I give it four stars out of five. It shows that it doesn’t matter who you are or where you come from, as long as your dad is powerful and connected and you have at least one friend who is black and one who is in a wheelchair you can save the world.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/percy-jackson-the-lightning-thief/329257/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/percy-jackson-the-lightning-thief/329257/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 13 Feb 2010 05:57:02 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-329257-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/percy-jackson-the-lightning-thief/329257.rss">Percy Jackson &amp; The Lightning Thief</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
