<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Help me out please :)</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/help-me-out-please/315011</link>
    <description>1.Well, does anybody know how to make Karils X Bow hit npcs? It does the emote and well no damage on npcs, Can anybody help me get it work?  Please.

2. Walk to npc? Can somebody help me make it so if you are to far away from the npc/person when ranging you&#39;ll walk towards it then start ranging and not sit there and say &quot;Too far away to Range&quot; Also can somebody help me have walk to npc with melee and attack right away, not walk to it and wait till you click on it again before you begin attacking.

3. Npc Retreat? Can somebody help me make it so when you run far enough away from npcs they&#39;ll retreat back to their spawn spot and not follow you till they can&#39;t move anymore.?

4. Magic range, please help me make it so the magic only shoots from a certain distance and not as far as you can see the npc. I would like to have it have the same magic distance as RuneScape&#39;s. Please help

Yes these are all for Delta based 317.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 19 Nov 2009 16:03:16 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/help-me-out-please/315011.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Help me out please :)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Keegan1 Keegan_]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/keegan1">@Keegan1</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>1.Well, does anybody know how to make Karils X Bow hit npcs? It does the emote and well no damage on npcs, Can anybody help me get it work?  Please.</p>
<ol start="2">
<li>
<p>Walk to npc? Can somebody help me make it so if you are to far away from the npc/person when ranging you’ll walk towards it then start ranging and not sit there and say “Too far away to Range” Also can somebody help me have walk to npc with melee and attack right away, not walk to it and wait till you click on it again before you begin attacking.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Npc Retreat? Can somebody help me make it so when you run far enough away from npcs they’ll retreat back to their spawn spot and not follow you till they can’t move anymore.?</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Magic range, please help me make it so the magic only shoots from a certain distance and not as far as you can see the npc. I would like to have it have the same magic distance as RuneScape’s. Please help</p>
</li>
</ol>
<p>Yes these are all for Delta based 317.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/help-me-out-please/315011/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/help-me-out-please/315011/1</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 19 Nov 2009 16:03:16 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-315011-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/help-me-out-please/315011.rss">Help me out please :)</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
