<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Searching for a partner || Linux VPS Ready || Make $$$</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/searching-for-a-partner-linux-vps-ready-make/470535</link>
    <description>Hello MoparScape Users,
I&#39; understand that I&#39;m a new member here and might not be that trusted - but I thought it was worth posting here as a lot of people might be interested. I&#39;ll introduce myself, my name is Lewis, I&#39;m 18 and from the UK. I&#39;m somewhat experienced with JAVA (I can edit servers, I used to be a contributor on RSCA - RuneScape Botting Forum, which was a rank that was given to certain members for making HQ Java Scripts for the bot) - but am much better with HTML/PHP/MySQL.

I&#39;m searching for someone that is interested in starting a RuneScape Private Server with me (We&#39;ll both be owners). I have a linux VPS which has been pre-paid for the next 2 and a half months - so if you have a server, we can literally upload the files and start running the vps - it&#39;ll be online 24/7 and will probably handle 50+ players easily.

I own https://efyu.net (http://efyu.net/proof.txt) which lets users complete surveys in return for points (EFYU has over 700 members). I would be interested in setting up a page for the server, where users can complete surveys for ingame cash, items, ranks, etc.. Each time a user completes a survey, we get anywhere from $1-30 depending on the survey they complete, via PayPal at the end of the month (Check adworkmedia.com - it&#39;s very trusted, ranked #1 on affpaying.com - we&#39;re guaranteed to be paid).

I am looking for someone who can code the server - and preferably already has a server that we can start with asap.

Professionalism -
I&#39;m looking for someone VERY professional. I will be monetizing the server and everything will be split 50/50 - (minus hosting costs), by allowing users to donate via paypal, rsgp, or by completing surveys in return for ingame rsgp, items, ranks etc. - Please do not PM me if you&#39;re not a professional person. Everything will be split between the owners.

Website -
I want to make a website for the server. The website will have the following options - Registration, High Scores, Forum, Donations - but with the option to complete survey. We will not be using a subdomain (we&#39;ll be using a .com). We can choose a name at any time.

To sum it up we can -
Get the server up and running as soon as possible, with 24/7 uptime as I have a vps.
Create a website for the server with everything intergrated (Registration, High Scores, Forum, Donations - but with the option to complete surveys)
Earn a lot of money for us both.

PM ME FOR MY SKYPE.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 01 Dec 2012 15:29:53 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/searching-for-a-partner-linux-vps-ready-make/470535.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Searching for a partner || Linux VPS Ready || Make $$$</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@PvPXile PvPXile]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/pvpxile">@PvPXile</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Not too sure about you as you seem money orientated, but I could work with you.</p>
<p>Skype Louis.RSW</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/searching-for-a-partner-linux-vps-ready-make/470535/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/searching-for-a-partner-linux-vps-ready-make/470535/3</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 01 Dec 2012 15:29:53 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-470535-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/searching-for-a-partner-linux-vps-ready-make/470535.rss">Searching for a partner || Linux VPS Ready || Make $$$</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Searching for a partner || Linux VPS Ready || Make $$$</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@boemboem2 boemboem2]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/boemboem2">@boemboem2</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Maby we can make this together??</p>
<p>Look at the post below for more info!<br>
<aside class="onebox whitelistedgeneric">
  <header class="source">
      <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/uploads/default/original/2X/1/1f0dc167bcf798bdbd70b03bf0fd1bc836e54e1a.png" class="site-icon" width="32" height="32">
      <a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/" target="_blank">moparisthebest.com</a>
  </header>
  <article class="onebox-body">
    <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/default-apple-touch-icon.png" class="thumbnail onebox-avatar" width="144" height="144">

<h3><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/" target="_blank">moparisthebest.com</a></h3>

<p>programming, irc, cars</p>


  </article>
  <div class="onebox-metadata">
    
    
  </div>
  <div style="clear: both"></div>
</aside>
</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/searching-for-a-partner-linux-vps-ready-make/470535/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/searching-for-a-partner-linux-vps-ready-make/470535/2</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 01 Dec 2012 13:55:59 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-470535-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/searching-for-a-partner-linux-vps-ready-make/470535.rss">Searching for a partner || Linux VPS Ready || Make $$$</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Searching for a partner || Linux VPS Ready || Make $$$</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Owner6 Owner]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/owner6">@Owner6</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Hello MoparScape Users,<br>
I’ understand that I’m a new member here and might not be that trusted - but I thought it was worth posting here as a lot of people might be interested. I’ll introduce myself, my name is Lewis, I’m 18 and from the UK. I’m somewhat experienced with JAVA (I can edit servers, I used to be a contributor on RSCA - RuneScape Botting Forum, which was a rank that was given to certain members for making HQ Java Scripts for the bot) - but am much better with HTML/PHP/MySQL.</p>
<p>I’m searching for someone that is interested in starting a RuneScape Private Server with me (We’ll both be owners). I have a linux VPS which has been pre-paid for the next 2 and a half months - so if you have a server, we can literally upload the files and start running the vps - it’ll be online 24/7 and will probably handle 50+ players easily.</p>
<p>I own <a href="https://efyu.net" rel="nofollow noopener">https://efyu.net</a> (<a href="http://efyu.net/proof.txt" rel="nofollow noopener">http://efyu.net/proof.txt</a>) which lets users complete surveys in return for points (EFYU has over 700 members). I would be interested in setting up a page for the server, where users can complete surveys for ingame cash, items, ranks, etc… Each time a user completes a survey, we get anywhere from $1-30 depending on the survey they complete, via PayPal at the end of the month (Check <a href="http://adworkmedia.com" rel="nofollow noopener">adworkmedia.com</a> - it’s very trusted, ranked <span class="hashtag">#1</span> on <a href="http://affpaying.com" rel="nofollow noopener">affpaying.com</a> - we’re guaranteed to be paid).</p>
<p>I am looking for someone who can code the server - and preferably already has a server that we can start with asap.</p>
<p>Professionalism -<br>
I’m looking for someone VERY professional. I will be monetizing the server and everything will be split 50/50 - (minus hosting costs), by allowing users to donate via paypal, rsgp, or by completing surveys in return for ingame rsgp, items, ranks etc. - Please do not PM me if you’re not a professional person. Everything will be split between the owners.</p>
<p>Website -<br>
I want to make a website for the server. The website will have the following options - Registration, High Scores, Forum, Donations - but with the option to complete survey. We will not be using a subdomain (we’ll be using a .com). We can choose a name at any time.</p>
<p>To sum it up we can -<br>
Get the server up and running as soon as possible, with 24/7 uptime as I have a vps.<br>
Create a website for the server with everything intergrated (Registration, High Scores, Forum, Donations - but with the option to complete surveys)<br>
Earn a lot of money for us both.</p>
<p>PM ME FOR MY SKYPE.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/searching-for-a-partner-linux-vps-ready-make/470535/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/searching-for-a-partner-linux-vps-ready-make/470535/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 01 Dec 2012 00:04:42 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-470535-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/searching-for-a-partner-linux-vps-ready-make/470535.rss">Searching for a partner || Linux VPS Ready || Make $$$</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
