<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Trying to edit Easy RSCD! New help me!</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/trying-to-edit-easy-rscd-new-help-me/324067</link>
    <description>okay this probably sounds way nooby, but im just getting into and i i need help. i went to change the npc names and i know i did that part correctly, but when i restart everything it doesnt show the new npcs name. now i know im supposed to compress the file, but when i right click it only gives me the option to compress and email.... never just compress. i think this may be why its not working? can anyone explain how to do it correctly. ive looked at the tutorials and i just dont understand it. also i was looking at another tut on the server and they mentioned that the sides had to be correct. can someone explain what this means and how to do it in a little more depth? last but not least i downloaded the sprite editor, packer and unpacker. when i try to open the sprite editor as a program when i say &quot;run....&quot; the black screen comes up and says &#39;ant&#39; not recognized and doesnt open.... can someone explain how to get this to work? and 1 more thing, how do i make the server public? i read kryptix explanation for it, but its too brief. can someone make a tutorial for it or explain in a little more depth.

I know this is alot of stuff, but please understand that im new and everyone has to start from the beginning. please take the time to answer my questions.

Thanks,
Nick</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 06 Jan 2010 09:20:41 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/trying-to-edit-easy-rscd-new-help-me/324067.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Trying to edit Easy RSCD! New help me!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@aaronsc aaronsc]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/aaronsc">@aaronsc</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Go into your client, then go into conf. from there drag your NPC’s into your input folder, decompress it. Then copy all your information from NPC.xml into your NPC’s.rscd. Once you have copied and saved the information, move the NPC’s.rscd into your input folder, from your output folder, and compress. Put it back into your client side, and everything should work fine.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/trying-to-edit-easy-rscd-new-help-me/324067/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/trying-to-edit-easy-rscd-new-help-me/324067/3</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 06 Jan 2010 09:20:41 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-324067-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/trying-to-edit-easy-rscd-new-help-me/324067.rss">Trying to edit Easy RSCD! New help me!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Trying to edit Easy RSCD! New help me!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Nuk Nuk]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/nuk">@Nuk</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <blockquote>i went to change the npc names and i know i did that part correctly, but when i restart everything it doesnt show the new npcs name.</blockquote> 
You also need to edit NPCs.rscd on client side
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/trying-to-edit-easy-rscd-new-help-me/324067/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/trying-to-edit-easy-rscd-new-help-me/324067/2</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 05 Jan 2010 23:12:01 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-324067-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/trying-to-edit-easy-rscd-new-help-me/324067.rss">Trying to edit Easy RSCD! New help me!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Trying to edit Easy RSCD! New help me!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@nicka22 nicka22]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/nicka22">@nicka22</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>okay this probably sounds way nooby, but im just getting into and i i need help. i went to change the npc names and i know i did that part correctly, but when i restart everything it doesnt show the new npcs name. now i know im supposed to compress the file, but when i right click it only gives me the option to compress and email… never just compress. i think this may be why its not working? can anyone explain how to do it correctly. ive looked at the tutorials and i just dont understand it. also i was looking at another tut on the server and they mentioned that the sides had to be correct. can someone explain what this means and how to do it in a little more depth? last but not least i downloaded the sprite editor, packer and unpacker. when i try to open the sprite editor as a program when i say “run…” the black screen comes up and says ‘ant’ not recognized and doesnt open… can someone explain how to get this to work? and 1 more thing, how do i make the server public? i read kryptix explanation for it, but its too brief. can someone make a tutorial for it or explain in a little more depth.</p>
<p>I know this is alot of stuff, but please understand that im new and everyone has to start from the beginning. please take the time to answer my questions.</p>
<p>Thanks,<br>
Nick</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/trying-to-edit-easy-rscd-new-help-me/324067/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/trying-to-edit-easy-rscd-new-help-me/324067/1</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 05 Jan 2010 18:30:06 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-324067-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/trying-to-edit-easy-rscd-new-help-me/324067.rss">Trying to edit Easy RSCD! New help me!</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
