<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>A more interesting dynamic</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/a-more-interesting-dynamic/450633</link>
    <description>griefing as a completely allowable thing, PvP turned on, if anyone griefs my shit I hunt them down with my homies and we raid their shit. install something like [url=https://github.com/Exultant/PrisonPearl]prison pearl[/url] so i get to do whatever i want with them and the mods don&#39;t have to waste their time banning idiots when i can have fun chasing them and taunting them when they&#39;re stuck in the end. if griefing is too easy, install [url=https://github.com/Exultant/Citadel]citadel[/url] so they can&#39;t grief my shit too quick. bitchez

edit: since that was a poor way of actually conveying my point, basically implementing player-based justice and letting the players deal with people so if they want to stop griefers they can act to stop them and get something out of it ie. equipment and bragging rights. it&#39;s also a much more realistic system, and it could allow players to group up to fight the bad guys. whaddya think?</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 25 Jul 2012 17:40:27 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Minecraft</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/a-more-interesting-dynamic/450633.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>A more interesting dynamic</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@_s11 s1gma]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/_s11">@_s11</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“xx matty xx, post:29, topic:450633”]I don’t think something like citadel is a bad idea, but I’m not sure what it does exactly. Something like this would surely be helpful?</p>
<p>[ul][li]Any player can remove blocks which they placed[/li]<br>
[li]Removing someone else’s block takes more time, where this time is proportional to the time since the block was placed. So if it was placed 24 hours ago it would break at normal speed, and if it was placed a week ago it would take considerably longer[/li]<br>
[li]If the original block placer has not logged in for some time then their blocks can be made weaker. I think this is an ok tradeoff because without this their blocks wouldn’t have protection anyway and wont be reporting any damage during their inactivity.[/li]<br>
[li]This stops abuse (ie, placing blocks in peoples houses/cities) because they can be removed easily if done quickly[/li]<br>
[li]With the old res mod, people used to barricade themselves in impenetrable houses and made everyone a bit antisocial. With this, people can still gain entry - it just takes longer[/li]<br>
[li]Could also do something where a players “strength” increases the longer they play, and could also have friend lists so that people working together can edit each others stuff.[/li][/ul]</p>
<p>I’m sure this would have a massive impact on griefing, as the only players able to do any significant damage would be on the friends list of the person they’re griefing. And I’m not sure about any problems? It would be less vanilla, of course, but imo it’s more realistic that it’s difficult to break down someones house (and I’m not sure why we have to religiously keep the server vanilla, provided we’re not doing stupid shit).[/quote]you’ve actually described some things similar to how citadel works, however the time based system is represented through resources used to reinforce (a player for a longer time will be able to afford to reinforce with iron or diamond whereas a newbie can only really use smoothstone). players can bypass their own reinforcements, but the system still needs to implement group reinforcement (it already has group privacy for chests/furnaces though). new 1-day griefers will practically be limited to reinforcement with stone only so it’s difficult for them to abuse the system unless they bide their time gathering before griefing as stone really isn’t much of a block protection, it’s mainly for TNT proofing a house.</p>
<p>edit: if anyone is interested in a server that uses the proposed systems, pm me (it’s great but premium-only).</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/a-more-interesting-dynamic/450633/30">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/a-more-interesting-dynamic/450633/30</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jul 2012 17:40:27 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-450633-30</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/a-more-interesting-dynamic/450633.rss">A more interesting dynamic</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>A more interesting dynamic</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@xx_matty_xx Justin Bieber]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/xx_matty_xx">@xx_matty_xx</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I don’t think something like citadel is a bad idea, but I’m not sure what it does exactly. Something like this would surely be helpful?</p>
<p>[ul][li]Any player can remove blocks which they placed[/li]<br>
[li]Removing someone else’s block takes more time, where this time is proportional to the time since the block was placed. So if it was placed 24 hours ago it would break at normal speed, and if it was placed a week ago it would take considerably longer[/li]<br>
[li]If the original block placer has not logged in for some time then their blocks can be made weaker. I think this is an ok tradeoff because without this their blocks wouldn’t have protection anyway and wont be reporting any damage during their inactivity.[/li]<br>
[li]This stops abuse (ie, placing blocks in peoples houses/cities) because they can be removed easily if done quickly[/li]<br>
[li]With the old res mod, people used to barricade themselves in impenetrable houses and made everyone a bit antisocial. With this, people can still gain entry - it just takes longer[/li]<br>
[li]Could also do something where a players “strength” increases the longer they play, and could also have friend lists so that people working together can edit each others stuff.[/li][/ul]</p>
<p>I’m sure this would have a massive impact on griefing, as the only players able to do any significant damage would be on the friends list of the person they’re griefing. And I’m not sure about any problems? It would be less vanilla, of course, but imo it’s more realistic that it’s difficult to break down someones house (and I’m not sure why we have to religiously keep the server vanilla, provided we’re not doing stupid shit).</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/a-more-interesting-dynamic/450633/29">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/a-more-interesting-dynamic/450633/29</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jul 2012 08:43:37 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-450633-29</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/a-more-interesting-dynamic/450633.rss">A more interesting dynamic</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>A more interesting dynamic</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@asshole_rule asshole_rule]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/asshole_rule">@asshole_rule</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“reyx7, post:27, topic:450633”][quote author=asshole_rule link=topic=553505.msg4056178#msg4056178 date=1342986799]<br>
if we turn pvp on we get people like agl.<br>
[/quote]</p>
<p>Why is this bad?[/quote]</p>
<p>agl is a queer</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/a-more-interesting-dynamic/450633/28">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/a-more-interesting-dynamic/450633/28</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jul 2012 06:36:11 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-450633-28</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/a-more-interesting-dynamic/450633.rss">A more interesting dynamic</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>A more interesting dynamic</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@reyx7 reyx7]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/reyx7">@reyx7</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote" data-post="21" data-topic="450633">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/asshole_rule/40/5_e05bb34c421432ee4d40de30c10af3e5.png" class="avatar"> asshole_rule:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>if we turn pvp on we get people like agl.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Why is this bad?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/a-more-interesting-dynamic/450633/27">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/a-more-interesting-dynamic/450633/27</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jul 2012 02:29:57 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-450633-27</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/a-more-interesting-dynamic/450633.rss">A more interesting dynamic</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>A more interesting dynamic</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@_s11 s1gma]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/_s11">@_s11</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“Si Force, post:25, topic:450633”][quote author=s1gma link=topic=553505.msg4056050#msg4056050 date=1342972834]</p>
<aside class="quote">
<blockquote>
<p>I don’t agree with these changes to be honest. We’ve discussed and debated the effects of PvP on a server and in the end most people felt more comfortable with it off.</p>
<p>We aim to be a large community-based server who are close to eachother and who feel comfortable living near eachother, and PvP would destroy that confidence as it has done in the past. I don’t really like the idea of ‘member justice’ as you’ll always get the members (I’m not saying it is you or your friends) that will group together and go after a member for breaking a block or two within their property.</p>
<p>As for citadel, I don’t really know what that plugin achieves since I’m on my phone and won’t be able to research it until later…<br>
[/quote]i’m losing a little bit of patience with people not understanding that my argument is not just turning PvP on and leaving the world at that, the whole point of the extra dynamic of imprisonment would hopefully throw the challenge of keeping people safe on a few people who are powerful enough to enforce justice. of course, these enforcers aren’t at all likely to pop up if everyone here hates each other but that’s another interesting part of the natural social dynamic, do you help someone because it’s morally right or do you not help them because they broke your sand generator?</p>
<p>it’s odd that you’d suggest the idea that i’d be scared of my neighbour purely because PvP has been enabled, why should i be scared of him? if he’s liable to going nuts then he’s going to feel the consequences of doing so through imprisonment, and once imprisoned he’s probably not going to do that again. the only reason one should ever also be scared of his neighbour is when they’re too young/dumb to understand that <span class="bbcode-i">PvP enabled /= PvP server</span>.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Sorry I haven’t replied any sooner, I actually forgot about this discussion. I also find it interesting. I understand the concept of your idea, but I don’t particularly like the idea of the ‘prison system’. It seems that users with enough power and resources could set up some form of dictatorship (for lack of a better term). Also, is PvP not a fundamental part of your suggestion? That’s why I mentioned it.</p>
<p>How does this jail-pearl system work? I haven’t had time to read up on it, but I guess you could say that my lack of knowledge on it contributes to my disliking of it.[/quote]of course, a crazy oligarchy of powerful nutters could imprison anyone and everyone they wish, but i like to think of the whole ‘test’ for the server with this system is to not devolve into such a thing. i guess it falls down to the extent at which the populace are willing to cohabit peacefully, and who’s willing to form a society to be peaceful (be it a monarchy or anarcho-capitalism with a consistent judiciary system)</p>
<p>PvP is a fairly fundamental cog in the system as it’s the selected medium through which one can enforce justice, but i dislike the dismissal of the concept based purely on that it allows PvP to happen; the fundamental difference between PvP being enabled and PvP + imprisonment is that consequences are much higher for disrupting order and thus the prospect of being imprisoned can keep most people from engaging in PvP, especially if you’re the aggressor. think of it like real life, you can go out and punch someone but you don’t because it’s wrong, both morally and socially. same concept here, feel free to kill but expect consequences (in this case they’re player-enforced consequences, rather than the current system where the consequences for griefing is an admin-issued ban).</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/a-more-interesting-dynamic/450633/26">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/a-more-interesting-dynamic/450633/26</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jul 2012 02:25:22 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-450633-26</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/a-more-interesting-dynamic/450633.rss">A more interesting dynamic</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>A more interesting dynamic</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@si_force Si Force]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/si_force">@si_force</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“s1gma, post:19, topic:450633”][quote author=Si Force link=topic=553505.msg4055966#msg4055966 date=1342957226]<br>
I don’t agree with these changes to be honest. We’ve discussed and debated the effects of PvP on a server and in the end most people felt more comfortable with it off.</p>
<p>We aim to be a large community-based server who are close to eachother and who feel comfortable living near eachother, and PvP would destroy that confidence as it has done in the past. I don’t really like the idea of ‘member justice’ as you’ll always get the members (I’m not saying it is you or your friends) that will group together and go after a member for breaking a block or two within their property.</p>
<p>As for citadel, I don’t really know what that plugin achieves since I’m on my phone and won’t be able to research it until later…<br>
[/quote]i’m losing a little bit of patience with people not understanding that my argument is not just turning PvP on and leaving the world at that, the whole point of the extra dynamic of imprisonment would hopefully throw the challenge of keeping people safe on a few people who are powerful enough to enforce justice. of course, these enforcers aren’t at all likely to pop up if everyone here hates each other but that’s another interesting part of the natural social dynamic, do you help someone because it’s morally right or do you not help them because they broke your sand generator?</p>
<p>it’s odd that you’d suggest the idea that i’d be scared of my neighbour purely because PvP has been enabled, why should i be scared of him? if he’s liable to going nuts then he’s going to feel the consequences of doing so through imprisonment, and once imprisoned he’s probably not going to do that again. the only reason one should ever also be scared of his neighbour is when they’re too young/dumb to understand that <span class="bbcode-i">PvP enabled /= PvP server</span>.[/quote]</p>
<p>Sorry I haven’t replied any sooner, I actually forgot about this discussion. I also find it interesting. I understand the concept of your idea, but I don’t particularly like the idea of the ‘prison system’. It seems that users with enough power and resources could set up some form of dictatorship (for lack of a better term). Also, is PvP not a fundamental part of your suggestion? That’s why I mentioned it.</p>
<p>How does this jail-pearl system work? I haven’t had time to read up on it, but I guess you could say that my lack of knowledge on it contributes to my disliking of it.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/a-more-interesting-dynamic/450633/25">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/a-more-interesting-dynamic/450633/25</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 24 Jul 2012 22:14:51 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-450633-25</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/a-more-interesting-dynamic/450633.rss">A more interesting dynamic</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>A more interesting dynamic</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@_s11 s1gma]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/_s11">@_s11</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“triston001, post:23, topic:450633”]you say it in assumption the person can just pearl the nutso, but what if the nutso pearls you before you can, and pearls everyone else. or somebody sneaks by, pearls you, and imprisons you forever because they dont honestly give a shit. that kinda ruins the server for me. i like casual playing where i can just build with my buddies on here without fear of anything bad happening aslong as i dont screw shit up.[/quote]would one person seriously be able to pearl everyone else on the server? i’m severely worried about the equipment and resource divide between people if so. also, citadel and prisonpearl being complementary would allow stored pearls to be broken out of their holding and it features abilities to relay the coordinates of the pearl’s location to people too, so it’s not like people wouldn’t be able to bash you out if you’re unjustly pearled… assuming there isn’t a single megalomaniac able to stop everyone in their tracks, of course. i believe a situation where everyone but 1 is imprisoned would probably warrant admin intervention, however, unless the userbase is severely poor at handling the situation that wouldn’t happen since i’d expect any half-decent guys to try and break out the wrongfully imprisoned and imprison those in the wrong.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/a-more-interesting-dynamic/450633/24">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/a-more-interesting-dynamic/450633/24</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 23 Jul 2012 01:59:50 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-450633-24</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/a-more-interesting-dynamic/450633.rss">A more interesting dynamic</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>A more interesting dynamic</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@triston001 triston001]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/triston001">@triston001</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>you say it in assumption the person can just pearl the nutso, but what if the nutso pearls you before you can, and pearls everyone else. or somebody sneaks by, pearls you, and imprisons you forever because they dont honestly give a shit. that kinda ruins the server for me. i like casual playing where i can just build with my buddies on here without fear of anything bad happening aslong as i dont screw shit up.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/a-more-interesting-dynamic/450633/23">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/a-more-interesting-dynamic/450633/23</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 23 Jul 2012 00:08:30 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-450633-23</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/a-more-interesting-dynamic/450633.rss">A more interesting dynamic</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>A more interesting dynamic</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@_s11 s1gma]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/_s11">@_s11</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“relmitos, post:20, topic:450633”][quote author=s1gma link=topic=553505.msg4056050#msg4056050 date=1342972834]<br>
funnily enough, with my proposed system you’d actually be able to scare meep off with the prospect of being pearled for being nosey <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/wink.png?v=5" title=":wink:" class="emoji" alt=":wink:"><br>
[/quote]</p>
<p>You touch meep, you touch ME. Meep is mine, you shant have him.</p>
<p>This might be interesting and all, I say set up a server like this yourself.[/quote]i don’t have the resources to start one up, otherwise i would have.</p>
<p>[quote=“asshole_rule, post:21, topic:450633”]if we turn pvp on we get people like agl.[/quote]pearl him!</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/a-more-interesting-dynamic/450633/22">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/a-more-interesting-dynamic/450633/22</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 22 Jul 2012 21:38:21 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-450633-22</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/a-more-interesting-dynamic/450633.rss">A more interesting dynamic</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>A more interesting dynamic</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@asshole_rule asshole_rule]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/asshole_rule">@asshole_rule</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>if we turn pvp on we get people like agl.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/a-more-interesting-dynamic/450633/21">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/a-more-interesting-dynamic/450633/21</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 22 Jul 2012 19:53:19 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-450633-21</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/a-more-interesting-dynamic/450633.rss">A more interesting dynamic</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>A more interesting dynamic</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@relmitos relmitos]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/relmitos">@relmitos</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote quote-modified" data-post="19" data-topic="450633">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 s1gma:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>funnily enough, with my proposed system you’d actually be able to scare meep off with the prospect of being pearled for being nosey <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/wink.png?v=5" title=":wink:" class="emoji" alt=":wink:"></p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>You touch meep, you touch ME. Meep is mine, you shant have him.</p>
<p>This might be interesting and all, I say set up a server like this yourself.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/a-more-interesting-dynamic/450633/20">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/a-more-interesting-dynamic/450633/20</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 22 Jul 2012 17:38:20 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-450633-20</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/a-more-interesting-dynamic/450633.rss">A more interesting dynamic</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>A more interesting dynamic</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@_s11 s1gma]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/_s11">@_s11</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“Si Force, post:17, topic:450633”]I don’t agree with these changes to be honest. We’ve discussed and debated the effects of PvP on a server and in the end most people felt more comfortable with it off.</p>
<p>We aim to be a large community-based server who are close to eachother and who feel comfortable living near eachother, and PvP would destroy that confidence as it has done in the past. I don’t really like the idea of ‘member justice’ as you’ll always get the members (I’m not saying it is you or your friends) that will group together and go after a member for breaking a block or two within their property.</p>
<p>As for citadel, I don’t really know what that plugin achieves since I’m on my phone and won’t be able to research it until later…[/quote]i’m losing a little bit of patience with people not understanding that my argument is not just turning PvP on and leaving the world at that, the whole point of the extra dynamic of imprisonment would hopefully throw the challenge of keeping people safe on a few people who are powerful enough to enforce justice. of course, these enforcers aren’t at all likely to pop up if everyone here hates each other but that’s another interesting part of the natural social dynamic, do you help someone because it’s morally right or do you not help them because they broke your sand generator?</p>
<p>it’s odd that you’d suggest the idea that i’d be scared of my neighbour purely because PvP has been enabled, why should i be scared of him? if he’s liable to going nuts then he’s going to feel the consequences of doing so through imprisonment, and once imprisoned he’s probably not going to do that again. the only reason one should ever also be scared of his neighbour is when they’re too young/dumb to understand that <span class="bbcode-i">PvP enabled /= PvP server</span>.</p>
<p>also, isn’t this:</p>
<blockquote>I don't really like the idea of 'member justice' as you'll always get the members (I'm not saying it is you or your friends) that will group together and go after a member for breaking a block or two within their property.</blockquote>
exactly what shouldn't be be happening, given the member base, you'd expect them to have at least some sense of what's a good punishment for what assuming they aren't all 12 year olds that overreact when you break their flowers.
<p>[quote=“hat trix, post:18, topic:450633”][quote author=asshole_rule link=topic=553505.msg4055840#msg4055840 date=1342933178]</p>
<aside class="quote">
<blockquote>
<p>who the fuck gets along with meep, anyways? lol</p>
<p>I personally think the system now, if handled well, is flawless and should not be changed.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>you, and a couple 12 year olds dont like me.</p>
<p>only reason you don’t like me is because i broke your sand gen on accident.<br>
[/quote]</p>
<p>I don’t actually dislike you, lol. I just don’t like when people go snooping around on my island when im in the midst of building things <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=5" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"></p>
<p>on topic, The server is best like it is. If you want to experiment with plugins to see a better outcome, start hosting yourself. It’s not just our community who have the maturity level of a 5 year old child, Its a mixture of minecraft and moparscape.[/quote]funnily enough, with my proposed system you’d actually be able to scare meep off with the prospect of being pearled for being nosey <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/wink.png?v=5" title=":wink:" class="emoji" alt=":wink:"></p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">edit</span>: also, i’m actually quite enjoying this discussion. disregarding the misunderstandings of certain elements of my proposed gamestyle, it’s actually interesting what you guys have to say considering you play an almost entirely different type of minecraft to what i do.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/a-more-interesting-dynamic/450633/19">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/a-more-interesting-dynamic/450633/19</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 22 Jul 2012 16:00:34 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-450633-19</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/a-more-interesting-dynamic/450633.rss">A more interesting dynamic</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>A more interesting dynamic</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@hat_trix hat trix]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/hat_trix">@hat_trix</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“asshole_rule, post:16, topic:450633”][quote author=hat trix link=topic=553505.msg4055732#msg4055732 date=1342919255]<br>
who the fuck gets along with meep, anyways? lol</p>
<p>I personally think the system now, if handled well, is flawless and should not be changed.<br>
[/quote]</p>
<p>you, and a couple 12 year olds dont like me.</p>
<p>only reason you don’t like me is because i broke your sand gen on accident.[/quote]</p>
<p>I don’t actually dislike you, lol. I just don’t like when people go snooping around on my island when im in the midst of building things <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=5" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"></p>
<p>on topic, The server is best like it is. If you want to experiment with plugins to see a better outcome, start hosting yourself. It’s not just our community who have the maturity level of a 5 year old child, Its a mixture of minecraft and moparscape.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/a-more-interesting-dynamic/450633/18">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/a-more-interesting-dynamic/450633/18</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 22 Jul 2012 12:35:31 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-450633-18</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/a-more-interesting-dynamic/450633.rss">A more interesting dynamic</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>A more interesting dynamic</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@si_force Si Force]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/si_force">@si_force</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I don’t agree with these changes to be honest. We’ve discussed and debated the effects of PvP on a server and in the end most people felt more comfortable with it off.</p>
<p>We aim to be a large community-based server who are close to eachother and who feel comfortable living near eachother, and PvP would destroy that confidence as it has done in the past. I don’t really like the idea of ‘member justice’ as you’ll always get the members (I’m not saying it is you or your friends) that will group together and go after a member for breaking a block or two within their property.</p>
<p>As for citadel, I don’t really know what that plugin achieves since I’m on my phone and won’t be able to research it until later…</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/a-more-interesting-dynamic/450633/17">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/a-more-interesting-dynamic/450633/17</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 22 Jul 2012 11:40:26 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-450633-17</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/a-more-interesting-dynamic/450633.rss">A more interesting dynamic</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>A more interesting dynamic</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@asshole_rule asshole_rule]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/asshole_rule">@asshole_rule</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“hat trix, post:14, topic:450633”]who the fuck gets along with meep, anyways? lol</p>
<p>I personally think the system now, if handled well, is flawless and should not be changed.[/quote]</p>
<p>you, and a couple 12 year olds dont like me.</p>
<p>only reason you don’t like me is because i broke your sand gen on accident.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/a-more-interesting-dynamic/450633/16">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/a-more-interesting-dynamic/450633/16</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 22 Jul 2012 04:59:38 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-450633-16</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/a-more-interesting-dynamic/450633.rss">A more interesting dynamic</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>A more interesting dynamic</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@_s11 s1gma]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/_s11">@_s11</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“asshole_rule, post:12, topic:450633”][quote author=s1gma link=topic=553505.msg4055427#msg4055427 date=1342895831]</p>
<aside class="quote">
<blockquote>
<p>What happens when i destroy your whole house and never login again.<br>
[/quote]what happens if i destroy your whole house now and never login again? that type of person will always be a plague to any server that allows block breaking/placement by someone new.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Don’t take that as an insult. I was asking what you’ll do in that situation.[/quote]it wasn’t taken as an insult, it’s just a situation that i don’t feel would help anyone’s argument because it’s a flaw in any system allowing people to abuse trust. personally i wouldn’t rage out, i’d rebuild, but that’s due to me having to deal with it a fair amount anyway on other servers and i’ve never particularly had a problem with rebuilding what i’ve put there in the first place. my personal view is probably a minority view, i can understand why people rage out at building a magnificent, huge building that then gets burnt down by an asshole griefer.</p>
<p>[quote=“triston001, post:13, topic:450633”]what about people who dont get along and decide to do wrongful injustice? like me and meep. we dont get along, what would stop us from imprisoning eachother just for the hell of it?and because we have the current system, were forced to deal with it and have to get along. <span class="bbcode-s"> in a way, this is less childish and forces us to be more grown up about our problems to work it out.</span>[/quote]i’m sure both of you would reluctantly come to a solution if you both recognise that the prospect of being in the end forever is quite scary and you’ve been thrown in the deep end to deal with the solution in a much more ‘real’ environment where you both have the power to effectively end each other. it boils down to your capability to handle the situation, and from previous experience of a similar system, not everyone could handle the situation and you did end up with unfortunate cases of people being pearled effectively forever through a person’s negligence.</p>
<p>[quote=“hat trix, post:14, topic:450633”]who the fuck gets along with meep, anyways? lol</p>
<p>I personally think the system now, if handled well, is flawless and should not be changed.[/quote]i’ve never questioned the flawlessness of it, my proposal is an experimental system that’s a lot more natural in giving the players more freedom, and expecting them to deal with the freedom maturely. it may not actually work with this server, i and Tom have discussed potential problems such as the usage of hacked clients to login and how it’s easy to evade the end by relinking account and name (easily programmatically fixed though), and perhaps even the general maturity of the community may not be able to take on the added liberties associated with a system that allows one person to effectively control the fate of a perhaps less fortunate person (but misfortune isn’t always necessarily unwarranted, a griefer would put themselves in the situation via their actions)</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/a-more-interesting-dynamic/450633/15">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/a-more-interesting-dynamic/450633/15</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 22 Jul 2012 03:29:30 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-450633-15</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/a-more-interesting-dynamic/450633.rss">A more interesting dynamic</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>A more interesting dynamic</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@hat_trix hat trix]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/hat_trix">@hat_trix</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>who the fuck gets along with meep, anyways? lol</p>
<p>I personally think the system now, if handled well, is flawless and should not be changed.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/a-more-interesting-dynamic/450633/14">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/a-more-interesting-dynamic/450633/14</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 22 Jul 2012 01:07:35 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-450633-14</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/a-more-interesting-dynamic/450633.rss">A more interesting dynamic</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>A more interesting dynamic</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@triston001 triston001]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/triston001">@triston001</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>what about people who dont get along and decide to do wrongful injustice? like me and meep. we dont get along, what would stop us from imprisoning eachother just for the hell of it?and because we have the current system, were forced to deal with it and have to get along. <span class="bbcode-s"> in a way, this is less childish and forces us to be more grown up about our problems to work it out.</span></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/a-more-interesting-dynamic/450633/13">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/a-more-interesting-dynamic/450633/13</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 22 Jul 2012 00:39:49 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-450633-13</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/a-more-interesting-dynamic/450633.rss">A more interesting dynamic</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>A more interesting dynamic</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@asshole_rule asshole_rule]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/asshole_rule">@asshole_rule</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“s1gma, post:6, topic:450633”][quote author=asshole_rule link=topic=553505.msg4055410#msg4055410 date=1342894904]<br>
What happens when i destroy your whole house and never login again.<br>
[/quote]what happens if i destroy your whole house now and never login again? that type of person will always be a plague to any server that allows block breaking/placement by someone new.[/quote]</p>
<p>Don’t take that as an insult. I was asking what you’ll do in that situation.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/a-more-interesting-dynamic/450633/12">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/a-more-interesting-dynamic/450633/12</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 21 Jul 2012 21:02:52 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-450633-12</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/a-more-interesting-dynamic/450633.rss">A more interesting dynamic</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>A more interesting dynamic</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@_s11 s1gma]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/_s11">@_s11</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“omgilikepie, post:10, topic:450633”]The plugins that we have now we actually need and use to keep the player base up. These plugins you are suggesting just add on even more. <em>we’ve recently been denied a pugin for the end to have it reset the dragon without resetting the end, as well as having a plugin for spleef I’m pretty sure</em> That being said, they were denied because they were not crucial to the gameplay, and neither is the plugin you want. The server is working good with the current system we have, as far as I can tell you just want to go around and torment people for breaking some blocks when they probably don’t even know how to play the game yet, because you have no way of knowing. We have the server the way it is without pvp to keep us more of a community that works together, and that is what it has been based off of for a while now. That is one of the reasons that the map is only 1000x1000, so that people don’t go way off in the distance to separate them selves from other people.[/quote]i don’t think you understand the magnitude of what these plugins change, sure they aren’t essential to the server but i wouldn’t have ever argued that, instead it’s a large paradigm shift that could be tried out on a server reset or whatever. i’d have never expected these plugins to be added to the server because it’s effectively the opposite of what there is now, it would be nonsensical to suggest the immediate change and i don’t get why you assumed i would have requested immediate change or whatever.</p>
<p>isn’t the whole “not knowing” argument just as contrasting with the current style of the server now? really, how can you ever assert that someone won’t be a menace for as long as they can gain some sort of ability to change the game world? extensive background checks aren’t possible, and any halfwitted griefer can just put on a smiley face and then promptly burn down your house, it’s an argument against giving non-trusted people any form of power in general.</p>
<p>the idea of perhaps adding these plugins eventually would that it adds another layer of collaboration between people, so you don’t just work together to build but you work together to enforce justice and eliminate those that want to get in the way of that, i don’t think you’re getting the message that the enabling PvP is only part of the game mechanic changes that i’ve proposed, i am fully aware that the community is functional without PvP now and only enabling PvP without the ability to enforce consequences for initiating force won’t work at all, which is exactly what the method of imprisonment i suggested aims to address. my idea is even nicely harmonious with the map limits since a griefer can’t just run off as far as they can go; there’s a limit on how far they can hide from you.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/a-more-interesting-dynamic/450633/11">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/a-more-interesting-dynamic/450633/11</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 21 Jul 2012 20:17:28 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-450633-11</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/a-more-interesting-dynamic/450633.rss">A more interesting dynamic</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>A more interesting dynamic</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@omgilikepie omgilikepie]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/omgilikepie">@omgilikepie</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>The plugins that we have now we actually need and use to keep the player base up. These plugins you are suggesting just add on even more. <em>we’ve recently been denied a pugin for the end to have it reset the dragon without resetting the end, as well as having a plugin for spleef I’m pretty sure</em> That being said, they were denied because they were not crucial to the gameplay, and neither is the plugin you want. The server is working good with the current system we have, as far as I can tell you just want to go around and torment people for breaking some blocks when they probably don’t even know how to play the game yet, because you have no way of knowing. We have the server the way it is without pvp to keep us more of a community that works together, and that is what it has been based off of for a while now. That is one of the reasons that the map is only 1000x1000, so that people don’t go way off in the distance to separate them selves from other people.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/a-more-interesting-dynamic/450633/10">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/a-more-interesting-dynamic/450633/10</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 21 Jul 2012 19:32:03 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-450633-10</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/a-more-interesting-dynamic/450633.rss">A more interesting dynamic</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>A more interesting dynamic</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@_s11 s1gma]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/_s11">@_s11</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote quote-modified" data-post="7" data-topic="450633">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/omgilikepie/40/5_e05bb34c421432ee4d40de30c10af3e5.png" class="avatar"> omgilikepie:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>We’ve already gone over most of these issues recently. PvP will stay off as it has been decided that in the end it does more harm than good. Yes PvP has it’s advantages, but it also has its disadvantages. Like the people who would pvp new players as soon as they could. As far as all those plugins go to help you “Take justice in your hands”. We have a moderating team that do a good job at helping to rollback damage and ban/mute people when needed. That is half of the reason why we have them. We are trying not to be dependent on plugins, because the more plugins you have, the more annoying it can be. Some plugins can interfere with the other plugins we have. Also, when Minecraft updates to the newest version, the reason in the past it has taken us so long to update is because of us waiting for both bukkit and our other plugins to update too. Now that Minecraft and Bukkit have joined together that wait should be gone. While we do have a few things that are not “Vanilla”, we are trying to keep as vanilla as possible with this server. Read around in the boards a little bit and you can find all that I have just said pretty much if you don’t believe me.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>first of all, people PvPing newbies should warrant that a squad rolls out to kill that person as i would personally regard them as a griefer, disregarding exact semantics. that’s merely a crime solvable by the proposition of the imprisonment system (and a big player-decided punishment should be proposed for such people, i personally hate them)</p>
<p>keeping vanilla minecraft is an important virtue of any server for me, but i guess this falls down to the argument at how far from vanilla is “correct” to one’s own eyes, and i don’t personally recognise a server as being close to vanilla SMP if it focuses only on the constructive side of the ordeal, which may be sufficient for you but the game’s dynamics allowing for both construction and destruction makes me feel like i’m part of a world that contains good and bad, rather than just playing lego where i can hit sheep with a sword as an added bonus.</p>
<p>regarding the plugin dependency argument, it seems odd that you’d criticise my suggestion of plugins when you play a server that relies upon them anyway for delivering justice, limiting the world’s bounds and linking the server to a database. i have recognised that the citadel plugin would interfere with the chest-locking (LWC?) plugin, but one could easily disable either LWC (to fit in with the general gamemode the other plugins would mold, where it’s hard to crack a chest open but possible. make a vault of reinforced obsidian if that’s such a worry!) or disable the chest locking features of citadel.</p>
<p>[quote=“relmitos, post:8, topic:450633”]No I Meant servers where pvp is enabled and griefing is allowed. Theres plenty of servers like that, we’re just not one of them. I wouldn’t be playing if griefing was allowed.[/quote]yes, and that was exactly the ‘former’ i was referring to, those servers don’t particularly work due to douchebags just running around the server with the best armour killing everyone. my suggestions and the plugins that constitute it give griefing consequences, but only for as long as the player wants to enforce such consequences. it also makes griefing difficult, but provides material benefit for those that want to chase down those that went against the odds to grief something. if you’re successful, you’re effectively repaid by them losing their items and justice is done (and you can have fun with summoning the imprisoned and taunting them if you’re cruel). if it’s hard to raid their base, they’re imprisoned! why not extort its position out of them in return for them being ‘free’?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/a-more-interesting-dynamic/450633/9">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/a-more-interesting-dynamic/450633/9</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 21 Jul 2012 19:16:10 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-450633-9</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/a-more-interesting-dynamic/450633.rss">A more interesting dynamic</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>A more interesting dynamic</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@relmitos relmitos]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/relmitos">@relmitos</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>No I Meant servers where pvp is enabled and griefing is allowed. Theres plenty of servers like that, we’re just not one of them. I wouldn’t be playing if griefing was allowed.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/a-more-interesting-dynamic/450633/8">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/a-more-interesting-dynamic/450633/8</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 21 Jul 2012 18:47:01 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-450633-8</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/a-more-interesting-dynamic/450633.rss">A more interesting dynamic</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>A more interesting dynamic</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@omgilikepie omgilikepie]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/omgilikepie">@omgilikepie</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>We’ve already gone over most of these issues recently. PvP will stay off as it has been decided that in the end it does more harm than good. Yes PvP has it’s advantages, but it also has its disadvantages. Like the people who would pvp new players as soon as they could. As far as all those plugins go to help you “Take justice in your hands”. We have a moderating team that do a good job at helping to rollback damage and ban/mute people when needed. That is half of the reason why we have them. We are trying not to be dependent on plugins, because the more plugins you have, the more annoying it can be. Some plugins can interfere with the other plugins we have. Also, when Minecraft updates to the newest version, the reason in the past it has taken us so long to update is because of us waiting for both bukkit and our other plugins to update too. Now that Minecraft and Bukkit have joined together that wait should be gone. While we do have a few things that are not “Vanilla”, we are trying to keep as vanilla as possible with this server. Read around in the boards a little bit and you can find all that I have just said pretty much if you don’t believe me.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/a-more-interesting-dynamic/450633/7">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/a-more-interesting-dynamic/450633/7</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 21 Jul 2012 18:45:26 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-450633-7</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/a-more-interesting-dynamic/450633.rss">A more interesting dynamic</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>A more interesting dynamic</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@_s11 s1gma]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/_s11">@_s11</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“asshole_rule, post:5, topic:450633”]What happens when i destroy your whole house and never login again.[/quote]what happens if i destroy your whole house now and never login again? that type of person will always be a plague to any server that allows block breaking/placement by someone new.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/a-more-interesting-dynamic/450633/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/a-more-interesting-dynamic/450633/6</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 21 Jul 2012 18:37:11 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-450633-6</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/a-more-interesting-dynamic/450633.rss">A more interesting dynamic</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
