<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Akriam&#39;s Library</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/akriams-library/16525</link>
    <description>[size=20pt]AKRIAM&#39;S LIBRARY[/size]

Well seeing as how this is now a writing board also, I will be extremely active here. Well, as some of you know, I love to write stories. I have writen the storyline for a game called Elddem, and am currently writing one for my own MMORPG called Areithe (see my signarute ;D). 

Anyways, I want to be an author when I grow up, so I suppose I will post some of my stories here. If you need a story for something PM me and I we will work something out :P)

So without further ado:

[code]AKRIAM&#39;s LIBRARY
1.)Elddem Storyline-Page 1 Post 2
2.)Nightshadow and Nightshade-Page 1 Post 3
[/code]


If I have a new story I will post it and add it the the library. Since I think it is against the rules to reserve posts for my own stories, they will be scatered all over this thread. Also, if you have a story, post it, and I will add it to a list entiteld &quot;(Your name)&#39;s Library&quot;.

Thanks,
Akriam [size=7pt](GASP Inc.)[/size]</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 29 Sep 2006 20:11:25 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>General Discussion</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/akriams-library/16525.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Akriam&#39;s Library</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Akriam Akriam]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/akriam">@Akriam</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Alright, ya the Elddem storyline is supposed to be a history. I could have gone into more detail, but I didn’t want to write a book.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/akriams-library/16525/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/akriams-library/16525/5</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 29 Sep 2006 20:11:25 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-16525-5</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/akriams-library/16525.rss">Akriam&#39;s Library</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Akriam&#39;s Library</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@therealjdb JDB`]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/therealjdb">@therealjdb</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Well, I just read .::Elddem Storyline::. and I have to say that it wasn’t bad or anything just IMO it could have a more developed story line. When I was reading it I felt as though I were reading a history report rather then a story. I had to keep asking myself questions like “Why is this happening?” for example the war when the portal was discovered, why was there a war? Why were the people upset about it, I guess I just like more detail. Overall I give it a 6.5/10. I’ll read the other posts later seeing as I’m at school and this period is almost over <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=9" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/akriams-library/16525/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/akriams-library/16525/4</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 29 Sep 2006 20:09:14 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-16525-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/akriams-library/16525.rss">Akriam&#39;s Library</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Akriam&#39;s Library</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Akriam Akriam]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/akriam">@Akriam</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>This is a series of stories I did when I was like 10, enjoy <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/wink.png?v=9" title=":wink:" class="emoji" alt=":wink:"></p>
<p>BOOK1:Nightshadow</p>
<p>“WE are almost ready for it’s first test”, Mr. Jay said. Him and his lab partner were working on a secret weapon illegally for the Russians. “Hey hurry up.” Mr. Gandy Mr. Jays partner said. “Ok I am ready.” Mr. Jay said.<br>
Boom! A big exploshion boomed through the lab.  Through the crater in the wall, which was made by the explosion, came 5 masked men. Ththththth an ak57 rocketed and hit Mr. Jay in the chest. Mr. Gandy tried to take cover but was to late. Hiss, a bullet came smashing through Mr. Gandy’s leg. He could hear voices saying get it and then a buzzing of a helicopter in the distance.</p>
<p>Chapter 2:Deabriefing</p>
<pre><code>“Hello agents 1, 3, 5, 8, and 10. Said the chief commander of the CIA. “Please take a seat at the table. I am sure you all know about the incident in Alaska yesterday.” Now I should tell you that we have gotten information from M16 that the terrorists that abducted the weapon known as “KnighShadow” is asking that we pay them $100,000,000,000,000 in order for them to hand the weapon over.” 
“So what if they have the weapon what does it do?” said agent3. 
Please agent 3. All they have to do is take over a satellite somehow, which I highly doubt is not in their power and insert it into it’s anti asteroid defense system…and. The commander was cut of by agent 3,”But why is it so dangerous.” 
“Well I would tell you if you would stop butting in.” Now” he began. “They could simply charge it up with the solar power panels and turn the sun’s rays into a pure form of energy and then well I guess from my understanding they could fire it at just about anything.” The commander said in an uneasy voice, and that is why we need to stop them… 
</code></pre>
<p>Chapter 3 SO It Begins</p>
<p>“Agents I want you to check up on their base in Siberia. “ The commander said,” Your plane awaits you.”<br>
About 8 hours later they were hovering above the XSSD terrorist base. All of a sudden they heard an amplified voice saying something unintelligible and a rocket heading toward their plane. Three agents [1, 8, 10] parachuted out of the plane just in time. The pilot, copilot, and agent3 and 5 were dead. The agents watched as there plan exploded and landed on the ground as fiery bits and pieces of a plane. All of a sudden they heard gunshots. They could see in the distance through a patch of trees computer controlled defense systems were firing at a group of M16 agents that must have been their to investigate also. There were about 5 agents that ran in retreat into the woods in the direction of agents 1, 8, and 10.</p>
<p>Chapter 4 Catching Up</p>
<pre><code>Gunshots boomed. Three rockets sped toward the party of the 8 men. Agents 1 and 5 died along with 3 of the British agents. The 3 men dashed to the woods. All of a sudden they heard the amplified voice say intruder alert rapaciously. 10 men in camouflage came running toward them agent 8 pulled out his P-2k gun and shot 2 of the terrorists. It was to late the other 8 men had seized them. Ththththththththth 4 of the terrorists fell to the ground as 5 more M16 agents came running toward them. Thththththththththththth the other 4 were no more. The group of men stood there petrified. 
Agent 8 finally realized the British agents were soldiers. They had been sent in to try to reclaim and destroy Knight Shadow. Soon a group of 34 men had assembled. They split into groups of 8 and charged into battle. Booooooooom!!!! 8 rockets were fired and 2 groups turned to ashes. The 2 remaining groups retreated to the woods but be fore they reached it computer defense machine guns rose up from the ground and took out 3 of the MI6 soldiers.  
</code></pre>
<p>Chapter 5 You Can Run But You Can’t Hide</p>
<pre><code> As the group ran into the forest a unit of ten terrorists bounded out of a patch of clearing and shot their m16 guns taking out3 men. Agent 8 shot and killed 5 of the terrorists. The British soldiers took out the rest. 
</code></pre>
<p>A hour later it started it started to rain. The group of men had escaped and called a chopper [on a radio] to come and pick them up.<br>
Another 7 hours later they were picked up. When passing the enemy base a thththththththththth was heard. The fuel tank of the helicopter was shot.<br>
“We need to stop in England. We don’t have enough fuel to go on.” The pilot said in a calm voice. He showed no sign of worry.</p>
<p>Chapter 6 England Detour</p>
<pre><code>“Hmmmm it looks like you need a new oil tank. Oke doky I can do that.” The gas attendant said. “But it will take time and money.” 
“Which we have none of.” Austin the new unofficial commander for the English troops [since the real one was shot] said. 
Ththththththht Harry, the gas attendant fell to the ground. 
Austin turned to see a bullet hissing toward him. Ahhhhhhhhh!!!!! A soldier had taken the bullet. Agent 8 turned and saw a chopper releasing a rocket. 
RUN!!!!!!!!!!!!!!! Agent 8 yelled. Quick across the bridge, we can get backup if we stop at M16 
</code></pre>
<p>Chapter 7 London Bridge Is Falling Down</p>
<pre><code>Once they had defeated the 15 terrorists with the help of backup. They received a video message from the enemy saying: You have denied the ransom for the weapon and tried outsmart us. You have obstructed our base and you will pay. We will not destroy you. We will give you one and one more chance only to pay up. But for all the trouble you have caused you cannot go unpunished.  
All of a sudden through the window a stream of yellow light came streaming down from the sky.  
“What is that?” agent 8 said. Whatever it was it was heading for the London Bridge!!!  
As soon as it made contact with the bridge it spread out over the bridge covering it entirely. Two seconds later it started on fire. About a minute later it blew up and evaporated taking about 242 lives with it. Soon all the water under it evaporated too. In another few minutes everything in 25 feet of the bridge was gone…TO BE CONTINUED IN BOOK 2 
</code></pre>
<p>BOOK 2: Nightshade</p>
<p>Chapter 1 What Was That?<br>
As the group looked out of the window in awe agent 8 was thinking that is what it does agent 3. All of a sudden they heard an explosion. They looked out of the window to see that a rocket had hit level 4 of the M16 agency by one of the 3 helicopters hovering out side.<br>
“Hit the deck” Austin said as the sprinkler system went of and at the same time one of the machine guns on one of the helicopters shot and killed 4 of the soldiers and hitting Austin in the leg. A yellow beam came from an extra gun on the helicopter hitting and doing the same thing to the bridge as it did to the soldier that was hit by it. Thththththhthththt ththththththht ththththththththt thththththththt ththththththth ththththhtht. There were shots fired everywhere. Boom! Another 3 rockets made contact with the building. The yellow streams were firing as fast as the machine gun bullets.<br>
Agent 8, Austin, and 4 soldiers got out alive before the building exploded.</p>
<p>Chapter 2 The Damage Is Done</p>
<pre><code>As they ran out of the building the building exploded. Everyone in side was dead. There were terrorists everywhere. Before reaching a hiding place they heard the buzzing of 5 American helicopters overhead. They boarded into one of the helicopters. As they got higher and higher they saw the yellow stream of light making contact with 2 of the helicopters. 
About 4 hours later London had been taken over completely. “So that was a taste of what Knightshade can do, I wonder what the whole thing will be like.” Austin said. When they got back to the CIA head quarters, the commander and chief of the CIA said, “I would like you to meet somebody very important.” He cleared his throught. “Well he claims to have important information of some sort that would be of great value to you on this so called search and destroy mission I will be sending you on. I will stop wasting valuable time by talking. Let him in thetime is right. Well here he is. I soppose you don’t know the face of this man? Well he is the one and only Mr.[He possed to cough several times] the one and only Mr. Gandy. 
</code></pre>
<p>Chapter 3 Mr. Gandy</p>
<p>“I have come to tell you about the weapon called kni….” He paused, choked, clasped his hands over his throat, and fell over dead. A sniper had shot him. A second later agent 8 gave a shriek of pain. He had been shot in the leg with a sniper also. The Commander of the CIA collapsed. Austin’s ear had been shot off completely of. Before another shot was let of agent 8 had shot the sniper on the roof that he had somehow known. The man he shot seemed familiar. Shaggy bearded. “Wait this isn’t possible.” He said.<br>
The door snapped as 3 bullets crashed through it. The door opened. “No. It’s not…not possible your dead.” At that second Mr. Gandy got up. Also the man standing in the doorway was an exact duplicate of Mr. Gandy!</p>
<p>Chapter 4 Send In The Clones</p>
<pre><code>All of a sudden both Mr. Gandies shrivled up and evaporated. They had ben shot with some tipe of poisones dart. Over the loud speaker a voice was heard “I warned you Mr. Gandy. I couldn’t have you giving away any information about my plan.” The voice chuckled. Then eight men walked through the door. They were the ones that were chasing the Mr. Gandies.</code></pre>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/akriams-library/16525/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/akriams-library/16525/3</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 29 Sep 2006 08:01:43 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-16525-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/akriams-library/16525.rss">Akriam&#39;s Library</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Akriam&#39;s Library</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Akriam Akriam]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/akriam">@Akriam</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>.::Elddem Storyline::.<br>
My name is Ferge, and this is an account of the history of Elddem, from the man who saw it’s beginning, and will see it’s end…<br>
Elddem is not an ordinary place as you may imagine. It is filled with magic and wonder. Most children dream of a place such as this, that is, a place of such greatness you will never want to leave. But wherever there is such as nice place as this, there is someone trying to stop that peace.<br>
It all began a few thousand years back, when the world we now live in today became so overrun with anger and hatred that the gods threatened to destroy our world. One great man, Ferge pleaded with the gods to spare the world they had created. The gods listened and instead of destroying the world, made a new world, one you will know as Elddem. The gods brought Ferge to the new world and made him a mighty ruler. Ferge was very grateful, but he missed his family. Ferge wanted to be with his loved ones, so he created a portal to his world, Elddem, for his family to come through. When the rest of the world found out about this portal, a great war was waged, and many people from both sides were killed. The gods, sickened by the destruction of Elddem closed the portal and put a curse on Ferge and his family that he would never die, but still feel the pains of the world he once belonged to. Elddem was no longer perfect, so the gods had a meeting trying to decide what to do. They decided that they would send monsters into the world to keep the men inline. This brought forth different races such as elves and dwarves. The gods also sent their soldiers to be among the people so they would stay in line. No longer would the people become disruptive, or so the gods thought.</p>
<p>The people were obedient for many years, but eventually a Ferge could not take it any longer. He felt horrible and wanted to die. He recruited an army and tried to kill the gods.<br>
The gods thought it no longer fit to live among the people, so they destroyed every living thing in Elddem accept Ferge and his family, so the memory of the past would be forgotten. They then repopulated Elddem and created a small island for them to live on. This island is protected by thousands of curses and spells, and a human can only reach it’s lands by the gods request. Today Elddem is much like Earth; accept for the fact that is a magical place, one full of wonder. That might be the soul reason that the gods did not destroy Elddem, because they thought it could become a better place, a place unlike Earth, and they had hoped that one day, Elddem would be fit for the gods to live amongst the people once again.<br>
With the constant discovery of new creatures in Elddem, the people eventually started using the creatures as they used horses and ox back on Earth. It was inevitable that the humans eventually found the dragon. The people who found it knew how powerful this creature was just by looking at it, so they kept it a secret. They formed a tribe called the dragoons, and with every passing second they spent with the dragons, the magic from the dragons started to rub off on them. The dragoons had become so powerful that they could not continue to be a secret. The gods gave the dragoons great power and glory. The dragoons were peaceful, so the gods gave them the task of ruling over Elddem, and they did a great job of it. The whole world of Elddem seemed to be in a better mood. This age is referred to as the “Golden Age”. After about 600 years of this great period in Elddem, an army from and uncharted island in the east plotted to attack the dragoons so they could rule the Elddem.<br>
There was a great war, lasting 34 years. When it finally looked as if the army from the east, or as they preferred themselves to be called the Imperials, were about to lose, the Imperials knew they had to dishonor themselves if they whished to win the Great War. They poisoned the dragon’s water supply, so the dragons would catch diseases. The diseases eventually spread to the dragoons, and the Imperials had wiped the dragons and dragoons off the face of the Elddem, or so they had thought. The gods protected a small group of dragons and dragoons, knowing they were the purest race in all of Elddem. The dragoons appear around the world of Elddem every now and then, and if you are lucky enough to see one, you are extremely lucky. Today the dragoons help the gods keep everything under control. It is said that if you see one your luck is so great that you will become rich.<br>
It is not sure as to the exact time, but Elddem historians like to believe that between the 600th and 653rd year of the Imperials reign Ferge was brought to the gods, and had a great revelation. He saw that he was the cause of the pain, and started to run out the door to try and do something about it, when the gods removed the curse because they saw that he was once again a pure heart. He immediately turned to dust and died. His family had been returned the age they were before the curse was put on them. The gods sent a man to Ferge’s family, and when the doorknob turned, and the door opened, Ferge stepped through the door. He had been reborned as a man, an immortal man with such pure heart that the gods trusted him in leading an army to free the people from the Imperials tyranny.<br>
Who was Ferge’s army you say? The dragoons. They had repopulated among themselves, and had become even more powerful. Even though they had less numbers than the Imperials, they knew in their hearts they could destroy them.  Ferge’s army won the first battle of that war, with very few casualties. That victory was followed by many wins and loses, but they knew they could win, it just wouldn’t be easy.<br>
About two in a half years into the war the gods knew that Ferge, even though he was immortal, was tired and missing his family, so they let him go back (no one knows exactly where “back” is, but it is some remote location) to his family. The leader who took Ferge’s place is doing just fine, and Ferge will sometimes appear on the battlefield, although rarely.<br>
Now it is time to say a word about you, young one.  You were born in the 3rd year of this war and it is now the 21st year. Now that you are ready to leave your family and go out on your own, you must know some things and remember you can visit your family anytime you want. But the most important thing is BE CAREFUL IN THE IMPERIAL’S LAND!<br>
Copyright - © 2006 SoulGamerz/Elddem/Akriam</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/akriams-library/16525/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/akriams-library/16525/2</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 29 Sep 2006 07:55:03 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-16525-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/akriams-library/16525.rss">Akriam&#39;s Library</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Akriam&#39;s Library</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Akriam Akriam]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/akriam">@Akriam</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[size=20pt]AKRIAM’S LIBRARY[/size]</p>
<p>Well seeing as how this is now a writing board also, I will be extremely active here. Well, as some of you know, I love to write stories. I have writen the storyline for a game called Elddem, and am currently writing one for my own MMORPG called Areithe (see my signarute ;D).</p>
<p>Anyways, I want to be an author when I grow up, so I suppose I will post some of my stories here. If you need a story for something PM me and I we will work something out :P)</p>
<p>So without further ado:</p>
<p><code>AKRIAM's LIBRARY
1.)Elddem Storyline-Page 1 Post 2
2.)Nightshadow and Nightshade-Page 1 Post 3
</code></p>
<p>If I have a new story I will post it and add it the the library. Since I think it is against the rules to reserve posts for my own stories, they will be scatered all over this thread. Also, if you have a story, post it, and I will add it to a list entiteld “(Your name)'s Library”.</p>
<p>Thanks,<br>
Akriam [size=7pt](GASP Inc.)[/size]</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/akriams-library/16525/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/akriams-library/16525/1</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 29 Sep 2006 07:53:41 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-16525-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/akriams-library/16525.rss">Akriam&#39;s Library</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
