<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>[Coder needed.] &#39;Project Aryan&#39;</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/coder-needed-project-aryan/395432</link>
    <description>[center]Please read the whole thread before leaving or leaving a reply.

Dear Users,
It is my pleasure to welcome you to the development team recruitment thread of &#39;Project Aryan&#39;. At the moment, we have nothing, literally. We do not have a source, a coder, forums or anything. I will be able to make free forums when necessary however there are more important things to do. I know that a lot of you may come to this thread, read a bit and then leave straight away. I can understand this, after all I have just made this thread with literally nothing. I know you may think what&#39;s the point in applying or even reading if we don&#39;t even have a source.  However, I can gurantee that this development is going to be big, the other owner and myself, as well as the coder that we recruit from this thread, are going to try our hardest to make the server as perfect and appealing as possible. We aren&#39;t even going to get over the first hurdle if we can&#39;t find a willing and active coder for us, so we really need you, if you code, to think things through and possibly apply. In saying this though, we are going to need the best coder possible. Just because I say we need one, does not mean that I am searching as quick as possible just for anybody, we are going to be looking for an experienced coder who will be active and loyal to the project. Unfortunately, because of the fact that we do not even have a server, there is no way for me to get any pictures in order to attract people. I understand that, so please do not make a reply saying that we need pictures or some sort of attraction if we are going to want a development team. So please, if you are an experienced coder who is willing to be a part of this project, or know somebody that could be, then please either fill out an application or get them to.
The server/source will be worked off whichever base the coder decides, however it will be a blank source, as we do not want to leech. If the coder decides that he would like another coder to work with to speed up the job, then we will either update this thread, invite another member that applied earlier, or create a new thread. 

[b][u]APPLICATION[/u][/b]
[b]Real name: 
Your age: 
Your time-zone: 
MSN: 
How long have you been coding:
How many hours will you be able to put into coding per day: 
Would you prefer to have another coder with you if you are accepted: 
[/b]

Thank you for reading,
Aŕcaɳe.

Okay guys, I know this must look really bad now, I just remembered I created a new account. I haven&#39;t been on the MoparScape forums for more then a week, however I created this new account just before creating this thread. It must look bad as I am new; have 10 reputation and don&#39;t have pictures. I really hope you guys can trust me on this one, I am going to put my heart and soul into this project.

Thanks.[/center]</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 21 May 2011 18:21:46 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/coder-needed-project-aryan/395432.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>[Coder needed.] &#39;Project Aryan&#39;</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@farme farme]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/farme">@farme</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Real name: Steven<br>
Your age: 16<br>
MSN: <a href="mailto:farmer4life2010@hotmail.com">farmer4life2010@hotmail.com</a><br>
How long have you been coding:3years<br>
How many hours will you be able to put into coding per day: A lot not a fix number over 10 for sure<br>
Would you prefer to have another coder with you if you are accepted:yes but a skilled 1:)</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/coder-needed-project-aryan/395432/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/coder-needed-project-aryan/395432/5</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 21 May 2011 18:21:46 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-395432-5</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/coder-needed-project-aryan/395432.rss">[Coder needed.] &#39;Project Aryan&#39;</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Coder needed.] &#39;Project Aryan&#39;</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@pokemonn pokemonn]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/pokemonn">@pokemonn</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Real name: Alex<br>
Your age: 15<br>
Your time-zone: eastern<br>
MSN: <a href="mailto:prededor5@hotmail.com">prededor5@hotmail.com</a><br>
How long have you been coding: 4 years<br>
How many hours will you be able to put into coding per day: depends,about 1-10hrs<br>
Would you prefer to have another coder with you if you are accepted: ill work with the guy above</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/coder-needed-project-aryan/395432/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/coder-needed-project-aryan/395432/4</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 21 May 2011 17:36:41 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-395432-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/coder-needed-project-aryan/395432.rss">[Coder needed.] &#39;Project Aryan&#39;</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Coder needed.] &#39;Project Aryan&#39;</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@kendal25 kendal25]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/kendal25">@kendal25</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Real name: Ryan Suits<br>
Your age: 17<br>
Your time-zone: -5<br>
MSN: <a href="mailto:myownum@live.com">myownum@live.com</a><br>
How long have you been coding:3years<br>
How many hours will you be able to put into coding per day: depends on what i am doing maybe 30-60<br>
Would you prefer to have another coder with you if you are accepted:yes</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/coder-needed-project-aryan/395432/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/coder-needed-project-aryan/395432/3</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 20 May 2011 15:15:12 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-395432-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/coder-needed-project-aryan/395432.rss">[Coder needed.] &#39;Project Aryan&#39;</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Coder needed.] &#39;Project Aryan&#39;</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Shadowspkin Shadowspkin]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/shadowspkin">@Shadowspkin</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>MMmmm,  Nice explanation I guess and Good  post for most part… For a source I recommend RiotScape V4 for a server your MAKING and not LEECHING… If you need help  my MSN is <a href="mailto:Shadows-pking@hotmail.com">Shadows-pking@hotmail.com</a> I dont plan on coding for you as im trying to take a brake from it but Ill try an help you. Also a nice place to go for some help is " * " Sorry if I cant say that if a mod see’s this im not sure if I can say other websites or not.</p>
<p>[size=7pt]* - Not without a moderators approval  ;)[/size]</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/coder-needed-project-aryan/395432/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/coder-needed-project-aryan/395432/2</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 19 May 2011 22:41:42 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-395432-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/coder-needed-project-aryan/395432.rss">[Coder needed.] &#39;Project Aryan&#39;</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Coder needed.] &#39;Project Aryan&#39;</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Arca_e Aŕcaɳe]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/arca_e">@Arca_e</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[center]Please read the whole thread before leaving or leaving a reply.</p>
<p>Dear Users,<br>
It is my pleasure to welcome you to the development team recruitment thread of ‘Project Aryan’. At the moment, we have nothing, literally. We do not have a source, a coder, forums or anything. I will be able to make free forums when necessary however there are more important things to do. I know that a lot of you may come to this thread, read a bit and then leave straight away. I can understand this, after all I have just made this thread with literally nothing. I know you may think what’s the point in applying or even reading if we don’t even have a source.  However, I can gurantee that this development is going to be big, the other owner and myself, as well as the coder that we recruit from this thread, are going to try our hardest to make the server as perfect and appealing as possible. We aren’t even going to get over the first hurdle if we can’t find a willing and active coder for us, so we really need you, if you code, to think things through and possibly apply. In saying this though, we are going to need the best coder possible. Just because I say we need one, does not mean that I am searching as quick as possible just for anybody, we are going to be looking for an experienced coder who will be active and loyal to the project. Unfortunately, because of the fact that we do not even have a server, there is no way for me to get any pictures in order to attract people. I understand that, so please do not make a reply saying that we need pictures or some sort of attraction if we are going to want a development team. So please, if you are an experienced coder who is willing to be a part of this project, or know somebody that could be, then please either fill out an application or get them to.<br>
The server/source will be worked off whichever base the coder decides, however it will be a blank source, as we do not want to leech. If the coder decides that he would like another coder to work with to speed up the job, then we will either update this thread, invite another member that applied earlier, or create a new thread.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b"><span class="bbcode-u">APPLICATION</span></span><br>
<span class="bbcode-b">Real name:<br>
Your age:<br>
Your time-zone:<br>
MSN:<br>
How long have you been coding:<br>
How many hours will you be able to put into coding per day:<br>
Would you prefer to have another coder with you if you are accepted:<br>
</span></p>
<p>Thank you for reading,<br>
Aŕcaɳe.</p>
<p>Okay guys, I know this must look really bad now, I just remembered I created a new account. I haven’t been on the MoparScape forums for more then a week, however I created this new account just before creating this thread. It must look bad as I am new; have 10 reputation and don’t have pictures. I really hope you guys can trust me on this one, I am going to put my heart and soul into this project.</p>
<p>Thanks.[/center]</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/coder-needed-project-aryan/395432/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/coder-needed-project-aryan/395432/1</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 17 May 2011 19:22:17 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-395432-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/coder-needed-project-aryan/395432.rss">[Coder needed.] &#39;Project Aryan&#39;</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
