<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>317 Help?</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/317-help/518979</link>
    <description>Hi guys,
Please don&#39;t hate on me for being an absolute noob, but I guess if I don&#39;t ask then I&#39;ll never find out. What&#39;s the difference between a client and a server? Basically what I want is a 317 private server which I can play on with a group of my mates but open to the public at the same time if anyone wants to play it. I haven&#39;t found a clear enough tutorial for me to achieve this. I have been trying all day with no success, downloading blank servers and stuff like that, playing with client.java and compiling, all to no avail. I just need some knowledge so I can get this project done. Could someone give me some pointers or something? Cheers
Sorry for being a noob</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 13 May 2013 14:41:24 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/317-help/518979.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>317 Help?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@sk8rdude461 sk8rdude461]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/sk8rdude461">@sk8rdude461</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>The client holds the visual side of the game. What I mean is it holds all the items for you to actually see and play the game. It sends data over to the server and the server will relay data to tell have the client show what you did.<br>
So like walking. You see your player and map. You then click a place on the map. That gets sent to the server from the client. The server verifies that you can walk there, and tells the client to animate the player and go ahead and walk to the position.</p>
<p>Now, you’re going to download a client AND source in a package, hopefully it comes with the cache. You want to get updated JRE and JDK. If you have a 64 bit Computer and OS, you want to get both the x86 and x64 downloads for JDK and JRE, if you need links, I can get you them.</p>
<p>From there you’re going to want to open the server and clients compiler.bat and make sure they have this in there:<br>
“C:\Program Files\Java\jdk1.7.0_21\bin\javac.exe”<br>
and there will be junk after that.<br>
The version of JDK is important as it will give a “The system cannot find path…” error otherwise.</p>
<p>From there you’re going to want to edit the IP in the client. Find client.java (CLIENT SIDED) and search either “127.0.0.1” or “server =” usually most 317’s have server =.<br>
You want to set it to 127.0.0.1 as that’s local host.<br>
Then run the compiler for the client.<br>
Now Run the server and make sure it doesn’t have an IP you need to change (Project Insanity’s don’t have on, most delta’s do).<br>
After the server is running, run the client.<br>
Login with any user/pass and you’re golden.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/317-help/518979/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/317-help/518979/5</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 13 May 2013 14:41:24 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-518979-5</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/317-help/518979.rss">317 Help?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>317 Help?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@GodexCAB GodexCAB]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/godexcab">@GodexCAB</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote quote-modified" data-post="3" data-topic="518979">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/rangerunner2/40/5_e05bb34c421432ee4d40de30c10af3e5.png" class="avatar"> rangerunner2:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>I have downloaded Renegadepkz server and client by JIMBO purely as a test to see if I can get my friends to be able to join my server. What do I need to do now? I have gone into GUI.java in the client folder, changed ‘serverip = ***’ to my no-ip address and zipped the client. My friend downloaded it and is having no success connecting. Could someone help? Thanks</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>When running your server and no-ip, go to <a href="http://canyouseeme.org" rel="nofollow noopener">canyouseeme.org</a> and type in 43594 for the port. If your port can be connected to then it will say it can you see, and people can play your game. If it says it cannot see you, then you need to port forward so that people can play your server.<br>
If you do not know how to port forward, there are tutorials, but I cannot help you with port forwarding, I have to use Hamachi so I dont need to port forward</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/317-help/518979/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/317-help/518979/4</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 12 May 2013 21:26:24 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-518979-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/317-help/518979.rss">317 Help?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>317 Help?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@rangerunner2 rangerunner2]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/rangerunner2">@rangerunner2</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I have downloaded Renegadepkz server and client by JIMBO purely as a test to see if I can get my friends to be able to join my server. What do I need to do now? I have gone into GUI.java in the client folder, changed ‘serverip = ***’ to my no-ip address and zipped the client. My friend downloaded it and is having no success connecting. Could someone help? Thanks</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/317-help/518979/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/317-help/518979/3</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 12 May 2013 19:27:07 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-518979-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/317-help/518979.rss">317 Help?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>317 Help?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@GodexCAB GodexCAB]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/godexcab">@GodexCAB</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>A client is the thing you load to play the server(source). The server(source) is the game. There are some clients you can use to play any RSPS server/source.</p>
<p>You need a no-ip (with port forwarding) or a Hamachi (without port forwarding) for other people to play on your server.<br>
Good luck.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/317-help/518979/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/317-help/518979/2</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 11 May 2013 22:02:48 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-518979-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/317-help/518979.rss">317 Help?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>317 Help?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@rangerunner2 rangerunner2]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/rangerunner2">@rangerunner2</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Hi guys,<br>
Please don’t hate on me for being an absolute noob, but I guess if I don’t ask then I’ll never find out. What’s the difference between a client and a server? Basically what I want is a 317 private server which I can play on with a group of my mates but open to the public at the same time if anyone wants to play it. I haven’t found a clear enough tutorial for me to achieve this. I have been trying all day with no success, downloading blank servers and stuff like that, playing with client.java and compiling, all to no avail. I just need some knowledge so I can get this project done. Could someone give me some pointers or something? Cheers<br>
Sorry for being a noob</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/317-help/518979/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/317-help/518979/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 11 May 2013 21:14:58 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-518979-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/317-help/518979.rss">317 Help?</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
