<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Woodstock 99 thoughts</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/woodstock-99-thoughts/551321</link>
    <description>I remember hearing about a failed woodstock event when I was a child but didn&#39;t know much about it untill just recently as I was looking at an article on the original 1969 Woodstock and it had links to the Woodstock 99 saying it was such an extreme failure in comparison to the original.

Before you argue about the subject I hope you atleast have a decent prior knowledge of it , otherwise I want you to research Woodstock 99 from some of these links and other sources.. , https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Woodstock_1999 particurly the bit on the problems of it .. And http://www.rollingstone.com/music/news/19-worst-things-about-woodstock-99-20140731
And some of the youtube videos of the drama.

 But above all have a look at some of the live performances especially those of Limp bizkit when they performed &quot;break stuff&quot; and a fück load of the audience started breaking stuff including the outside fencing , and when red hot chili peppers played the cover of jimi Hendrix song &quot;fire&quot; and bon fires started lighting up all over the grounds.

At first look when reading these articles on what was going on and how big the fück up was I thought I would never want to of been there ... In the ultimate daggy late 90s with complete assholes breaking stuff at a festival that is supposed to be about peace.

But after seeing some of the live performances of some of my favourite bands arguably in their prime playing complete un altered and uncensored music and how a lot of the violence/destruction could be argued as a rebellion and protest to the corporate greed of the festival organisers which relates a lot to the world today. As well as  other performances such as insane clown posse funny song &quot;fück the world&quot; where they said &quot;fück that faggot eminem&quot; as they famously had beef at the time.

 I started to think that it was a once in a life time festival that would have been horrible at times to be to but you would have no better live soundtrack to go through hell to and it was &quot;the death of the 90s&quot; and when punk rock was ultimately still cool.  I would honestly give  anything to have experienced Woodstock 99.

I know I may look like an idiot especially if you have known about the event for lot longer than me, but these are justs my thoughts I thought I might share.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 02 May 2015 19:47:52 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>General Discussion</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/woodstock-99-thoughts/551321.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Woodstock 99 thoughts</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@runerunerune runerunerune]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/runerunerune">@runerunerune</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I remember hearing about a failed woodstock event when I was a child but didn’t know much about it untill just recently as I was looking at an article on the original 1969 Woodstock and it had links to the Woodstock 99 saying it was such an extreme failure in comparison to the original.</p>
<p>Before you argue about the subject I hope you atleast have a decent prior knowledge of it , otherwise I want you to research Woodstock 99 from some of these links and other sources… , <a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Woodstock_1999" rel="nofollow noopener">https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Woodstock_1999</a> particurly the bit on the problems of it … And <a href="http://www.rollingstone.com/music/news/19-worst-things-about-woodstock-99-20140731" rel="nofollow noopener">http://www.rollingstone.com/music/news/19-worst-things-about-woodstock-99-20140731</a><br>
And some of the youtube videos of the drama.</p>
<p>But above all have a look at some of the live performances especially those of Limp bizkit when they performed “break stuff” and a fück load of the audience started breaking stuff including the outside fencing , and when red hot chili peppers played the cover of jimi Hendrix song “fire” and bon fires started lighting up all over the grounds.</p>
<p>At first look when reading these articles on what was going on and how big the fück up was I thought I would never want to of been there … In the ultimate daggy late 90s with complete assholes breaking stuff at a festival that is supposed to be about peace.</p>
<p>But after seeing some of the live performances of some of my favourite bands arguably in their prime playing complete un altered and uncensored music and how a lot of the violence/destruction could be argued as a rebellion and protest to the corporate greed of the festival organisers which relates a lot to the world today. As well as  other performances such as insane clown posse funny song “fück the world” where they said “fück that faggot eminem” as they famously had beef at the time.</p>
<p>I started to think that it was a once in a life time festival that would have been horrible at times to be to but you would have no better live soundtrack to go through hell to and it was “the death of the 90s” and when punk rock was ultimately still cool.  I would honestly give  anything to have experienced Woodstock 99.</p>
<p>I know I may look like an idiot especially if you have known about the event for lot longer than me, but these are justs my thoughts I thought I might share.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/woodstock-99-thoughts/551321/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/woodstock-99-thoughts/551321/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 02 May 2015 19:47:52 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-551321-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/woodstock-99-thoughts/551321.rss">Woodstock 99 thoughts</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
