<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>317 Deob Programming</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/317-deob-programming/223428</link>
    <description>I&#39;ve been trying to find out how to load custom backgrounds on a deob, I thought it had something to do with method37, method56, method106, method7, method64, or method140.  Oh, here&#39;s translations if you aren&#39;t sure what they do.

method37 - write Background Texture
method56 - create Background And Logo
method106 - draw Startup Backgrounds
method7 - createLogIn
method64 - reset Login Screen
method140 - show LogIn

I&#39;ve already edited method56 to delete the logo, and here is what I have so far:

[URL=http://imageshack.us][IMG]http://img106.imageshack.us/img106/250/screenshot0006nv2.png[/img][/URL]

I then edited something like this: [b]Image image = Toolkit.getDefaultToolkit().createImage(abyte0);[/b], but then I get this:

[URL=http://imageshack.us][IMG]http://img117.imageshack.us/img117/7169/screenshot0007vr1.png[/img][/URL]

Any help would be very much appreciated as I&#39;m stuck on a very annoying obstacle.

I thought this would fit this subject as I am talking about client hacking, and it&#39;s not just a simple dumb question like, &quot;how i add modelz pls?&quot;</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 02 Aug 2008 00:57:17 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/317-deob-programming/223428.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>317 Deob Programming</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Soul_Pr1nc3 Soul Pr1nc3]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/soul_pr1nc3">@Soul_Pr1nc3</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>naise</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/317-deob-programming/223428/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/317-deob-programming/223428/4</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 02 Aug 2008 00:57:17 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-223428-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/317-deob-programming/223428.rss">317 Deob Programming</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>317 Deob Programming</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@TeleNubby TeleNubby]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/telenubby">@TeleNubby</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Oh, you posted here too? <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=6" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"> You didn’t have to PM me the whole thing, then. <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/wink.png?v=6" title=":wink:" class="emoji" alt=":wink:"></p>
<p>I PMed you a solution just a few moments ago (one of many ways to accomplish this task), if you’re still interested.</p>
<p>EDIT: Might as well post it here for the public…</p>
<p>[quote=“TeleNubby”]Hey U WAN DIE?! What’s crackin’?</p>
<p>Method140() is not <span class="bbcode-i">JUST</span> <span class="bbcode-i">showing</span> login. It pretty much handles all interaction at the login-interface level. Any clicks, button presses, etc (this does NOT include the drawing).</p>
<p>What you want to focus on is method56(). The <span class="bbcode-b">parameter i</span> of type Integer.TYPE (located inside of the parantheses - this is called the method parameter, or argument, but you must remember there can be more than one) is simply a dummy. A dummy is something that is there to fool you, and is never used in anything important. Jagex’s obfuscator (program that obfuscates bytecode for a rougher time when it comes to decompiling, which can also rename fields and classes to your disadvantage like it has done here) throws those in here and there all in an attempt to confuse you.</p>
<p>A few examples of dummies:</p>
<pre><code class="lang-auto">public method dummy1(int i)
{
      if(i != 0) return;
      else
      {
             //Do stuff
      }
}</code></pre>
<pre><code class="lang-auto">public method dummy2(int i)
{
      if(i &gt; 100)
      {
            //Do stuff
      }
      else return;
}</code></pre>
<pre><code class="lang-auto">public method dummy3(int i)
{
      int usedValue = 100/i;
      otherMethod(usedValue);
}</code></pre>
<p>I’m sure you get the picture by now. But take a look at the last one. It’s hard to tell what the paramater i is doing in that one. But after what you would call ‘dumping’ the value (debugging or printing out the value of the field for your knowledge - a simple System.out.println(param); would work fine) sometimes the value is ALWAYS the same. This means it is a constant. It still is a dummy, but instead of being variable, it stays the same. So to get rid of the dummy in this case, just replace i with the value that is staying constant.</p>
<hr>
<p>Enough about dummies, that should clear a few things up for now. <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=6" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"> Your question was focused on how to load/draw custom backgrounds. Well this can be done in a few ways, so I will go about listing a few for you to decide.</p>
<p>Lets take another look at method56(). You were right with your description. It DOES draw the background AND the logo. The thing is, Jagex has stored the background image in the cache as only half! Yes, that’s right. Why? Because the image is symmetrical, or both halves are the same when one of them is flipped. Sort of like a butterfly. <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/wink.png?v=6" title=":wink:" class="emoji" alt=":wink:"></p>
<p>With that in mind, there is no real reason for them to store two times as much data in the cache (a waste of space), so they only store half of their background image. But because of this, they must draw the second half using the first half directly in the client. Method56() is exactly where this takes place. After a little refactoring and looking over the client (refactoring is the term used for replacing/renaming chunks of data to in someway represent its original form before obfuscation, so pretty much to get it to resemble the source code Jagex has <span class="bbcode-i">as much as possible.</span>), you can see that <span class="bbcode-b">Class30_Sub2_Sub1_Sub1 is actually the Sprite class.</span></p>
<p>Take a look at this right here:</p>
<pre><code class="lang-auto">Class30_Sub2_Sub1_Sub1 class30_sub2_sub1_sub1 = new Class30_Sub2_Sub1_Sub1(abyte0, this);</code></pre>
<p>This creates a new instance of Class30_Sub2_Sub1_Sub1, using the data found in abyte0. Take a closer look at the Class30_Sub2_Sub1_Sub1 class and the constructor used in the above line of code. I highly suggest it to understand a little more about what’s going on (remember, Class30_Sub2_Sub1_Sub1 is the Sprite class, so are creating a new Sprite using the byte array). What is the data abyte0 represents? Well, abyte0 is a byte array, so it is a collection of bytes stored in an array.</p>
<p>Abyte0 is initialized (or given meaning/value to) at this point:</p>
<pre><code class="lang-auto">byte abyte0[] = aClass44_1053.method571("title.dat", null);</code></pre>
<p>After more and more refactoring, you can see aClass44_1053 represents a StreamLoader instance (if I am correct - bear in mind these new class/field/method names I’m giving you are custom and you are not limited to using those, feel free to make up your own), and method 571() reads from that StreamLoader instance and returns a byte array.</p>
<p>After taking matters into your hands, you can find out that abyte0 is the data for the background image! How you can find this out? Simply dump the byte[] using the FileOutputStream class (by dump , this time I mean save it as a physical file) as a JPEG image (Jagex uses the JPEG format for most of their images). Now that you know you are standing in the correct position, you can continue down the road. <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=6" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
<p>Alright, we know enough information to begin loading custom sprites, now. Lets take a look again at this line:</p>
<pre><code class="lang-auto">byte abyte0[] = aClass44_1053.method571("title.dat", null);</code></pre>
<p>We now know enough that abyte0 is the background image used at startup. So instead of using the data of the image <span class="bbcode-i">Jagex has in store for the client</span>, <span class="bbcode-b">you can replace that byte array with the data of an image of your choosing!</span>. To obtain the data, or byte array, of the image you want to use, simply read from the file using the FileInputStream class. A good discussion involing the accomplishment of this task can be found here: <a href="http://forums.sun.com/thread.jspa?messageID=2393574" rel="nofollow noopener">http://forums.sun.com/thread.jspa?messageID=2393574</a> (located at the official Sun Java programming forums). So in conclusion, instead of using their image data, use your own!</p>
<p>Feel free to try out the method I described. I’m positive and can pretty much garuntee you it’ll work when done correctly. I hope you enjoyed reading this message, and if not, I hope you at least learned something today. If you need anymore help, feel free to contact me. <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=6" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
<p>Yours truly,<br>
TeleNubby.[/quote]</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/317-deob-programming/223428/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/317-deob-programming/223428/3</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 02 Aug 2008 00:39:34 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-223428-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/317-deob-programming/223428.rss">317 Deob Programming</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>317 Deob Programming</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Scarecrows Scarecrows]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/scarecrows">@Scarecrows</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I posted a topic for the 317 deob in the download section, i edited the Class30_Sub2_Sub1_Sub1 to load custom background image, you can grab from there or simply make the background image load from a URL " getImage"</p>
<pre><code>        Image image = Toolkit.getDefaultToolkit().getImage(new URL(""));</code></pre>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/317-deob-programming/223428/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/317-deob-programming/223428/2</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 02 Aug 2008 00:14:52 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-223428-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/317-deob-programming/223428.rss">317 Deob Programming</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>317 Deob Programming</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@U_WAN_DIE U WAN DIE?]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/u_wan_die">@U_WAN_DIE</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I’ve been trying to find out how to load custom backgrounds on a deob, I thought it had something to do with method37, method56, method106, method7, method64, or method140.  Oh, here’s translations if you aren’t sure what they do.</p>
<p>method37 - write Background Texture<br>
method56 - create Background And Logo<br>
method106 - draw Startup Backgrounds<br>
method7 - createLogIn<br>
method64 - reset Login Screen<br>
method140 - show LogIn</p>
<p>I’ve already edited method56 to delete the logo, and here is what I have so far:</p>
<p><a href="http://imageshack.us" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener"><img src="http://img106.imageshack.us/img106/250/screenshot0006nv2.png" alt width="" height=""></a></p>
<p>I then edited something like this: <span class="bbcode-b">Image image = Toolkit.getDefaultToolkit().createImage(abyte0);</span>, but then I get this:</p>
<p><a href="http://imageshack.us" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener"><img src="http://img117.imageshack.us/img117/7169/screenshot0007vr1.png" alt width="" height=""></a></p>
<p>Any help would be very much appreciated as I’m stuck on a very annoying obstacle.</p>
<p>I thought this would fit this subject as I am talking about client hacking, and it’s not just a simple dumb question like, “how i add modelz pls?”</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/317-deob-programming/223428/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/317-deob-programming/223428/1</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2008 23:35:57 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-223428-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/317-deob-programming/223428.rss">317 Deob Programming</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
