<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Sigh, another project I guess</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/sigh-another-project-i-guess/140187</link>
    <description>Well, Dimmu didn&#39;t turn out so good, because people stopped posting. I decided to start a new project based on PimpScape (Yes I know, &quot;pmg pimpscape is lyk for lozerz lelelele!&quot;)

I don&#39;t know what I&#39;ll be naming it, so lets go with Projekt Nameless (Yes I know I spelled Project wrong, it&#39;s the whole point lols.)

What else.. I won&#39;t be making a site, because it&#39;ll end up not being used, because I&#39;m still working on bits of Dimmu.

So, lets see...

Updates:
Name changed
Removed tons of shit
Added in a couple custom methods for special reasons &gt;.&gt;

Future updates:
More classes, smaller client
Specials
Few more skills for now
Enhance PKing
Better Magic
Better Ranging
Work on PKing again

That&#39;s probably it for now, nothing special, just another project that will fail, because I&#39;m bored with Dimmu because of the LACK OF POSTS.

Sooooo...
Thanks for reading, I&#39;ll update this daily probably, and might end up using this as a base for a server.
Sincerely,
Fr33b1e</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 04 Sep 2007 02:41:33 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/sigh-another-project-i-guess/140187.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Sigh, another project I guess</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Fr33b1e Fr33b1e]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/fr33b1e">@Fr33b1e</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Well, Dimmu didn’t turn out so good, because people stopped posting. I decided to start a new project based on PimpScape (Yes I know, “pmg pimpscape is lyk for lozerz lelelele!”)</p>
<p>I don’t know what I’ll be naming it, so lets go with Projekt Nameless (Yes I know I spelled Project wrong, it’s the whole point lols.)</p>
<p>What else… I won’t be making a site, because it’ll end up not being used, because I’m still working on bits of Dimmu.</p>
<p>So, lets see…</p>
<p>Updates:<br>
Name changed<br>
Removed tons of shit<br>
Added in a couple custom methods for special reasons &gt;.&gt;</p>
<p>Future updates:<br>
More classes, smaller client<br>
Specials<br>
Few more skills for now<br>
Enhance PKing<br>
Better Magic<br>
Better Ranging<br>
Work on PKing again</p>
<p>That’s probably it for now, nothing special, just another project that will fail, because I’m bored with Dimmu because of the LACK OF POSTS.</p>
<p>Sooooo…<br>
Thanks for reading, I’ll update this daily probably, and might end up using this as a base for a server.<br>
Sincerely,<br>
Fr33b1e</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/sigh-another-project-i-guess/140187/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/sigh-another-project-i-guess/140187/1</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 04 Sep 2007 02:41:33 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-140187-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/sigh-another-project-i-guess/140187.rss">Sigh, another project I guess</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
