<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>732 Packet Error</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/732-packet-error/468947</link>
    <description>Decided to start trying to learn higher revision coding, but i&#39;m still fairly new..

I&#39;m sure i&#39;m just being an idiot when i ask this but i really don&#39;t have the experience to figure it out i suppose, so if someone could kindly explain this so i can try to learn it i would be greatly appreciative.

Basically what&#39;s going on is, There was an anti-leech on the source i decided to use in  the NPCHandler which i had fixed, now when i kill an NPC I get this and my client crashes right after, which i think is another part of the anti-leech, but i&#39;ve never done much with packets so i&#39;m extremely lost... anyway, the error in the RUN.CMD Looks like this:

[CODE]
[WorldPacketsDecoder] Missing packet 16, expected size: 2, actual size: 2
[/CODE]

I&#39;m not sure if i&#39;m looking at the right bit, but my guess was it was something to do with this in the WorldPacketsDecoder
[CODE]
PACKET_SIZES[16] = 2;
[/CODE]

Like i said i&#39;m very unsure what this is because i&#39;m new to these high revisions. But if someone could explain what is causing this/What is needed to fix it i would greatly appreciate it!

~Thanks in Advance!</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 17 Nov 2012 02:18:02 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/732-packet-error/468947.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>732 Packet Error</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Bludstained Bludstained]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/bludstained">@Bludstained</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Decided to start trying to learn higher revision coding, but i’m still fairly new…</p>
<p>I’m sure i’m just being an idiot when i ask this but i really don’t have the experience to figure it out i suppose, so if someone could kindly explain this so i can try to learn it i would be greatly appreciative.</p>
<p>Basically what’s going on is, There was an anti-leech on the source i decided to use in  the NPCHandler which i had fixed, now when i kill an NPC I get this and my client crashes right after, which i think is another part of the anti-leech, but i’ve never done much with packets so i’m extremely lost… anyway, the error in the RUN.CMD Looks like this:</p>
<pre><code class="lang-auto">[WorldPacketsDecoder] Missing packet 16, expected size: 2, actual size: 2</code></pre>
<p>I’m not sure if i’m looking at the right bit, but my guess was it was something to do with this in the WorldPacketsDecoder</p>
<pre><code class="lang-auto">PACKET_SIZES[16] = 2;</code></pre>
<p>Like i said i’m very unsure what this is because i’m new to these high revisions. But if someone could explain what is causing this/What is needed to fix it i would greatly appreciate it!</p>
<p>~Thanks in Advance!</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/732-packet-error/468947/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/732-packet-error/468947/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 17 Nov 2012 02:18:02 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-468947-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/732-packet-error/468947.rss">732 Packet Error</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
