<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Help plz very wierd</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/help-plz-very-wierd/202648</link>
    <description>ok... whenever i get into a game server for some reason i cant see my own character and i cant see anyone elses. sometimes i can see people. i can see them on my minimap andi  can see thier text. plz idk what to do bout it. ive restarted my comp ive refreshed the game multiple times and i played on different servers and it still happens. i tryed to play it on another client and it just lags like crazy. i noticed that i can walk around and talk normally but when i click on my armour thing to see what im wearing and stuff it laggs me out of the game no matter what im doing. i have absolutely no idea what has happend.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 02 May 2008 08:52:56 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/help-plz-very-wierd/202648.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Help plz very wierd</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@M_A_R_I_N_E_C_O_D_E M A R I N E C O D E]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/m_a_r_i_n_e_c_o_d_e">@M_A_R_I_N_E_C_O_D_E</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>my only advice for that is reset cache files and cookies</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/help-plz-very-wierd/202648/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/help-plz-very-wierd/202648/2</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2008 08:52:56 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-202648-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/help-plz-very-wierd/202648.rss">Help plz very wierd</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Help plz very wierd</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@bubba1 bubba1]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/bubba1">@bubba1</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>ok… whenever i get into a game server for some reason i cant see my own character and i cant see anyone elses. sometimes i can see people. i can see them on my minimap andi  can see thier text. plz idk what to do bout it. ive restarted my comp ive refreshed the game multiple times and i played on different servers and it still happens. i tryed to play it on another client and it just lags like crazy. i noticed that i can walk around and talk normally but when i click on my armour thing to see what im wearing and stuff it laggs me out of the game no matter what im doing. i have absolutely no idea what has happend.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/help-plz-very-wierd/202648/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/help-plz-very-wierd/202648/1</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2008 05:32:18 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-202648-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/help-plz-very-wierd/202648.rss">Help plz very wierd</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
