<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Feminism</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/feminism/532213</link>
    <description>Well I couldn&#39;t but help notice on a certain YouTube video that some young lady is so fixated on the world being so feminist. It was almost like she believed that the world was against her or females. So I sat down for a good 5 minutes and came to a conclusion to believe that I have never actually meet or came across someone who was against feminism. Though myself, I don&#39;t like to portray myself as a feminist because I don&#39;t believe in such a fictitious belief to the point where I see males vs females. I see feminism to the point where males were genetically built differently to females to adapt to our environment for the simple fact of survival. An example of this is a study of females brains actually shutting down during sex while males brains stay active, why? Because during the Jurassic times males were the bron, they were the guardians of the village, if you were getting down and dirty with your lady then someone would need to be on alert if any dinos came roaring in. But seeing from this point of view feminist would take that and say its sexist? Why? Well this isn&#39;t a fair test but if I were to take 500 middle aged ladies and 500 teenage ladies I can guarantee you that a bigger percentage of the teenage side would be feminist, again why? Well we all know that teenagers need a sense of recognition, a sense of wanting to be heard, a sense of starting the new trend. You put together the results and see what you get, a raging teenaged school girl who probably has a perfect life but has to find the next best thing to rant about online in hopes that she&#39;ll get more twitter followers, facebook likes or youtube comments. 

I don&#39;t know, its just a small rant from myself and just a small portion of perspectives on my wide variety of beliefs. Please do not take this the wrong way though, I am all for world equality its just my rant on those we believe in things that are quite fiction. I might also state that all statistics and ideas from my rant above are all speculation, no experiments or recordings were taken in place to back up my &#39;proof&#39;. I&#39;d like to think that we can have a civil discussion on different sides of the story which is what I am aiming to look for, your opinion. So yeah, comment below your opinion on feminism or feminist, i&#39;d be more than happy to debate any bull shit we can both come up with.

If anyone was wondering where I got this from it was actually from Robin Thickes music video called blurred lines.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 28 Sep 2013 22:21:02 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>General Discussion</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/feminism/532213.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Feminism</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@RandQm RandQm]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/randqm">@RandQm</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>They want to be equal as long as it turns out positive for them, that’s basically what it is all about.<br>
We still have to pay their drinks, carry the heavy stuff etc… DUDE IM A WOMAN<br>
But when somebody is carrying 50kg sacks of cement, and they carry a 10 one at work they want equal payement.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/feminism/532213/35">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/feminism/532213/35</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 28 Sep 2013 22:21:02 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-532213-35</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/feminism/532213.rss">Feminism</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Feminism</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Techkid Techkid]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/techkid">@Techkid</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“TabbyKiller, post:1, topic:532213”]Well I couldn’t but help notice on a certain YouTube video that some young lady is so fixated on the world being so feminist. It was almost like she believed that the world was against her or females. So I sat down for a good 5 minutes and came to a conclusion to believe that I have never actually meet or came across someone who was against feminism. Though myself, I don’t like to portray myself as a feminist because I don’t believe in such a fictitious belief to the point where I see males vs females. I see feminism to the point where males were genetically built differently to females to adapt to our environment for the simple fact of survival. An example of this is a study of females brains actually shutting down during sex while males brains stay active, why? Because during the Jurassic times males were the bron, they were the guardians of the village, if you were getting down and dirty with your lady then someone would need to be on alert if any dinos came roaring in. But seeing from this point of view feminist would take that and say its sexist? Why? Well this isn’t a fair test but if I were to take 500 middle aged ladies and 500 teenage ladies I can guarantee you that a bigger percentage of the teenage side would be feminist, again why? Well we all know that teenagers need a sense of recognition, a sense of wanting to be heard, a sense of starting the new trend. You put together the results and see what you get, a raging teenaged school girl who probably has a perfect life but has to find the next best thing to rant about online in hopes that she’ll get more twitter followers, facebook likes or youtube comments.</p>
<p>I don’t know, its just a small rant from myself and just a small portion of perspectives on my wide variety of beliefs. Please do not take this the wrong way though, I am all for world equality its just my rant on those we believe in things that are quite fiction. I might also state that all statistics and ideas from my rant above are all speculation, no experiments or recordings were taken in place to back up my ‘proof’. I’d like to think that we can have a civil discussion on different sides of the story which is what I am aiming to look for, your opinion. So yeah, comment below your opinion on feminism or feminist, i’d be more than happy to debate any bull shit we can both come up with.</p>
<p>If anyone was wondering where I got this from it was actually from Robin Thickes music video called blurred lines.[/quote]<br>
Your put so much thought into this… Anyways i think people can’t get over women being equal to men because of strength and other things. Just like racism it will always be there unless someone comes and stops it at once. Some things never change and its a way of life. Don’t be sad about it though. God is coming soon and he will change all this evil people do in this world. My opinion so don’t judge me about my religion i believe what i want you can do as you like.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/feminism/532213/34">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/feminism/532213/34</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 28 Sep 2013 04:41:33 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-532213-34</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/feminism/532213.rss">Feminism</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Feminism</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@CoderOops CoderOops]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/coderoops">@CoderOops</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote" data-post="2" data-topic="532213">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/drubrkletern/40/5_e05bb34c421432ee4d40de30c10af3e5.png" class="avatar"> drubrkletern:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Women looking for superiority not equal rights anymore thats feminism in a nutshell which should now appropriately be called feminazis</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>As long as boobs are ok, im fine with it.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/feminism/532213/33">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/feminism/532213/33</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Sep 2013 19:07:56 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-532213-33</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/feminism/532213.rss">Feminism</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Feminism</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Uncalled Uncalled]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/uncalled">@Uncalled</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote" data-post="12" data-topic="532213">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/frell/40/5_e05bb34c421432ee4d40de30c10af3e5.png" class="avatar"> Frell:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>they want equal rights until it comes to paying for dinner</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<aside class="quote" data-post="13" data-topic="532213">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/user_avatar/forum.moparisthebest.com/davidi2/40/2579_1.png" class="avatar"> Davidi2:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>they want equal rights until it comes to anything at all bad*</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>[quote=“Lothy, post:14, topic:532213”]Yeah, I’ve noticed the glaring lack of petitioning for more responsibility.[/quote]No bullshit, all valid points. If you want equal rights, don’t have double standards. I’ve noticed the majority of females I talk to have outrageous double standards.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/feminism/532213/32">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/feminism/532213/32</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 Sep 2013 20:36:11 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-532213-32</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/feminism/532213.rss">Feminism</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Feminism</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@bowserjr2 Bowser jr]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/bowserjr2">@bowserjr2</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“Frell, post:29, topic:532213”][quote author=Bowser jr link=topic=651004.msg4368912#msg4368912 date=1380217312]</p>
<aside class="quote">
<blockquote>
<aside class="quote">
<blockquote>
<p>Sexual harassment is also the degrading of females, to be treated like a piece of meat in your own workplace does not feel good. That is fine, see what ever you want to see but that doesn’t mean it is right.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>dont dress like a slut</p>
<p>girls have this idea that they can get away with provoking guys and expect a double standard. If I walk around shirtless girls usually touch me and I’ve had pictures taken of me without permission while in hottubs and shit</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>OK, but just because you’re shirtless doesn’t mean that they have the right to touch you.<br>
[/quote]<br>
That just bleeds out of feminism and into general laws. If you grab someones ass on the street they can have you arrested[/quote]<br>
Isn’t it fair? I know of guys who also feel uncomfortable when you touch their ass. (Luckily he didn’t report me). It is a false assumption to think that this just applies to girls.</p>
<p>EDIT: I’m not sexist, I would never do that do a girl without permission.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/feminism/532213/31">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/feminism/532213/31</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 Sep 2013 19:48:14 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-532213-31</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/feminism/532213.rss">Feminism</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Feminism</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Ambokile Ambokile]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/ambokile">@Ambokile</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“Bowser jr, post:28, topic:532213”][quote author=Ambokile link=topic=651004.msg4368858#msg4368858 date=1380209569]<br>
Technically in many laws, rape is only defined as penetration with a penis. Is this not feminism?<br>
[/quote]<br>
Not here. Women can rape men here, and they do not necessary get away with it.[/quote]</p>
<p>Sadly in the UK it’s only men.<br>
<aside class="onebox wikipedia">
  <header class="source">
      <a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Rape_in_English_law" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">en.wikipedia.org</a>
  </header>
  <article class="onebox-body">
    <img src="//upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/en/thumb/6/6c/Wiki_letter_w.svg/40px-Wiki_letter_w.svg.png" class="thumbnail onebox-full-image" width="40" height="40">

<h3><a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Rape_in_English_law" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Rape in English law</a></h3>

<p>Rape is a statutory offence in England and Wales. According to the law, rape occurs when one person penetrates another with their penis without the consent of the person being penetrated. If a victim is forcefully penetrated with an object, this is classed as "Assault by Penetration" (section 2). If the victim is forcefully made to penetrate another, the act can be prosecuted as "Causing a person to engage in sexual activity without consent" (section 4). The offence is created by section 1 of the...</p>

  </article>
  <div class="onebox-metadata">
    
    
  </div>
  <div style="clear: both"></div>
</aside>
</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/feminism/532213/30">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/feminism/532213/30</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 Sep 2013 19:42:43 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-532213-30</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/feminism/532213.rss">Feminism</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Feminism</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Frell Frell]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/frell">@Frell</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“Bowser jr, post:28, topic:532213”][quote author=Frell link=topic=651004.msg4368615#msg4368615 date=1380158069]</p>
<aside class="quote">
<blockquote>
<p>Sexual harassment is also the degrading of females, to be treated like a piece of meat in your own workplace does not feel good. That is fine, see what ever you want to see but that doesn’t mean it is right.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>dont dress like a slut</p>
<p>girls have this idea that they can get away with provoking guys and expect a double standard. If I walk around shirtless girls usually touch me and I’ve had pictures taken of me without permission while in hottubs and shit<br>
[/quote]<br>
OK, but just because you’re shirtless doesn’t mean that they have the right to touch you.[/quote]<br>
That just bleeds out of feminism and into general laws. If you grab someones ass on the street they can have you arrested</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/feminism/532213/29">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/feminism/532213/29</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 Sep 2013 18:22:49 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-532213-29</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/feminism/532213.rss">Feminism</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Feminism</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@bowserjr2 Bowser jr]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/bowserjr2">@bowserjr2</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote" data-post="27" data-topic="532213">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/ambokile/40/5_e05bb34c421432ee4d40de30c10af3e5.png" class="avatar"> Ambokile:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Technically in many laws, rape is only defined as penetration with a penis. Is this not feminism?</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Not here. Women can rape men here, and they do not necessary get away with it.</p>
<p>Feminists here have pushed for gender neutral conscription. So it is a lie that feminists just want special rights.</p>
<p>[quote=“Frell, post:20, topic:532213”][quote author=amy_webb link=topic=651004.msg4368606#msg4368606 date=1380157360]<br>
Sexual harassment is also the degrading of females, to be treated like a piece of meat in your own workplace does not feel good. That is fine, see what ever you want to see but that doesn’t mean it is right.<br>
[/quote]<br>
dont dress like a slut</p>
<p>girls have this idea that they can get away with provoking guys and expect a double standard. If I walk around shirtless girls usually touch me and I’ve had pictures taken of me without permission while in hottubs and shit[/quote]<br>
OK, but just because you’re shirtless doesn’t mean that they have the right to touch you.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/feminism/532213/28">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/feminism/532213/28</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 Sep 2013 17:41:52 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-532213-28</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/feminism/532213.rss">Feminism</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Feminism</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Ambokile Ambokile]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/ambokile">@Ambokile</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote quote-modified" data-post="21" data-topic="532213">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/amy_webb/40/5_e05bb34c421432ee4d40de30c10af3e5.png" class="avatar"> amy_webb:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Guys walk around with short shorts and no tops on and they aren’t raped, yet girls who walk around with short shorts and something that covers their breasts are. Double standards, yer, for who?</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Technically in many laws, rape is only defined as penetration with a penis. Is this not feminism?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/feminism/532213/27">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/feminism/532213/27</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 Sep 2013 15:32:49 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-532213-27</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/feminism/532213.rss">Feminism</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Feminism</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@lothy Lothy]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/lothy">@lothy</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>By its very nature, feminism is an attack on men’s position in society (i.e., smashing the patriarchy). Even if that attack is merely a dilution of power (or rights, to use your term of choice) as opposed to taking that power away and for yourself.<br>
Sure feminism is about equality, not taking rights away from the dominate group, but that’s what it boils down to.</p>
<p>That’s also why most men aren’t receptive to modern feminism. Generally men are fine with it in academia (think women’s studies) because that’s really just someone preaching to the choir - nobody cares that there are a bunch of 20 somethings in a classroom listening to a female lecture about whatever those lectures are about.<br>
But in practice we’re collectively happy with the status quo (and can you blame us? Nobody likes to come second place, or to tie, when they can come in first place).</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/feminism/532213/26">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/feminism/532213/26</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 Sep 2013 06:52:38 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-532213-26</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/feminism/532213.rss">Feminism</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Feminism</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@TabbyKiller TabbyKiller]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/tabbykiller">@TabbyKiller</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote quote-modified" data-post="18" data-topic="532213">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/amy_webb/40/5_e05bb34c421432ee4d40de30c10af3e5.png" class="avatar"> amy_webb:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Sexual harassment is also the degrading of females, to be treated like a piece of meat in your own workplace does not feel good. That is fine, <span class="bbcode-b">see what ever you want to see but that doesn’t mean it is right.</span></p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Likewise Amy. Though, Davids short but well said post is the answer to your, I guess you can call rather interesting statement.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/feminism/532213/25">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/feminism/532213/25</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 Sep 2013 04:20:42 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-532213-25</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/feminism/532213.rss">Feminism</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Feminism</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@amy_webb1 amy_webb]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/amy_webb1">@amy_webb1</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I don’t see how increasing women’s rights would decrease men’s right as they are already set in stone and have been since society started. I agree, feminist activists are usually over the top in what they desire and too forceful. However, not all feminists are like this, only the ones you see protesting and speaking out. Gender roles have been putting the both sexes for many years now. Gays are being forced into their natural role despite being different, women being criticised for doing anything that isn’t lady like. There is a stereotype where men work to bring home the bacon and women take care of the children, these days are long gone. When will society move on from gender roles and accept that the time for the “perfect” family is over?</p>
<p>Personally, i think women are at a point where they’ve the rights they need to feel equal it is just the personality of other around them that causes inequality. Instead of debating about women’s rights, society should be trying to further homosexual rights because right now the world is showing them a great injustice.</p>
<p>The only way to stop it is to bring women’s self worth up, because from a young age women are given this stereotype to follow and keep that value with them until shown otherwise.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/feminism/532213/24">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/feminism/532213/24</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 Sep 2013 02:14:37 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-532213-24</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/feminism/532213.rss">Feminism</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Feminism</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Frell Frell]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/frell">@Frell</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote quote-modified" data-post="21" data-topic="532213">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/amy_webb/40/5_e05bb34c421432ee4d40de30c10af3e5.png" class="avatar"> amy_webb:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>And the girls who don’t dress like “sluts” and are still sexually harassed?</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Not as common but it still happens</p>
<p>theres no way to stop that though, men will always try and let you know they think of you in that way</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/feminism/532213/23">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/feminism/532213/23</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 Sep 2013 02:02:38 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-532213-23</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/feminism/532213.rss">Feminism</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Feminism</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@thiefmn6092 thiefmn6092]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/thiefmn6092">@thiefmn6092</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote quote-modified" data-post="21" data-topic="532213">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/amy_webb/40/5_e05bb34c421432ee4d40de30c10af3e5.png" class="avatar"> amy_webb:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Guys walk around with short shorts and no tops on and they aren’t raped, yet girls who walk around with short shorts and something that covers their breasts are. Double standards, yer, for who?</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>the second i read this any level of seriousness i treated your posts with went out the window</p>
<p>like any other struggle between two social entities in history (e.g social classes or races), feminism furthers one side at the cost of the other - man in this case. feminism is reverse discrimination and i do not consider it any more of a “equal struggle” then any other kind of supposedly equalizing movement in todays world. i am a firm believer in gender roles and have no desire to see the harmony that exists without group conflict disrupted.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/feminism/532213/22">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/feminism/532213/22</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 Sep 2013 01:47:22 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-532213-22</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/feminism/532213.rss">Feminism</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Feminism</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@amy_webb1 amy_webb]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/amy_webb1">@amy_webb1</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>And the girls who don’t dress like “sluts” and are still sexually harassed? There is a social view that only skimpy girls are harassed or raped but that isn’t always the case. You’ve girls that are the most unattractive whales you could ever see and they’ve been attacked or raped, god knows why.</p>
<p>Guys walk around with short shorts and no tops on and they aren’t raped, yet girls who walk around with short shorts and something that covers their breasts are. Double standards, yer, for who?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/feminism/532213/21">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/feminism/532213/21</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 Sep 2013 01:30:53 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-532213-21</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/feminism/532213.rss">Feminism</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Feminism</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Frell Frell]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/frell">@Frell</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote quote-modified" data-post="18" data-topic="532213">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/amy_webb/40/5_e05bb34c421432ee4d40de30c10af3e5.png" class="avatar"> amy_webb:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Sexual harassment is also the degrading of females, to be treated like a piece of meat in your own workplace does not feel good. That is fine, see what ever you want to see but that doesn’t mean it is right.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>dont dress like a slut</p>
<p>girls have this idea that they can get away with provoking guys and expect a double standard. If I walk around shirtless girls usually touch me and I’ve had pictures taken of me without permission while in hottubs and shit</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/feminism/532213/20">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/feminism/532213/20</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 Sep 2013 01:14:29 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-532213-20</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/feminism/532213.rss">Feminism</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Feminism</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@davidi2 Davidi2]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/davidi2">@davidi2</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>TIL sexual harassment only happens to females</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/feminism/532213/19">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/feminism/532213/19</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 Sep 2013 01:09:09 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-532213-19</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/feminism/532213.rss">Feminism</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Feminism</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@amy_webb1 amy_webb]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/amy_webb1">@amy_webb1</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Sexual harassment is also the degrading of females, to be treated like a piece of meat in your own workplace does not feel good. That is fine, see what ever you want to see but that doesn’t mean it is right.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/feminism/532213/18">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/feminism/532213/18</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 Sep 2013 01:02:40 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-532213-18</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/feminism/532213.rss">Feminism</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Feminism</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@TabbyKiller TabbyKiller]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/tabbykiller">@TabbyKiller</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Sexual harassment has nothing to do with feminism, its a criminal act therefore I see it as a crime rather than discrimination against women. You might as well be saying that rape is an act of anti-feminism. But yeah, all I see is bull shit and more bull shit.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/feminism/532213/17">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/feminism/532213/17</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 25 Sep 2013 11:11:08 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-532213-17</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/feminism/532213.rss">Feminism</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Feminism</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@amy_webb1 amy_webb]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/amy_webb1">@amy_webb1</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <blockquote>Don't try bull shit a bull shitter Amy because I don't know if this is just me but it seems you're holding a grudge (for what? idk) and have to go against everything I am saying, sure you have your beliefs but it just so happens to be everything against what I have said.</blockquote>
<p>I’m not “bull shitting” you, and i am not holding a grudge against you for anything however it appears that you’ve become aggressive toward me for some unknown reason. Yes, i have my views and opinions on things, but just because they’re the opposite of yours doesn’t mean i’m out to get you. Do you think everyone with opposing beliefs to yours is holding a grudge? That is silly.</p>
<blockquote>Also as I've said many times, I'm not against feminism but the main point of this topic is to bring up the thought about how feminism is being overseen as black vs white, obama vs syria etc (no pun or relation intended, honestly) When honestly, there really is next to no discrimination against women. But yes if you read I had already stated that it may be different where you live but I've been to Australia many times and I've never witnessed such a thing.</blockquote>
<p>There is discrimination against women all over the world, yes first world countries are trying to stop it and some have succeeded but others haven’t. You see sexual harassment happening all the time in work places, yes, it happens to males but more so reported by females. Just because you don’t witness something that does not mean it isn’t real or happening, it seems like a very close minded way to think about it.</p>
<p>Let the sexist comments commence by the looks of the previous comments.</p>
<p>I don’t understand how you think women have less responsibilities then men, please elaborate.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/feminism/532213/16">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/feminism/532213/16</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 25 Sep 2013 10:37:59 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-532213-16</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/feminism/532213.rss">Feminism</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Feminism</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@drubrkletern drubrkletern]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/drubrkletern">@drubrkletern</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote" data-post="12" data-topic="532213">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/frell/40/5_e05bb34c421432ee4d40de30c10af3e5.png" class="avatar"> Frell:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>they want equal rights until it comes to paying for dinner</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<aside class="quote" data-post="13" data-topic="532213">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/user_avatar/forum.moparisthebest.com/davidi2/40/2579_1.png" class="avatar"> Davidi2:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>they want equal rights until it comes to anything at all bad*</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<aside class="quote" data-post="14" data-topic="532213">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/user_avatar/forum.moparisthebest.com/lothy/40/51_1.png" class="avatar"> Lothy:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Yeah, I’ve noticed the glaring lack of petitioning for more responsibility.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>and thats exactly what pisses me off the most about it</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/feminism/532213/15">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/feminism/532213/15</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 25 Sep 2013 06:05:53 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-532213-15</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/feminism/532213.rss">Feminism</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Feminism</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@lothy Lothy]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/lothy">@lothy</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Yeah, I’ve noticed the glaring lack of petitioning for more responsibility.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/feminism/532213/14">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/feminism/532213/14</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 25 Sep 2013 05:54:15 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-532213-14</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/feminism/532213.rss">Feminism</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Feminism</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@davidi2 Davidi2]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/davidi2">@davidi2</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>they want equal rights until it comes to anything at all bad*</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/feminism/532213/13">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/feminism/532213/13</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 25 Sep 2013 03:24:22 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-532213-13</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/feminism/532213.rss">Feminism</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Feminism</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Frell Frell]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/frell">@Frell</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>they want equal rights until it comes to paying for dinner</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/feminism/532213/12">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/feminism/532213/12</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 25 Sep 2013 03:14:29 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-532213-12</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/feminism/532213.rss">Feminism</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Feminism</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@TabbyKiller TabbyKiller]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/tabbykiller">@TabbyKiller</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“amy_webb, post:8, topic:532213”]I’m not quite sure about what you mean by your first statement.</p>
<p>The main movement of women’s rights happened after WWII, the being of women’s liberation was introduced by the suffragettes in the early 1900s. I believe we’re looking toward a fourth wave movement of women’s rights and equality.</p>
<p>Discrimination happens everywhere, you might not see it but it is happening. There are laws to prevent discrimination but that does not stop it from happening. Women may be given less opportunities due to having children or prior responsibilities, employers might not believe they can handle the job on an emotional level ect.</p>
<p>I believe evolution will continue to happen until the species dies, we aren’t adapting because we aren’t adjusting ourselves to new conditions.</p>
<p>We don’t have to have the same point of view or agree, this is the point of debate. My last paragraph never suggested anything toward me thinking i am completely right, i was saying that my point of view might be discarded due to the majorities view. Generally, when a minority poses an opinion that person is targeted and with my last paragraph i was hoping to avoid that. However, you seem to have misinterpreted what i was saying.[/quote]<br>
Don’t try bull shit a bull shitter Amy because I don’t know if this is just me but it seems you’re holding a grudge (for what? idk) and have to go against everything I am saying, sure you have your beliefs but it just so happens to be everything against what I have said.</p>
<p>Also as I’ve said many times, I’m not against feminism but the main point of this topic is to bring up the thought about how feminism is being overseen as black vs white, obama vs syria etc (no pun or relation intended, honestly) When honestly, there really is next to no discrimination against women. But yes if you read I had already stated that it may be different where you live but I’ve been to Australia many times and I’ve never witnessed such a thing.</p>
<p>[quote=“Arcik, post:10, topic:532213”]This thread is really funny, post are hilarious.</p>
<p>Are you sure the lady in the video was not getting at gay people? (nothing wrong with gays). Guys like girls, girls like guys, lets make a baby? Don’t like females? Don’t have baby, don’t be loved by a female, get the love from a guy.</p>
<p>There’s my logic :)[/quote]<br>
I touched on homosexuality in a topic not that long ago, I believe the focal point was on the Westbaro Baptist Church or something.</p>
<p>[quote=“Slave Scyth, post:9, topic:532213”]I hate feminism with a passion. Feminists are the most annoying women (and men, like wtf) I’ve ever met. “Man privilege” or that bullshit.</p>
<p>Men are stronger than women and naturally are supposed to be looked up to more than women are. That’s not sexist; that’s nature.</p>
<p>There was something I read somewhere that gave a theory for why women are becoming more and more depressed on average. By nature women are supposed to be motherly and take care of the home. As they move into the workplace, this is going against what their nature wants and as a result: depression.</p>
<p>Middle-class white men have had an advantage in the past, but now with feminism and affirmative action in a lot of cases we’re getting the short end of the stick simply to “be equal,” which is not equal at all in most of those cases.[/quote]<br>
That theory is actually kind of interesting and looks like a good thing to research if I wanted and had the time to.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/feminism/532213/11">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/feminism/532213/11</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 25 Sep 2013 02:42:38 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-532213-11</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/feminism/532213.rss">Feminism</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
