<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Insanity-Pkz</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/insanity-pkz/444324</link>
    <description>Hello,
Recently I&#39;ve been wanting to restart with Rsps as its quite decent money and even better of its not boring! Currently this thread will be quite simple until next week as I&#39;ve got a fair bit of things going on in real life and anytime I have spare will be spent on the server. This is my first proper server development where I wont be taking the easy option, I&#39;ll be going for the quality option. I appreciate any critism, suggestions and so forth yous all have to offer(:.

[size=18pt]Enough of the chit chat, time for to talk about the server[/size]

The source I&#39;m using is PI Reloaded V2 With Netty ( http://google.com/runescape-development/google/downloads/398807-pi-reloaded-v2-netty-pc-clan-chat-stablest-pi-can-hold-2000-players.html ).
It is very basic and will need a lot of work however I think I can make it work(:. I&#39;m not too great at Java so I think by using the best source I can find that still resembles the structure I&#39;m used to would be best for me. On the plus side at least I wont have random crap in this source that nobody ever users as the source is super bare. Its missing so many methods, I add in one but then end up needing to add a few more in, oh the joys!

The client I&#39;m using is Project Insanity - Normal PI - All Dupes fixed ( http://google.com/runescape-development/google/downloads/308712-project-insanity-normal-pi-all-dupes-fixed.html ). I&#39;m using this as I don&#39;t like the 317 loading 377 that was reccomended to be used with the source(too old school for my liking), I thought 317 loading 474 was a start. I plan on later adding in a few items, characters, npcs and animations (lots of them) later on. I only want to add in items that are actually used which will mean for a smaller cache(Uncompressed 21.5mb atm). The reasoning I want to add more content in is because I don&#39;t want to limit the server. If I like something from the newer revisions I&#39;m going to use it, simples.

Currently the source is my priority as there is a lot that needs done, [s]even my prayer doesn&#39;t work atm ;c[/s]. This will be a learning experience for me and hopefully this will be a half decent server when I&#39;m done with it(:.

Tasks completed:
Removing normal teleports(i.e. teleport to lumbridge actually teleports you to lumbridge) and replacing them with teleports to skilling zones and so forth, like DSPK servers.
Added animation to using bones on alter.
Tweaked minor settings in client and source to how I prefer them.

Tasks started:

Re adding quite a few files so that skills start working again, ripping them all from my old modified ErasedPkz just so its semi uptodate and it&#39;ll not be super different from other peoples sources. This will affect stability but its a price I&#39;m willing to pay, for the moment at least.

Given up on:

[size=24pt][b]
I will add media in next week when I do the thread properly.[/b][/size]
Stability wise can hold 300&#39;ish players(this is not how many connections it can have, it is how players that can play without lag) on a 1gb ram and quadcore 2.5ghz proccessor.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 10 Jun 2012 03:53:18 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/insanity-pkz/444324.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Insanity-Pkz</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@kingman002 kingman002]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/kingman002">@kingman002</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Good luck on this.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/insanity-pkz/444324/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/insanity-pkz/444324/5</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 10 Jun 2012 03:53:18 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-444324-5</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/insanity-pkz/444324.rss">Insanity-Pkz</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Insanity-Pkz</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@k1ng0frs k1ng0frs]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/k1ng0frs">@k1ng0frs</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>good luck</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/insanity-pkz/444324/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/insanity-pkz/444324/4</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 10 Jun 2012 02:50:59 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-444324-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/insanity-pkz/444324.rss">Insanity-Pkz</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Insanity-Pkz</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Kidpaparoach Kidpaparoach]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/kidpaparoach">@Kidpaparoach</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote" data-post="2" data-topic="444324">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/endlesskarma/40/5_e05bb34c421432ee4d40de30c10af3e5.png" class="avatar"> EndlessKarma:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>add me on skype bgonzalez31 or via PM</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Why? If you want to discuss something pm me, if further discussion is required then I’ll add you on Skype.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/insanity-pkz/444324/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/insanity-pkz/444324/3</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 10 Jun 2012 01:50:03 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-444324-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/insanity-pkz/444324.rss">Insanity-Pkz</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Insanity-Pkz</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@EndlessKarma EndlessKarma]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/endlesskarma">@EndlessKarma</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>add me on skype bgonzalez31 or via PM</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/insanity-pkz/444324/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/insanity-pkz/444324/2</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 10 Jun 2012 01:33:28 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-444324-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/insanity-pkz/444324.rss">Insanity-Pkz</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Insanity-Pkz</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Kidpaparoach Kidpaparoach]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/kidpaparoach">@Kidpaparoach</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Hello,<br>
Recently I’ve been wanting to restart with Rsps as its quite decent money and even better of its not boring! Currently this thread will be quite simple until next week as I’ve got a fair bit of things going on in real life and anytime I have spare will be spent on the server. This is my first proper server development where I wont be taking the easy option, I’ll be going for the quality option. I appreciate any critism, suggestions and so forth yous all have to offer(:.</p>
<p>[size=18pt]Enough of the chit chat, time for to talk about the server[/size]</p>
<p>The source I’m using is PI Reloaded V2 With Netty ( <a href="http://google.com/runescape-development/google/downloads/398807-pi-reloaded-v2-netty-pc-clan-chat-stablest-pi-can-hold-2000-players.html" rel="nofollow noopener">http://google.com/runescape-development/google/downloads/398807-pi-reloaded-v2-netty-pc-clan-chat-stablest-pi-can-hold-2000-players.html</a> ).<br>
It is very basic and will need a lot of work however I think I can make it work(:. I’m not too great at Java so I think by using the best source I can find that still resembles the structure I’m used to would be best for me. On the plus side at least I wont have random crap in this source that nobody ever users as the source is super bare. Its missing so many methods, I add in one but then end up needing to add a few more in, oh the joys!</p>
<p>The client I’m using is Project Insanity - Normal PI - All Dupes fixed ( <a href="http://google.com/runescape-development/google/downloads/308712-project-insanity-normal-pi-all-dupes-fixed.html" rel="nofollow noopener">http://google.com/runescape-development/google/downloads/308712-project-insanity-normal-pi-all-dupes-fixed.html</a> ). I’m using this as I don’t like the 317 loading 377 that was reccomended to be used with the source(too old school for my liking), I thought 317 loading 474 was a start. I plan on later adding in a few items, characters, npcs and animations (lots of them) later on. I only want to add in items that are actually used which will mean for a smaller cache(Uncompressed 21.5mb atm). The reasoning I want to add more content in is because I don’t want to limit the server. If I like something from the newer revisions I’m going to use it, simples.</p>
<p>Currently the source is my priority as there is a lot that needs done, <span class="bbcode-s">even my prayer doesn’t work atm ;c</span>. This will be a learning experience for me and hopefully this will be a half decent server when I’m done with it(:.</p>
<p>Tasks completed:<br>
Removing normal teleports(i.e. teleport to lumbridge actually teleports you to lumbridge) and replacing them with teleports to skilling zones and so forth, like DSPK servers.<br>
Added animation to using bones on alter.<br>
Tweaked minor settings in client and source to how I prefer them.</p>
<p>Tasks started:</p>
<p>Re adding quite a few files so that skills start working again, ripping them all from my old modified ErasedPkz just so its semi uptodate and it’ll not be super different from other peoples sources. This will affect stability but its a price I’m willing to pay, for the moment at least.</p>
<p>Given up on:</p>
<p>[size=24pt]<span class="bbcode-b"><br>
I will add media in next week when I do the thread properly.</span>[/size]<br>
Stability wise can hold 300’ish players(this is not how many connections it can have, it is how players that can play without lag) on a 1gb ram and quadcore 2.5ghz proccessor.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/insanity-pkz/444324/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/insanity-pkz/444324/1</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 07 Jun 2012 21:42:03 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-444324-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/insanity-pkz/444324.rss">Insanity-Pkz</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
