<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Does it exist?</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/does-it-exist/537621</link>
    <description>Is there any downloadable 307 client and server that comes anywhere close to the real 2006-2007 version of RS? That would mean with at least working combat, NPCs, doors, gates, a good amount of monster spawns, skills, etc. Not expecting things like quests or minigames, but just core features like that so you could properly play the game to an extent without digging into it too much.

I&#39;m asking this because I was wondering if I could play a semi-decent copy of oldschool RS singleplayer so I could just beat up stuff and skill on my own little home server. I would also need the downloadable server and client so that I could just run the server and that would be it, as I have no experience with programming and have no desire to learn for a small pastime I think would be cool.

I hope that point is clear though, I am not overly insistent on finding this magical, ready-to-download server and client that may or may not exist as I&#39;m not trying to open up my own private server, I just think it would be very nice to play an old version of RS solo on my PC for old times&#39; sake. 

If this download does exist somewhere, I would be very grateful if someone could post the link. If it doesn&#39;t, then oh well.

Thanks.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 26 Dec 2013 06:26:58 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>General Discussion</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/does-it-exist/537621.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Does it exist?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Zark Zark]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/zark">@Zark</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Oops, sorry. Am I able to move this?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/does-it-exist/537621/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/does-it-exist/537621/3</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 Dec 2013 06:26:58 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-537621-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/does-it-exist/537621.rss">Does it exist?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Does it exist?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Dan0194 Dan0194]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/dan0194">@Dan0194</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>You could get the 2006scape source, that’s probably your best bet.</p>
<p>btw wrong section use Download Requests.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/does-it-exist/537621/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/does-it-exist/537621/2</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 Dec 2013 06:24:37 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-537621-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/does-it-exist/537621.rss">Does it exist?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Does it exist?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Zark Zark]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/zark">@Zark</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Is there any downloadable 307 client and server that comes anywhere close to the real 2006-2007 version of RS? That would mean with at least working combat, NPCs, doors, gates, a good amount of monster spawns, skills, etc. Not expecting things like quests or minigames, but just core features like that so you could properly play the game to an extent without digging into it too much.</p>
<p>I’m asking this because I was wondering if I could play a semi-decent copy of oldschool RS singleplayer so I could just beat up stuff and skill on my own little home server. I would also need the downloadable server and client so that I could just run the server and that would be it, as I have no experience with programming and have no desire to learn for a small pastime I think would be cool.</p>
<p>I hope that point is clear though, I am not overly insistent on finding this magical, ready-to-download server and client that may or may not exist as I’m not trying to open up my own private server, I just think it would be very nice to play an old version of RS solo on my PC for old times’ sake.</p>
<p>If this download does exist somewhere, I would be very grateful if someone could post the link. If it doesn’t, then oh well.</p>
<p>Thanks.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/does-it-exist/537621/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/does-it-exist/537621/1</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 Dec 2013 06:21:49 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-537621-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/does-it-exist/537621.rss">Does it exist?</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
