<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Czar source is not working right! Not updating players!</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/czar-source-is-not-working-right-not-updating-players/181116</link>
    <description>I tried everything to fix this! I can&#39;t find the problem... Will someone please help me out.

I will try to explain it the best way possible, here are the problems.

If the person is lets say 10 squares away from me meaning I can see them on my screen. Then I use lets say &quot;xteletome&quot; command on them. On my screen they are still standing 10 squares away and on their screen they are actually on top of me... What is up with that??? But thats not the only problem.

Here is the same problem.

If i&#39;m logged in, and they log in it doesen&#39;t update them at all on my screen its like if the server wasen&#39;t communicating with my client. When I log in it says how many players are online, well that never changes until I log out and back in.

I can&#39;t use any commands on the person unless I log out and log back in meaning they have to be on the server before me.

Can someone please help??

I am using the JDK jdk1.6.0_03

----------------------------------------------------------------------

Just to clerify some things,

Its not a command problem, I did not mess up while coding some things (Just to make sure I downloaded fresh copy, unchanged and launched it and it was the same). 

I don&#39;t know what can be wrong.

Ohhhhh and this didn&#39;t do any good so don&#39;t tell me that can be wrong:
[CODE]updateRequired = true;
appearanceUpdateRequired = true;
[/CODE]

Anyone have ideas?</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 13 Feb 2008 09:51:49 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/czar-source-is-not-working-right-not-updating-players/181116.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Czar source is not working right! Not updating players!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@elitescouter elitescouter]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/elitescouter">@elitescouter</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I tried everything to fix this! I can’t find the problem… Will someone please help me out.</p>
<p>I will try to explain it the best way possible, here are the problems.</p>
<p>If the person is lets say 10 squares away from me meaning I can see them on my screen. Then I use lets say “xteletome” command on them. On my screen they are still standing 10 squares away and on their screen they are actually on top of me… What is up with that??? But thats not the only problem.</p>
<p>Here is the same problem.</p>
<p>If i’m logged in, and they log in it doesen’t update them at all on my screen its like if the server wasen’t communicating with my client. When I log in it says how many players are online, well that never changes until I log out and back in.</p>
<p>I can’t use any commands on the person unless I log out and log back in meaning they have to be on the server before me.</p>
<p>Can someone please help??</p>
<p>I am using the JDK jdk1.6.0_03</p>
<hr>
<p>Just to clerify some things,</p>
<p>Its not a command problem, I did not mess up while coding some things (Just to make sure I downloaded fresh copy, unchanged and launched it and it was the same).</p>
<p>I don’t know what can be wrong.</p>
<p>Ohhhhh and this didn’t do any good so don’t tell me that can be wrong:</p>
<p><code>updateRequired = true;
appearanceUpdateRequired = true;
</code></p>
<p>Anyone have ideas?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/czar-source-is-not-working-right-not-updating-players/181116/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/czar-source-is-not-working-right-not-updating-players/181116/1</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 13 Feb 2008 09:51:49 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-181116-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/czar-source-is-not-working-right-not-updating-players/181116.rss">Czar source is not working right! Not updating players!</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
