<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Offering my services for server owners</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/offering-my-services-for-server-owners/23012</link>
    <description>I&#39;ll start this message by just stating what I&#39;m offering.  If you are interested, please read on, if not, I won&#39;t waste anymore of your time.  What I am offering is my computer and internet service as a 24 hour host for your client.  I have set up a method which is completely safe for you and for me as I will have no access to your folder and you will have no access to my computer other than the folder I set up for you.  [b]I&#39;m not asking for admin or even player moderator, all I&#39;m asking for is to have a reliable 24 hour a day, 7 day a week server to play on[/b].  I will hopefully be able to host a few of the more popular servers if you guys would like that, that way all of us here at moparscape can enjoy them all the time, not just the times the people who own the servers can run them.

The next section is where I will introduce myself, and the paragraph after that will be the means of how I will run your server where you will be completely safe from me stealing your coding or messing up the players of your server.

Hello all you java programmers.  My name is Matt and I recently graduated from a school in North Carolina with a degree in Computer Engineering.  I&#39;m currently waiting til January to start my next stage of schooling which will be getting my degree in computer science.  I have quite a bit of experience with computers and work with them everyday on a part time basis, but I just don&#39;t have the time or know how to program my own client to run.  I am a fairly serious player of runescape, however recently I&#39;ve really been getting into these private servers as I just seem to have much more fun on them.  I&#39;ve had a few problems finding a reliable server to play so this is where this idea came from.  I realize that I&#39;m new here and you guys have no reason to trust me to run your server, however the next paragraph should make you guys feel more at ease.

I have locked my computer completely down other than a few folders that I have set up for any of you programmers to use.  You will be able to access these files using a program called Remote Administrator which you can get a free 30 day trial at [url=Http://www.radmin.com]Http://www.radmin.com[/url].  Once you have access to the folder I will make for you, you can encrypt and password protect this folder any way you would like to keep me out.  I will allow you the ability to edit only java and config files to protect myself from viruses or keyloggers or anything to that affect.

Anyone who has read this far, should have a decent knowledge of computers and will realize that there is no way I can screw you guys over.  My computer is on 24/7 and I think this is a pretty awesome option for you guys.  I would just like to ask that the client in question have quite a few members before we get it moved to my computer as I don&#39;t want it to be used as a test server, but rather as a permanent home for your client.

Thanks for reading guys, and feel free to either PM me through these forums, email me at mattjewebay@hotmail.com, or just reply to this post if you are interested or have any questions about the offer.

 - Matt (Finger)</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2008 01:25:53 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/offering-my-services-for-server-owners/23012.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Offering my services for server owners</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@dyde08 dyde08]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/dyde08">@dyde08</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>hm…he hasnt even taking quiz…-.-</p>
<p>really dont trust this guy.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/offering-my-services-for-server-owners/23012/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/offering-my-services-for-server-owners/23012/6</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2008 01:25:53 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-23012-6</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/offering-my-services-for-server-owners/23012.rss">Offering my services for server owners</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Offering my services for server owners</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@SivanScape SivanScape]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/sivanscape">@SivanScape</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Iam sure he has a reason.</p>
<p>1: Will anyone just run a server 24/7 7days a week for a stranger?<br>
2: He wont even ask for admin/mod lol?<br>
3: Making a website and hes paying for it after 30day trail?</p>
<p>lol i don’t really trust this.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/offering-my-services-for-server-owners/23012/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/offering-my-services-for-server-owners/23012/5</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2008 01:13:11 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-23012-5</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/offering-my-services-for-server-owners/23012.rss">Offering my services for server owners</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Offering my services for server owners</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@semiautoxxx semiautoxxx]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/semiautoxxx">@semiautoxxx</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>So, are you saying that you’ll let us on your PC for you on our server?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/offering-my-services-for-server-owners/23012/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/offering-my-services-for-server-owners/23012/4</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2008 00:47:35 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-23012-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/offering-my-services-for-server-owners/23012.rss">Offering my services for server owners</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Offering my services for server owners</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Zuno Zuno]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/zuno">@Zuno</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Hmm. I’ll think about it. I do have a nice server that is just getting started it is up and running and I have some players already, and sadly I can’t host it 24/7. If you read this and wish to host it please message me via message center <a href="http://moparisthebest.com/smf.index.php" rel="nofollow noopener">moparisthebest.com/smf.index.php</a>.</p>
<p><img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/expressionless.png?v=6" title=":expressionless:" class="emoji" alt=":expressionless:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/offering-my-services-for-server-owners/23012/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/offering-my-services-for-server-owners/23012/3</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2008 23:57:29 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-23012-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/offering-my-services-for-server-owners/23012.rss">Offering my services for server owners</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Offering my services for server owners</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@froggy226 froggy226]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/froggy226">@froggy226</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Hey! Im trying to get a server set up, but I have no idea how.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/offering-my-services-for-server-owners/23012/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/offering-my-services-for-server-owners/23012/2</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2006 06:15:47 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-23012-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/offering-my-services-for-server-owners/23012.rss">Offering my services for server owners</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Offering my services for server owners</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Finger Finger]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/finger">@Finger</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I’ll start this message by just stating what I’m offering.  If you are interested, please read on, if not, I won’t waste anymore of your time.  What I am offering is my computer and internet service as a 24 hour host for your client.  I have set up a method which is completely safe for you and for me as I will have no access to your folder and you will have no access to my computer other than the folder I set up for you.  <span class="bbcode-b">I’m not asking for admin or even player moderator, all I’m asking for is to have a reliable 24 hour a day, 7 day a week server to play on</span>.  I will hopefully be able to host a few of the more popular servers if you guys would like that, that way all of us here at moparscape can enjoy them all the time, not just the times the people who own the servers can run them.</p>
<p>The next section is where I will introduce myself, and the paragraph after that will be the means of how I will run your server where you will be completely safe from me stealing your coding or messing up the players of your server.</p>
<p>Hello all you java programmers.  My name is Matt and I recently graduated from a school in North Carolina with a degree in Computer Engineering.  I’m currently waiting til January to start my next stage of schooling which will be getting my degree in computer science.  I have quite a bit of experience with computers and work with them everyday on a part time basis, but I just don’t have the time or know how to program my own client to run.  I am a fairly serious player of runescape, however recently I’ve really been getting into these private servers as I just seem to have much more fun on them.  I’ve had a few problems finding a reliable server to play so this is where this idea came from.  I realize that I’m new here and you guys have no reason to trust me to run your server, however the next paragraph should make you guys feel more at ease.</p>
<p>I have locked my computer completely down other than a few folders that I have set up for any of you programmers to use.  You will be able to access these files using a program called Remote Administrator which you can get a free 30 day trial at <a href="Http://www.radmin.com" rel="nofollow noopener">Http://www.radmin.com</a>.  Once you have access to the folder I will make for you, you can encrypt and password protect this folder any way you would like to keep me out.  I will allow you the ability to edit only java and config files to protect myself from viruses or keyloggers or anything to that affect.</p>
<p>Anyone who has read this far, should have a decent knowledge of computers and will realize that there is no way I can screw you guys over.  My computer is on 24/7 and I think this is a pretty awesome option for you guys.  I would just like to ask that the client in question have quite a few members before we get it moved to my computer as I don’t want it to be used as a test server, but rather as a permanent home for your client.</p>
<p>Thanks for reading guys, and feel free to either PM me through these forums, email me at <a href="mailto:mattjewebay@hotmail.com">mattjewebay@hotmail.com</a>, or just reply to this post if you are interested or have any questions about the offer.</p>
<ul>
<li>Matt (Finger)</li>
</ul>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/offering-my-services-for-server-owners/23012/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/offering-my-services-for-server-owners/23012/1</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 08 Nov 2006 05:12:57 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-23012-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/offering-my-services-for-server-owners/23012.rss">Offering my services for server owners</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
