<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Lubuntu - LXDE meets Ubuntu</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/lubuntu-lxde-meets-ubuntu/351208</link>
    <description>http://distrowatch.com/table.php?distribution=lubuntu

Anyone try it yet? Its quite fast. At least compared to gnome, xfce, or kde. I&#39;ve been interested in lxde for a while, but have always found the look to be quite repulsive. I found that Lubuntu&#39;s lxde themed interface is much much nicer then the standard lxde package installation on ubuntu (it&#39;s a basic clearlooks kinda thing, but it&#39;s ages better then the lxde default). Plus it comes with very lite apps, such as pcmanfm instead of nautilus (very speedy), leafpad instead of gedit, and my favorite web browser, Google Chrome. 

I&#39;m actually typing from Ubuntu at the moment but if your looking for a lite linux distro, or just interested in lxde, I&#39;d definitely consider Lubuntu.

More here - [url=http://www.linux-mag.com/id/7520]http://www.linux-mag.com/id/7520[/url] &lt;&lt; Including some memory statistics that were quite surprising. It turns out that Xubuntu uses more memory than Ubuntu (with &quot;everyday applications&quot; open).

-Dzo</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 26 Jul 2010 13:30:52 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Technology</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/lubuntu-lxde-meets-ubuntu/351208.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Lubuntu - LXDE meets Ubuntu</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Unhandled Unhandled]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/unhandled">@Unhandled</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Might try it…too bad the name sounds absolutely homosexual as fuck.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/lubuntu-lxde-meets-ubuntu/351208/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/lubuntu-lxde-meets-ubuntu/351208/2</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jul 2010 13:30:52 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-351208-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/lubuntu-lxde-meets-ubuntu/351208.rss">Lubuntu - LXDE meets Ubuntu</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Lubuntu - LXDE meets Ubuntu</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Dzo -Dzo-]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/dzo">@Dzo</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p><a href="http://distrowatch.com/table.php?distribution=lubuntu" class="onebox" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">http://distrowatch.com/table.php?distribution=lubuntu</a></p>
<p>Anyone try it yet? Its quite fast. At least compared to gnome, xfce, or kde. I’ve been interested in lxde for a while, but have always found the look to be quite repulsive. I found that Lubuntu’s lxde themed interface is much much nicer then the standard lxde package installation on ubuntu (it’s a basic clearlooks kinda thing, but it’s ages better then the lxde default). Plus it comes with very lite apps, such as pcmanfm instead of nautilus (very speedy), leafpad instead of gedit, and my favorite web browser, Google Chrome.</p>
<p>I’m actually typing from Ubuntu at the moment but if your looking for a lite linux distro, or just interested in lxde, I’d definitely consider Lubuntu.</p>
<p>More here - <a href="http://www.linux-mag.com/id/7520" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">http://www.linux-mag.com/id/7520</a> &lt;&lt; Including some memory statistics that were quite surprising. It turns out that Xubuntu uses more memory than Ubuntu (with “everyday applications” open).</p>
<p>-Dzo</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/lubuntu-lxde-meets-ubuntu/351208/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/lubuntu-lxde-meets-ubuntu/351208/1</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jul 2010 07:20:01 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-351208-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/lubuntu-lxde-meets-ubuntu/351208.rss">Lubuntu - LXDE meets Ubuntu</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
