<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Aidz</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/aidz/123628</link>
    <description>This came in my mind as I was writing gangsta rap in the Homework Help section. I was going to write this story myself, but I decided that it&#39;d be more fun to let you guys do it. You guys have to write a story of any length using the components I give you. Seriously, this stuff writes itself.

Components: PaulT, lawl, a firewall with a hole in it, an anti-virus, HIV, a backdoor, and bondage equipment. Oh, and whores.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 16 Jul 2007 06:22:41 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>General Discussion</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/aidz/123628.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Aidz</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@gothic_queen casey.]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/gothic_queen">@gothic_queen</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I have no clue what I just wrote.</p>
<p>It was a dark night, many dark figures were walking around.<br>
It was a typical night in the city of whores, where hiv was free, anything went.<br>
Two dark firgue’s bumped into eachother.</p>
<p>“What the hell man?” said one figure</p>
<p>“Lawl” yelled the other figure.</p>
<p>“Lawl?” said the first figure</p>
<p>“Lawl” yelled the other figure</p>
<p>“I am lawl you bitch”</p>
<p>“Oh hai, it is I, PaulT”</p>
<p>“Listen, I’ve been watching too much porn, my firewall has a hole in it…” moaned PaulT</p>
<p>" Here, take this, it should help."</p>
<p>“omg this is great, it’s working!”</p>
<p>“Hey baby, can I come in through your back door?” whispered some tranny</p>
<p>“Man, I’m not into that stuff, beter luck with Pwnd” grunted PaulT</p>
<p><em>The tranny smiled, turned around, and skipped away.</em></p>
<p>"Now, what is this you give me “Lawl?”</p>
<p>“It’s a anti-virus, now fuck off.”</p>
<p>*Block’s away, you hear the tranny yelling Bondage, bondage!</p>
<p>Fin.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/aidz/123628/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/aidz/123628/6</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 16 Jul 2007 06:22:41 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-123628-6</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/aidz/123628.rss">Aidz</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Aidz</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@PaulT PaulT]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/pault">@PaulT</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>The oddest thing, man, happened yesterday. I woke up as usual at about noon, went to the web for some surfing, like normal, and I notice that my computer is running like a sick dog. So I take a peek at my processes and I see a little something I like to call Backdoorbug0113.exe. So I turn my computer off and head out my backdoor, hop the fence to my neighbors yard, and knock. Nobodies home to borrow a laptop from, so I go in and before I can steal anything good I hear a faint “Uhhhh”. Moans in the basement huh? I head downstairs and  it’s dark and smells like sex and there’s a gimp hung up, the whole Pulp Fiction deal. A Cambodian whore comes up behind me and starts whispering sweet nothings in my ear while a big spade pops out of the dark and hits me on the head with a shovel. It all goes purple and fuzzy untill I wake up in the hospital with tubes pumping anti-virus medication through my body and Lawl by my side.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/aidz/123628/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/aidz/123628/5</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 16 Jul 2007 05:26:24 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-123628-5</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/aidz/123628.rss">Aidz</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Aidz</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@therealjdb JDB`]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/therealjdb">@therealjdb</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Haha, wow didn’t expect to see my name in here haha.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/aidz/123628/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/aidz/123628/4</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 16 Jul 2007 05:09:55 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-123628-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/aidz/123628.rss">Aidz</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Aidz</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Aftermath_961 Aftermath]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/aftermath_961">@Aftermath_961</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Nah, it was good.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/aidz/123628/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/aidz/123628/3</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 16 Jul 2007 04:51:26 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-123628-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/aidz/123628.rss">Aidz</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Aidz</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@RXVL RXVL]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/rxvl">@RXVL</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I’ll give my shot at it =p.</p>
<p>One day, lawl was developing a program to bring down the internetz while some whores knocked on his door. He opened it and they handed him bondage equipment. They proceded towards his bed room to give him HIV. Meanwhile, in a parralel universe, PaulT, jme_009, RXVL, and therealjdb were all sitting around smoking pot and came up with the idea to create a fire. This would be no average fire, it would have a hole in it so that when it became big, the developers would be able to use the backdoor in it to hack people. Of course they would have to get past the anti-virus, but it was Norton Internet Security Dumbass People Edition. Back in the other unvierse, lawl had officialy gotten the HIVs and kicked the whores out by rigging a giant sligshot of panties to shot them out… In Java. Lawl went online and saw that a person name lwal had posted a firewall, so he downloaded it. He used the jotti virus scan to scan it, and found that there was a hole in it. So lawl h4xd his hard drive to get the firewall, and inserted his tiny penis in the hole. Soon, the firewall had HIV and the other 1024 STDs that lawl had, so he reposted it. Soon, the entire world had a firewall with HIV and all the networks crashed, causing an armeggedan. In the other universe, Paul, Jamie, RXVL, and jdb laughed until their heads imploded, causing a giant vacumm in their universe, which made everything expand and explode.</p>
<p>The End.</p>
<p>As you can see, I suck at writing and just wasted about 3 minutes of your life, have a good day :).</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/aidz/123628/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/aidz/123628/2</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 16 Jul 2007 04:43:32 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-123628-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/aidz/123628.rss">Aidz</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Aidz</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Aftermath_961 Aftermath]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/aftermath_961">@Aftermath_961</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>This came in my mind as I was writing gangsta rap in the Homework Help section. I was going to write this story myself, but I decided that it’d be more fun to let you guys do it. You guys have to write a story of any length using the components I give you. Seriously, this stuff writes itself.</p>
<p>Components: PaulT, lawl, a firewall with a hole in it, an anti-virus, HIV, a backdoor, and bondage equipment. Oh, and whores.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/aidz/123628/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/aidz/123628/1</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 16 Jul 2007 04:19:43 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-123628-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/aidz/123628.rss">Aidz</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
