<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Potential User Submission - Loveandpower</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/potential-user-submission-loveandpower/524476</link>
    <description>A submission from Loveandpower. He said he is happy for it to be trimmed down as we see fit.

[quote=&quot;Loveandpower&quot;]My possible article is concerning RSPS economies, why the fail, why they work. Note* I am Cruel Truth of several forums that&#39;s why you may see it on some server forums.

[hr]

I am tired of people trying to act like they know what a real economy is without having lived in it. Therefore, here is a rough outlook on how an economy is really done on servers, why it fails, and how it can be improved upon. 


[u]If you can find ways to improve it even more feel free to post![/u]




Once upon a time, there was a leeched server. This server had all the really great features that even this server somewhat relates to. Good/bad ? Who cares!


There once was one player. This one player got on before several others did and got several stats(mostly combat of course!) up before everybody else. This person thus, started the economy when the time came. 


The second and third person came on and saw these really cool items(weapons/armor most likely...) and were like &quot;hey dude, that freaking thing is awesome! How much you want for it?&quot;


The mighty warrior by this point laughs at the lesser being and says &quot;you must train up to even use this little grasshopper!&quot; &quot;I tell you what though, this is a genuine, only one of a kind item in the server! I will let you have it for &lt;insertinsanepricehere&gt;. 


The little newbie says &quot;lol I don&#39;t have that much sorry...&quot; 


The mighty warrior says &quot;That&#39;s okay mate work up you will have it soon.&quot;


The little newbie says &quot;How can I make money on this server?&quot;


The mighty warrior grins thinking he is helping a new player! &quot;We have several ways of making money I suggest thieving and PvM!&quot;


&quot;Gee thanks Mr. strong guy in dragon full helm!&quot;


So two days later, we have a level 85 slayer who is going for a whip, a skiller who is dead set on staying&quot;level three&quot;, three guys camping td&#39;s trying to get &quot;dem claws&quot;, and one guy who is going &quot;ANYBODY WANNA PK, OMG THIS SERVER SUCKS NOBODY WANTS TO PK!&quot;


Now, let&#39;s take out the human factor of voting for now we will come back to this. We have ten people online, this means you can imagine that on the average server, we probably have AT LEAST 100m already in the game.


Then, one day the five more people join after seeing the shiny advertisement made for the server! Yay! More people to talk to! So now we have five more PvMer&#39;s. 


A week later you have people selling items for 500m-1b each. 


[b]WHAT loveING HAPPENED?

Simple answer: No Challenge![/b]


Let&#39;s rewind a couple of steps shall we? Before the five new PvMer&#39;s came what was the main goal for the current players? To be the richest? To gain a certain item? To be the coolest? 


You have three PvMer&#39;s who on average will get a drop every 50-100 kills. If a kill takes a minute(just estimating of course) then that means it takes an hour and a half for one drop. 


One drop x 4 = 6 hours of gameplay = a decent time to play in a day for the generic young person.


4 x 3 = 12 drops in a day, 12 x 7 = 72 drops that week. 


By just assuming these drops were...let&#39;s say PvP armor to keep it simple!


You have a hood, a top, a bottom, and a weapon right? That&#39;s four pieces! 


THAT IS 12 RANDOM VARIOUS PARTS OF OUTFITS FOR PvP armor.


But wait, there is more! How many people do you know who camps a boss? How many peopel do you know who plays on more than one account? How many people do you know who ACTUALLY ABUSE VOTES!




[u][b][Chapter 2:][/b][/u]


I believe you get the overall picture I am drawing...every day more people will join, with that comes dupers, abusers, xloggers, toucgh noogies, and etc.


What are the consequences of this massive overdose of items entering the eco?


-People quit
-People rage
-People want to make it easier so they can have the same items
-People want xp raised so they can get items faster
-People want this
-People want that
The list goes on!


Sound familiar? It should , look at our suggestions board!


Items are coming in, nothing is going out. What comes first the chicken or the egg? I have a better question than that... who is going to eat that egg? You going to eat that chicken? Cause I am hungry I will take scrambled eggs yes please. :)


Okay so now you see the issue as to WHY it fails. You can say all you want &quot;but gold is being transferred&quot;


Yeah, and your just printing more and more of it by having gold from thieving and etc etc....DUDE!




[u][b][Chapter 3:][/u]


What can be done about this?[/b]


-make items HARDER to get 
-Discontinue items
-Increase drop rates
-Put limits on how many times a monster can be done in a day
-make EVERYTHING HARDER


I guess I should explain the reasoning in this.


From a marketing standpoint you have to keep players happy but at the same time you have to weigh the pros/cons of what makes them happy versus what that happiness will cost in the short end and the long end.




[b]Other suggestions/thoughts:[/b]


-Make new content UNIQUE content. You need a piece of cake to draw people in but don&#39;t make them clingers!
-A server isn&#39;t totally made up an eco, there is a human factor of &quot;respect&quot; as well.  Look at a very well known server that starts with an &quot;s&quot; for example.
-Improve the environment for all forms of players not just the majority group of PvMer&#39;s. Remember a eco is ran by the items supplied by the players not by the store(or it should be to be fully successful.) For example: look at Runescape. They have BASIC gear in the shops and then you go from there. 
-Keep in mind that you will lose some, and win some players. That&#39;s where the respect comes in.
-Advertising in the proper areas at the proper times is key. Ever seen servers such as the one that starts with &quot;s&quot;? They have advertisements everywhere!
-Have a creative outlook. Don&#39;t look at doing stuff like the regular game, but make your own ( which I can see you have been doing somewhat )




[u][b][Chapter 4:][/b][/u]


The extras!


[b]Voting[/b]

I can see where voting is a huge part of a beginning server I really can. But when you have people who abuse a server it just hurts you more than helps. Going back to the example of the ratio of drops to players, now the reality of this heh...multiply that by 100 fold.


[b]Age of players[/b]

Uh yeah...let&#39;s just be honest here okay? The average player will be about thirteen. Yeah so what are you saying? I am saying take their words at a grain of salt. You are the developer, you are the one responsible for building this server economy up! Not them! If you want the players to supply the eco correctly then you have to give them the bare necessities and don&#39;t back down to quitting threats.[/quote]</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 29 Jul 2013 21:06:13 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Community Suggestions</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/potential-user-submission-loveandpower/524476.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Potential User Submission - Loveandpower</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Ambokile Ambokile]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/ambokile">@Ambokile</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I’ve had a discussion with L&amp;p and the submission as it stands is just too long to go into the issue. It’s very long winded yet issue articles should be short and punchy. I’ve told him that if he gets it back to me within 24 hours, sufficiently shortened, then it may be added, but as it stands it wont be in the issue.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/potential-user-submission-loveandpower/524476/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/potential-user-submission-loveandpower/524476/2</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 29 Jul 2013 21:06:13 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-524476-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/potential-user-submission-loveandpower/524476.rss">Potential User Submission - Loveandpower</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Potential User Submission - Loveandpower</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Ambokile Ambokile]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/ambokile">@Ambokile</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>A submission from Loveandpower. He said he is happy for it to be trimmed down as we see fit.</p>
<p>[quote=“Loveandpower”]My possible article is concerning RSPS economies, why the fail, why they work. Note* I am Cruel Truth of several forums that’s why you may see it on some server forums.</p>
<p>[hr]</p>
<p>I am tired of people trying to act like they know what a real economy is without having lived in it. Therefore, here is a rough outlook on how an economy is really done on servers, why it fails, and how it can be improved upon.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-u">If you can find ways to improve it even more feel free to post!</span></p>
<p>Once upon a time, there was a leeched server. This server had all the really great features that even this server somewhat relates to. Good/bad ? Who cares!</p>
<p>There once was one player. This one player got on before several others did and got several stats(mostly combat of course!) up before everybody else. This person thus, started the economy when the time came.</p>
<p>The second and third person came on and saw these really cool items(weapons/armor most likely…) and were like “hey dude, that freaking thing is awesome! How much you want for it?”</p>
<p>The mighty warrior by this point laughs at the lesser being and says “you must train up to even use this little grasshopper!” "I tell you what though, this is a genuine, only one of a kind item in the server! I will let you have it for .</p>
<p>The little newbie says “lol I don’t have that much sorry…”</p>
<p>The mighty warrior says “That’s okay mate work up you will have it soon.”</p>
<p>The little newbie says “How can I make money on this server?”</p>
<p>The mighty warrior grins thinking he is helping a new player! “We have several ways of making money I suggest thieving and PvM!”</p>
<p>“Gee thanks Mr. strong guy in dragon full helm!”</p>
<p>So two days later, we have a level 85 slayer who is going for a whip, a skiller who is dead set on staying"level three", three guys camping td’s trying to get “dem claws”, and one guy who is going “ANYBODY WANNA PK, OMG THIS SERVER SUCKS NOBODY WANTS TO PK!”</p>
<p>Now, let’s take out the human factor of voting for now we will come back to this. We have ten people online, this means you can imagine that on the average server, we probably have AT LEAST 100m already in the game.</p>
<p>Then, one day the five more people join after seeing the shiny advertisement made for the server! Yay! More people to talk to! So now we have five more PvMer’s.</p>
<p>A week later you have people selling items for 500m-1b each.</p>
<p>[b]WHAT loveING HAPPENED?</p>
<p>Simple answer: No Challenge![/b]</p>
<p>Let’s rewind a couple of steps shall we? Before the five new PvMer’s came what was the main goal for the current players? To be the richest? To gain a certain item? To be the coolest?</p>
<p>You have three PvMer’s who on average will get a drop every 50-100 kills. If a kill takes a minute(just estimating of course) then that means it takes an hour and a half for one drop.</p>
<p>One drop x 4 = 6 hours of gameplay = a decent time to play in a day for the generic young person.</p>
<p>4 x 3 = 12 drops in a day, 12 x 7 = 72 drops that week.</p>
<p>By just assuming these drops were…let’s say PvP armor to keep it simple!</p>
<p>You have a hood, a top, a bottom, and a weapon right? That’s four pieces!</p>
<p>THAT IS 12 RANDOM VARIOUS PARTS OF OUTFITS FOR PvP armor.</p>
<p>But wait, there is more! How many people do you know who camps a boss? How many peopel do you know who plays on more than one account? How many people do you know who ACTUALLY ABUSE VOTES!</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-u"><span class="bbcode-b">[Chapter 2:]</span></span></p>
<p>I believe you get the overall picture I am drawing…every day more people will join, with that comes dupers, abusers, xloggers, toucgh noogies, and etc.</p>
<p>What are the consequences of this massive overdose of items entering the eco?</p>
<p>-People quit<br>
-People rage<br>
-People want to make it easier so they can have the same items<br>
-People want xp raised so they can get items faster<br>
-People want this<br>
-People want that<br>
The list goes on!</p>
<p>Sound familiar? It should , look at our suggestions board!</p>
<p>Items are coming in, nothing is going out. What comes first the chicken or the egg? I have a better question than that… who is going to eat that egg? You going to eat that chicken? Cause I am hungry I will take scrambled eggs yes please. <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=5" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
<p>Okay so now you see the issue as to WHY it fails. You can say all you want “but gold is being transferred”</p>
<p>Yeah, and your just printing more and more of it by having gold from thieving and etc etc…DUDE!</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-u">[b][Chapter 3:]</span></p>
<p>What can be done about this?[/b]</p>
<p>-make items HARDER to get<br>
-Discontinue items<br>
-Increase drop rates<br>
-Put limits on how many times a monster can be done in a day<br>
-make EVERYTHING HARDER</p>
<p>I guess I should explain the reasoning in this.</p>
<p>From a marketing standpoint you have to keep players happy but at the same time you have to weigh the pros/cons of what makes them happy versus what that happiness will cost in the short end and the long end.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Other suggestions/thoughts:</span></p>
<p>-Make new content UNIQUE content. You need a piece of cake to draw people in but don’t make them clingers!<br>
-A server isn’t totally made up an eco, there is a human factor of “respect” as well.  Look at a very well known server that starts with an “s” for example.<br>
-Improve the environment for all forms of players not just the majority group of PvMer’s. Remember a eco is ran by the items supplied by the players not by the store(or it should be to be fully successful.) For example: look at Runescape. They have BASIC gear in the shops and then you go from there.<br>
-Keep in mind that you will lose some, and win some players. That’s where the respect comes in.<br>
-Advertising in the proper areas at the proper times is key. Ever seen servers such as the one that starts with “s”? They have advertisements everywhere!<br>
-Have a creative outlook. Don’t look at doing stuff like the regular game, but make your own ( which I can see you have been doing somewhat )</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-u"><span class="bbcode-b">[Chapter 4:]</span></span></p>
<p>The extras!</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Voting</span></p>
<p>I can see where voting is a huge part of a beginning server I really can. But when you have people who abuse a server it just hurts you more than helps. Going back to the example of the ratio of drops to players, now the reality of this heh…multiply that by 100 fold.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Age of players</span></p>
<p>Uh yeah…let’s just be honest here okay? The average player will be about thirteen. Yeah so what are you saying? I am saying take their words at a grain of salt. You are the developer, you are the one responsible for building this server economy up! Not them! If you want the players to supply the eco correctly then you have to give them the bare necessities and don’t back down to quitting threats.[/quote]</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/potential-user-submission-loveandpower/524476/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/potential-user-submission-loveandpower/524476/1</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2013 13:02:55 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-524476-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/potential-user-submission-loveandpower/524476.rss">Potential User Submission - Loveandpower</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
