<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Can&#39;t make ANY servers on laptop?</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/cant-make-any-servers-on-laptop/469194</link>
    <description>[b]Sorry-it&#39;s a bit long[/b]
Okay so about a year ago I got into making an rsps with my brother. Me and him set it up on an old desktop we used to have and it worked fine for a while. We got it online and everything and were still in the middle of coding it when we had to get rid of the desktop. Before getting rid of it I transfered all the files from the desktop onto my laptop to continue with the server but when I tried to open the server on the laptop it wouldn&#39;t connect and left me at the login screen. Everything was just as it was on the desktop and I only made the necessary changes i.e. updating the jdk version in the .bat files. Well recently I&#39;ve wanted to get back into coding my server and couldnt get it to work for the life of me so I [b]completely[/b] erased a whole few months of work and downloaded [b]several[/b] different clients/sources, with no prevail. I know I have port forwarded 100% correctly and I have my client.java text set to local (127.0.0.1) and I still cant log in. I&#39;m using the InsidiaX v2 client and source. It&#39;s about the 15th I&#39;ve tried tonight. Can anybody help me? Tv me and check my files to make sure I didnt do something wrong? Any help at all is appreciated. Thanks.

EDIT:
Also, I checked my server status on Runelocus and MoparScape and
both times it said my server was &quot;Online.&quot; 
When I go to canyoueeme.org it says my port is open and it can be seen.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 19 Nov 2012 14:36:37 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Game Development</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/cant-make-any-servers-on-laptop/469194.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Can&#39;t make ANY servers on laptop?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@xXThatOneSkaterKidXx xXThatOneSkaterKidXx]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/xxthatoneskaterkidxx">@xXThatOneSkaterKidXx</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p><span class="bbcode-b">Sorry-it’s a bit long</span><br>
Okay so about a year ago I got into making an rsps with my brother. Me and him set it up on an old desktop we used to have and it worked fine for a while. We got it online and everything and were still in the middle of coding it when we had to get rid of the desktop. Before getting rid of it I transfered all the files from the desktop onto my laptop to continue with the server but when I tried to open the server on the laptop it wouldn’t connect and left me at the login screen. Everything was just as it was on the desktop and I only made the necessary changes i.e. updating the jdk version in the .bat files. Well recently I’ve wanted to get back into coding my server and couldnt get it to work for the life of me so I <span class="bbcode-b">completely</span> erased a whole few months of work and downloaded <span class="bbcode-b">several</span> different clients/sources, with no prevail. I know I have port forwarded 100% correctly and I have my client.java text set to local (127.0.0.1) and I still cant log in. I’m using the InsidiaX v2 client and source. It’s about the 15th I’ve tried tonight. Can anybody help me? Tv me and check my files to make sure I didnt do something wrong? Any help at all is appreciated. Thanks.</p>
<p>EDIT:<br>
Also, I checked my server status on Runelocus and MoparScape and<br>
both times it said my server was “Online.”<br>
When I go to <a href="http://canyoueeme.org" rel="nofollow noopener">canyoueeme.org</a> it says my port is open and it can be seen.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/cant-make-any-servers-on-laptop/469194/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/cant-make-any-servers-on-laptop/469194/1</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 19 Nov 2012 14:36:37 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-469194-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/cant-make-any-servers-on-laptop/469194.rss">Can&#39;t make ANY servers on laptop?</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
