<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Rules (DO NOT TAKE THIS AS FAKE) provent yourself from Getting Banned</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rules-do-not-take-this-as-fake-provent-yourself-from-getting-banned/308706</link>
    <description>This section has been lacking an official rule set for quite some time, and I&#39;ve been thinking about throwing one in, so here it is (Rog3r reminded me earlier to get to it ):

There&#39;s going to be a new rule added, to settle the confusion, and to allow something new for once. Here they are:

[b]1)[/b] All content posted must be yours and yours ONLY! If broken, a punishment will be given depending on the material posted and the situation at hand. People helping out here and there is, of course, allowed, as long as the majority of the project belongs to you. There is an exception though: if it was a team project it is okay for all members to own credit and to be posted only if credit is given where credit is due.

[b]2)[/b] Do NOT post harmful content! No viruses, malware, or spyware are allowed on this forum! If you are caught, be expecting a mute at the least. Depending on the infection and previous offenses, you may or may not be punished with a permanent ban from these forums.

[b]3) [/b] Do NOT post scans for viruses and other malware. Firstly, when the topic creator posts his/her own scan, it shows that they&#39;re usually IS an infection in the download. Common sense there. Secondly, you should have your own scanner by now, and you could use that if you&#39;d really like. But most importantly, virus scanners do not pick up harmful content in source code! Java is also a binary language when compiled, and the scanner will usually not pick anything up when it scans over the compiled output.

[b]4)[/b] NEW RULE: NON-SERVER &amp; NON-CLIENT DOWNLOADS ARE ALLOWED (e.g. tools)! This has never been allowed before, but hey, we decided to give it a go. The tool posted must follow all rules and have an appropriate connection to RS2 private servers. If rules start to get broken and content gets out of hand, this rule will be revoked, and no longer will we allow non-server/non-client material to be posted.

[b]5)[/b] No Requests Rather straightforward - don&#39;t post a topic requesting a certain source download link to be given to you.  Use your resources such as the search button to your advantage.  Doing so will result in a warning or moderation.  

[b]6)[/b] No *.bat / list files PERIOD! There are stupid and a waste of time to bother with. Learn to program with a real language. If you&#39;re beatiful server includes one of these in the topic itself (if its included in the download its okay) then it&#39;ll be locked and you&#39;ll be punished. Forgot to mention, they only work on Windows, too. Also lists aren&#39;t really a download as it is usually a text file with some scribbles in it. The official Moparscape client already has a list. USE IT!

[b]7) [/b] Don&#39;t post download lists! These are a waste of your time.  If someone wants a source, they can use the search button.

[b]8)[/b] Having topic titles involving &quot;About to remove&quot; , &quot;Post or ill remove&quot;, or something similar will result in a lock and a warn/mute. Refer to this topic for complete details.[br][br][size=1]Posted on: October 15, 2009, 08:16:44 am[/size][hr]Please follow these &quot;[url=http://rules]rules[/url]&quot;.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 15 Oct 2009 15:09:15 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>General Discussion</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rules-do-not-take-this-as-fake-provent-yourself-from-getting-banned/308706.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Rules (DO NOT TAKE THIS AS FAKE) provent yourself from Getting Banned</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@_Rich Rich]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/_rich">@_Rich</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote no-group" data-post="2" data-topic="308706">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 Infinity Zr:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>We dont need a mimic</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rules-do-not-take-this-as-fake-provent-yourself-from-getting-banned/308706/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rules-do-not-take-this-as-fake-provent-yourself-from-getting-banned/308706/4</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 15 Oct 2009 15:09:15 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-308706-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rules-do-not-take-this-as-fake-provent-yourself-from-getting-banned/308706.rss">Rules (DO NOT TAKE THIS AS FAKE) provent yourself from Getting Banned</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Rules (DO NOT TAKE THIS AS FAKE) provent yourself from Getting Banned</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@hussain123 hussain123]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/hussain123">@hussain123</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>People agree with the “rules” but usually it’s mistaking, some of that, has been read by a Global Moderator this after-noon at 6:00pm.<br>
He agree’d i could post this in the “Server Download” section.</p>
<p>It’s hard to believe when you first read it, but keep reading it all over again, and you will fully know the rules.<br>
Some rules may be difficult for you to understand or manage to read…<br>
If you have trouble, please contact a member of the staff or Contact me on here.</p>
<p>Thank-you for taking part in this progress (“Section”).</p>
<p>Hussain123</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rules-do-not-take-this-as-fake-provent-yourself-from-getting-banned/308706/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rules-do-not-take-this-as-fake-provent-yourself-from-getting-banned/308706/3</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 15 Oct 2009 14:21:01 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-308706-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rules-do-not-take-this-as-fake-provent-yourself-from-getting-banned/308706.rss">Rules (DO NOT TAKE THIS AS FAKE) provent yourself from Getting Banned</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Rules (DO NOT TAKE THIS AS FAKE) provent yourself from Getting Banned</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Infinity_Zr Infinity Zr]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/infinity_zr">@Infinity_Zr</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>We dont need a mimic</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rules-do-not-take-this-as-fake-provent-yourself-from-getting-banned/308706/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rules-do-not-take-this-as-fake-provent-yourself-from-getting-banned/308706/2</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 15 Oct 2009 14:17:21 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-308706-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rules-do-not-take-this-as-fake-provent-yourself-from-getting-banned/308706.rss">Rules (DO NOT TAKE THIS AS FAKE) provent yourself from Getting Banned</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Rules (DO NOT TAKE THIS AS FAKE) provent yourself from Getting Banned</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@hussain123 hussain123]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/hussain123">@hussain123</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>This section has been lacking an official rule set for quite some time, and I’ve been thinking about throwing one in, so here it is (Rog3r reminded me earlier to get to it ):</p>
<p>There’s going to be a new rule added, to settle the confusion, and to allow something new for once. Here they are:</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">1)</span> All content posted must be yours and yours ONLY! If broken, a punishment will be given depending on the material posted and the situation at hand. People helping out here and there is, of course, allowed, as long as the majority of the project belongs to you. There is an exception though: if it was a team project it is okay for all members to own credit and to be posted only if credit is given where credit is due.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">2)</span> Do NOT post harmful content! No viruses, malware, or spyware are allowed on this forum! If you are caught, be expecting a mute at the least. Depending on the infection and previous offenses, you may or may not be punished with a permanent ban from these forums.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">3) </span> Do NOT post scans for viruses and other malware. Firstly, when the topic creator posts his/her own scan, it shows that they’re usually IS an infection in the download. Common sense there. Secondly, you should have your own scanner by now, and you could use that if you’d really like. But most importantly, virus scanners do not pick up harmful content in source code! Java is also a binary language when compiled, and the scanner will usually not pick anything up when it scans over the compiled output.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">4)</span> NEW RULE: NON-SERVER &amp; NON-CLIENT DOWNLOADS ARE ALLOWED (e.g. tools)! This has never been allowed before, but hey, we decided to give it a go. The tool posted must follow all rules and have an appropriate connection to RS2 private servers. If rules start to get broken and content gets out of hand, this rule will be revoked, and no longer will we allow non-server/non-client material to be posted.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">5)</span> No Requests Rather straightforward - don’t post a topic requesting a certain source download link to be given to you.  Use your resources such as the search button to your advantage.  Doing so will result in a warning or moderation.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">6)</span> No *.bat / list files PERIOD! There are stupid and a waste of time to bother with. Learn to program with a real language. If you’re beatiful server includes one of these in the topic itself (if its included in the download its okay) then it’ll be locked and you’ll be punished. Forgot to mention, they only work on Windows, too. Also lists aren’t really a download as it is usually a text file with some scribbles in it. The official Moparscape client already has a list. USE IT!</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">7) </span> Don’t post download lists! These are a waste of your time.  If someone wants a source, they can use the search button.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">8)</span> Having topic titles involving “About to remove” , “Post or ill remove”, or something similar will result in a lock and a warn/mute. Refer to this topic for complete details.[br][br][size=1]Posted on: October 15, 2009, 08:16:44 am[/size][hr]Please follow these “<a href="http://rules" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">rules</a>”.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rules-do-not-take-this-as-fake-provent-yourself-from-getting-banned/308706/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rules-do-not-take-this-as-fake-provent-yourself-from-getting-banned/308706/1</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 15 Oct 2009 14:11:14 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-308706-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rules-do-not-take-this-as-fake-provent-yourself-from-getting-banned/308706.rss">Rules (DO NOT TAKE THIS AS FAKE) provent yourself from Getting Banned</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
