<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Serverstatus</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/serverstatus/272732</link>
    <description>Well, I think it doesn&#39;t really belong to server help so fix me if I&#39;m wrong. Anyway, I had my server posted on serverstatus page and it was there for a while, about 4 days. Then it got removed from the list. Now, one other server have been posting their server under my ip and advertising their own by putting there their own screenshots and their server ip. There are several servers with same problem. Even if it gets removed from the list, it will be readded right after it. I don&#39;t even get a chance to post my own. It&#39;s so annoying. Is there a way to solve it and stop them from doing it? It&#39;s not even rs private server. They are adversing CS 1.6. I pmed staff member but didnt get any response.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 12 Apr 2009 08:16:20 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/serverstatus/272732.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Serverstatus</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Runekeep Runekeep]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/runekeep">@Runekeep</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>You can block specific requests from an incoming domain. I use iptables firewall on linux to do this.</p>
<p>The easy way is to change your port before your add the server again. This gets rather tedious though, as the way above does also.</p>
<p>Good luck!</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/serverstatus/272732/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/serverstatus/272732/2</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 12 Apr 2009 08:16:20 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-272732-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/serverstatus/272732.rss">Serverstatus</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Serverstatus</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@ats3 ats3]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/ats3">@ats3</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Well, I think it doesn’t really belong to server help so fix me if I’m wrong. Anyway, I had my server posted on serverstatus page and it was there for a while, about 4 days. Then it got removed from the list. Now, one other server have been posting their server under my ip and advertising their own by putting there their own screenshots and their server ip. There are several servers with same problem. Even if it gets removed from the list, it will be readded right after it. I don’t even get a chance to post my own. It’s so annoying. Is there a way to solve it and stop them from doing it? It’s not even rs private server. They are adversing CS 1.6. I pmed staff member but didnt get any response.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/serverstatus/272732/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/serverstatus/272732/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 12 Apr 2009 07:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-272732-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/serverstatus/272732.rss">Serverstatus</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
