<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>ServerStatus?</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/serverstatus/373339</link>
    <description>Okay,

So ForeverPkers linked their Vote4Cash to down vote me due to my idiotic players constantly spamming his server. I worked out the problem with James, the owner, but another problem persists. I had problems with my VPS, so I got a new one--with a new IP. Apparently, the owner of SnakeGaming bought a VPS from the same company I bought mine from, and coincidentally got My old VPS&#39;s IP. So now he has -1.1K votes, and I have his server posted. I don&#39;t know where to post this, so I guessed here would be fine. I need this fixed as soon as possible--this is the last problem that persists til I can post my server around again.

Thanks,
Sam</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 15 Dec 2010 03:44:50 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>General Discussion</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/serverstatus/373339.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>ServerStatus?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Scape-JAVA Scape-JAVA]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/scape-java">@Scape-JAVA</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Try private messaging MITB about your issue, we can’t do anything, unfortunately.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/serverstatus/373339/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/serverstatus/373339/2</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 15 Dec 2010 03:44:50 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-373339-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/serverstatus/373339.rss">ServerStatus?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>ServerStatus?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Penetration Penetration]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/penetration">@Penetration</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Okay,</p>
<p>So ForeverPkers linked their Vote4Cash to down vote me due to my idiotic players constantly spamming his server. I worked out the problem with James, the owner, but another problem persists. I had problems with my VPS, so I got a new one–with a new IP. Apparently, the owner of SnakeGaming bought a VPS from the same company I bought mine from, and coincidentally got My old VPS’s IP. So now he has -1.1K votes, and I have his server posted. I don’t know where to post this, so I guessed here would be fine. I need this fixed as soon as possible–this is the last problem that persists til I can post my server around again.</p>
<p>Thanks,<br>
Sam</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/serverstatus/373339/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/serverstatus/373339/1</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 15 Dec 2010 02:45:02 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-373339-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/serverstatus/373339.rss">ServerStatus?</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
