<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>How To Zombify Your Dead Batteries!</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-zombify-your-dead-batteries/144904</link>
    <description>Have you ever been listening to your CD or MP3 player, and your in the mood for music, but then your batteries go dead?

Have you ever needed batteries, but forgot to get new ones at the store, and now your left with just a bunch of dead batteries that you probably won&#39;t/can&#39;t use?

Have you ever had any other battery related problem, which concern your not being able to reuse dead batteries?

If you answered YES to any of these questions, this guide is definitely for you!

Hello, I&#39;m Dregen, your all around battery guru :)

I will teach you tricks on how to exploit and squeeze some extra minutes or even HOURS of power from your dead batteries! If you find anything in my guide to be faulty, please let me know, as I have only gathered this information by testing, and a tiny bit from word-of-mouth. Thank you.

Please note that the items that use batteries I will call APPLIANCES! This can mean a CD/MP3 player, a Game Boy, whatever.

First of all, why use normal batteries and not rechargeable batteries? I have no clue. But this is for those people who are either too lazy to use rechargeable batteries, or don&#39;t want to use them (Including me, lol ;) ).

Now for the long awaited tips and tricks :)

The first, and most IMPORTANT step of all is to gather up as many dead batteries as you can! In your vehicle, home, school bus, friend&#39;s house, it doesn&#39;t matter, just as long as they still have enough juice in &#39;em to use. Having a somewhat large battery storage will help you in the long run with this guide. I once had more then 15 batteries in my coat pockets so I&#39;m assuming they shouldn&#39;t be that hard to find.

Second, find a place to store your batteries. Like i said before, you can use your coat pockets, or maybe an empty pocket on your schoolbag you don&#39;t use. Doesn&#39;t have to be too fancy, it&#39;s just to hold them and keep them somewhat safe from the elements. You don&#39;t need to worry about hiding them, I&#39;m sure no one will steal them unless they are incredibly stupid, they have read my guide :|

Extra tip: Something that helps is having 1-3 commercial brand batteries, such as Duracell, Rayovac, or Energizer. These batteries usually have a lot of power, and are good to pair up other dead batteries with, whether the commercial brand battery is dead or not. Here&#39;s my reliability/power containment rank for each of the three brands listed.

Rayovac : #1 (Highest)
Duracell:  #2 (Lower)
Energizer: #3 (Lowest)

Of course, I mainly use Rayovac so this chart may be way off.

I think Rayovac make these cheaper &quot;Heavy Duty&quot; batteries, so note that these ado NOT contain more power than the more expensive one, but far less. Just thought I would make a note of that.

Okay, now here&#39;s how you do it.

I&#39;m using a 2 battery appliance as an example. Take your dead batteries, and grab whichever one has the most power. This is probably gonna be your standard commercial brand battery. Stick the good battery in a slot. Now take another dead battery, and stick it in. Attempt to turn on your appliance. If it works, congratulations. If it doesn&#39;t try try again. Take another dead battery, replace it with the other bad battery, and repeat this procedure until it works.

Seems pretty simple, huh? That&#39;s not all. Here a few tips to take some of those batteries and give them a temporary power jump, so you can reuse them more and more often.

Changing the temperature of a battery can do harm, or it can do good. Say for example, it&#39;s a cold winter day, and your batteries turn cold when you get on the bus from school, and it turns out your appliance will now have less battery power or won&#39;t work at all.

Stop! Don&#39;t think your batteries are dead. It&#39;s just the temperature of the batteries that is affecting their power. Take your batteries from the appliance, and hold them in your hands and warm them up. Once they are warm, stick them back in. Notice that the battery power is now much higher than before, and your appliance has more energy.

Now it may seem cold kills off batteries, but this isn&#39;t entirely true. Sometimes sticking your batteries in the fridge for a bit will give your batteries about 15-30 minutes of more juice. But it doesn&#39;t last long. Once the batteries warm up, they lose most of their energy.

Now, it&#39;s not just cold. Heat, which I touched on very briefly before, can give your batteries more energy. Even heating up a battery that seems warm, by squeezing in your hand for a bit, STILL can give your battery more power. I usually do this to re-energize my dead batteries. It&#39;s like giving them a shot of steroids.

Here are a few more tips that may be of use to you.

The more batteries an appliance needs, the harder it is to get it to work with dead batteries. Dead batteries seem to affect these more than they do when your using an appliance that requires less batteries. This is probably because these use more power, and it can be quite difficult trying to power up 4 dead batteries to the point where you can use them all at once. And even if you manage to do it, it won&#39;t last long at all. I haven&#39;t tested this much, so if this is wrong, correct me.

Commercial brand batteries may not be good enough for a dead battery pair if it is dead enough. Make sure to figure out how much power the battery is.

If a battery will outright not work at all (in other words, dead... truly dead), throw it away. It will be of no use to you.

That&#39;s it! Thanks for reading this guide. I definitely enjoying writing this, because it gave me something to do in Study Hall at school. I hope these methods help you save money, and also help us SAVE OUR ENVIRONMENT BY CONSUMING LESS BATTERIES! If you need help, or find a problem in my guide, once again, don&#39;t hesitate to ask me.

Have some fun bringing dead batteries back to life! Mhuwhahahaha!
[b]
EDIT: Another tip to get batteries more juice below!

I will use a fake story as an example.

Okay, say your listening to your MP3 player on the way to school, and the batteries go dead. You don&#39;t do any of these methods, or switch out the battery. You just leave it in.

Now, when you get back from school, you attempt to try to turn it on again. It works.

The point of that is... That if you stop using a battery for a bit, it will recharge some power! Neato, huh?

[i]Extra Tip - Credits To Rspoon

&quot;Also, you can use batteries that died when using a mouse, on other things. The amount of power the battery uses up depends on the item its in.

Like, my mouse&#39;s batteries had died, so I switched them with my remotes batteries, and both of those things worked perfectly, because the remote didnt use up as much power.&quot; [/i][/b]</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 06 Oct 2007 18:29:13 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>General Discussion</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-zombify-your-dead-batteries/144904.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>How To Zombify Your Dead Batteries!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@n00b_pk3r n00b pk3r]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/n00b_pk3r">@n00b_pk3r</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>i’d do this if i was bored as hell lol</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-zombify-your-dead-batteries/144904/27">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-zombify-your-dead-batteries/144904/27</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 06 Oct 2007 18:29:13 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-144904-27</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-zombify-your-dead-batteries/144904.rss">How To Zombify Your Dead Batteries!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>How To Zombify Your Dead Batteries!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Dregen Dregen]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/dregen">@Dregen</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“rspoon, post:25, topic:144904”]No, she doesn’t. His tutorial explains many more ways to get batteries to work again then just-</p>
<p>“Put a dead and a working battery together.”</p>
<p>Some of these ways I’d be interested in trying. <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=6" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"></p>
<p>[b]Also, you can use batteries that died when using a mouse, on other things. The amount of power the battery uses up depends on the item its in.</p>
<p>Like, my mouse’s batteries had died, so I switched them with my remotes batteries, and both of those things worked perfectly, because the remote didnt use up as much power.[/b][/quote]</p>
<p>Ah, Rspoon, good tip. I’ll stick it in my original post and give you credits.</p>
<p>I think I had done that before, but I forgot. Not sure.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-zombify-your-dead-batteries/144904/26">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-zombify-your-dead-batteries/144904/26</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 01 Oct 2007 03:39:36 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-144904-26</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-zombify-your-dead-batteries/144904.rss">How To Zombify Your Dead Batteries!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>How To Zombify Your Dead Batteries!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@rspoon rspoon]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/rspoon">@rspoon</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>No, she doesn’t. His tutorial explains many more ways to get batteries to work again then just-</p>
<p>“Put a dead and a working battery together.”</p>
<p>Some of these ways I’d be interested in trying. <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=6" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"></p>
<p>Also, you can use batteries that died when using a mouse, on other things. The amount of power the battery uses up depends on the item its in.</p>
<p>Like, my mouse’s batteries had died, so I switched them with my remotes batteries, and both of those things worked perfectly, because the remote didnt use up as much power.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-zombify-your-dead-batteries/144904/25">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-zombify-your-dead-batteries/144904/25</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 30 Sep 2007 18:09:18 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-144904-25</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-zombify-your-dead-batteries/144904.rss">How To Zombify Your Dead Batteries!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>How To Zombify Your Dead Batteries!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Monkey_wacko Monkey wacko]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/monkey_wacko">@Monkey_wacko</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Silab does have a point there…</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-zombify-your-dead-batteries/144904/24">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-zombify-your-dead-batteries/144904/24</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 30 Sep 2007 14:45:08 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-144904-24</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-zombify-your-dead-batteries/144904.rss">How To Zombify Your Dead Batteries!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>How To Zombify Your Dead Batteries!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@rspoon rspoon]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/rspoon">@rspoon</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“ThugLife, post:17, topic:144904”]What are you? 10 years old?<br>
Batteries cost next to nothing, i would rather spend the money than waste my time with this tutorial, no offense to the tutorial writer or anything its a well explained and written tutorial, i’m just saying there is not much sense behind it.[/quote]</p>
<p>Erm, the economy isnt doing so great right now. If people started thinking like “Well, buying it would just save me time”, you probably wouldnt be doing too great on cash.</p>
<p>Anyways, great tutorial. Heh, there arent very many tuts anymore that actually explain alot about the certain thing your teaching.</p>
<p>Im sure my dad would love this tutorial, if it still works, why throw it out? <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/smiley.png?v=6" title=":smiley:" class="emoji" alt=":smiley:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-zombify-your-dead-batteries/144904/23">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-zombify-your-dead-batteries/144904/23</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 29 Sep 2007 23:36:13 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-144904-23</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-zombify-your-dead-batteries/144904.rss">How To Zombify Your Dead Batteries!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>How To Zombify Your Dead Batteries!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@brush200400 brush200400]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/brush200400">@brush200400</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>i thought this thread would be about corroding dead batteries which would be cooler than giving more juice to dead batteries.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-zombify-your-dead-batteries/144904/22">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-zombify-your-dead-batteries/144904/22</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 26 Sep 2007 06:45:26 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-144904-22</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-zombify-your-dead-batteries/144904.rss">How To Zombify Your Dead Batteries!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>How To Zombify Your Dead Batteries!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Dregen Dregen]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/dregen">@Dregen</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“ThugLife, post:17, topic:144904”]What are you? 10 years old?<br>
Batteries cost next to nothing, i would rather spend the money than waste my time with this tutorial, no offense to the tutorial writer or anything its a well explained and written tutorial, i’m just saying there is not much sense behind it.[/quote]</p>
<p>Nah, but close, 13.</p>
<p>Thug, it’s not THAT hard to remember. If it was, I wouldn’t have been doing it like everyday on the bus when I was in 7th grade. Just takes a little bit of memory.</p>
<p>Well, thanks that you said it was well written and everything <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=6" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"> That’s kinda what I was aiming for too, but whatever.</p>
<p>Also, if you don’t feel it takes the time to do it, you don’t need to do it. This is just if you’re REALLY desperate to have something to do, listen to, etc. I’m not really a guy who can pull fresh batteries out of my ass every five minutes, so I have to make do with what I have, and what I can do with it.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-zombify-your-dead-batteries/144904/21">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-zombify-your-dead-batteries/144904/21</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 23 Sep 2007 08:40:51 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-144904-21</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-zombify-your-dead-batteries/144904.rss">How To Zombify Your Dead Batteries!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>How To Zombify Your Dead Batteries!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@dragonus18 dragonus18]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/dragonus18">@dragonus18</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote no-group" data-post="19" data-topic="144904">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 ThugLife:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Yeah, and while your on a bus you don’t usually carry around loads of other dead batteries and be able to follow and remember this tutorial.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>ok you have a point there…</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-zombify-your-dead-batteries/144904/20">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-zombify-your-dead-batteries/144904/20</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 23 Sep 2007 04:54:03 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-144904-20</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-zombify-your-dead-batteries/144904.rss">How To Zombify Your Dead Batteries!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>How To Zombify Your Dead Batteries!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@tL tL]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/tl">@tL</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Yeah, and while your on a bus you don’t usually carry around loads of other dead batteries and be able to follow and remember this tutorial.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-zombify-your-dead-batteries/144904/19">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-zombify-your-dead-batteries/144904/19</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 23 Sep 2007 04:49:25 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-144904-19</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-zombify-your-dead-batteries/144904.rss">How To Zombify Your Dead Batteries!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>How To Zombify Your Dead Batteries!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@dragonus18 dragonus18]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/dragonus18">@dragonus18</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“ThugLife, post:17, topic:144904”]What are you? 10 years old?<br>
Batteries cost next to nothing, i would rather spend the money than waste my time with this tutorial, no offense to the tutorial writer or anything its a well explained and written tutorial, i’m just saying there is not much sense behind it.[/quote]</p>
<p>no i’m 13</p>
<p>and i’m just trying to say that if your on the bus or somehitng and your listening to music on your cd player and it runs out of bateries it would be kind of hard to go out and buy them but if you read the tutorial and remember it you could listen to your music longer and not have to kick the fat kids ass. also if your under 16 and can’t drive and you need batteries and your mom or dad aren’t going to run to the store jsut for some batteries. now thats the sense behind it</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-zombify-your-dead-batteries/144904/18">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-zombify-your-dead-batteries/144904/18</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 23 Sep 2007 04:37:22 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-144904-18</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-zombify-your-dead-batteries/144904.rss">How To Zombify Your Dead Batteries!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>How To Zombify Your Dead Batteries!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@tL tL]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/tl">@tL</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>What are you? 10 years old?<br>
Batteries cost next to nothing, i would rather spend the money than waste my time with this tutorial, no offense to the tutorial writer or anything its a well explained and written tutorial, i’m just saying there is not much sense behind it.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-zombify-your-dead-batteries/144904/17">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-zombify-your-dead-batteries/144904/17</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 23 Sep 2007 04:33:56 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-144904-17</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-zombify-your-dead-batteries/144904.rss">How To Zombify Your Dead Batteries!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>How To Zombify Your Dead Batteries!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@dragonus18 dragonus18]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/dragonus18">@dragonus18</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote no-group" data-post="15" data-topic="144904">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 ThugLife:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>You could of run to the shop and bought some in the time of following this tutorial.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>but that would cost money…</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-zombify-your-dead-batteries/144904/16">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-zombify-your-dead-batteries/144904/16</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 23 Sep 2007 04:31:49 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-144904-16</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-zombify-your-dead-batteries/144904.rss">How To Zombify Your Dead Batteries!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>How To Zombify Your Dead Batteries!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@tL tL]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/tl">@tL</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>You could of run to the shop and bought some in the time of following this tutorial.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-zombify-your-dead-batteries/144904/15">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-zombify-your-dead-batteries/144904/15</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 23 Sep 2007 04:30:20 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-144904-15</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-zombify-your-dead-batteries/144904.rss">How To Zombify Your Dead Batteries!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>How To Zombify Your Dead Batteries!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@vraj82192 vraj82192]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/vraj82192">@vraj82192</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Yeah Ive done that before. My brothers iPod runs outta power all the time and like when I think its really really low I turn it off. And after like 20 mins its back to half… I’m like wtF? but I tried it again and it lasted for like cuple mins longer and it was just really random. but it does last longer if there about to go dead or have gone dead.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-zombify-your-dead-batteries/144904/14">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-zombify-your-dead-batteries/144904/14</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 23 Sep 2007 04:20:05 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-144904-14</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-zombify-your-dead-batteries/144904.rss">How To Zombify Your Dead Batteries!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>How To Zombify Your Dead Batteries!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Dregen Dregen]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/dregen">@Dregen</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“llib, post:8, topic:144904”][quote author=Dregen link=topic=198508.msg1768647#msg1768647 date=1190269708]<br>
I once had more then 15 batteries in my coat pockets so I’m assuming they shouldn’t be that hard to find.<br>
[/quote]</p>
<p>Do you have any idea how hard that is to believe.[/quote]</p>
<p>Haha, it may be hard to believe, but it’s true. when I was in like 7th grade i listened to my CD player 24/7 and had loads of batteries. Plus, my dad’s vehicle had loads due to us not throwing them away sooo… yeah.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-post="9" data-topic="144904">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/user_avatar/forum.moparisthebest.com/kloplop321/40/181_2.png" class="avatar"> kloplop321:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>all I can say is that you are using up the batteries to hard that they are at the point of when they do absolutly nothing, they are at the cliff of major corroding?</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Not quite. None of my batteries had corroded while doing this. Well maybe one or two, I dunno.</p>
<p>Also, another tip coming! I forgot to put this one in, so I will edit my first post to get it in, after I type it here.</p>
<p>Okay, say your listening to your MP3 player on the way to school, and the batteries go dead. You don’t do any of these methods, or switch out the battery. You just leave it in.</p>
<p>Now, when you get back from school, you attempt to try to turn it on again. It works.</p>
<p>The point of that is… That if you stop using a battery for a bit, it will recharge some power! Neato, huh?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-zombify-your-dead-batteries/144904/13">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-zombify-your-dead-batteries/144904/13</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 22 Sep 2007 07:24:57 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-144904-13</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-zombify-your-dead-batteries/144904.rss">How To Zombify Your Dead Batteries!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>How To Zombify Your Dead Batteries!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Aff Aff]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/aff">@Aff</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Great guide, I tested it out and it works… I tested all the possibilities you mentioned and they work <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/smiley.png?v=6" title=":smiley:" class="emoji" alt=":smiley:"> Except for using two dead ones, which kind of screwed up… But thanks <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=6" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-zombify-your-dead-batteries/144904/12">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-zombify-your-dead-batteries/144904/12</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 21 Sep 2007 19:51:18 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-144904-12</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-zombify-your-dead-batteries/144904.rss">How To Zombify Your Dead Batteries!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>How To Zombify Your Dead Batteries!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Yz85Racer Yz85Racer]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/yz85racer">@Yz85Racer</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“3.65 kilos, post:10, topic:144904”]Um…nice guide?</p>
<p>I didn’t know that temperature can affect batteries…but I guess that’s believable.[/quote]<br>
Yah, you put them into the freezer for a while and you get a bit more out of them. Worked for me.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-zombify-your-dead-batteries/144904/11">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-zombify-your-dead-batteries/144904/11</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 21 Sep 2007 12:54:11 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-144904-11</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-zombify-your-dead-batteries/144904.rss">How To Zombify Your Dead Batteries!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>How To Zombify Your Dead Batteries!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@3.65_kilos 3.65 kilos]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/3.65_kilos">@3.65_kilos</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Um…nice guide?</p>
<p>I didn’t know that temperature can affect batteries…but I guess that’s believable.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-zombify-your-dead-batteries/144904/10">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-zombify-your-dead-batteries/144904/10</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 21 Sep 2007 12:48:19 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-144904-10</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-zombify-your-dead-batteries/144904.rss">How To Zombify Your Dead Batteries!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>How To Zombify Your Dead Batteries!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@kloplop321 kloplop321]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/kloplop321">@kloplop321</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>all I can say is that you are using up the batteries to hard that they are at the point of when they do absolutly nothing, they are at the cliff of major corroding?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-zombify-your-dead-batteries/144904/9">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-zombify-your-dead-batteries/144904/9</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 21 Sep 2007 08:40:44 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-144904-9</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-zombify-your-dead-batteries/144904.rss">How To Zombify Your Dead Batteries!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>How To Zombify Your Dead Batteries!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@llib llib]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/llib">@llib</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote no-group" data-post="1" data-topic="144904">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/dregen/40/5_6259e4fa9dfe0dec282fb0955bb1974c.png" class="avatar"> Dregen:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>I once had more then 15 batteries in my coat pockets so I’m assuming they shouldn’t be that hard to find.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Do you have any idea how hard that is to believe.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-zombify-your-dead-batteries/144904/8">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-zombify-your-dead-batteries/144904/8</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 21 Sep 2007 06:20:40 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-144904-8</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-zombify-your-dead-batteries/144904.rss">How To Zombify Your Dead Batteries!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>How To Zombify Your Dead Batteries!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@xxlegitxx xxlegitxx]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/xxlegitxx">@xxlegitxx</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote no-group" data-post="5" data-topic="144904">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/heaven/40/5_6259e4fa9dfe0dec282fb0955bb1974c.png" class="avatar"> Heaven:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Lol SS just owned Dregen.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Not quite.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-zombify-your-dead-batteries/144904/7">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-zombify-your-dead-batteries/144904/7</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 21 Sep 2007 05:31:15 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-144904-7</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-zombify-your-dead-batteries/144904.rss">How To Zombify Your Dead Batteries!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>How To Zombify Your Dead Batteries!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Dregen Dregen]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/dregen">@Dregen</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>You don’t have to just use one charged battery. Both of them can be dead if you like. Now, even if they don’t work when paired together, you can change the core temperature of the batteries and that probably will give more power, and therefore your appliance will work.</p>
<p>What I’m trying to say about commercial brand batteries is that they last longer, and they contain more power then that 30 pack of batteries at the store you found for just a couple bucks.</p>
<p>This method of using dead batteries can take a lot of testing. You may have to switch batteries with one another and make a conclusion to how much power each one has. I’ll try to post and example here of doing it when I have the time.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-zombify-your-dead-batteries/144904/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-zombify-your-dead-batteries/144904/6</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 21 Sep 2007 05:29:46 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-144904-6</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-zombify-your-dead-batteries/144904.rss">How To Zombify Your Dead Batteries!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>How To Zombify Your Dead Batteries!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Heaven Heaven]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/heaven">@Heaven</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Lol SS just owned Dregen.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-zombify-your-dead-batteries/144904/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-zombify-your-dead-batteries/144904/5</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 21 Sep 2007 05:28:51 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-144904-5</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-zombify-your-dead-batteries/144904.rss">How To Zombify Your Dead Batteries!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>How To Zombify Your Dead Batteries!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@silabsoft RuneAgent]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/silabsoft">@silabsoft</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>putting in 1 dead and 1 charged is only using more power from the charged one. thus killing the charged battery faster.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-zombify-your-dead-batteries/144904/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-zombify-your-dead-batteries/144904/4</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 20 Sep 2007 13:45:55 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-144904-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-zombify-your-dead-batteries/144904.rss">How To Zombify Your Dead Batteries!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>How To Zombify Your Dead Batteries!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Mrquarter Mrquarter]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/mrquarter">@Mrquarter</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Yes, I think he is trying to say to use a good and a bad battery together?</p>
<p>I just sorta buy batteries or use Rechargeable.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-zombify-your-dead-batteries/144904/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-zombify-your-dead-batteries/144904/3</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 20 Sep 2007 07:56:59 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-144904-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-zombify-your-dead-batteries/144904.rss">How To Zombify Your Dead Batteries!</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
