<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Stopping webclient reload errors</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/stopping-webclient-reload-errors/284318</link>
    <description>It&#39;s a common problem that webclients have trouble running more than once in the same browser session. I&#39;ve now made my webclient able to reload in the same session limitless times, however if a player reloads the client or navigates away from the page while it is loading it refuses to reload a second time.

I think this is because the client opens the cache for reading [making it read only] and because the user closes the webclient as it is loading, the client doesn&#39;t have chance to close the inputstream. Then on the second load maybe the client can&#39;t access the cache because it is apparently already in use. This may be completely wrong, it&#39;s just my guess. Can anyone shed any light?</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 19 Jun 2009 07:22:15 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Game Development</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/stopping-webclient-reload-errors/284318.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Stopping webclient reload errors</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@The_cook_from_runesc The cook from runescape]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/the_cook_from_runesc">@The_cook_from_runesc</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>It’s a common problem that webclients have trouble running more than once in the same browser session. I’ve now made my webclient able to reload in the same session limitless times, however if a player reloads the client or navigates away from the page while it is loading it refuses to reload a second time.</p>
<p>I think this is because the client opens the cache for reading [making it read only] and because the user closes the webclient as it is loading, the client doesn’t have chance to close the inputstream. Then on the second load maybe the client can’t access the cache because it is apparently already in use. This may be completely wrong, it’s just my guess. Can anyone shed any light?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/stopping-webclient-reload-errors/284318/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/stopping-webclient-reload-errors/284318/1</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 19 Jun 2009 07:22:15 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-284318-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/stopping-webclient-reload-errors/284318.rss">Stopping webclient reload errors</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
