<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Can some one suggest something to me?</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/can-some-one-suggest-something-to-me/275761</link>
    <description>READ. please don&#39;t be afraid to read all of this. i know it looks like alot to read, but its not :D

hi moparscape server owners and kick &quot;a&quot; players,
I need to know what is the best server source and client that is in the range of 377(higher then 317)-417(not 474).

I really would like to know because I love all the cool features but some of them are too complicated for my lil&#39; brain to understand. like how the files in 474 are all scrambled gives me a head ache, but the way 317 frames look on the client and the way their graphics look with stupid items also makes me wana stay in the bathroom forever. 

so please......PLEASE (if that&#39;s not the magic word then the only other words i could think of are thank you and your welcome) help me out.

oh and btw...  :eek: I HAVE BEEN LOCKED AWAY IN THE DOWNLOAD SECTION ALL LAST NIGHT!!! GOOGLE DOESN&#39;T HELP AND NETIHER DOES YAHOO, ASK, SILABSOFT, OR google OR EVEN GOD HIM SELF( sorry bro...) EVEN THE SEARCH ENGINE ON THIS SITE IS FUTILE FAIL! (if i type 474 source in the moparscape search engine nothing comes up)  :eek:  :(  :mad:

 :confused: help please... if you can. please  :confused:

thank you in advance  :| (&lt;--- that advanced thank you is for people who actually do something... not just post links like google.com or &quot;lmgtfy&quot;)  :|


edit: ok things come up on this website about 474&#39;s. BUT THEY ARE ALL questions or tuts or anything but good downloads.. and all the downloads i have are crap and too hard to edit so i need 377-417.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 26 Apr 2009 17:46:24 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/can-some-one-suggest-something-to-me/275761.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Can some one suggest something to me?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@grayfoxx grayfoxx]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/grayfoxx">@grayfoxx</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>READ. please don’t be afraid to read all of this. i know it looks like alot to read, but its not <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/smiley.png?v=6" title=":smiley:" class="emoji" alt=":smiley:"></p>
<p>hi moparscape server owners and kick “a” players,<br>
I need to know what is the best server source and client that is in the range of 377(higher then 317)-417(not 474).</p>
<p>I really would like to know because I love all the cool features but some of them are too complicated for my lil’ brain to understand. like how the files in 474 are all scrambled gives me a head ache, but the way 317 frames look on the client and the way their graphics look with stupid items also makes me wana stay in the bathroom forever.</p>
<p>so please…PLEASE (if that’s not the magic word then the only other words i could think of are thank you and your welcome) help me out.</p>
<p>oh and btw…  :eek: I HAVE BEEN LOCKED AWAY IN THE DOWNLOAD SECTION ALL LAST NIGHT!!! GOOGLE DOESN’T HELP AND NETIHER DOES YAHOO, ASK, SILABSOFT, OR google OR EVEN GOD HIM SELF( sorry bro…) EVEN THE SEARCH ENGINE ON THIS SITE IS FUTILE FAIL! (if i type 474 source in the moparscape search engine nothing comes up)  :eek:  <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/frowning.png?v=6" title=":frowning:" class="emoji" alt=":frowning:">  :mad:</p>
<p><img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/confused.png?v=6" title=":confused:" class="emoji" alt=":confused:"> help please… if you can. please  <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/confused.png?v=6" title=":confused:" class="emoji" alt=":confused:"></p>
<p>thank you in advance  <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/expressionless.png?v=6" title=":expressionless:" class="emoji" alt=":expressionless:"> (&lt;— that advanced thank you is for people who actually do something… not just post links like <a href="http://google.com" rel="nofollow noopener">google.com</a> or “lmgtfy”)  <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/expressionless.png?v=6" title=":expressionless:" class="emoji" alt=":expressionless:"></p>
<p>edit: ok things come up on this website about 474’s. BUT THEY ARE ALL questions or tuts or anything but good downloads… and all the downloads i have are crap and too hard to edit so i need 377-417.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/can-some-one-suggest-something-to-me/275761/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/can-some-one-suggest-something-to-me/275761/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 26 Apr 2009 17:46:24 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-275761-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/can-some-one-suggest-something-to-me/275761.rss">Can some one suggest something to me?</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
