<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>[Game?] Post your story:</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/game-post-your-story/37780</link>
    <description>[b]Intro:[/b]
As you are reading this you should keep in mind, I cherish leadership and respectability. I can never seem to achieve the amount of respect I should so desire, as you will read later on. Most of the things I do, I do to gain respect: (About 600 posts here, am an SRL member, was a &#39;veteran member&#39; on RS2 Cheating, which is like a CM here). Keep that in mind while I tell you my frazziling and dazziling story of:

[glow=red,2,300]HOW I BECAME AKRIAM![/glow]


[b]My Past: [/b]

Well, were to begin. Let us see, ah yes, when I started playing a little game many of you may know as RuneScape. Two years back my friend (g00dg0d) found this game, and introduced it to my class. I did not believe that there could be such a thing as an &#39;online game&#39;, so he proved me wrong. He showed it to me and I instantly fell in love. I played and played, and when I was about level 35 I became a RuneScape Member. I had not yet taken of the name Akriam.

[b]My Days as a RUNESCAPE MEMBER:[/b]

Not long after I became a RuneScape member, me and Ariethe started a clan. We were both about level 35, so it was nothing impressive. We posted our thread on the RS Forums and waited, and waited, and waited some more. When finally, a person named Gae Nicca posted on our thread. She/He agreed to join. Not longer after that level 80&#39;s and 90&#39;s were also joining. The clan &#39;Dragoon Knights&#39; had flourished. We had 93 members at our peak. The RS Clan board is probably the most active out of all the &#39;non-sale&#39; boards. I was even recognized in game. Many people came up to me (suprized at my level) and said &#39;WOW you are the leader of DK?&#39; Soon after our clan was at its height, I was ranked the #1 Up and coming (21st overall) clan leader, and my clan was ranked 6th up and coming (26th overall) best clan. I feel it was a real achievement because I proved even if you are not a high rank/level you can still be important, as I only reached level 63 on that account which I still have today. Awile after I bought my one of my clan members accounts (as he had a started a new one). I still have that account today also.

[b]THE NAME:[/b]

I can not remember exactly when, but I decided to create and account name &#39;Akriam****&#39;, the main character from a book I had just written. He was to be a great account. I mainly focused on woodcutting, and alot of other non-combat skills. (Don&#39;t search for him in HS, you won&#39;t find the exact name, I am getting him unbanned currently ;) and to all Jagex staff the read this, I don&#39;t auto on that one don&#39;t worry!). I got him to a fairly high levels when I was level 3 or 4 (like 200 overall), when I believe I met Zezima&#39;s only other noob account he has ever made. He mentions it with his interview on Tip.It. He says while his main (Zezima) was trapped in a cave, he created a new account and only got it to level 9. The account I met was called workingto99 and had AMAZING stats, and also she (yes it was a girl account) mentioned being friends with Zezima.

[b]Cheating:[/b]

Yep, as every RS noob does, they search for RuneScape hacks on google. After handing out a level 3&#39;s username and pass to many various people, I quit searching for hacks, untill I found a program called IonDuper (something like that). It actually worked once (but on Classic :(). This led me to believe there was some way of cheating, and so, I stumbled upon Sythe.org. I registered under the name Akriam Rohme. After searching there, I found Kaitnieks, and after looking at the private server section I was determend to learn more. I came here. Miss Silabsoft helped me through my early days, and I got the URMTE code for spawning objects started, though I did not actually code it. After alot more posting, and alot more time here I am typing this. And the rest is history (err....I think you guys should know who I am by now ;D).

[b]
Today:[/b]

I dressed up as a wisemen for my Christmas Program, and earned the nickname &#39;The Pimp of the Orient&#39; as I was wearing a paper crown and a purple robe/dress. I may post a picture later  ;D


That&#39;s my story post yours!</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 25 Dec 2006 00:36:26 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>General Discussion</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/game-post-your-story/37780.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>[Game?] Post your story:</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Akriam Akriam]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/akriam">@Akriam</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Cool, everyone else post also <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=6" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"> The un-named, lol, I actually always wondered about your name <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=6" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/game-post-your-story/37780/8">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/game-post-your-story/37780/8</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 25 Dec 2006 00:36:26 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-37780-8</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/game-post-your-story/37780.rss">[Game?] Post your story:</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Game?] Post your story:</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@The_Un-Named The Un-Named]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/the_un-named">@The_Un-Named</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p><span class="bbcode-b">Intro:</span></p>
<p>Hi.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">My Past: </span></p>
<p>Started RS about 3 weeks before elemental workshop quest, tried selling my acc on rs, got scammed, got banned, recoerd the level 54 account and ditched it for the existing 81 I made to replace it.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">My Days as a RUNESCAPE MEMBER:</span></p>
<p>I made a clan also for rangers,  not specifically pure as I was still in my ‘green period’ of my new acc and had def. Eww. Did this, that, this, got bored, hardly play, auto this, that. Give up.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">THE NAME:</span></p>
<p>I got flamed on Sythe for having zezima as an acc name(some shit about zezima would never auto). No name = no flame.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Cheating:</span></p>
<p>Well I joined Kaitnieks about 2 weeks before Aryan. Before that I had I was at the many forum mixes of RuneScapeCPS or something, there last known site was EliteScape.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Today:</span></p>
<p>Today I stick around on mopar, do some SCAR, complain about the cold on all nighters, drink coffee, eat, and all the uhh human stuff.</p>
<p>PS, I can still play RSC.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/game-post-your-story/37780/7">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/game-post-your-story/37780/7</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 24 Dec 2006 22:51:24 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-37780-7</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/game-post-your-story/37780.rss">[Game?] Post your story:</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Game?] Post your story:</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Hex_Key Hex Key]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/hex_key">@Hex_Key</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Nicks auto fighter was the bomb, dont diss that shit</p>
<p>&lt;3 Mopman</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/game-post-your-story/37780/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/game-post-your-story/37780/6</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 22 Dec 2006 05:48:48 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-37780-6</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/game-post-your-story/37780.rss">[Game?] Post your story:</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Game?] Post your story:</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Akriam Akriam]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/akriam">@Akriam</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Cool stories everyone, I had a fun time reading them all. Keep posting <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=6" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/game-post-your-story/37780/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/game-post-your-story/37780/5</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 22 Dec 2006 04:30:17 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-37780-5</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/game-post-your-story/37780.rss">[Game?] Post your story:</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Game?] Post your story:</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@haody haody]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/haody">@haody</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>… lol …</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/game-post-your-story/37780/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/game-post-your-story/37780/4</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Dec 2006 23:22:21 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-37780-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/game-post-your-story/37780.rss">[Game?] Post your story:</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Game?] Post your story:</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Mopman Mopman]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/mopman">@Mopman</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p><span class="bbcode-b">Intro</span><br>
Yeah I copied that layout too. Sue me.<br>
I am Mopman, hear me rawrrr… playfully, like a sexy… kitten?</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">The Past</span><br>
Er… 6? 5? Years ago… possibly less, I have no real sense of time. High school was boring, found Runescape somehow and got to like level 20, got a few mates into it and we wasted all of our evenings for a year or two. All was good in Mopman-land. Until I realised, they were better than me at the game, which led to…</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Cheating</span><br>
So, I googled for hax. The first I found was a small app by the name of NICKS AUTOMINER. It was hardcore shit, seriously. I never really autoed with it properly, mainly because it was a pile of wank, think I did get a few mining levels with it though.</p>
<p>Next I found out about the existance of Autorune and possibly Runebot, although my sense of time is skewed, Runebot may have been earlier/later, but eitherway I heard about them both and knew I’d never get them, which led to the discovery of SCAR. Happily auto’d with that for a bit (other peoples scripts obviously ;)) until fatigue, when i left for a bit and then came back when it was gotten around (sleepwalker). The rest is pretty much boring, but I will add that g0ne and sean were cunts to me in those days, and my 13 year old self hated them with all its heart.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">The Name</span><br>
Self-explanatory:</p>
<p><img src="http://myspace-266.vo.llnwd.net/00836/66/25/836375266_l.jpg" alt width="" height=""><br>
<span class="bbcode-b">Today</span><br>
Today I woke up at 12pm, ate a burger, spent the rest of the day drinking coffee on IRC, and it’s now 5am and I’m about to go to bed.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/game-post-your-story/37780/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/game-post-your-story/37780/3</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Dec 2006 10:33:16 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-37780-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/game-post-your-story/37780.rss">[Game?] Post your story:</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Game?] Post your story:</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@pookey71 Pookey71]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/pookey71">@pookey71</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p><span class="bbcode-b">Intro:</span><br>
As you are reading this you this you are probably thinking “Omfg he stole Akriam layout” Then you are correct,i was to lazy to make my own.<br>
Well you are wondering how i am the Fable Creature of the net called Pookey71!<br>
Read on.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">My Past: </span><br>
Well it all started 2 years ago.I was a 10 year old…I was just discovering the net.One day a older kid (We where in a mixed 5/6 class) was talking to me,he was like "Omfg i saw this pimping game"I was like "What is it?"He said these 2 words that brought me here today,they where “Runescape” I was amazed at Runescape…So i joined.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">THE NAME:</span><br>
Well while waiting for runescape to come up (We hade Dial up) I was reading Garfield ( <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=6" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"> ) I was reading a particular skit. Odie hade Pooky in his mouth…Garfield comes up and says “How dare you treat pooky like this” thus following to Pimpslap Odie. I was laughing as a joke i searched Pooky.They didn’t have it.I saw Pookey71.I thought easy to say and it looks cool (H).That is how I came about. (Not born but my Online Life )</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">The Quest:</span><br>
I guess what fueled my obbsesive Runescape playing was becuase i was getting bullied.Severly,it was my E-Home,no one Judge me or anything.I liked it.I wasn’t a “Money Making” type person,but jesus did i have good skills.My time is Runescape was a well spent one…I was in a <span class="bbcode-b">Very</span> Succesful clan (Australian one) I then started my own with a friend (Cheese939) It was called A&amp;Z Drunken Fishes…It didn’t go far <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/expressionless.png?v=6" title=":expressionless:" class="emoji" alt=":expressionless:"> But i learnt a valuble lesson.Runescape was blinding me.I was still getting bullied.But i was getting sick of Runescape.Lucky my Primary school years finished.I was now the school Holidays.I played Runescape for AGES…Everyday…I started Highschool.I never spoke a word of Runescape.Lucky i didn’t get bullied in those few months.In around June i found “Moparscape” on Youtube…I was Amazed i searched for days for the website (It was <span class="bbcode-b">Really</span> hard Becuase you guys where comming here.I finnaly found it.As a noob i was amazed.So i join.Tryed to code and failed <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/expressionless.png?v=6" title=":expressionless:" class="emoji" alt=":expressionless:"> Computer got fried…And i was without a computer for 3 months (I think)I was getting a social life ( I was amazed i got Invited to a party :O)So i came back coded Pookeyscape and then left Moparscape…</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b"><br>
Today:</span></p>
<p>I made 10 Different sigs…Called my self Pimp acouple time.Was told to go down the skatepark.But wasn’t aloud <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/expressionless.png?v=6" title=":expressionless:" class="emoji" alt=":expressionless:"> Got Acdc and Gorillazz Albums.Got told i was Pimping…Then wrote this <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/smiley.png?v=6" title=":smiley:" class="emoji" alt=":smiley:"></p>
<p>PS.Some stuff said here maynot be real in past <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/expressionless.png?v=6" title=":expressionless:" class="emoji" alt=":expressionless:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/game-post-your-story/37780/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/game-post-your-story/37780/2</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Dec 2006 09:45:35 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-37780-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/game-post-your-story/37780.rss">[Game?] Post your story:</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Game?] Post your story:</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Akriam Akriam]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/akriam">@Akriam</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p><span class="bbcode-b">Intro:</span><br>
As you are reading this you should keep in mind, I cherish leadership and respectability. I can never seem to achieve the amount of respect I should so desire, as you will read later on. Most of the things I do, I do to gain respect: (About 600 posts here, am an SRL member, was a ‘veteran member’ on RS2 Cheating, which is like a CM here). Keep that in mind while I tell you my frazziling and dazziling story of:</p>
<p>[glow=red,2,300]HOW I BECAME AKRIAM![/glow]</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">My Past: </span></p>
<p>Well, were to begin. Let us see, ah yes, when I started playing a little game many of you may know as RuneScape. Two years back my friend (g00dg0d) found this game, and introduced it to my class. I did not believe that there could be such a thing as an ‘online game’, so he proved me wrong. He showed it to me and I instantly fell in love. I played and played, and when I was about level 35 I became a RuneScape Member. I had not yet taken of the name Akriam.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">My Days as a RUNESCAPE MEMBER:</span></p>
<p>Not long after I became a RuneScape member, me and Ariethe started a clan. We were both about level 35, so it was nothing impressive. We posted our thread on the RS Forums and waited, and waited, and waited some more. When finally, a person named Gae Nicca posted on our thread. She/He agreed to join. Not longer after that level 80’s and 90’s were also joining. The clan ‘Dragoon Knights’ had flourished. We had 93 members at our peak. The RS Clan board is probably the most active out of all the ‘non-sale’ boards. I was even recognized in game. Many people came up to me (suprized at my level) and said ‘WOW you are the leader of DK?’ Soon after our clan was at its height, I was ranked the <span class="hashtag">#1</span> Up and coming (21st overall) clan leader, and my clan was ranked 6th up and coming (26th overall) best clan. I feel it was a real achievement because I proved even if you are not a high rank/level you can still be important, as I only reached level 63 on that account which I still have today. Awile after I bought my one of my clan members accounts (as he had a started a new one). I still have that account today also.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">THE NAME:</span></p>
<p>I can not remember exactly when, but I decided to create and account name ‘Akriam****’, the main character from a book I had just written. He was to be a great account. I mainly focused on woodcutting, and alot of other non-combat skills. (Don’t search for him in HS, you won’t find the exact name, I am getting him unbanned currently <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/wink.png?v=6" title=":wink:" class="emoji" alt=":wink:"> and to all Jagex staff the read this, I don’t auto on that one don’t worry!). I got him to a fairly high levels when I was level 3 or 4 (like 200 overall), when I believe I met Zezima’s only other noob account he has ever made. He mentions it with his interview on Tip.It. He says while his main (Zezima) was trapped in a cave, he created a new account and only got it to level 9. The account I met was called workingto99 and had AMAZING stats, and also she (yes it was a girl account) mentioned being friends with Zezima.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Cheating:</span></p>
<p>Yep, as every RS noob does, they search for RuneScape hacks on google. After handing out a level 3’s username and pass to many various people, I quit searching for hacks, untill I found a program called IonDuper (something like that). It actually worked once (but on Classic :(). This led me to believe there was some way of cheating, and so, I stumbled upon <a href="http://Sythe.org" rel="nofollow noopener">Sythe.org</a>. I registered under the name Akriam Rohme. After searching there, I found Kaitnieks, and after looking at the private server section I was determend to learn more. I came here. Miss Silabsoft helped me through my early days, and I got the URMTE code for spawning objects started, though I did not actually code it. After alot more posting, and alot more time here I am typing this. And the rest is history (err…I think you guys should know who I am by now ;D).</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b"><br>
Today:</span></p>
<p>I dressed up as a wisemen for my Christmas Program, and earned the nickname ‘The Pimp of the Orient’ as I was wearing a paper crown and a purple robe/dress. I may post a picture later  ;D</p>
<p>That’s my story post yours!</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/game-post-your-story/37780/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/game-post-your-story/37780/1</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Dec 2006 09:24:09 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-37780-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/game-post-your-story/37780.rss">[Game?] Post your story:</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
