<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>[PHP] Introduction to MySQLi [PHP]</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/php-introduction-to-mysqli-php/461307</link>
    <description>Okay, so since everyone&#39;s became a huge faggot about people who aren&#39;t using MySQLi or PDO when contacting databases I thought I&#39;d teach you all my way.

If you&#39;d like to take a look at an introduction to PDO, take a look at [url=http://skyrealm.net/smf/index.php/topic,7514.0.html]Orpheus&#39;s tutorial[/url] on it.

I choose mysqli as my choice because I believe it&#39;s better than PDO, PDO has multi driver support which is a huge advantage but I think that MySQLi totally outweighs it otherwise. Without further ado, here is my MySQLi introduction.

[b]Part 1 - Declaring Variables &amp; Connecting.[/b]
Okay, so this is only 5 lines of code as it is if you were using mysql_connect(). However, this is MySQLimproved so we&#39;ll take a look.
[code=php]
$database = &quot;tutorial&quot;;
$user = &quot;ruby&quot;;
$pass = &quot;password&quot;;
$server = &quot;localhost&quot;;

$con = new mysqli($server, $user, $pass, $database);
[/code]
As usual you&#39;re just declaring four variables, one holding the database name, the username, the password and the server it&#39;s hosted on. We&#39;re then declaring $con which holds the connection. This is only telling PHP to initiate a new mysqli connection using $server, $user, $pass and $database.

Simple enough, right? All you have to do is replace mysql_connect with new mysqli.

[b]Part 2 - Running a Query[/b]
Okay, so this is similar to the conventional ways but there&#39;s a few changes, take a look.
[code=php]
$query = $con-&gt;prepare(&quot;SELECT * FROM `something` LIMIT 5&quot;);
$result = $con-&gt;query($query);
[/code]
All we&#39;re doing here is showing that $query is our mysql statement which would be entered as usual. $result is only saying that $con has to send the query held in $query. Not too difficult, right?

[b]Part 3 - Echoing the Query.[/b]
This is a little different than  the conventional method as with everything is, but does the same job. Lets take a look.
[code=php]
if($result-&gt;num_rows &gt; 0) {
while($row = $result-&gt;fetch_assoc()) {
echo htmlspecialchars($row[&#39;username&#39;]);	
   }
}
else {
echo &#39;Empty table.&#39;;	
}
$con-&gt;close();
[/code]

Okay, so this is merely just saying that if there is more than 0 rows in the database initiate a while loop and gain all of the rows from the mysql database. If there is 0 rows in the database echo an error message. We then close the connection.

[b]Part 4 - Preparing Statements[/b]
In this part of the tutorial we will cover preparing statements in order to insert them into a database. Here&#39;s the code:
[code=php]
    if ($stmt = $con-&gt;prepare(&quot;INSERT INTO `users` VALUES($username, $email, $message)&quot;) ) {
        $stmt-&gt;bind_param(&quot;sss&quot;, $username, $email, $message);
        $stmt-&gt;execute();
        $stmt-&gt;close();
    } else {
        echo &#39;error preparing statement&#39;;
    }
[/code]

Okay, so  to start this off we&#39;re opening and if statement and declaring $stmt as our statement variable. We then prepare the statement using $con-&gt;prepare which prepares our statement. we then bind the parameters of our statement, executing the statement and closing the statement. If this fails, it&#39;ll echo the error message &quot;error preparing statement&quot;.

It&#39;s as simple as that. Use it or don&#39;t, it&#39;s up to you :).</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 22 Sep 2012 12:05:16 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>General Programming</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/php-introduction-to-mysqli-php/461307.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>[PHP] Introduction to MySQLi [PHP]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Ruby_Forums_Coder Ruby]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/ruby_forums_coder">@Ruby_Forums_Coder</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Okay, so since everyone’s became a huge faggot about people who aren’t using MySQLi or PDO when contacting databases I thought I’d teach you all my way.</p>
<p>If you’d like to take a look at an introduction to PDO, take a look at <a href="http://skyrealm.net/smf/index.php/topic,7514.0.html" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">Orpheus’s tutorial</a> on it.</p>
<p>I choose mysqli as my choice because I believe it’s better than PDO, PDO has multi driver support which is a huge advantage but I think that MySQLi totally outweighs it otherwise. Without further ado, here is my MySQLi introduction.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Part 1 - Declaring Variables &amp; Connecting.</span><br>
Okay, so this is only 5 lines of code as it is if you were using mysql_connect(). However, this is MySQLimproved so we’ll take a look.</p>
<pre><code class="lang-auto">$database = "tutorial";
$user = "ruby";
$pass = "password";
$server = "localhost";

$con = new mysqli($server, $user, $pass, $database);</code></pre>
<p>As usual you’re just declaring four variables, one holding the database name, the username, the password and the server it’s hosted on. We’re then declaring $con which holds the connection. This is only telling PHP to initiate a new mysqli connection using $server, $user, $pass and $database.</p>
<p>Simple enough, right? All you have to do is replace mysql_connect with new mysqli.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Part 2 - Running a Query</span><br>
Okay, so this is similar to the conventional ways but there’s a few changes, take a look.</p>
<pre><code class="lang-auto">$query = $con-&gt;prepare("SELECT * FROM `something` LIMIT 5");
$result = $con-&gt;query($query);</code></pre>
<p>All we’re doing here is showing that $query is our mysql statement which would be entered as usual. $result is only saying that $con has to send the query held in $query. Not too difficult, right?</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Part 3 - Echoing the Query.</span><br>
This is a little different than  the conventional method as with everything is, but does the same job. Lets take a look.</p>
<pre><code class="lang-auto">if($result-&gt;num_rows &gt; 0) {
while($row = $result-&gt;fetch_assoc()) {
echo htmlspecialchars($row['username']);	
   }
}
else {
echo 'Empty table.';	
}
$con-&gt;close();</code></pre>
<p>Okay, so this is merely just saying that if there is more than 0 rows in the database initiate a while loop and gain all of the rows from the mysql database. If there is 0 rows in the database echo an error message. We then close the connection.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Part 4 - Preparing Statements</span><br>
In this part of the tutorial we will cover preparing statements in order to insert them into a database. Here’s the code:</p>
<pre><code class="lang-auto">    if ($stmt = $con-&gt;prepare("INSERT INTO `users` VALUES($username, $email, $message)") ) {
        $stmt-&gt;bind_param("sss", $username, $email, $message);
        $stmt-&gt;execute();
        $stmt-&gt;close();
    } else {
        echo 'error preparing statement';
    }</code></pre>
<p>Okay, so  to start this off we’re opening and if statement and declaring $stmt as our statement variable. We then prepare the statement using $con-&gt;prepare which prepares our statement. we then bind the parameters of our statement, executing the statement and closing the statement. If this fails, it’ll echo the error message “error preparing statement”.</p>
<p>It’s as simple as that. Use it or don’t, it’s up to you :).</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/php-introduction-to-mysqli-php/461307/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/php-introduction-to-mysqli-php/461307/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 22 Sep 2012 12:05:16 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-461307-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/php-introduction-to-mysqli-php/461307.rss">[PHP] Introduction to MySQLi [PHP]</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
