<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>&lt;&gt;L2Merch&lt;&gt;</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/l2merch/384160</link>
    <description>If you find a flaw let me know  :rolleyes:

Still not done.

[center][size=12pt][b]L2Merch[/b][/size][/center]
[center][b]Made by : MarketExpert[/b][/center]


[center][b]..::Basic Intro::..[/b][/center]
Merchanting or &quot;merching&quot; is hands down the best way to make money in runescape. Why? Because you can easily make 1mill by only being logged in 5 minutes out of the day. This guide is going to show you exactly what to look for in the market and how to use it to your advantage.


[center][b]..::The Basics::..[/b][/center]
Every time you attempt a merch there are a few things you should do. 

[b]Study the specific item[/b] - Using the GE Database allows you to look at the item graphs over the last 30 - 90 - 180 day period. You not only going to want to find an item that is about to rise but really your going to want to look at the IMPORTANCE of an item. Many people don&#39;t realize what wine of zamorak is for. (It is for Herblore).


[b]Look for events[/b] - Is a double exp weekend about to occur? Is the wildy being re-opened or shutdown? Is a new skill about to arise!? These are events that can make an extreme sway in the market. Looking at before the wild was re-opened the price of pvp items went up. A lot of people thought they were making the smart decision by trying to merch lobsters! When really everyone had them all dumping them into the market at once caused them to drop 100gp. Which brings us to our next basic rule.


[b]Item Population[/b] - I try to avoid items that are extremely common in the world. For example willow logs. So many of them are in the game that they really are not going anywhere. Occasionally they may make a move but honestly its not much of a merch. If the item is extremely common the best way to go is with p2p items. Such as maples and pure essence. (Maples are f2p now, I know.)


[b]Be confident!!![/b] - If you are scared of losing your money this is not for you. To get behind some big merch opportunities your going to need some guts and confidence. I really would not see why anybody would lack confidence because it is only pixels.


[b]Do not put all of your eggs in the same basket![/b] - Dumping all your money into one specific item is very risky and not not advised unless you know what you are doing. If you put your money into 10 items and 5/5 items rise you really have a better chance of making money. If you dump all your money into one item and that item fails your stuck with that item and it is only going to continue to drop! Statistically it is just better if you don&#39;t dump all your money into one item. Ill explain more if necessary. 


[b]&quot;Chain Reactions&quot;[/b] - If you see that all the ores jump on one day but yet the bars did nothing or fell your going to see a chain reaction. Ores turn into bars so the items relate. You will have a pretty good chance of making money if you buy into the bars. Another scenario is one that I took advantage of recently. If you see rune essence fall hard but all f2p runes are rising. What do you think? Obviously it allows for f2p players to make some cash so they are going to buy rune essence. Be sure to watch the runes to see if they continue to rise or fall! It may just let you know what you do with that starting item.

[b]Patience Young Padawan[/b] - Most of the time your going to be doing merchs that last anywhere from 1 hour to 24 hours. If your all over the place you may just be out of the merch. There are so many times I see people buy an item for 100gp and yet 20 minutes later sell it for 95 gp just so they can say abort. Yea its 5gp... but if you have 10k of them item that is 50k and every loser who is sitting there doing is feeding some kid on the other end 50k a swap. This goes back to being confident and studying that specific item!


[b]Stay away from &quot;Merch Clans[/b]&quot; - Obviously you should not be part of them because they work on a pyramid scheme. Meaning that the leader buys the item weeks before and he sells it to all the followers so that they have to deal with the item why he collects. Also make sure to look at merch clans so you can avoid there item and look into items that relate to their item! Chain Reaction advantage! Oh not to mention merch clans are run by 12 year old kiddies.


[center][b]..::Types of Markets::..[/b][/center]
I really do not know what to name these as I believe I am the first to write about them. Anyways, the runescape market fluctuates based on the time of year. I am not going to go full detail into this because I am still studying this specific subject.

[b]WTF is going on market[/b] - This is the most recent one. When Jagex announced the reopening of free trade and the wild it really got to everybody. Nobody could determine what way the market was going to head. Are items going to rise? Wait free trade is opened up maybe gp will be worthless?! This is what happened. When trade limit opened up it allowed for RWT and people with mass amounts of gp wanted to protect their networth. So they dropped all their items and bought into rares. Rares are like gold and silver IRL. When stocks are down people dump their cash into gold. Anyways this is a type of market that was caused by Jagex.

[b]Buyers Market[/b]- Here is another type of market which is caused by Jagex through events. Whenever a double exp weekend is put into place... what happens? Everybody starts buying..buying..buying!! Raw materials are where it is at. Anything related to a skill is where people invest. In turn you see combat items lower because of this. People want to take their whips / items and turn them into easy exp. After the buyer market is over look into combat items.

[b]Summer[/b] - When summer comes around it allows for 12 year skiddies to get off school and no life runescape. What are they going to want to do? Something fun of course. Look into items that are appealing for the summer skiddies. I believe Dragon Claws are a good example of a item that jumped up last year around summer.


[center][b]..::Types Of Merchs::..[/b][/center]
This basically explains what type of merch opportunities are available to you and which one is best for you.

[b]Long Term[/b] - If you believe your item is going to rise in the future, meaning months to years a long term merch is best for you. The most obvious example of a long term merch is rares. As they are discontinued they are bound to go.

[b]Short Term[/b] - This is usually based on a few day to a week. Buying an item and sticking to it for a few days hoping for the best outcome.

[b]Hit &amp; Quit[/b] - These are my personal favorite merch types. Buying into an item for one day only and having it jump and immediately getting out of the item the following day. Yes you could make more money if you do a short term investment but I like to hit it and quit it.

[b]&quot;Filtering&quot;[/b] - This is where the cash is at. Buy an item below value and sell it at mid or even above the price. If you can&#39;t buy below mid try buying at mid and selling for over. This acts like a filter if you have enough money to manipulate the item because your buying at mid. No matter what people will have to wait in line behind you to grab that item. They won&#39;t want to waste their time so they will spend the extra few GP. Great example is what I did with chaos runes. Bought them at mid and sold for 2gp over.. yea 2gp but if you filter 500k of that item in a day it comes to be 1mill gp.

[center][b]..::Tricks::..[/b][/center]

[b]Make Money On A Falling Item[/b] - You do not have to make money on items that are rising! If your skilling, lets say smithing and you see that coal is about to drop hugely.. why not sell the coal you have right now and re-buy it when it levels out? Say it is 250gp and you sell it, and you buy it at 200gp. You just got a free coal for every 4 coal you sold! Which if you have 4k coal basically allows you to have 1k free coal lolololol. :D</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 19 Mar 2011 16:12:23 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/l2merch/384160.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>&lt;&gt;L2Merch&lt;&gt;</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@arham_4 arham 4]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/arham_4">@arham_4</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Nice details</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/l2merch/384160/23">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/l2merch/384160/23</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 19 Mar 2011 16:12:23 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-384160-23</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/l2merch/384160.rss">&lt;&gt;L2Merch&lt;&gt;</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>&lt;&gt;L2Merch&lt;&gt;</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@chassy13 Chassy13]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/chassy13">@chassy13</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote" data-post="20" data-topic="384160">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 Miss Silabsoft:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>in theory too many people merchanting one item would lower profits and possibly cause the item to bubble pop. However people forget that the grand exchange links ALL CHARACTERS ACROSS EVERY SERVER meaning that all items are traded in large quantities daily.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>This is true, but there also has to be a lot of people selling the item. Most items won’t have a problem but if the item I was doing a few days ago was leaked and many people we buying them, it would slow way down.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/l2merch/384160/22">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/l2merch/384160/22</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 28 Feb 2011 05:56:23 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-384160-22</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/l2merch/384160.rss">&lt;&gt;L2Merch&lt;&gt;</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>&lt;&gt;L2Merch&lt;&gt;</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@IlikeArrays IlikeArrays]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/ilikearrays">@IlikeArrays</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I will occasionally release some good opportunities. A few people have received some over pm. Also my cc “marketexpert” the clan title is the item I recommend (If I am not doing it) usually suggest 3 items a week so yea.</p>
<p>In my past experiences if you are doing an item keep it to yourself as you will earn more money.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/l2merch/384160/21">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/l2merch/384160/21</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 28 Feb 2011 05:48:51 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-384160-21</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/l2merch/384160.rss">&lt;&gt;L2Merch&lt;&gt;</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>&lt;&gt;L2Merch&lt;&gt;</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@silabsoft RuneAgent]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/silabsoft">@silabsoft</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“k0 twin, post:19, topic:384160”][quote author=Chassy13 link=topic=479922.msg3514636#msg3514636 date=1298863027]</p>
<aside class="quote">
<blockquote>
<p>Nice job <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=5" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"></p>
<p>People should post what they are currently having success with merching here. Help each other out.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Bad idea unless it’s a huge bulk item.<br>
[/quote]<br>
Why…?[/quote]<br>
in theory too many people merchanting one item would lower profits and possibly cause the item to bubble pop. However people forget that the grand exchange links ALL CHARACTERS ACROSS EVERY SERVER meaning that all items are traded in large quantities daily.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/l2merch/384160/20">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/l2merch/384160/20</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 28 Feb 2011 05:37:24 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-384160-20</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/l2merch/384160.rss">&lt;&gt;L2Merch&lt;&gt;</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>&lt;&gt;L2Merch&lt;&gt;</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@k0_twin k0 twin]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/k0_twin">@k0_twin</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“Chassy13, post:18, topic:384160”][quote author=k0 twin link=topic=479922.msg3514628#msg3514628 date=1298862484]<br>
Nice job <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=5" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"></p>
<p>People should post what they are currently having success with merching here. Help each other out.<br>
[/quote]</p>
<p>Bad idea unless it’s a huge bulk item.[/quote]<br>
Why…?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/l2merch/384160/19">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/l2merch/384160/19</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 28 Feb 2011 05:25:57 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-384160-19</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/l2merch/384160.rss">&lt;&gt;L2Merch&lt;&gt;</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>&lt;&gt;L2Merch&lt;&gt;</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@chassy13 Chassy13]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/chassy13">@chassy13</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“k0 twin, post:17, topic:384160”]Nice job <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=5" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"></p>
<p>People should post what they are currently having success with merching here. Help each other out.[/quote]</p>
<p>Bad idea unless it’s a huge bulk item.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/l2merch/384160/18">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/l2merch/384160/18</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 28 Feb 2011 03:17:07 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-384160-18</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/l2merch/384160.rss">&lt;&gt;L2Merch&lt;&gt;</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>&lt;&gt;L2Merch&lt;&gt;</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@k0_twin k0 twin]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/k0_twin">@k0_twin</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Nice job <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=5" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"></p>
<p>People should post what they are currently having success with merching here. Help each other out.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/l2merch/384160/17">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/l2merch/384160/17</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 28 Feb 2011 03:08:04 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-384160-17</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/l2merch/384160.rss">&lt;&gt;L2Merch&lt;&gt;</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>&lt;&gt;L2Merch&lt;&gt;</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@reyx7 reyx7]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/reyx7">@reyx7</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote" data-post="14" data-topic="384160">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/thug-life/40/5_e05bb34c421432ee4d40de30c10af3e5.png" class="avatar"> Thug-life:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>It is not only pixels. It is time and effort.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Ok, lets say you log on to your account and everything is gone.<br>
What are you going to be doing one month later? Earning it back or greiving?</p>
<p>Nice guide btw.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/l2merch/384160/16">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/l2merch/384160/16</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 28 Feb 2011 02:19:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-384160-16</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/l2merch/384160.rss">&lt;&gt;L2Merch&lt;&gt;</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>&lt;&gt;L2Merch&lt;&gt;</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@n10si_t n10si t]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/n10si_t">@n10si_t</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote" data-post="14" data-topic="384160">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/thug-life/40/5_e05bb34c421432ee4d40de30c10af3e5.png" class="avatar"> Thug-life:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>It is not only pixels. It is time and effort.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>BLOOD SWEAT TEARS</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/l2merch/384160/15">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/l2merch/384160/15</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 28 Feb 2011 02:16:37 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-384160-15</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/l2merch/384160.rss">&lt;&gt;L2Merch&lt;&gt;</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>&lt;&gt;L2Merch&lt;&gt;</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@tL tL]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/tl">@tL</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>It is not only pixels. It is time and effort.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/l2merch/384160/14">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/l2merch/384160/14</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 28 Feb 2011 02:12:40 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-384160-14</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/l2merch/384160.rss">&lt;&gt;L2Merch&lt;&gt;</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>&lt;&gt;L2Merch&lt;&gt;</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Andrew_Ferguson The317Guy]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/andrew_ferguson">@Andrew_Ferguson</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Looks like someone stole L2Merch from me lol <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/wink.png?v=5" title=":wink:" class="emoji" alt=":wink:"> (Live to merch)</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/l2merch/384160/13">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/l2merch/384160/13</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 28 Feb 2011 01:19:50 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-384160-13</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/l2merch/384160.rss">&lt;&gt;L2Merch&lt;&gt;</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>&lt;&gt;L2Merch&lt;&gt;</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@IlikeArrays IlikeArrays]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/ilikearrays">@IlikeArrays</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote quote-modified" data-post="10" data-topic="384160">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/kickingjamie/40/5_e05bb34c421432ee4d40de30c10af3e5.png" class="avatar"> kickingjamie:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>dragon pickaxe right now are perfect. i’ve bought 10 for 8.9m each and now they are rising again to there normal 10-11m. happy days.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>No. They were perfect 2 weeks ago.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/l2merch/384160/12">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/l2merch/384160/12</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 27 Feb 2011 23:29:49 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-384160-12</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/l2merch/384160.rss">&lt;&gt;L2Merch&lt;&gt;</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>&lt;&gt;L2Merch&lt;&gt;</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@ranger_squad ranger squad]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/ranger_squad">@ranger_squad</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I’m still unsure about WHAT items to filter :S</p>
<p>If you could pm me a tip, I’d be grateful <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/smiley.png?v=5" title=":smiley:" class="emoji" alt=":smiley:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/l2merch/384160/11">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/l2merch/384160/11</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 27 Feb 2011 22:57:28 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-384160-11</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/l2merch/384160.rss">&lt;&gt;L2Merch&lt;&gt;</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>&lt;&gt;L2Merch&lt;&gt;</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@kickingjamie kickingjamie]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/kickingjamie">@kickingjamie</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>dragon pickaxe right now are perfect. i’ve bought 10 for 8.9m each and now they are rising again to there normal 10-11m. happy days.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/l2merch/384160/10">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/l2merch/384160/10</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 27 Feb 2011 22:19:08 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-384160-10</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/l2merch/384160.rss">&lt;&gt;L2Merch&lt;&gt;</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>&lt;&gt;L2Merch&lt;&gt;</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@IlikeArrays IlikeArrays]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/ilikearrays">@IlikeArrays</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>^<br>
Rubies  <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/wink.png?v=5" title=":wink:" class="emoji" alt=":wink:"></p>
<p>Reminds me to post the “Filtering Technique”</p>
<p>Oh, I kept onto my falling item recently… Made a bad decision, well I went 15:1  (15 great items vs 1 bad decision) and I decided to hold onto it. Double exp weekend was announced and now 4 days later I am in for the big!</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/l2merch/384160/9">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/l2merch/384160/9</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 27 Feb 2011 07:20:25 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-384160-9</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/l2merch/384160.rss">&lt;&gt;L2Merch&lt;&gt;</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>&lt;&gt;L2Merch&lt;&gt;</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@silabsoft RuneAgent]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/silabsoft">@silabsoft</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Ive been doing ruby’s for a few weeks now you can i flip 5k ruby’s 3 times a day purchasing at any market price and then selling 10% higher (Making well over 100gp per ruby) do the math :p.</p>
<p>Another thing I find incredibly helpful is I do not hang onto falling items. Recently I purchased some strength potions that started falling I took a loss and sold then for less than I purchased but I also started purchasing them again at a much lower price. Selling the ones that lost me money gave me enough capital to buy more than I originally had due to the price dropping. I was then able to dump at a higher price and turn a profit.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/l2merch/384160/8">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/l2merch/384160/8</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 27 Feb 2011 07:18:20 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-384160-8</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/l2merch/384160.rss">&lt;&gt;L2Merch&lt;&gt;</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>&lt;&gt;L2Merch&lt;&gt;</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@doom_j doom_j]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/doom_j">@doom_j</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I am going to see if I can make rune scimmys drop to less then 15k <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=5" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/l2merch/384160/7">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/l2merch/384160/7</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 27 Feb 2011 03:51:42 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-384160-7</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/l2merch/384160.rss">&lt;&gt;L2Merch&lt;&gt;</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>&lt;&gt;L2Merch&lt;&gt;</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@rip4d rip4d]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/rip4d">@rip4d</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>You should add to the merchanting clans part that they sometimes manipulate items. The leaders will buy the item, but they will have others buy even more, so they will inevitably rise. I’m in a small merching CC regularly, and a while ago we accidentally manipulated dwarf weed o.o (seriously, we saw the chance of a VERY SMALL rise, and we took it. It ended up rising a good 100-150gp :s )</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/l2merch/384160/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/l2merch/384160/6</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 27 Feb 2011 03:46:25 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-384160-6</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/l2merch/384160.rss">&lt;&gt;L2Merch&lt;&gt;</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>&lt;&gt;L2Merch&lt;&gt;</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@doom_j doom_j]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/doom_j">@doom_j</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>lol I fucked up rune scimmys. <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/smiley.png?v=5" title=":smiley:" class="emoji" alt=":smiley:"></p>
<p>300gp taken off in a day… <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=5" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/l2merch/384160/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/l2merch/384160/5</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 27 Feb 2011 03:45:01 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-384160-5</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/l2merch/384160.rss">&lt;&gt;L2Merch&lt;&gt;</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>&lt;&gt;L2Merch&lt;&gt;</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@gravenfire23 gravenfire23]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/gravenfire23">@gravenfire23</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Nice i needed somthing like this</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/l2merch/384160/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/l2merch/384160/4</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 27 Feb 2011 02:45:36 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-384160-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/l2merch/384160.rss">&lt;&gt;L2Merch&lt;&gt;</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>&lt;&gt;L2Merch&lt;&gt;</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@IlikeArrays IlikeArrays]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/ilikearrays">@IlikeArrays</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I still have more to write <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/smiley.png?v=5" title=":smiley:" class="emoji" alt=":smiley:"><br>
After I get the basics out of the way I am going to go into some advanced stuff which will really open your eyes.<br>
Not to mention pictures! Only taking a break now so I can look at it to see if it is appealing to the eyes.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/l2merch/384160/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/l2merch/384160/3</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 27 Feb 2011 02:43:01 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-384160-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/l2merch/384160.rss">&lt;&gt;L2Merch&lt;&gt;</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>&lt;&gt;L2Merch&lt;&gt;</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Cole1497 Cole1497]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/cole1497">@Cole1497</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Thank you for this. I merched yellow dye, though it only raised a bit.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/l2merch/384160/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/l2merch/384160/2</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 27 Feb 2011 02:36:27 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-384160-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/l2merch/384160.rss">&lt;&gt;L2Merch&lt;&gt;</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>&lt;&gt;L2Merch&lt;&gt;</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@IlikeArrays IlikeArrays]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/ilikearrays">@IlikeArrays</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>If you find a flaw let me know  :rolleyes:</p>
<p>Still not done.</p>
<p>[center][size=12pt]<span class="bbcode-b">L2Merch</span>[/size][/center]<br>
[center]<span class="bbcode-b">Made by : MarketExpert</span>[/center]</p>
<p>[center]<span class="bbcode-b">…::Basic Intro::…</span>[/center]<br>
Merchanting or “merching” is hands down the best way to make money in runescape. Why? Because you can easily make 1mill by only being logged in 5 minutes out of the day. This guide is going to show you exactly what to look for in the market and how to use it to your advantage.</p>
<p>[center]<span class="bbcode-b">…::The Basics::…</span>[/center]<br>
Every time you attempt a merch there are a few things you should do.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Study the specific item</span> - Using the GE Database allows you to look at the item graphs over the last 30 - 90 - 180 day period. You not only going to want to find an item that is about to rise but really your going to want to look at the IMPORTANCE of an item. Many people don’t realize what wine of zamorak is for. (It is for Herblore).</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Look for events</span> - Is a double exp weekend about to occur? Is the wildy being re-opened or shutdown? Is a new skill about to arise!? These are events that can make an extreme sway in the market. Looking at before the wild was re-opened the price of pvp items went up. A lot of people thought they were making the smart decision by trying to merch lobsters! When really everyone had them all dumping them into the market at once caused them to drop 100gp. Which brings us to our next basic rule.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Item Population</span> - I try to avoid items that are extremely common in the world. For example willow logs. So many of them are in the game that they really are not going anywhere. Occasionally they may make a move but honestly its not much of a merch. If the item is extremely common the best way to go is with p2p items. Such as maples and pure essence. (Maples are f2p now, I know.)</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Be confident!!!</span> - If you are scared of losing your money this is not for you. To get behind some big merch opportunities your going to need some guts and confidence. I really would not see why anybody would lack confidence because it is only pixels.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Do not put all of your eggs in the same basket!</span> - Dumping all your money into one specific item is very risky and not not advised unless you know what you are doing. If you put your money into 10 items and 5/5 items rise you really have a better chance of making money. If you dump all your money into one item and that item fails your stuck with that item and it is only going to continue to drop! Statistically it is just better if you don’t dump all your money into one item. Ill explain more if necessary.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">“Chain Reactions”</span> - If you see that all the ores jump on one day but yet the bars did nothing or fell your going to see a chain reaction. Ores turn into bars so the items relate. You will have a pretty good chance of making money if you buy into the bars. Another scenario is one that I took advantage of recently. If you see rune essence fall hard but all f2p runes are rising. What do you think? Obviously it allows for f2p players to make some cash so they are going to buy rune essence. Be sure to watch the runes to see if they continue to rise or fall! It may just let you know what you do with that starting item.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Patience Young Padawan</span> - Most of the time your going to be doing merchs that last anywhere from 1 hour to 24 hours. If your all over the place you may just be out of the merch. There are so many times I see people buy an item for 100gp and yet 20 minutes later sell it for 95 gp just so they can say abort. Yea its 5gp… but if you have 10k of them item that is 50k and every loser who is sitting there doing is feeding some kid on the other end 50k a swap. This goes back to being confident and studying that specific item!</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Stay away from "Merch Clans</span>" - Obviously you should not be part of them because they work on a pyramid scheme. Meaning that the leader buys the item weeks before and he sells it to all the followers so that they have to deal with the item why he collects. Also make sure to look at merch clans so you can avoid there item and look into items that relate to their item! Chain Reaction advantage! Oh not to mention merch clans are run by 12 year old kiddies.</p>
<p>[center]<span class="bbcode-b">…::Types of Markets::…</span>[/center]<br>
I really do not know what to name these as I believe I am the first to write about them. Anyways, the runescape market fluctuates based on the time of year. I am not going to go full detail into this because I am still studying this specific subject.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">WTF is going on market</span> - This is the most recent one. When Jagex announced the reopening of free trade and the wild it really got to everybody. Nobody could determine what way the market was going to head. Are items going to rise? Wait free trade is opened up maybe gp will be worthless?! This is what happened. When trade limit opened up it allowed for RWT and people with mass amounts of gp wanted to protect their networth. So they dropped all their items and bought into rares. Rares are like gold and silver IRL. When stocks are down people dump their cash into gold. Anyways this is a type of market that was caused by Jagex.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Buyers Market</span>- Here is another type of market which is caused by Jagex through events. Whenever a double exp weekend is put into place… what happens? Everybody starts buying…buying…buying!! Raw materials are where it is at. Anything related to a skill is where people invest. In turn you see combat items lower because of this. People want to take their whips / items and turn them into easy exp. After the buyer market is over look into combat items.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Summer</span> - When summer comes around it allows for 12 year skiddies to get off school and no life runescape. What are they going to want to do? Something fun of course. Look into items that are appealing for the summer skiddies. I believe Dragon Claws are a good example of a item that jumped up last year around summer.</p>
<p>[center]<span class="bbcode-b">…::Types Of Merchs::…</span>[/center]<br>
This basically explains what type of merch opportunities are available to you and which one is best for you.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Long Term</span> - If you believe your item is going to rise in the future, meaning months to years a long term merch is best for you. The most obvious example of a long term merch is rares. As they are discontinued they are bound to go.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Short Term</span> - This is usually based on a few day to a week. Buying an item and sticking to it for a few days hoping for the best outcome.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Hit &amp; Quit</span> - These are my personal favorite merch types. Buying into an item for one day only and having it jump and immediately getting out of the item the following day. Yes you could make more money if you do a short term investment but I like to hit it and quit it.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">“Filtering”</span> - This is where the cash is at. Buy an item below value and sell it at mid or even above the price. If you can’t buy below mid try buying at mid and selling for over. This acts like a filter if you have enough money to manipulate the item because your buying at mid. No matter what people will have to wait in line behind you to grab that item. They won’t want to waste their time so they will spend the extra few GP. Great example is what I did with chaos runes. Bought them at mid and sold for 2gp over… yea 2gp but if you filter 500k of that item in a day it comes to be 1mill gp.</p>
<p>[center]<span class="bbcode-b">…::Tricks::…</span>[/center]</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Make Money On A Falling Item</span> - You do not have to make money on items that are rising! If your skilling, lets say smithing and you see that coal is about to drop hugely… why not sell the coal you have right now and re-buy it when it levels out? Say it is 250gp and you sell it, and you buy it at 200gp. You just got a free coal for every 4 coal you sold! Which if you have 4k coal basically allows you to have 1k free coal lolololol. <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/smiley.png?v=5" title=":smiley:" class="emoji" alt=":smiley:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/l2merch/384160/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/l2merch/384160/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 27 Feb 2011 02:33:04 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-384160-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/l2merch/384160.rss">&lt;&gt;L2Merch&lt;&gt;</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
