<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Help meh will ++rep</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/help-meh-will-rep/384005</link>
    <description>Alright, my problem is that i can&#39;t seem to get my webclient online, i think it may because of port forwarding.. i change the port it connect to on the client and the source to 43593 (default is 43594) because i had a feeling a program was stopping it from working. I was wondering if someone could help me by trying to get it online themselves so i can know if its port forwarding or if its a problem with the source/client.

I started to build my server from the released &quot;CreativeScape&quot; server base (so if there are any known errors with the base can you please tell me)

Add me on MSN &quot;Mattz_strong@hotmail.com&quot; if you want the server files to check if its my port forwarding, otherwise leave a comment telling me what you think might be wrong and i&#39;ll check back on this post every 10-20 mins.

Thanks :]

P.S. I am pretty sure its my port forwarding failness (I&#39;ve had normal clients up before, never a webclient though).</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 26 Feb 2011 07:17:36 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Game Development</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/help-meh-will-rep/384005.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Help meh will ++rep</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@rosejuice rosejuice]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/rosejuice">@rosejuice</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Alright, my problem is that i can’t seem to get my webclient online, i think it may because of port forwarding… i change the port it connect to on the client and the source to 43593 (default is 43594) because i had a feeling a program was stopping it from working. I was wondering if someone could help me by trying to get it online themselves so i can know if its port forwarding or if its a problem with the source/client.</p>
<p>I started to build my server from the released “CreativeScape” server base (so if there are any known errors with the base can you please tell me)</p>
<p>Add me on MSN <a>"Mattz_strong@hotmail.com</a>" if you want the server files to check if its my port forwarding, otherwise leave a comment telling me what you think might be wrong and i’ll check back on this post every 10-20 mins.</p>
<p>Thanks :]</p>
<p>P.S. I am pretty sure its my port forwarding failness (I’ve had normal clients up before, never a webclient though).</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/help-meh-will-rep/384005/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/help-meh-will-rep/384005/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 26 Feb 2011 07:17:36 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-384005-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/help-meh-will-rep/384005.rss">Help meh will ++rep</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
