<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Fasvita: A free online virtual pet site</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/fasvita-a-free-online-virtual-pet-site/219567</link>
    <description>Hello everyone, I was asked by my sister to do a virtual pet site from scratch. I decided to comply on the basis that she would head up the project (gather artists, come up with the content, etc.)

The result thus far is located at http://efvee.freewebspace4me.com (The domain http://www.fasvita.com is an alternative link, but it&#39;s using URL forwarding for the time being, so you won&#39;t be able to properly view the source if you follow this route.)

I&#39;m by no means new to the virtual pet game business as I have volunteered for quite a few virtual pet games as a PHP programmer. I consider developing them as a hobby, and I&#39;m well aware of how strange a hobby it is (no need to tell me.) In fact, I currently work for a small web design and consulting company.

Anyway, I decided to use the CodeIgniter framework for this project. I find that the model, view, controller design pattern is excellent for organization... coupled with extensive libraries, and helpers; it can make development truly a pleasure. Also, I can make security an abstraction as CodeIgniter comes with great filtering against common web vulnerabilities e.g. XSS, SQL injection, etc. I was going to use PHPCake, but I made the decision to use CodeIgniter based on the fact that I believe CodeIgniter embodies the essence of PHP better than PHPCake. It&#39;s only been around a week of development in my spare time, but it&#39;s coming along fine.

I was just wondering if any of you had input on the future of this site. It&#39;s always good to hear opinions on best practices, common pitfalls, and anything else you can come up with. I don&#39;t mind ratings, but keep in mind that this site is brand new, and I as well as the artists we currently have, don&#39;t have that much time.

Note: We&#39;re always looking for artists, so post here if you feel you can help out, and we&#39;ll see if there&#39;s a place for you on the Fasvita team.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 12 Jul 2008 15:49:11 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>General Programming</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/fasvita-a-free-online-virtual-pet-site/219567.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Fasvita: A free online virtual pet site</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@ThAt0n36Uy Elijah]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/that0n36uy">@ThAt0n36Uy</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>They’re pets. Kind of like those online pokemon. There isn’t an actual game.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/fasvita-a-free-online-virtual-pet-site/219567/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/fasvita-a-free-online-virtual-pet-site/219567/3</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 12 Jul 2008 15:49:11 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-219567-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/fasvita-a-free-online-virtual-pet-site/219567.rss">Fasvita: A free online virtual pet site</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Fasvita: A free online virtual pet site</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@ThAt0n36Uy Elijah]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/that0n36uy">@ThAt0n36Uy</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I can help with design of pets.</p>
<p>I think you should first work on the background stuff, getting a basic system working. And then revamp the entire front end with a more visually pleasing website.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/fasvita-a-free-online-virtual-pet-site/219567/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/fasvita-a-free-online-virtual-pet-site/219567/2</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 12 Jul 2008 14:50:29 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-219567-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/fasvita-a-free-online-virtual-pet-site/219567.rss">Fasvita: A free online virtual pet site</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Fasvita: A free online virtual pet site</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@unlimitedorb unlimitedorb]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/unlimitedorb">@unlimitedorb</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Hello everyone, I was asked by my sister to do a virtual pet site from scratch. I decided to comply on the basis that she would head up the project (gather artists, come up with the content, etc.)</p>
<p>The result thus far is located at <a href="http://efvee.freewebspace4me.com" rel="nofollow noopener">http://efvee.freewebspace4me.com</a> (The domain <a href="http://www.fasvita.com" rel="nofollow noopener">http://www.fasvita.com</a> is an alternative link, but it’s using URL forwarding for the time being, so you won’t be able to properly view the source if you follow this route.)</p>
<p>I’m by no means new to the virtual pet game business as I have volunteered for quite a few virtual pet games as a PHP programmer. I consider developing them as a hobby, and I’m well aware of how strange a hobby it is (no need to tell me.) In fact, I currently work for a small web design and consulting company.</p>
<p>Anyway, I decided to use the CodeIgniter framework for this project. I find that the model, view, controller design pattern is excellent for organization… coupled with extensive libraries, and helpers; it can make development truly a pleasure. Also, I can make security an abstraction as CodeIgniter comes with great filtering against common web vulnerabilities e.g. XSS, SQL injection, etc. I was going to use PHPCake, but I made the decision to use CodeIgniter based on the fact that I believe CodeIgniter embodies the essence of PHP better than PHPCake. It’s only been around a week of development in my spare time, but it’s coming along fine.</p>
<p>I was just wondering if any of you had input on the future of this site. It’s always good to hear opinions on best practices, common pitfalls, and anything else you can come up with. I don’t mind ratings, but keep in mind that this site is brand new, and I as well as the artists we currently have, don’t have that much time.</p>
<p>Note: We’re always looking for artists, so post here if you feel you can help out, and we’ll see if there’s a place for you on the Fasvita team.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/fasvita-a-free-online-virtual-pet-site/219567/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/fasvita-a-free-online-virtual-pet-site/219567/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 12 Jul 2008 12:36:30 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-219567-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/fasvita-a-free-online-virtual-pet-site/219567.rss">Fasvita: A free online virtual pet site</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
