<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>[474] Simplex 2007 | Replica</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/474-simplex-2007-replica/520993</link>
    <description>[CENTER][IMG]http://oi40.tinypic.com/bexz0o.jpg[/img]

[URL=http://&quot;http://simplex07.org&quot;][IMG]http://i.imgur.com/7YIOxgN.png[/img][/URL]

[URL=http://&quot;http://simplex07.org/forums/index.php?pageid=webclient&quot;][IMG]http://i.imgur.com/g3gfTLf.png[/img][/URL]

[URL=http://&quot;http://simplex07.org/SClient.jar&quot;][IMG]http://i.imgur.com/cMx9Mn1.png[/img][/URL]
[/CENTER]

[B][I]About Us:[/I][/B]
[QUOTE]If you&#39;re taking the time to read this then obviously you&#39;ve taken a somewhat small interest in the Simplex 2007 server.  Before I continue, let me first state that yes, I have recently joined RuneLocus.  More specifically, I joined for the sole purpose of advertising.  However, please don&#39;t let my join date affect your outlook on me or my advertisement.  I have been involved in the private server community for well over 6 years, and know multiple OO languages(Ruby, C#).  Aside from that, let me also state that this server uses the [b]Hyperion[/b] framework with credits to the following people -


[ul][li]Graham, for Hyperion[/li]
[li]Shiver[/li]
[li]123sk8[/li]
[li]Scu11, and the rest of the Rs2-server team.  If you&#39;d like your name posted(as I don&#39;t know everyone involded, just request it.)[/li]
[li]Vastico[/li]
[li]Huey &amp; Killamess for the many things his release will help me with.[/li]
[li]Martin[/li]
[li]Barry[/li][/ul]


- If there&#39;s someone I&#39;ve missed, please know it&#39;s not intentional.  Again, these are just the credits for the initial framework.  I will continue to use this framework until I&#39;ve finished porting over [b]Apollo[/b](another framework) to 474.  Thank you for reading this piece of information, let me stop boring you now lolking.
[/QUOTE]

[B][I]What is Simplex?:[/I][/B]
Simplex is a [b]true[/b] 474 server that strives to replicate RuneScape during it&#39;s golden era.  Whether this ranges from content, to the community, we strive for perfection in every way possible.  Where others slack, we succeed.  Where others ignore, we listen.  Have you ever yearned for a server that&#39;s dedicated to the community and takes into consideration what players say?  Or how about a stable and consistent game play experience?  Or better yet, what about a true economy?  Not a place where donators dominate the highscores, or control the economy.  A place where every player exists in equality.  Well here at Simplex, those are our exact means.  We believe that all players should have a fair game play.  What this means is there&#39;s no &quot;donation for items/ranks/gold&quot;.  No custom content that shouldn&#39;t be added, such as items.  Have you ever heard of Dodian?  If you have, then you will know what we strive to accomplish.  If not, than why not give it a try?


[IMG]http://i.imgur.com/ysuyYR5.png[/img]


[b]Hosting 24/7.[/b]

[ul][li][B]Server:[/B]
Simplex server runs off a Windows box VPS(Not linux for other reasons.  I&#39;m very good with SSH).  3g Memory, Duel(No more power is needed, I&#39;ve already done tests and a few benchmarks and Simplex could easily handle 1,000 players if it got to that point).[/li]
[li][B]Site:[/B]
The site runs off a CentOS Linux box VPS.  We also use another Linux box for DDoS tunneling.  I don&#39;t think site statistics matter, but so you know the site wont go down.[/li][/ul]


[B]Active Community and friendly staff.[/B]

[ul][li][B]Info:[/B]
An active community is a big concern for Simplex.  With strive to keep the community active not only in-game but also on the forums.  All our staff is individually selected and all have a professional outlook on the future of Simplex.[/li][/ul]


[b]Simplex Server Info.[/B]

[ul][li][B]Economy:[/B]
We take pride in our servers economy.  It is what we like to call a &#39;true&#39; economy.  In other words the economy is not flooded with unnecessary items or coins.  Everything that has been earned on the server has been earned by the players.  There has been no items/coins/stats given out.  So as this is a true economy, all skills actually have meaning to them.  This gives players a sense of accomplishment and stimulates game play; that is what I believe.[/li]
[li][B]Skills:[/B]
Currently, most skills work with the exception of a few.  I will list them now and give a brief explanation after -[/li]
[list]
[li]Woodcutting[/li]
[li]Fletching[/li]
[li]Crafting[/li]
[li]Mining[/li]
[li]Smithing[/li]
[li]Fishing[/li]
[li]Cooking[/li]
[li]Thieving[/li]
[li]Agility[/li]
[li]Runecrafting[/li]
[/list]
- Now the skills listed above all work perfectly(to a certain extent).  Some of the skills may be incomplete, i.e you cannot stall thieve yet, however the parts of skills that do work are perfect.  Take Woodcutting for example, they globally fall down and respawn.  I myself am working on improving existing skills and creating ones that aren&#39;t currently available.  At the moment I&#39;m in the process of developing player owned houses for construction.

[b]Perfected combat:[/b]
Perfect.  There is no exception to this.  From the formulas to the following down to the sound system.  Combat is perfect in every way possible we could think of.  We also have a sound system implemented on most combat.  All spell sounds are added(cast, hit, splash), most of the range/melee ones as well(that we could find).

[b]Regional Music System:[/b]
Yes, we have an awesome regional music system that was rewritten and implemented by myself.  We currently have support for [b][i]27[/i][/b] different regions(constantly adding more daily).  I&#39;m also in the process of writing the music interface so players may have the option on which tracks they&#39;d like to play.

[B]Clan Chat:[/B]
It&#39;s perfect.  Your clan setup will save all functions you set, including ranks for players in your clan(even if you&#39;re offline).  When you first login you will auto join the clan chat &#39;Official&#39; which is used for main server help, info instead of a yell channel.  We also use the &#39;Official&#39; clan ranking system for our moderator selection process.


[CENTER]
[IMG]http://i.imgur.com/a3G33a2.png[/img]
Promotional Video(Recorded by the VPS funder)
[youtube]https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=lOFMDfBzFvs[/youtube]

(These are just various images to go with the rules of forum)
[IMG]http://i39.tinypic.com/2vlprlv.png[/img]
[IMG]http://i40.tinypic.com/2ziwmtt.png[/img]
[IMG]http://i43.tinypic.com/20trpjb.png[/img][/CENTER]


And that&#39;s it for now folks.  I really hate doing advertising so I cba with media, but I will update daily if I must.:eek:

This was just posted from RuneLocus.[/ul]</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 07 Jun 2013 20:38:33 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/474-simplex-2007-replica/520993.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>[474] Simplex 2007 | Replica</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@hadees12 hadees12]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/hadees12">@hadees12</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Thanks.^^</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/474-simplex-2007-replica/520993/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/474-simplex-2007-replica/520993/3</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 07 Jun 2013 20:38:33 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-520993-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/474-simplex-2007-replica/520993.rss">[474] Simplex 2007 | Replica</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[474] Simplex 2007 | Replica</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@drubrkletern drubrkletern]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/drubrkletern">@drubrkletern</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>cool</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/474-simplex-2007-replica/520993/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/474-simplex-2007-replica/520993/2</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 07 Jun 2013 20:26:51 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-520993-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/474-simplex-2007-replica/520993.rss">[474] Simplex 2007 | Replica</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[474] Simplex 2007 | Replica</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@hadees12 hadees12]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/hadees12">@hadees12</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[CENTER]<div class="lightbox-wrapper"><a class="lightbox" href="http://oi40.tinypic.com/bexz0o.jpg" title="bexz0o.jpg" rel="nofollow noopener"><img src="http://oi40.tinypic.com/bexz0o.jpg" alt width="690" height="167"><div class="meta">
<svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-far-image svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#far-image"></use></svg><span class="filename">bexz0o.jpg</span><span class="informations">700×170</span><svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-discourse-expand svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#discourse-expand"></use></svg>
</div></a></div></p>
<p><a data-bbcode="true"><img src="http://i.imgur.com/7YIOxgN.png" alt width="111" height="18"></a></p>
<p><a data-bbcode="true"><img src="http://i.imgur.com/g3gfTLf.png" alt width="134" height="18"></a></p>
<p><a data-bbcode="true"><img src="http://i.imgur.com/cMx9Mn1.png" alt width="259" height="18"></a><br>
[/CENTER]</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b"><span class="bbcode-i">About Us:</span></span></p>
<p>[QUOTE]If you’re taking the time to read this then obviously you’ve taken a somewhat small interest in the Simplex 2007 server.  Before I continue, let me first state that yes, I have recently joined RuneLocus.  More specifically, I joined for the sole purpose of advertising.  However, please don’t let my join date affect your outlook on me or my advertisement.  I have been involved in the private server community for well over 6 years, and know multiple OO languages(Ruby, C#).  Aside from that, let me also state that this server uses the <span class="bbcode-b">Hyperion</span> framework with credits to the following people -</p>
<p>[ul][li]Graham, for Hyperion[/li]<br>
[li]Shiver[/li]<br>
[li]123sk8[/li]<br>
[li]Scu11, and the rest of the Rs2-server team.  If you’d like your name posted(as I don’t know everyone involded, just request it.)[/li]<br>
[li]Vastico[/li]<br>
[li]Huey &amp; Killamess for the many things his release will help me with.[/li]<br>
[li]Martin[/li]<br>
[li]Barry[/li][/ul]</p>
<ul>
<li>If there’s someone I’ve missed, please know it’s not intentional.  Again, these are just the credits for the initial framework.  I will continue to use this framework until I’ve finished porting over <span class="bbcode-b">Apollo</span>(another framework) to 474.  Thank you for reading this piece of information, let me stop boring you now lolking.<br>
[/QUOTE]</li>
</ul>
<p><span class="bbcode-b"><span class="bbcode-i">What is Simplex?:</span></span><br>
Simplex is a <span class="bbcode-b">true</span> 474 server that strives to replicate RuneScape during it’s golden era.  Whether this ranges from content, to the community, we strive for perfection in every way possible.  Where others slack, we succeed.  Where others ignore, we listen.  Have you ever yearned for a server that’s dedicated to the community and takes into consideration what players say?  Or how about a stable and consistent game play experience?  Or better yet, what about a true economy?  Not a place where donators dominate the highscores, or control the economy.  A place where every player exists in equality.  Well here at Simplex, those are our exact means.  We believe that all players should have a fair game play.  What this means is there’s no “donation for items/ranks/gold”.  No custom content that shouldn’t be added, such as items.  Have you ever heard of Dodian?  If you have, then you will know what we strive to accomplish.  If not, than why not give it a try?</p>
<p><img src="http://i.imgur.com/ysuyYR5.png" alt width="306" height="28"></p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Hosting 24/7.</span></p>
<p>[ul][li]<span class="bbcode-b">Server:</span><br>
Simplex server runs off a Windows box VPS(Not linux for other reasons.  I’m very good with SSH).  3g Memory, Duel(No more power is needed, I’ve already done tests and a few benchmarks and Simplex could easily handle 1,000 players if it got to that point).[/li]<br>
[li]<span class="bbcode-b">Site:</span><br>
The site runs off a CentOS Linux box VPS.  We also use another Linux box for DDoS tunneling.  I don’t think site statistics matter, but so you know the site wont go down.[/li][/ul]</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Active Community and friendly staff.</span></p>
<p>[ul][li]<span class="bbcode-b">Info:</span><br>
An active community is a big concern for Simplex.  With strive to keep the community active not only in-game but also on the forums.  All our staff is individually selected and all have a professional outlook on the future of Simplex.[/li][/ul]</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Simplex Server Info.</span></p>
<p>[ul][li]<span class="bbcode-b">Economy:</span><br>
We take pride in our servers economy.  It is what we like to call a ‘true’ economy.  In other words the economy is not flooded with unnecessary items or coins.  Everything that has been earned on the server has been earned by the players.  There has been no items/coins/stats given out.  So as this is a true economy, all skills actually have meaning to them.  This gives players a sense of accomplishment and stimulates game play; that is what I believe.[/li]<br>
[li]<span class="bbcode-b">Skills:</span><br>
Currently, most skills work with the exception of a few.  I will list them now and give a brief explanation after -[/li]<br>
[list]<br>
[li]Woodcutting[/li]<br>
[li]Fletching[/li]<br>
[li]Crafting[/li]<br>
[li]Mining[/li]<br>
[li]Smithing[/li]<br>
[li]Fishing[/li]<br>
[li]Cooking[/li]<br>
[li]Thieving[/li]<br>
[li]Agility[/li]<br>
[li]Runecrafting[/li]<br>
[/list]</p>
<ul>
<li>Now the skills listed above all work perfectly(to a certain extent).  Some of the skills may be incomplete, i.e you cannot stall thieve yet, however the parts of skills that do work are perfect.  Take Woodcutting for example, they globally fall down and respawn.  I myself am working on improving existing skills and creating ones that aren’t currently available.  At the moment I’m in the process of developing player owned houses for construction.</li>
</ul>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Perfected combat:</span><br>
Perfect.  There is no exception to this.  From the formulas to the following down to the sound system.  Combat is perfect in every way possible we could think of.  We also have a sound system implemented on most combat.  All spell sounds are added(cast, hit, splash), most of the range/melee ones as well(that we could find).</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Regional Music System:</span><br>
Yes, we have an awesome regional music system that was rewritten and implemented by myself.  We currently have support for <span class="bbcode-b"><span class="bbcode-i">27</span></span> different regions(constantly adding more daily).  I’m also in the process of writing the music interface so players may have the option on which tracks they’d like to play.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Clan Chat:</span><br>
It’s perfect.  Your clan setup will save all functions you set, including ranks for players in your clan(even if you’re offline).  When you first login you will auto join the clan chat ‘Official’ which is used for main server help, info instead of a yell channel.  We also use the ‘Official’ clan ranking system for our moderator selection process.</p>
<p>[CENTER]<br>
<img src="http://i.imgur.com/a3G33a2.png" alt width="129" height="28"><br>
Promotional Video(Recorded by the VPS funder)<br>
[youtube]<a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=lOFMDfBzFvs%5B/youtube%5D" rel="nofollow noopener">https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=lOFMDfBzFvs[/youtube]</a></p>
<p>(These are just various images to go with the rules of forum)<br>
<div class="lightbox-wrapper"><a class="lightbox" href="http://i39.tinypic.com/2vlprlv.png" title="2vlprlv.png" rel="nofollow noopener"><img src="http://i39.tinypic.com/2vlprlv.png" alt width="690" height="455"><div class="meta">
<svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-far-image svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#far-image"></use></svg><span class="filename">2vlprlv.png</span><span class="informations">762×503</span><svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-discourse-expand svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#discourse-expand"></use></svg>
</div></a></div><br>
<div class="lightbox-wrapper"><a class="lightbox" href="http://i40.tinypic.com/2ziwmtt.png" title="2ziwmtt.png" rel="nofollow noopener"><img src="http://i40.tinypic.com/2ziwmtt.png" alt width="690" height="453"><div class="meta">
<svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-far-image svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#far-image"></use></svg><span class="filename">2ziwmtt.png</span><span class="informations">762×501</span><svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-discourse-expand svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#discourse-expand"></use></svg>
</div></a></div><br>
<div class="lightbox-wrapper"><a class="lightbox" href="http://i43.tinypic.com/20trpjb.png" title="20trpjb.png" rel="nofollow noopener"><img src="http://i43.tinypic.com/20trpjb.png" alt width="690" height="454"><div class="meta">
<svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-far-image svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#far-image"></use></svg><span class="filename">20trpjb.png</span><span class="informations">764×503</span><svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-discourse-expand svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#discourse-expand"></use></svg>
</div></a></div>[/CENTER]</p>
<p>And that’s it for now folks.  I really hate doing advertising so I cba with media, but I will update daily if I must.:eek:</p>
<p>This was just posted from RuneLocus.[/ul]</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/474-simplex-2007-replica/520993/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/474-simplex-2007-replica/520993/1</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 07 Jun 2013 20:23:07 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-520993-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/474-simplex-2007-replica/520993.rss">[474] Simplex 2007 | Replica</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
