<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Need RSCD Forum Source</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/need-rscd-forum-source/418238</link>
    <description>Ok so... I am having some trouble. &quot;Lol K&quot; was helping me to host an RSCAngel server and forums on a private VPS I purchased. I don&#39;t know why, but for some reason, he decided to delete everything I had and peace out. 

I have some back up forums but am missing a few things and was wondering if I could get some help. I have some forums on my localhost but am missing the register.php ... I&#39;m not super sure what I&#39;m missing so let me try to describe it.
There was a register page that had a link to the forums ... It had highscores, transfer character, an admin panel to view player&#39;s bank, inventory, etc., an add a subscription page, and other stuff. After you registered an account, you could link to the forums. I&#39;m pretty sure it was based off of an RSCD source but am not sure.

Anyways.. If anyone is good at mysql, webhosting, and stuff... Let me know. I&#39;ll do my best to reward any help given.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 15 Oct 2011 12:59:43 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/need-rscd-forum-source/418238.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Need RSCD Forum Source</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@cleako cleako]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/cleako">@cleako</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I’m pretty sure it should. Overall you really want to get away from using it unless you know what you are doing. The default PunBB that comes with RSCD is full of vulnerabilities that have allowed many servers to be hacked. I tried to replace it with Fluxbb and clean up most of them with RSCD_v25_3’s package but I would not use it these days.</p>
<p>In the next few weeks to next few months, I will open source the current website that a friend and I have built from scratch that interfaces with the current version of PHPBB for the community to use. There is no room for “leech proof”/password stealing/SQL injection vulnerable junk on here anymore. The development community can really benefit from good work and its important we keep it going as RSC is has been and will always be important to each of us. There is still plenty of fresh interest in RSC and there is no reason to let it die yet.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/need-rscd-forum-source/418238/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/need-rscd-forum-source/418238/3</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 15 Oct 2011 12:59:43 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-418238-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/need-rscd-forum-source/418238.rss">Need RSCD Forum Source</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Need RSCD Forum Source</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@vortex vortex]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/vortex">@vortex</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p><a href="http://sourceforge.net/projects/rscdv25/files/Open%20RSCD_v25/v1.3/Open_RSCD_v25_3.rar/download" class="onebox" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">http://sourceforge.net/projects/rscdv25/files/Open%20RSCD_v25/v1.3/Open_RSCD_v25_3.rar/download</a><br>
has some php files, dunno if they work with your version though</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/need-rscd-forum-source/418238/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/need-rscd-forum-source/418238/2</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 15 Oct 2011 07:35:41 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-418238-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/need-rscd-forum-source/418238.rss">Need RSCD Forum Source</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Need RSCD Forum Source</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@A_Gh0st A Gh0st]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/a_gh0st">@A_Gh0st</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Ok so… I am having some trouble. “Lol K” was helping me to host an RSCAngel server and forums on a private VPS I purchased. I don’t know why, but for some reason, he decided to delete everything I had and peace out.</p>
<p>I have some back up forums but am missing a few things and was wondering if I could get some help. I have some forums on my localhost but am missing the register.php … I’m not super sure what I’m missing so let me try to describe it.<br>
There was a register page that had a link to the forums … It had highscores, transfer character, an admin panel to view player’s bank, inventory, etc., an add a subscription page, and other stuff. After you registered an account, you could link to the forums. I’m pretty sure it was based off of an RSCD source but am not sure.</p>
<p>Anyways… If anyone is good at mysql, webhosting, and stuff… Let me know. I’ll do my best to reward any help given.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/need-rscd-forum-source/418238/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/need-rscd-forum-source/418238/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 15 Oct 2011 05:47:04 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-418238-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/need-rscd-forum-source/418238.rss">Need RSCD Forum Source</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
