<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Need help with 562</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/need-help-with-562/359185</link>
    <description>Okay, so for a while now, I&#39;ve been reading through my client, line by line, trying to discover how the program decrypts the cache (I&#39;m using a 562, not much is edited). The problem is that there is not one single decrypt method. Several methods run one after another until the entire packet is decrypted. This makes it very difficult to understand.

Anyway, here&#39;s my question: does anyone happen to have the RS2 Cache Editor that was posted on &quot;runesrver&quot; (by Lazaro) that they could upload for me? It was posted several years ago (based upon the post I&#39;m looking at), so the download link is down. I read on the post that it works for 562 so I&#39;m hoping that it could help me with my cache project.

EDIT: Instead of just the RS2 Cache Editor posted above, does anyone have ANY cache extractor that works with 562 cache? The editor part I can code myself. I really only need a program that reads the standard &quot;main_file_cache.dat2&quot; file, along with the index files (&quot;idx&quot; extensions) and outputs all the sprites, models, etc. contained inside.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 08 Sep 2010 02:10:42 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Game Development</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/need-help-with-562/359185.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Need help with 562</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Project_Realm Project Realm]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/project_realm">@Project_Realm</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Okay, so for a while now, I’ve been reading through my client, line by line, trying to discover how the program decrypts the cache (I’m using a 562, not much is edited). The problem is that there is not one single decrypt method. Several methods run one after another until the entire packet is decrypted. This makes it very difficult to understand.</p>
<p>Anyway, here’s my question: does anyone happen to have the RS2 Cache Editor that was posted on “runesrver” (by Lazaro) that they could upload for me? It was posted several years ago (based upon the post I’m looking at), so the download link is down. I read on the post that it works for 562 so I’m hoping that it could help me with my cache project.</p>
<p>EDIT: Instead of just the RS2 Cache Editor posted above, does anyone have ANY cache extractor that works with 562 cache? The editor part I can code myself. I really only need a program that reads the standard “main_file_cache.dat2” file, along with the index files (“idx” extensions) and outputs all the sprites, models, etc. contained inside.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/need-help-with-562/359185/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/need-help-with-562/359185/1</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 08 Sep 2010 02:10:42 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-359185-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/need-help-with-562/359185.rss">Need help with 562</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
