<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Turkish idiot, TX (Mark Gore)</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/turkish-idiot-tx-mark-gore/444148</link>
    <description>So T_[b][/b]X makes a new account every time he&#39;s banned and he does so because it takes sooo long for any action to be taken against him. I report him as soon as I see him but it still takes sometimes days for anything to happen.

Here&#39;s his latest account: http://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php?action=profile;u=566619

As you can see all he&#39;s doing is flaming people (including myself) and spamming threads. When a moderator does eventually ban him they usually leave the posts there.

It would be good if RSC could be moderated with a bit more care, I know it&#39;s a pretty dead section and probably low priority but there still is a lot of players out there who care about RSC.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 05 Jun 2012 23:43:40 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Community Suggestions</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/turkish-idiot-tx-mark-gore/444148.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Turkish idiot, TX (Mark Gore)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@davidi2 Davidi2]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/davidi2">@davidi2</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>You know that if you report it and have proof its him (or like in this example, the person obviously just doesn’t belong here), it will be taken care of. The majority of staff do not exactly… relish… the thought of searching through the RSC sections to try and find rule breaking, but report it and it will be taken care of.</p>
<p>In TX’s case in particular, I have banned him multiple times, and we all (the staff) know he should be banned if caught. Just report him if you find him, there is nothing else to be discussed here.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/turkish-idiot-tx-mark-gore/444148/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/turkish-idiot-tx-mark-gore/444148/2</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 05 Jun 2012 23:43:40 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-444148-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/turkish-idiot-tx-mark-gore/444148.rss">Turkish idiot, TX (Mark Gore)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Turkish idiot, TX (Mark Gore)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Kryptix Kryptix]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/kryptix">@Kryptix</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>So T_<span class="bbcode-b"></span>X makes a new account every time he’s banned and he does so because it takes sooo long for any action to be taken against him. I report him as soon as I see him but it still takes sometimes days for anything to happen.</p>
<p>Here’s his latest account: <a href="http://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php?action=profile;u=566619" rel="nofollow noopener">http://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php?action=profile;u=566619</a></p>
<p>As you can see all he’s doing is flaming people (including myself) and spamming threads. When a moderator does eventually ban him they usually leave the posts there.</p>
<p>It would be good if RSC could be moderated with a bit more care, I know it’s a pretty dead section and probably low priority but there still is a lot of players out there who care about RSC.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/turkish-idiot-tx-mark-gore/444148/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/turkish-idiot-tx-mark-gore/444148/1</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 05 Jun 2012 23:24:56 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-444148-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/turkish-idiot-tx-mark-gore/444148.rss">Turkish idiot, TX (Mark Gore)</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
