<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Webclient error</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/webclient-error/267019</link>
    <description>well ill start with the background because i like to do that, always have and always will. i was starting to host my server and i had a client DL but some ppl dident want to dl it and wanted me to make a webclient so i just began to work on it and ive tried once before but never went full force into it and tried to complete it. although this time i tried to complete it but i have 1 error, it always redownloads the cache and then says &quot;client updated please refresh page&quot; so you refresh the page and it downloads it again its an endless cycle. I looked into it slightly and then decided ide prolly get to the solution faster by posting it on this forum and looking for it then just doing one or the other. Does anyone have a solution? At this point in time my friend has stopped hosting so the speed of the awnser is not to important, just the awnser.

 [ just in case you want to see the problem in action go to my website -theicescape.tk- and click weclient in the bar ]</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 12 Mar 2009 02:57:51 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Game Development</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/webclient-error/267019.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Webclient error</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@qw3rty qw3rty]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/qw3rty">@qw3rty</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>well ill start with the background because i like to do that, always have and always will. i was starting to host my server and i had a client DL but some ppl dident want to dl it and wanted me to make a webclient so i just began to work on it and ive tried once before but never went full force into it and tried to complete it. although this time i tried to complete it but i have 1 error, it always redownloads the cache and then says “client updated please refresh page” so you refresh the page and it downloads it again its an endless cycle. I looked into it slightly and then decided ide prolly get to the solution faster by posting it on this forum and looking for it then just doing one or the other. Does anyone have a solution? At this point in time my friend has stopped hosting so the speed of the awnser is not to important, just the awnser.</p>
<p>[ just in case you want to see the problem in action go to my website -theicescape.tk- and click weclient in the bar ]</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/webclient-error/267019/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/webclient-error/267019/1</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 12 Mar 2009 02:57:51 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-267019-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/webclient-error/267019.rss">Webclient error</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
