<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Wilderness &amp; Free Trade Q&amp;A</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/wilderness-free-trade-q-a/379372</link>
    <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;[b][u]General FAQ[/u][/b]

[b]How will the Grand Exchange work now?[/b]

Essentially it will work exactly how it worked before, just without any price restrictions. It means you will be able to offer to buy or sell at the price you think is right. 

[b]Will there be guide prices?[/b]

Yes. The guide price will be based on the previous day’s trading. The guide price will usually only change by a maximum of 5% per day, just as it currently works. 

[b]Will we be able to buy/sell items for whatever we want now?[/b]

Yes, assuming you find a buyer/ seller of course. 

[b]Can I give gifts to my friends now? Like a million if I wanted too?[/b]

Yes indeed! 

[b]You’ve said that the price limits will be removed, but what about the buying restrictions?[/b]

Buying restrictions will remain in place. These exist purely to reduce market monopoly and ensure a higher number of players can buy high demand objects like god swords. 

[b][u]Scamming[/u][/b]

[b]Will item scamming be a problem? What is being done to prevent item scamming?[/b]

Rules will still be in place to prevent item scamming, and players breaking those rules will suffer the wrath of our player support team. Warning screens, wildy walls, better examine options and clearer rules will help to prevent scamming – however, ultimately it’s up to you, the player to protect yourself just as it is today. Remember, if a deal sounds too good to be true, it probably is. 

[b]Will the trade warnings still be in the trade window to prevent item scamming?[/b]

Yes, and if people try to change the trade you will still have large red exclamation marks telling you that changes have occurred, which have to be re-confirmed. 

[b][u]Staking[/u][/b]

[b]What is going to happen with staking at the Duel Arena?[/b]

Staking is returning! So you will be able to bet anything tradable on the outcome of the battle. 

[b]Will I be able to stake in any other Activities?[/b]

You will be able to stake in Conquest! 

The rat pits also remains if you want to bet a few coins on your cats prowess, but that’s just for fun and has restrictions in place. 

[b]Will you add more options for staking in the Duel Arena? For example “No Degradable Items” or “Team Staking”?[/b]

Not at this time, but potentially in the future. 

[b]What’s happening to duel tournaments?[/b]

We are switching off the duel tournaments with a view to reworking the activity in the future. Simply put, it wasn’t providing the service that either the players or JAGEX wanted to offer, and we felt it was better to remove it totally. People’s ranks and hiscores will be preserved in case they are relevant in the future. 

[b][u]Price Checker[/u][/b]

[b]Will the price checker feature be removed/changed now that players can freely trade?[/b]

It’s not being removed, it just won’t show trade limits any more. It will show the guide price (discussed above). 

[b][u]Gravestones[/u][/b]

[b]How will gravestones work now?[/b]

If you die in the wilderness there will be no gravestone. At all. If you were killed by a player, they get the drop. If you were killed by monster, the drop appears for everyone immediately. 

Some areas of the wilderness are still PK free (like the original mage arena). In those areas AND in the rest of the game, a gravestone will appear and exist just as they do today. The gravestone can still be blessed and maintained by other players. A player returning to their gravestone will be able to reclaim all their lost items. 

If a player doesn’t return to their gravestone and it crumbles away, all players will be able to pick up the loot. 

[b][u]Lending Items[/u][/b]

[b]How will item lending work? Will it be changed in anyway?[/b]

You can’t use borrowed items in the wilderness and you can’t stake a lent item. Aside from that it’s exactly as it was before. This isn’t restricted to combat gear, no lent items can be used at all in the wilderness. 

If you enter the wilderness with one equipped you will have the lent item removed to your inventory, banked, or returned to the owner, depending on the space available. 

[b][u]Party Room[/u][/b]

[b]Will the Party Room be changed? Will they alert banks every time there is a drop on that world?[/b]

The party room remains in place but with no chest restrictions. Bankers and citizens will no longer chat spam. Items drop as soon as lever is pulled, there is no big countdown. 

Hopefully player owned party rooms in the future  

[b][u]Player-owned House Reward Chests[/u][/b]

[b]Will the limits on POH reward chests be lifted?[/b]

The coin restrictions for each level of reward chest have been increased dramatically, with the top level chest (magic) having no restrictions. 

[b][u]Dropping objects in the Wilderness[/u][/b]

[b]How will dropping items in the Wilderness work now?[/b]

If you manually drop items on the floor in the Wilderness, they will be visible to everyone immediately, as long as the items were tradeable. Untradeable items will never become visible to other players. 

If you manually put items on a table in the Wilderness, they will be visible to everyone immediately. 

[b][u]Wilderness/PvP Questions[/u][/b]

[b]Will we able to use extreme potions in the Wilderness?[/b]

No. However, a player with an “extreme” boost who enters the wilderness will have the boost reduced to “super” level. This duplicates the current function on PvP worlds. 

[b]What about untradeable items like Dungeoneering rewards/Korasi’s sword/fire capes etc? How will these work in the Wilderness?[/b]

One of three things will happen. Some objects will vanish, some drop cash (like anchor pre 07, will include Korasi’s sword), others drop a tradable equivalent (like summoning headgear that’s enchanted being dropped un-enchanted). Most popular untradeable PvP equipment will not vanish. 

[b]What about the revenants? What is going to happen with them?[/b]

Revenants will be added to a new PvP enabled dungeon. Revenants will have all PvP unique drops such as brawlers, corrupt dragon and statues added to them. Revenants will no longer teleblock or freeze opponents but will continue to change combat styles and generally cause havoc. 

The Forinthry bracelet now has new functionality – you can use it to repel revenants and also give temporary immunity to damage from them. 

[b]What is going to happen to all the old PvP world drops like statius sets or artifacts etc?[/b]

See above – will be dropped by revs. 

[b]Will we have all the old PvP mechanics back just as they were? Will there be any big changes?[/b]

It’s pretty much back as it was. 

There are a few extra escape routes in the wilderness than there were before, however most of them cannot be used whilst under attack. 

Obviously we have new weapons, curses and an entire summoning skill to generate new tactics. 

[b]What about all the quests that are in the Wilderness? Will these be left where they are or moved?[/b]

No player doing a quest will ever be under the threat of being killed by another player. Quests will exist in areas of the wilderness but these areas cannot be used for pking. 

Post quest rewards like the beacon network and spirit of summer portals will remain in the wilderness, with some gaining extra rewards to compensate for the extra risk. Players who already have the original reward can return to collect the “bonus” we have added. 

[b]Will I have to walk through the Wilderness to get to the lair of the Corporeal Beast?[/b]

No. The games necklace will have a teleport option that will take you into the first cave if you have completed Summers End. If you’re feeling brave you can walk there of course. 

[b]What about all the minigames/activities that are in the Wilderness? Will these be left where they are or moved?[/b]

They will be relocated. There is a new cave located just north of Falador called the “Gamers Grotto” which will contain Stealing Creation, Clan Wars and a portal to fist of Guthix. Previous teleport options will now direct the player here. 

Clan wars dangerous “free for all” battles will now follow standard wilderness rules of item loss. 

[b]What about penguins or shooting stars? Will they be moved out of the Wilderness?[/b]

We have not changed anything regarding the penguins or the shooting stars. 

[b]What about treasure trails?[/b] 

The number of possible treasure trail locations remains the same, however you won’t be sent to the wilderness as often as you were. 

[b]Will you add any “safe” worlds for non-pkers to use without fear of being killed?[/b]

No. It’s the wilderness, it’s not meant to be safe. 

[b]Changes to the engine, like RuneTek5 will change the way PvP works, as a lot of old tactics like trapping people. Will this be changed back?[/b]

No. 

[b]What about 1 itemers? I hate 1 itemers...[/b]

We’re designating a small number of worlds as High-Risk Wilderness Worlds. On those worlds, the Protect Item prayer and curse cannot be used inside the Wilderness. Outside the Wilderness, the prayer and curse will work as normal. You would be warned before logging into these worlds. 

[b]Are you changing the PvP and Bounty worlds?[/b]

Yes. PvP worlds will no longer exist. Bounty mechanics will be removed. Bounty and Rogue hiscores will remain. In the future we intend to create a new activity using bounty hunter gameplay. Those worlds previously used for PvP and bounties will now become suggested worlds for Pking and high risk wilderness (see above). 

[b]In the original wilderness there used to be a tactic of attacking a monster and deliberately trying not to kill it in order to escape from a pker. You changed it for PvP worlds. Are you bringing that back?[/b]

That tactic has been removed. Any player attacking a monster in the wilderness can be attacked by another player, even if you are in single way combat. 

[b][u]The volcano banker[/u][/b]

[b]Is the bank by the craters going to be removed?[/b] 

Yes. Look out for Maximillian Sackville in a bank near you! 

[b][u]Summoning[/u][/b] 

[b]How will Summoning work in the Wilderness?[/b]

While you are in the wilderness, your combat level will act as though you didn’t have any summoning, so will be a maximum of 126. All calculations regarding which other players you can fight will be based on this level, just as with F2P wilderness. 

If you have any summoning levels, your combat level display will indicate this. This will give other players an idea of your “potential” to summon aid. 

For example: 

If you are currently a level 138 player, your combat level in the wilderness would be displayed thus: 

xxepicpkerxx 126+12 

If you were in level 3 wilderness, you could fight players between level 123 and 126. Those players would be able to see the +12 and so would know of your potential to summon ALL familiars – particularly dangerous in multiway combat areas. 

[b]What happens when my familiar or I die while in the Wilderness?[/b]

When your familiar dies or despawns while carrying items in the Wilderness, the items will be dropped. If it was killed by another player, that player will get the dropped items first, then later to everyone as with normal wilderness kills. Otherwise, the items will become visible to EVERYONE immediately, so you can’t sneakily dismiss your familiar to prevent pkers getting the loot. 

If you are killed while your familiar is carrying items, those items will be awarded to your pker, just like the items in your inventory. 

[b]Can I attack other familiars? What will happen?[/b] 

Attacking someone’s familiar in the Wilderness will follow the standard rules of engagement, so you will be skulled if you’re the aggressor. 

Ordering your familiar to attack a player or familiar will follow exactly the same rules. 

[b][u]Other small changes to Wilderness content[/u][/b] 

[b]Anything else being added or changed?[/b] 

Runite rocks in the wilderness will refill much faster than other Runite rocks in the game. 

The chaos Elemental has had his drop table improved and can also drop the old PvP specific armour and weapons.&lt;/blockquote&gt;
http://services.runescape.com/m=forum/forums.ws?254,255,55,62204744

Sounds great tbh.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 22 Jan 2011 22:57:44 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/wilderness-free-trade-q-a/379372.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Wilderness &amp; Free Trade Q&amp;A</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@_Rich Rich]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/_rich">@_Rich</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p><a href="http://services.runescape.com/m=forum/forums.ws?254,255,55,62204744,goto,1" class="onebox" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">http://services.runescape.com/m=forum/forums.ws?254,255,55,62204744,goto,1</a></p>
<p>^ Their live Q&amp;A session was today.</p>
<p>Also:</p>
<p><img src="http://img833.imageshack.us/img833/6587/modmarkwtf.png" alt width="" height=""></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/wilderness-free-trade-q-a/379372/15">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/wilderness-free-trade-q-a/379372/15</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 22 Jan 2011 22:57:44 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-379372-15</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/wilderness-free-trade-q-a/379372.rss">Wilderness &amp; Free Trade Q&amp;A</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Wilderness &amp; Free Trade Q&amp;A</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@abatssk8ter abatssk8ter]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/abatssk8ter">@abatssk8ter</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Oooo, so JaGex is no longer controlling the economy huh, and street prices will rein supreme?</p>
<p>RuneHQ has logged in.</p>
<p>Oh and GF green drags.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/wilderness-free-trade-q-a/379372/14">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/wilderness-free-trade-q-a/379372/14</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 22 Jan 2011 02:30:26 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-379372-14</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/wilderness-free-trade-q-a/379372.rss">Wilderness &amp; Free Trade Q&amp;A</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Wilderness &amp; Free Trade Q&amp;A</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@rip4d rip4d]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/rip4d">@rip4d</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I can’t wait to see the PvP dungeon, gonna get some brawlers <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/smiley.png?v=5" title=":smiley:" class="emoji" alt=":smiley:"></p>
<p>Inb4vestadrops.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/wilderness-free-trade-q-a/379372/13">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/wilderness-free-trade-q-a/379372/13</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 22 Jan 2011 02:19:34 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-379372-13</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/wilderness-free-trade-q-a/379372.rss">Wilderness &amp; Free Trade Q&amp;A</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Wilderness &amp; Free Trade Q&amp;A</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@nicks nicks]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/nicks">@nicks</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>this helped with a few questions</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/wilderness-free-trade-q-a/379372/12">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/wilderness-free-trade-q-a/379372/12</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 22 Jan 2011 02:06:04 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-379372-12</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/wilderness-free-trade-q-a/379372.rss">Wilderness &amp; Free Trade Q&amp;A</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Wilderness &amp; Free Trade Q&amp;A</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@davidi2 Davidi2]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/davidi2">@davidi2</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Looking good <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/smiley.png?v=5" title=":smiley:" class="emoji" alt=":smiley:"></p>
<p>I could use some GP <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=5" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/wilderness-free-trade-q-a/379372/11">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/wilderness-free-trade-q-a/379372/11</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 22 Jan 2011 01:56:06 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-379372-11</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/wilderness-free-trade-q-a/379372.rss">Wilderness &amp; Free Trade Q&amp;A</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Wilderness &amp; Free Trade Q&amp;A</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@the_elve_age the elve age]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/the_elve_age">@the_elve_age</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“The Soul, post:6, topic:379372”][quote author=LilXCj link=topic=475217.msg3475276#msg3475276 date=1295648142]<br>
Looks like they removed the 2 minute restriction on dropping items. Now people will see them immediately.<br>
[/quote]</p>
<p>I think that’s only for the wilderness.[/quote]</p>
<p>It is.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/wilderness-free-trade-q-a/379372/10">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/wilderness-free-trade-q-a/379372/10</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 22 Jan 2011 01:10:22 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-379372-10</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/wilderness-free-trade-q-a/379372.rss">Wilderness &amp; Free Trade Q&amp;A</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Wilderness &amp; Free Trade Q&amp;A</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Clawz_fury lare69]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/clawz_fury">@Clawz_fury</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote no-group" data-post="8" data-topic="379372">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/xxlukexx/40/5_1887921562df0dabfae55079ddabeb03.png" class="avatar"> xxlukexx:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Sounds good, answered all my questions  ;D</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/wilderness-free-trade-q-a/379372/9">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/wilderness-free-trade-q-a/379372/9</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 21 Jan 2011 23:42:39 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-379372-9</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/wilderness-free-trade-q-a/379372.rss">Wilderness &amp; Free Trade Q&amp;A</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Wilderness &amp; Free Trade Q&amp;A</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@xxlukexx xxlukexx]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/xxlukexx">@xxlukexx</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Sounds good, answered all my questions  ;D</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/wilderness-free-trade-q-a/379372/8">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/wilderness-free-trade-q-a/379372/8</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 21 Jan 2011 23:33:26 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-379372-8</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/wilderness-free-trade-q-a/379372.rss">Wilderness &amp; Free Trade Q&amp;A</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Wilderness &amp; Free Trade Q&amp;A</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@drunk_mario drunk mario]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/drunk_mario">@drunk_mario</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>thanks for the guide! helped a lot!</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/wilderness-free-trade-q-a/379372/7">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/wilderness-free-trade-q-a/379372/7</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 21 Jan 2011 23:03:31 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-379372-7</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/wilderness-free-trade-q-a/379372.rss">Wilderness &amp; Free Trade Q&amp;A</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Wilderness &amp; Free Trade Q&amp;A</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@the_soul The Soul]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/the_soul">@the_soul</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote no-group" data-post="5" data-topic="379372">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/lilxcj/40/5_1887921562df0dabfae55079ddabeb03.png" class="avatar"> LilXCj:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Looks like they removed the 2 minute restriction on dropping items. Now people will see them immediately.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I think that’s only for the wilderness.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/wilderness-free-trade-q-a/379372/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/wilderness-free-trade-q-a/379372/6</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 21 Jan 2011 22:23:03 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-379372-6</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/wilderness-free-trade-q-a/379372.rss">Wilderness &amp; Free Trade Q&amp;A</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Wilderness &amp; Free Trade Q&amp;A</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@LilXCj LilXCj]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/lilxcj">@LilXCj</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Looks like they removed the 2 minute restriction on dropping items. Now people will see them immediately.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/wilderness-free-trade-q-a/379372/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/wilderness-free-trade-q-a/379372/5</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 21 Jan 2011 22:15:42 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-379372-5</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/wilderness-free-trade-q-a/379372.rss">Wilderness &amp; Free Trade Q&amp;A</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Wilderness &amp; Free Trade Q&amp;A</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@reyx7 reyx7]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/reyx7">@reyx7</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Glad to hear the improvements.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/wilderness-free-trade-q-a/379372/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/wilderness-free-trade-q-a/379372/4</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 21 Jan 2011 21:57:38 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-379372-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/wilderness-free-trade-q-a/379372.rss">Wilderness &amp; Free Trade Q&amp;A</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Wilderness &amp; Free Trade Q&amp;A</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@k0_twin k0 twin]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/k0_twin">@k0_twin</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Ahh thank you for this</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/wilderness-free-trade-q-a/379372/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/wilderness-free-trade-q-a/379372/3</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 21 Jan 2011 20:19:06 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-379372-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/wilderness-free-trade-q-a/379372.rss">Wilderness &amp; Free Trade Q&amp;A</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Wilderness &amp; Free Trade Q&amp;A</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@usman555 usman555]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/usman555">@usman555</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>My friend is so happy I can give him 500k now, because I don’t play any more. Lol.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/wilderness-free-trade-q-a/379372/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/wilderness-free-trade-q-a/379372/2</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 21 Jan 2011 19:55:41 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-379372-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/wilderness-free-trade-q-a/379372.rss">Wilderness &amp; Free Trade Q&amp;A</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Wilderness &amp; Free Trade Q&amp;A</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@_Rich Rich]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/_rich">@_Rich</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <blockquote>[b][u]General FAQ[/u][/b]
<p><span class="bbcode-b">How will the Grand Exchange work now?</span></p>
<p>Essentially it will work exactly how it worked before, just without any price restrictions. It means you will be able to offer to buy or sell at the price you think is right.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Will there be guide prices?</span></p>
<p>Yes. The guide price will be based on the previous day’s trading. The guide price will usually only change by a maximum of 5% per day, just as it currently works.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Will we be able to buy/sell items for whatever we want now?</span></p>
<p>Yes, assuming you find a buyer/ seller of course.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Can I give gifts to my friends now? Like a million if I wanted too?</span></p>
<p>Yes indeed!</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">You’ve said that the price limits will be removed, but what about the buying restrictions?</span></p>
<p>Buying restrictions will remain in place. These exist purely to reduce market monopoly and ensure a higher number of players can buy high demand objects like god swords.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b"><span class="bbcode-u">Scamming</span></span></p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Will item scamming be a problem? What is being done to prevent item scamming?</span></p>
<p>Rules will still be in place to prevent item scamming, and players breaking those rules will suffer the wrath of our player support team. Warning screens, wildy walls, better examine options and clearer rules will help to prevent scamming – however, ultimately it’s up to you, the player to protect yourself just as it is today. Remember, if a deal sounds too good to be true, it probably is.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Will the trade warnings still be in the trade window to prevent item scamming?</span></p>
<p>Yes, and if people try to change the trade you will still have large red exclamation marks telling you that changes have occurred, which have to be re-confirmed.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b"><span class="bbcode-u">Staking</span></span></p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">What is going to happen with staking at the Duel Arena?</span></p>
<p>Staking is returning! So you will be able to bet anything tradable on the outcome of the battle.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Will I be able to stake in any other Activities?</span></p>
<p>You will be able to stake in Conquest!</p>
<p>The rat pits also remains if you want to bet a few coins on your cats prowess, but that’s just for fun and has restrictions in place.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Will you add more options for staking in the Duel Arena? For example “No Degradable Items” or “Team Staking”?</span></p>
<p>Not at this time, but potentially in the future.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">What’s happening to duel tournaments?</span></p>
<p>We are switching off the duel tournaments with a view to reworking the activity in the future. Simply put, it wasn’t providing the service that either the players or JAGEX wanted to offer, and we felt it was better to remove it totally. People’s ranks and hiscores will be preserved in case they are relevant in the future.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b"><span class="bbcode-u">Price Checker</span></span></p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Will the price checker feature be removed/changed now that players can freely trade?</span></p>
<p>It’s not being removed, it just won’t show trade limits any more. It will show the guide price (discussed above).</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b"><span class="bbcode-u">Gravestones</span></span></p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">How will gravestones work now?</span></p>
<p>If you die in the wilderness there will be no gravestone. At all. If you were killed by a player, they get the drop. If you were killed by monster, the drop appears for everyone immediately.</p>
<p>Some areas of the wilderness are still PK free (like the original mage arena). In those areas AND in the rest of the game, a gravestone will appear and exist just as they do today. The gravestone can still be blessed and maintained by other players. A player returning to their gravestone will be able to reclaim all their lost items.</p>
<p>If a player doesn’t return to their gravestone and it crumbles away, all players will be able to pick up the loot.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b"><span class="bbcode-u">Lending Items</span></span></p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">How will item lending work? Will it be changed in anyway?</span></p>
<p>You can’t use borrowed items in the wilderness and you can’t stake a lent item. Aside from that it’s exactly as it was before. This isn’t restricted to combat gear, no lent items can be used at all in the wilderness.</p>
<p>If you enter the wilderness with one equipped you will have the lent item removed to your inventory, banked, or returned to the owner, depending on the space available.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b"><span class="bbcode-u">Party Room</span></span></p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Will the Party Room be changed? Will they alert banks every time there is a drop on that world?</span></p>
<p>The party room remains in place but with no chest restrictions. Bankers and citizens will no longer chat spam. Items drop as soon as lever is pulled, there is no big countdown.</p>
<p>Hopefully player owned party rooms in the future</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b"><span class="bbcode-u">Player-owned House Reward Chests</span></span></p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Will the limits on POH reward chests be lifted?</span></p>
<p>The coin restrictions for each level of reward chest have been increased dramatically, with the top level chest (magic) having no restrictions.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b"><span class="bbcode-u">Dropping objects in the Wilderness</span></span></p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">How will dropping items in the Wilderness work now?</span></p>
<p>If you manually drop items on the floor in the Wilderness, they will be visible to everyone immediately, as long as the items were tradeable. Untradeable items will never become visible to other players.</p>
<p>If you manually put items on a table in the Wilderness, they will be visible to everyone immediately.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b"><span class="bbcode-u">Wilderness/PvP Questions</span></span></p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Will we able to use extreme potions in the Wilderness?</span></p>
<p>No. However, a player with an “extreme” boost who enters the wilderness will have the boost reduced to “super” level. This duplicates the current function on PvP worlds.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">What about untradeable items like Dungeoneering rewards/Korasi’s sword/fire capes etc? How will these work in the Wilderness?</span></p>
<p>One of three things will happen. Some objects will vanish, some drop cash (like anchor pre 07, will include Korasi’s sword), others drop a tradable equivalent (like summoning headgear that’s enchanted being dropped un-enchanted). Most popular untradeable PvP equipment will not vanish.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">What about the revenants? What is going to happen with them?</span></p>
<p>Revenants will be added to a new PvP enabled dungeon. Revenants will have all PvP unique drops such as brawlers, corrupt dragon and statues added to them. Revenants will no longer teleblock or freeze opponents but will continue to change combat styles and generally cause havoc.</p>
<p>The Forinthry bracelet now has new functionality – you can use it to repel revenants and also give temporary immunity to damage from them.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">What is going to happen to all the old PvP world drops like statius sets or artifacts etc?</span></p>
<p>See above – will be dropped by revs.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Will we have all the old PvP mechanics back just as they were? Will there be any big changes?</span></p>
<p>It’s pretty much back as it was.</p>
<p>There are a few extra escape routes in the wilderness than there were before, however most of them cannot be used whilst under attack.</p>
<p>Obviously we have new weapons, curses and an entire summoning skill to generate new tactics.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">What about all the quests that are in the Wilderness? Will these be left where they are or moved?</span></p>
<p>No player doing a quest will ever be under the threat of being killed by another player. Quests will exist in areas of the wilderness but these areas cannot be used for pking.</p>
<p>Post quest rewards like the beacon network and spirit of summer portals will remain in the wilderness, with some gaining extra rewards to compensate for the extra risk. Players who already have the original reward can return to collect the “bonus” we have added.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Will I have to walk through the Wilderness to get to the lair of the Corporeal Beast?</span></p>
<p>No. The games necklace will have a teleport option that will take you into the first cave if you have completed Summers End. If you’re feeling brave you can walk there of course.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">What about all the minigames/activities that are in the Wilderness? Will these be left where they are or moved?</span></p>
<p>They will be relocated. There is a new cave located just north of Falador called the “Gamers Grotto” which will contain Stealing Creation, Clan Wars and a portal to fist of Guthix. Previous teleport options will now direct the player here.</p>
<p>Clan wars dangerous “free for all” battles will now follow standard wilderness rules of item loss.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">What about penguins or shooting stars? Will they be moved out of the Wilderness?</span></p>
<p>We have not changed anything regarding the penguins or the shooting stars.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">What about treasure trails?</span></p>
<p>The number of possible treasure trail locations remains the same, however you won’t be sent to the wilderness as often as you were.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Will you add any “safe” worlds for non-pkers to use without fear of being killed?</span></p>
<p>No. It’s the wilderness, it’s not meant to be safe.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Changes to the engine, like RuneTek5 will change the way PvP works, as a lot of old tactics like trapping people. Will this be changed back?</span></p>
<p>No.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">What about 1 itemers? I hate 1 itemers…</span></p>
<p>We’re designating a small number of worlds as High-Risk Wilderness Worlds. On those worlds, the Protect Item prayer and curse cannot be used inside the Wilderness. Outside the Wilderness, the prayer and curse will work as normal. You would be warned before logging into these worlds.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Are you changing the PvP and Bounty worlds?</span></p>
<p>Yes. PvP worlds will no longer exist. Bounty mechanics will be removed. Bounty and Rogue hiscores will remain. In the future we intend to create a new activity using bounty hunter gameplay. Those worlds previously used for PvP and bounties will now become suggested worlds for Pking and high risk wilderness (see above).</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">In the original wilderness there used to be a tactic of attacking a monster and deliberately trying not to kill it in order to escape from a pker. You changed it for PvP worlds. Are you bringing that back?</span></p>
<p>That tactic has been removed. Any player attacking a monster in the wilderness can be attacked by another player, even if you are in single way combat.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b"><span class="bbcode-u">The volcano banker</span></span></p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Is the bank by the craters going to be removed?</span></p>
<p>Yes. Look out for Maximillian Sackville in a bank near you!</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b"><span class="bbcode-u">Summoning</span></span></p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">How will Summoning work in the Wilderness?</span></p>
<p>While you are in the wilderness, your combat level will act as though you didn’t have any summoning, so will be a maximum of 126. All calculations regarding which other players you can fight will be based on this level, just as with F2P wilderness.</p>
<p>If you have any summoning levels, your combat level display will indicate this. This will give other players an idea of your “potential” to summon aid.</p>
<p>For example:</p>
<p>If you are currently a level 138 player, your combat level in the wilderness would be displayed thus:</p>
<p>xxepicpkerxx 126+12</p>
<p>If you were in level 3 wilderness, you could fight players between level 123 and 126. Those players would be able to see the +12 and so would know of your potential to summon ALL familiars – particularly dangerous in multiway combat areas.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">What happens when my familiar or I die while in the Wilderness?</span></p>
<p>When your familiar dies or despawns while carrying items in the Wilderness, the items will be dropped. If it was killed by another player, that player will get the dropped items first, then later to everyone as with normal wilderness kills. Otherwise, the items will become visible to EVERYONE immediately, so you can’t sneakily dismiss your familiar to prevent pkers getting the loot.</p>
<p>If you are killed while your familiar is carrying items, those items will be awarded to your pker, just like the items in your inventory.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Can I attack other familiars? What will happen?</span></p>
<p>Attacking someone’s familiar in the Wilderness will follow the standard rules of engagement, so you will be skulled if you’re the aggressor.</p>
<p>Ordering your familiar to attack a player or familiar will follow exactly the same rules.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b"><span class="bbcode-u">Other small changes to Wilderness content</span></span></p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Anything else being added or changed?</span></p>
<p>Runite rocks in the wilderness will refill much faster than other Runite rocks in the game.</p>
<p>The chaos Elemental has had his drop table improved and can also drop the old PvP specific armour and weapons.</p>
</blockquote><br>
<a href="http://services.runescape.com/m=forum/forums.ws?254,255,55,62204744" class="onebox" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">http://services.runescape.com/m=forum/forums.ws?254,255,55,62204744</a>
<p>Sounds great tbh.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/wilderness-free-trade-q-a/379372/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/wilderness-free-trade-q-a/379372/1</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 21 Jan 2011 19:49:41 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-379372-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/wilderness-free-trade-q-a/379372.rss">Wilderness &amp; Free Trade Q&amp;A</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
