<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Frames ? where do i put them?</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/frames-where-do-i-put-them/66729</link>
    <description>I read this but i don&#39;t know where i need to put it ? 
Let&#39;s move onto Frames now. Here are a few examples of Frames, sendQuests, and sendMessages being used:


Code:
sendQuest(&quot;@gre@Welcome to Freescape&quot;, 8145);
Code:
sendMessage(&quot;Oh dear you are dead!&quot;);
Code:
sendFrame126(&quot;TzHaar&quot;, 2484); 
Ok the first one &quot;showQuest&quot; is tell to show &quot;Welcome to Freescape&quot; on an interface (in this case the interface is inside the void MainHelpMenu.) The &quot;8145&quot; is the programmed frame of where the &quot;showQuest&quot; will show up in the Interface. Now the &quot;sendMessage&quot; is easy. When you die (in this sequence), then it will send a message in the chat box saying &quot;Oh dear you are dead!&quot;. This is simple enough. Now we will move onto the frame one. &quot;sendFrame126&quot; is saying that in that case (case 75 in this sequence) is sending frame126 to the amulet of glory saying in a frame &quot;TzHaar&quot;. This is as simple as it can get, sorry. I hope you understand the different purposes of this section of chapter 3.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 11 Mar 2007 14:24:54 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/frames-where-do-i-put-them/66729.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Frames ? where do i put them?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@jonaske jonaske]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/jonaske">@jonaske</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I read this but i don’t know where i need to put it ?<br>
Let’s move onto Frames now. Here are a few examples of Frames, sendQuests, and sendMessages being used:</p>
<p>Code:<br>
sendQuest("<span class="mention">@gre</span>@Welcome to Freescape", 8145);<br>
Code:<br>
sendMessage(“Oh dear you are dead!”);<br>
Code:<br>
sendFrame126(“TzHaar”, 2484);<br>
Ok the first one “showQuest” is tell to show “Welcome to Freescape” on an interface (in this case the interface is inside the void MainHelpMenu.) The “8145” is the programmed frame of where the “showQuest” will show up in the Interface. Now the “sendMessage” is easy. When you die (in this sequence), then it will send a message in the chat box saying “Oh dear you are dead!”. This is simple enough. Now we will move onto the frame one. “sendFrame126” is saying that in that case (case 75 in this sequence) is sending frame126 to the amulet of glory saying in a frame “TzHaar”. This is as simple as it can get, sorry. I hope you understand the different purposes of this section of chapter 3.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/frames-where-do-i-put-them/66729/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/frames-where-do-i-put-them/66729/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 11 Mar 2007 14:24:54 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-66729-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/frames-where-do-i-put-them/66729.rss">Frames ? where do i put them?</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
