<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Why cod4, 5 and 6 are bad games</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/why-cod4-5-and-6-are-bad-games/284550</link>
    <description>Ok, so, I&#39;ve been meaning to post this for a while now but I never got around to it, and I know 6 hasn&#39;t been released yet but there&#39;s a reason I&#39;ve included it. 

For anyone about to post tl;dr, this is mainly for cod fanboys, most of the points listed are pretty obvious and I&#39;d only expect someone with as much free time as me to actually read, and reply, such as tico.  :P

Hint: just scroll down to the bold bits for a summary.

Well, cod4, I wasn&#39;t going to buy it but I was told this game was the dogs bollocks, endless reviews praised it and even Yahtzee from Zero Punctuation said it was a good game, so I decided to buy it. After all, I had heard it &quot;revolutionized&quot; the FPS genre. Single player wasn&#39;t that good, and gameplay was worse. I mean, this is about cod and I know that, but almost instant deaths from shots are NOT realistic, and in games make them almost unplayable. Take for example, death by limb shots. Sure, it&#39;d be painful as heal and you probably would die of shock, bloodloss or whatever but it wouldn&#39;t kill you as quick as a headshot, and I know this is a reoccurring problem in FPS games but it&#39;s easily fixed, but anyway, on to multiplayer. As I&#39;m sure many of you may remember, multiplayer was full of faggots using lmgs, actually first, I&#39;ll discuss a few problems with cod4 specifically first.

Lets talk about lag. When I first got cod4 I had a 2mbit package and only in the last week have I been able to experience 20mbit speeds in games, and I&#39;ll explain more later, but on 2mbit I could play fine with not too many deaths due to me experiencing lag, to give you a comparison, say in Quake 4 or KZ2, if you lag, the enemeis stop, you stop, and you die because you&#39;re a sitting duck. In cod4 however(and 5), you can run, shoot and kill enemies while you&#39;re not synced with everyone else, and for the most part get away with lagging, I&#39;ve probably done it a lot of times, and it&#39;s happened to me more times than I can count to, well, not really but it&#39;s a big reason as to why I get a lot of extra kills and deaths. Another thing that is probably related to lag is hitboxes, I&#39;m sure you&#39;ve seen some css vids where the hitboxes are 2-3 ft in front of where they should be, and while cod4 isn&#39;t as bad as this, in a lot of the replays someone seems to be aiming say, towards my groin and get headshots(more on this in a bit) due to some fuckery with height levels.

Another problem with cod4 is bullet penetration, this was a big selling point and while it [s]works as expected[/s] is an interesting feature, it&#39;s funny how handgun bullets can penetrate several layers of brick walls and still kill. This, along with deep impact means the maps may as well be in an empty room without cover, which is basically what killhouse is. I can&#39;t really put much more here, bullets eat through everything as if they were made of steel, and while armour piercing rounds are made of hardened steel, it doesn&#39;t make much of a difference if you use deep impact or not, which suggests all rounds are armour piercing. 

Another thing terribly wrong in cod4 and 5 is firing from the hip, maybe I&#39;m just a console tard but honestly, I&#39;m just as good with a joystick while sniping in cod than I am with a mouse, I don&#39;t see why aiming has to be dummed down to the point where if they&#39;re in front of you, it doesn&#39;t matter if you actually aim on them or not, they still die if you shoot them first. I remember the days where high powered guns shot to the direct center of the screen, in cod4 and 5 they just slap a wide crosshair on all sniper rifles which really, REALLY won&#39;t hit anyone at close distance, even if you crouch. I mean, ok, supposedly there are ways of no-scoping perfectly but I&#39;ve tried and I tried hard, but the only kills I&#39;ve got while no-scoping were pure fluke where I didn&#39;t try the techniques I found on youtube.  :|

Finally that brings me to LMGs, balancing in cod4 is terrible. Lets take the MP5, it&#39;s accurate, useful at medium to long distance, nice fire rate, and kills very effectively, just like the m4. P90 does well, it does very well in fact and I&#39;d rather have it over any assault rifle in any situation. The rest of the smgs and assault rifles are a joke and usually have reduced damage in return for stats that won&#39;t help, such as range. Sniper rifles are next, and while the M40A3, Dragonuv(at a pinch) and the 50cal all act as sniper rifles should, the m21 often takes 2 shots to kill, and the r700 is a joke, 1 less bullet than M40A3 and for what? I can&#39;t really comment on shotguns as they work perfectly, which brings me to LMGs. They can kill anything through anything faster than you can aim and shoot, they&#39;re easy to use, come with HUUUUUUUGE clips and while the reloading times are slow to make up for it, you can use sleight of hand(stopping power isn&#39;t that useful with LMGs), and finding a place to reload and even change your knickers isn&#39;t THAT hard. Lets recap, most smgs are a little worse than assault rifles, the mp5 may as well be an assault rifle, and the p90 is the best of them. The sniper rifles are ok, but there&#39;s really no reason to use M21 and R700, and the other 3 are almost identical, shotguns are fine and LMGs act like all of these, with more ammo. 

[b]So, why is cod4 a bad game?[/b] It&#39;s very generic, it was hyped up, there&#39;s some bad gameplay issues that need fixing(for example, bullet penetration), guns need balancing, martyrdom is as stupid as it is annoying, grenades &quot;cook&quot; too long, there&#39;s a lot of network issues, did I mention it was hyped?

Now, cod5, I like cod5, mostly. For those who don&#39;t know, it&#39;s basically cod4 if it were reskinned. I&#39;ll try to keep treyarch bashing at a minimum but it&#39;s hard to resist. 

I&#39;ll start with lag same as last time. The first few hours I played of cod5 online I was surprised, I could actually play a game instead of spending 10 minutes joining a game for the host to fucking quit and games to fucking freeze, I can probably count the times games have ended due to host on both hands instead of needing a calculator for cod4. Generally the network code has improved dramatically, you can notice a difference. They seem to have borked something along the way though, maybe this was like it in cod4 but I haven&#39;t played it in a long time. Take a scenario, I have a double barrel shotgun, it&#39;s instant kill within a few feet and only takes 2 shots at 10 ft or so, I hide around a corner. Someone comes around the corner facing me(read: not shooting, not about to shoot), I go to shoot but nope, I&#39;ve already died. It took me a REALLY long time to figure out why this is happening, clients don&#39;t sync properly(and it isn&#39;t a ping issue, it has happened every game where I have a free 20mbit download speed available) so if you&#39;re an unlucky bastard who&#39;s not up to speed with everyone else, there isn&#39;t anything you can do other than hope your shots killed him and hope some more that no one&#39;s around that corner because by the time you see them you&#39;ll be dead, which brings me to my next argument. 

Weapons in cod5 are seriously a joke. The stg is basically the only good rifle. The others just don&#39;t have a big enough clip to damage ratio, and compared to say, PISTOLS, just don&#39;t work. Now, since machine guns were a huge problem in cod4, you&#39;d expect them to be nerfed in cod5 right? Well, if you said yes, go treat yourself to a cookie because they were, mostly. There are a lot of them, each having it&#39;s own strong and weak points, sort of. The biggest advantage is the ability to well, mount them using a bipod that you unlock, this gives dramatically reduced recoil and make machine guns a reliable option for medium to long range shooting that&#39;s better than anything other than bolt action rifles. Now, the problem is, instead of fucking trying to fix the glitch with bipods in prone, treyarch just removed it. Nice...  Bolt action rifles are okay I guess, can&#39;t complain about shotguns, and smgs, well, they&#39;re enough to make me trade the game in when I can be assed. Lets just say, smgs are cod4&#39;s lmgs, they have the least recoil of any automatic gun, they have ridiculous power, more than their real life equivalents, better range and penetration and all. Lets take the mp40, 2 shots to kill with stopping power, 3 or 4 without. If you have juggernaut it&#39;ll buy you: no extra time. The mp40 has less recoil than any gun in the game, and compared to the mp40 in cod2, it is an absolute joke. I honestly think treyarch employees just knocked off for lunch during balance testing and couldn&#39;t be assed to finish it. I mean, any noob can use the mp40 and they do, every single game I&#39;ve played on cod5 has had some faggot using an mp40. I just got off a game on cod5(as I&#39;m playing it between paragraphs) and every single time I died the enemy was using an mp40. I mean, the crosshair is pathetic on it(as it is with all smgs), [url=http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=AjHFgTMyjlM]watch this video[/url], you can see the recoil he gets after 2-3 shots, yet you can get (mostly) perfect kills firing it in full auto like [url=http://www.9thsspanzer.com/Images/PhotoGallery/Events/2007/Mifflin-April/MP40.jpg]this[/url]. If you fired the magnum or a rifle from the hip you just committed suicide, so why should smgs be different?

Finally there are the glitches, for every one treyarch fixes some retard adds another, it wasn&#39;t bad but jesus christ, it seems they just can&#39;t fix these things. I really can&#39;t comment but it has to be mentioned.

[b]So, why do I think cod5 is a bad game?[/b] Well, I was hoping it would fix some of the problems cod4 had, but in the end for what it fixed it added, heavily. You can just refer to the cod4 list as that&#39;s adequate, but I honestly think mp40 and smgs need to be added, the guns need balancing but these are just unbelievable. As I&#39;ve been playing recently(with 20mbit speeds, should have a decent ping) I still get killed quicker by an mp40 faster than I can shoot with a shotgun, and it&#39;s not the shotgun that&#39;s the problem. In the last few games I&#39;ve noticed, either my shotgun has bad taste in who it wants to kill or the game is fucked, at 5ft I &quot;hit&quot; with both shots but it won&#39;t kill them, I get sprayed with an mp40 and die faster than I can think of what I can do to not die. What&#39;s surprising is I get kills at 8-9 ft without needing to fire again, in the same games!

So, it&#39;s been around 2 hours since I started this post so I&#39;ll try to make the next bit quick: why I think cod6 will be bad. 

I&#39;ll start with camoflauge, this is a huge problem in cod4 or 5, you go in prone, move the crosshair a tiny bit to the left or right and your body swings 180 degrees with your legs sticking out wearing green neon lights saying &quot;his head is here&quot;, ready for a sniper to shoot. This happens regularly standing up, in crouch(which I should add, moving in crouch &quot;raises&quot; you but it doesn&#39;t raise your view angle so you have no way to tell if the enemy can actually see you, many times I&#39;ve been killed because my back is actually visible to them when to me it looks like it&#39;s 1 ft below the cover I&#39;m hiding behind). Next I think they&#39;ll break weapon balancing again. I won&#39;t be buying the game unless some highly biased fuck convinces me it&#39;s good(yes, I mean you thug) so I won&#39;t be around to tell, but I guarantee they&#39;ll fuck something up bad enough to make everyone and their dog abuse it. I also imagine there will be more network code bugs, but hopefully no glitches(considering cod4 was fine the most part). If martyrdom isn&#39;t removed or modified in, you know, a more humanly possible way then the multiplayer mode will definitely ruined, and generally the rest of the perks need balancing(and not by treyarch&#39;s staff who think like: &quot;we&#39;ll stick stopping power at a low level, add a powerful gun at low level and everyone else can go fuck themselves&quot;). Next I think they&#39;ll ignore weapon penetration, I like the idea of lead bullets actually disintegrating on hard surfaces while bullet penetration adds(or is removed completely, while armour piercing ammunition is added as a weapon addon) armour piercing ammunition which work like before. I think if a lot of this stuff is fixed it&#39;ll deserve the hype it&#39;s had, but I guess only time will tell.

So guys, thanks for reading, I&#39;m sure you had more fun reading this than I had playing cod 10 minutes, I&#39;ll look forward to some replies.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 08 Jul 2009 20:29:41 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Games</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/why-cod4-5-and-6-are-bad-games/284550.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Why cod4, 5 and 6 are bad games</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@The_Un-Named The Un-Named]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/the_un-named">@The_Un-Named</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote no-group quote-modified" data-post="67" data-topic="284550">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/goatee/40/5_513041d5f7104045db30895d3b90af16.png" class="avatar"> goatee:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>If it’s not good, then why do some many “pro-gamers” play it and use it to measure skill. Why would there be hype after the game is out and why would it still be popular nearly 2 years after its release?</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>So because “pro-gamers” still play it, it means it’s good? Because it has hype it’s good?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/why-cod4-5-and-6-are-bad-games/284550/71">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/why-cod4-5-and-6-are-bad-games/284550/71</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 08 Jul 2009 20:29:41 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-284550-71</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/why-cod4-5-and-6-are-bad-games/284550.rss">Why cod4, 5 and 6 are bad games</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Why cod4, 5 and 6 are bad games</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@fellixombc fellixombc]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/fellixombc">@fellixombc</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>COD4 hands down was a great game imo. COD5, lasted a week for me, but in general, it sucked.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/why-cod4-5-and-6-are-bad-games/284550/70">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/why-cod4-5-and-6-are-bad-games/284550/70</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 08 Jul 2009 05:38:37 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-284550-70</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/why-cod4-5-and-6-are-bad-games/284550.rss">Why cod4, 5 and 6 are bad games</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Why cod4, 5 and 6 are bad games</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@tL tL]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/tl">@tL</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“goatee, post:67, topic:284550”]It’s good because of the power weapons. It requires tactics (even if they are just “rush”) to get to them. Key locations and weapons can sway a game aloe. It’s not like Call of Duty where you can just pick up a kill by spraying and it’s a great game for teams/clans.</p>
<p>If it’s not good, then why do some many “pro-gamers” play it and use it to measure skill. Why would there be hype after the game is out and why would it still be popular nearly 2 years after its release?[/quote]<br>
The same reason wii fit is still popular</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/why-cod4-5-and-6-are-bad-games/284550/69">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/why-cod4-5-and-6-are-bad-games/284550/69</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jul 2009 19:01:03 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-284550-69</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/why-cod4-5-and-6-are-bad-games/284550.rss">Why cod4, 5 and 6 are bad games</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Why cod4, 5 and 6 are bad games</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@sanga282 sanga282]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/sanga282">@sanga282</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“goatee, post:67, topic:284550”]It’s good because of the power weapons. It requires tactics (even if they are just “rush”) to get to them. Key locations and weapons can sway a game aloe. It’s not like Call of Duty where you can just pick up a kill by spraying and it’s a great game for teams/clans.</p>
<p>If it’s not good, then why do some many “pro-gamers” play it and use it to measure skill. Why would there be hype after the game is out and why would it still be popular nearly 2 years after its release?[/quote]<br>
pro gamers use a PC, amateurs use consoles</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/why-cod4-5-and-6-are-bad-games/284550/68">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/why-cod4-5-and-6-are-bad-games/284550/68</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 06 Jul 2009 13:19:59 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-284550-68</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/why-cod4-5-and-6-are-bad-games/284550.rss">Why cod4, 5 and 6 are bad games</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Why cod4, 5 and 6 are bad games</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@goatee goatee]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/goatee">@goatee</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>It’s good because of the power weapons. It requires tactics (even if they are just “rush”) to get to them. Key locations and weapons can sway a game aloe. It’s not like Call of Duty where you can just pick up a kill by spraying and it’s a great game for teams/clans.</p>
<p>If it’s not good, then why do some many “pro-gamers” play it and use it to measure skill. Why would there be hype after the game is out and why would it still be popular nearly 2 years after its release?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/why-cod4-5-and-6-are-bad-games/284550/67">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/why-cod4-5-and-6-are-bad-games/284550/67</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 06 Jul 2009 13:18:03 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-284550-67</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/why-cod4-5-and-6-are-bad-games/284550.rss">Why cod4, 5 and 6 are bad games</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Why cod4, 5 and 6 are bad games</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@tL tL]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/tl">@tL</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“nohope, post:61, topic:284550”][quote author=sanga282 link=topic=376001.msg2846189#msg2846189 date=1246298023]</p>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p>All of the CoD games blow, they are all the same content with the same engine, with the same bugs. Or so it seems to me. Then again, I’m a <span class="bbcode-b">Halo geek</span>, what do I know?</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>halo sucks nigger balls<br>
[/quote]because its not for ps3? yes.[/quote]<br>
Because its shit? Yes.</p>
<p>Honestly, i would LOVE for someone to tell me what is so fuckin’ great about halo. The story is shit, the multiplayer is decent, but that alone isn’t anywhere near half the hype it gets.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/why-cod4-5-and-6-are-bad-games/284550/66">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/why-cod4-5-and-6-are-bad-games/284550/66</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 03 Jul 2009 00:04:48 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-284550-66</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/why-cod4-5-and-6-are-bad-games/284550.rss">Why cod4, 5 and 6 are bad games</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Why cod4, 5 and 6 are bad games</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@The_Un-Named The Un-Named]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/the_un-named">@The_Un-Named</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“Speljohan, post:58, topic:284550”][quote author=Cowie` link=topic=376001.msg2849201#msg2849201 date=1246445918]<br>
Don’t worry sanga, in the whole time I’ve played CoD4 and CoD5 with Tico he’s never been able to shoot a gun with some accuracy, he shoots a gun like he’s holding it backwards.<br>
[/quote]So do i cus its 999 hard on console.[/quote]</p>
<p>I actually prefer a console to pc now, for shooters anyway. Could just be a bad mouse though.  <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/expressionless.png?v=5" title=":expressionless:" class="emoji" alt=":expressionless:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/why-cod4-5-and-6-are-bad-games/284550/65">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/why-cod4-5-and-6-are-bad-games/284550/65</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 02 Jul 2009 19:16:47 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-284550-65</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/why-cod4-5-and-6-are-bad-games/284550.rss">Why cod4, 5 and 6 are bad games</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Why cod4, 5 and 6 are bad games</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@T41 t4]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/t41">@T41</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“Cowie`, post:62, topic:284550”][quote author=nohope link=topic=376001.msg2850390#msg2850390 date=1246501032]</p>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p>All of the CoD games blow, they are all the same content with the same engine, with the same bugs. Or so it seems to me. Then again, I’m a <span class="bbcode-b">Halo geek</span>, what do I know?</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>halo sucks nigger balls<br>
[/quote]because its not for ps3? yes.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Because the only people who play it are 13 year olds who like to jump 30ft in the air and eat bullets and rpgs.[/quote]<br>
I remember how I was watching someone ~16 years old playing and could hear high-pitch voices screaming through his headset.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group quote-modified" data-post="63" data-topic="284550">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/speljohan/40/5_513041d5f7104045db30895d3b90af16.png" class="avatar"> Speljohan:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Halo is terrible. Probably the most overrated game through all times, i mean srsly. It’s not different from any other shooter.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/why-cod4-5-and-6-are-bad-games/284550/64">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/why-cod4-5-and-6-are-bad-games/284550/64</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 02 Jul 2009 13:26:26 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-284550-64</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/why-cod4-5-and-6-are-bad-games/284550.rss">Why cod4, 5 and 6 are bad games</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Why cod4, 5 and 6 are bad games</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Speljohan Speljohan]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/speljohan">@Speljohan</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Halo is terrible. Probably the most overrated game through all times, i mean srsly. It’s not different from any other shooter.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/why-cod4-5-and-6-are-bad-games/284550/63">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/why-cod4-5-and-6-are-bad-games/284550/63</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 02 Jul 2009 11:13:27 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-284550-63</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/why-cod4-5-and-6-are-bad-games/284550.rss">Why cod4, 5 and 6 are bad games</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Why cod4, 5 and 6 are bad games</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@eVokki1 Cowie`]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/evokki1">@eVokki1</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“nohope, post:61, topic:284550”][quote author=sanga282 link=topic=376001.msg2846189#msg2846189 date=1246298023]</p>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p>All of the CoD games blow, they are all the same content with the same engine, with the same bugs. Or so it seems to me. Then again, I’m a <span class="bbcode-b">Halo geek</span>, what do I know?</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>halo sucks nigger balls<br>
[/quote]because its not for ps3? yes.[/quote]<br>
Because the only people who play it are 13 year olds who like to jump 30ft in the air and eat bullets and rpgs.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/why-cod4-5-and-6-are-bad-games/284550/62">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/why-cod4-5-and-6-are-bad-games/284550/62</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 02 Jul 2009 10:43:22 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-284550-62</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/why-cod4-5-and-6-are-bad-games/284550.rss">Why cod4, 5 and 6 are bad games</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Why cod4, 5 and 6 are bad games</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@nohope nohope]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/nohope">@nohope</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“sanga282, post:40, topic:284550”][quote author=Newty link=topic=376001.msg2846184#msg2846184 date=1246297685]<br>
All of the CoD games blow, they are all the same content with the same engine, with the same bugs. Or so it seems to me. Then again, I’m a <span class="bbcode-b">Halo geek</span>, what do I know?<br>
[/quote]<br>
halo sucks nigger balls[/quote]because its not for ps3? yes.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/why-cod4-5-and-6-are-bad-games/284550/61">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/why-cod4-5-and-6-are-bad-games/284550/61</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 02 Jul 2009 02:17:12 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-284550-61</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/why-cod4-5-and-6-are-bad-games/284550.rss">Why cod4, 5 and 6 are bad games</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Why cod4, 5 and 6 are bad games</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@eVokki1 Cowie`]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/evokki1">@eVokki1</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“Tico, post:59, topic:284550”][quote author=Cowie` link=topic=376001.msg2849201#msg2849201 date=1246445918]<br>
Don’t worry sanga, in the whole time I’ve played CoD4 and CoD5 with Tico he’s never been able to shoot a gun with some accuracy, he shoots a gun like he’s holding it backwards.<br>
[/quote]<br>
My accuracy is only what, like 1% lower then yours? :D[/quote]<br>
I sweat public games for ranks, shame the leaderboards aren’t effected by clan games. I’ll admit I spray on public games, all I need to do is get some weapons and perks and keep my k/d above 2.5</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/why-cod4-5-and-6-are-bad-games/284550/60">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/why-cod4-5-and-6-are-bad-games/284550/60</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jul 2009 12:31:57 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-284550-60</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/why-cod4-5-and-6-are-bad-games/284550.rss">Why cod4, 5 and 6 are bad games</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Why cod4, 5 and 6 are bad games</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Tico135 Tico]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/tico135">@Tico135</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote no-group quote-modified" data-post="57" data-topic="284550">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 Cowie`:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Don’t worry sanga, in the whole time I’ve played CoD4 and CoD5 with Tico he’s never been able to shoot a gun with some accuracy, he shoots a gun like he’s holding it backwards.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>My accuracy is only what, like 1% lower then yours? <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/smiley.png?v=5" title=":smiley:" class="emoji" alt=":smiley:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/why-cod4-5-and-6-are-bad-games/284550/59">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/why-cod4-5-and-6-are-bad-games/284550/59</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jul 2009 12:23:44 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-284550-59</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/why-cod4-5-and-6-are-bad-games/284550.rss">Why cod4, 5 and 6 are bad games</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Why cod4, 5 and 6 are bad games</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Speljohan Speljohan]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/speljohan">@Speljohan</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“Cowie`, post:57, topic:284550”]Don’t worry sanga, in the whole time I’ve played CoD4 and CoD5 with Tico he’s never been able to shoot a gun with some accuracy, he shoots a gun like he’s holding it backwards.[/quote]So do i cus its 999 hard on console.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/why-cod4-5-and-6-are-bad-games/284550/58">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/why-cod4-5-and-6-are-bad-games/284550/58</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jul 2009 12:04:24 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-284550-58</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/why-cod4-5-and-6-are-bad-games/284550.rss">Why cod4, 5 and 6 are bad games</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Why cod4, 5 and 6 are bad games</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@eVokki1 Cowie`]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/evokki1">@eVokki1</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Don’t worry sanga, in the whole time I’ve played CoD4 and CoD5 with Tico he’s never been able to shoot a gun with some accuracy, he shoots a gun like he’s holding it backwards.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/why-cod4-5-and-6-are-bad-games/284550/57">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/why-cod4-5-and-6-are-bad-games/284550/57</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jul 2009 10:58:38 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-284550-57</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/why-cod4-5-and-6-are-bad-games/284550.rss">Why cod4, 5 and 6 are bad games</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Why cod4, 5 and 6 are bad games</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@sanga282 sanga282]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/sanga282">@sanga282</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote no-group quote-modified" data-post="54" data-topic="284550">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 Tico:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Balancing is least bit of worries in COD4.  The majority of the guns can actually beat each other easily.  Each weapon has it’s own individual uniqueness, strengths, and weaknesses.  For example, an M16 at short-medium range will lose to an MP5.  However, at medium-long range, the M16 will overpower the MP5.  It is the same like this for a lot of guns, and for the most part the assault rifles will lose to a submachine gun at short range.  My best advice to you is not to dive completely into the battle and try to keep your distance when taking corners, etc. </p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>this is bullshit. I used to use both the M16 and the MP5 and to be honest you either can overpower a person from medium distance, its all about accuracy. If you arent good enough to keep the MP5 under control long enough to kill someone with an M16 shooting at you then you should keep practicing. Yes the weapons are unbalanced because you can beat people with a bigger guns with your MP5 so quickly they dont have time to react.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/why-cod4-5-and-6-are-bad-games/284550/56">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/why-cod4-5-and-6-are-bad-games/284550/56</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jul 2009 06:46:38 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-284550-56</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/why-cod4-5-and-6-are-bad-games/284550.rss">Why cod4, 5 and 6 are bad games</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Why cod4, 5 and 6 are bad games</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@The_Un-Named The Un-Named]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/the_un-named">@The_Un-Named</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote no-group" data-post="54" data-topic="284550">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 Tico:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>the only insisted suggestion is to purchase a higher connection monthly via your service provider</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>As I said, on cod5 at least, there was no difference in gameplay on 2mbit and 20mbit other than with 20mbit(1mbit up) I could host games. I can try cod4 but I doubt it’ll change, as I said I noticed improved network gameplay with cod5 but that could just be a bad ps3 port.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-post="54" data-topic="284550">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 Tico:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>My opinions are almost entirely the same with the sole exception of extremely underpowered pistols, and snipers.  The snipers in this game a joke, and there is simply no pleasing, as regardless if you have stopping power on or not, it will more then likely take two shots to kill people unless it is a headshot.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>It’s a bit unfair to use deagle as an example, but pistols aren’t underpowered. When I first started playing cod4, one of the things I liked most was, last stand worked. You could get shot down and if the enemy is on screen there is a good chance you can kill them, and before I had unlocked the deagles I found the more ammo the handgun had, the better it was. With last stand I could kill people so easily I actually started using pistols as a secondary weapon if say, I couldn’t reload in time or whatever.</p>
<p>Ps, for sniping, try the M40A3, I’ve never had a problem with it.</p>
<p>Pps, I am disappointed. I was expecting a 20 page reply in which me and you would end up with pistols at dawn to settle it.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/why-cod4-5-and-6-are-bad-games/284550/55">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/why-cod4-5-and-6-are-bad-games/284550/55</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jul 2009 05:43:09 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-284550-55</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/why-cod4-5-and-6-are-bad-games/284550.rss">Why cod4, 5 and 6 are bad games</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Why cod4, 5 and 6 are bad games</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Tico135 Tico]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/tico135">@Tico135</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Alright since I’ve obviously been neglecting a reply to this for quite some time until I actually got to read it, here goes.  It won’t be that long, because I surprising don’t feel up to picking out every single thing you said and criticizing you about it. <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/smiley.png?v=5" title=":smiley:" class="emoji" alt=":smiley:"></p>
<p>COD4 has some problems, and you were correct in identifying what they were exactly, (with the sole exception of lag, which is just bad luck if you are constantly getting into games with lag, the only insisted suggestion is to purchase a higher connection monthly via your service provider).</p>
<p>Speaking in regards to limb-shots, I do agree that it would be a pretty cool feature to see the running ability affected by an injury, or perhaps a limp or something.</p>
<p>Now, onto bullet penetration: yes, I do agree that there is a problem with bullet penetration.  But let me ask you this; can everyone equally shoot through the walls?  The answer is yes.  There is no limitation to anyone, so they don’t have to be cheating; which does keep the game fair.  It may not be the best of features, but it is a game and as infinity ward says, they don’t focus as much on realism as they do making the game a great experience.  It could use a few tweaks, but it was nice to see the feature included.</p>
<p>Honestly, I’ve found firing from the hip to work out with very little effectiveness.  Maybe it’s just me but lets just saw I’ve lost more fire-fights shooting from the hip then I’ve won (without steady aim of course).  I have however found that using steady aim is a completely different experience, and is more-than-not decided upon where shots are fired rather then who shot first.  And for the record, no-scoping is extremely easy once you get the hang of it.  I guess this one is decided entirely upon by individual experience, experimentation, and opinion.</p>
<p>Balancing is least bit of worries in COD4.  The majority of the guns can actually beat each other easily.  Each weapon has it’s own individual uniqueness, strengths, and weaknesses.  For example, an M16 at short-medium range will lose to an MP5.  However, at medium-long range, the M16 will overpower the MP5.  It is the same like this for a lot of guns, and for the most part the assault rifles will lose to a submachine gun at short range.  My best advice to you is not to dive completely into the battle and try to keep your distance when taking corners, etc.</p>
<p>My opinions are almost entirely the same with the sole exception of extremely underpowered pistols, and snipers.  The snipers in this game a joke, and there is simply no pleasing, as regardless if you have stopping power on or not, it will more then likely take two shots to kill people unless it is a headshot.</p>
<p>In regards to glitches, yes, I agree, they are pathetic.  They have honestly had glitches with every single thing they released, which is terrible on their part.  There is a reason for testing, and it is sad they were unable to pick up most of these things.</p>
<p>Now, in regards to Modern Warfare 2, we can’t say anything because we really don’t know anything.  I can almost guarantee you that martyrdom will be tweaked.  I can almost confirm this, as Infinity Ward’s community manager, Robert Bowling has said in various interviews that they had a lot of complaints about it via their Twitter feed, and were more the less looking at the replies that asked for them to tweak it.  An example of a rumor was only dropping the grenade on death if the player had one left to drop (if they hadn’t used it).</p>
<p>Other then that, if you want me to expand on anything just ask and I will be more then happy, because I know you were waiting for my reply in particular. <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=5" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/why-cod4-5-and-6-are-bad-games/284550/54">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/why-cod4-5-and-6-are-bad-games/284550/54</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jul 2009 01:10:29 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-284550-54</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/why-cod4-5-and-6-are-bad-games/284550.rss">Why cod4, 5 and 6 are bad games</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Why cod4, 5 and 6 are bad games</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@tL tL]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/tl">@tL</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote no-group quote-modified" data-post="52" data-topic="284550">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 Full Metalst:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>You don’t even do computer graphics, how the hell do you know?</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>He has a pair of his own eyes? You don’t need to be an expert to analyse video game graphics.</p>
<p>I do too think WaW’s graphics are slightly better though, but thats all a matter of opinion.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/why-cod4-5-and-6-are-bad-games/284550/53">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/why-cod4-5-and-6-are-bad-games/284550/53</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jul 2009 00:03:51 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-284550-53</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/why-cod4-5-and-6-are-bad-games/284550.rss">Why cod4, 5 and 6 are bad games</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Why cod4, 5 and 6 are bad games</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Full_Metalst Full Metalst]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/full_metalst">@Full_Metalst</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“Cowie`, post:51, topic:284550”][quote author=Full Metalst link=topic=376001.msg2848064#msg2848064 date=1246390262]</p>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p>All of the CoD games blow, they are all the same content with the same engine, with the same bugs. Or so it seems to me. Then again, I’m a <span class="bbcode-b">Halo geek</span>, what do I know?</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>halo sucks nigger balls<br>
[/quote]True story but the only good CoD-game was 2.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>The graphics on 1-4 sucked.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>WaW graphics are fucking terrible compared to Modern warfare, the fuck are you talking about you dumb gypsy.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>No, look at them. WaW’s graphics are clearly better. If you knew something about graphics, you’d shut up by now. Now stop talking, and stop your feud against me, since I’m still learning graphics, you took it here. I’ll report you to a moderator if you flame me again.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>You’re a retard for thinking WaW has better graphics. 'Sif graphics matter anyway, it’s the gameplay and experience that matters.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Did you actually look at them? WaW looks more real. Gameplay-wise, I guess COD4 could be better, not much of a difference, just the guns and the time.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>The WaW graphics look choppy, too sharp and not at all realistic.[/quote]<br>
You don’t even do computer graphics, how the hell do you know?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/why-cod4-5-and-6-are-bad-games/284550/52">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/why-cod4-5-and-6-are-bad-games/284550/52</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 30 Jun 2009 21:06:18 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-284550-52</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/why-cod4-5-and-6-are-bad-games/284550.rss">Why cod4, 5 and 6 are bad games</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Why cod4, 5 and 6 are bad games</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@eVokki1 Cowie`]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/evokki1">@eVokki1</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“Full Metalst, post:48, topic:284550”][quote author=Cowie` link=topic=376001.msg2847391#msg2847391 date=1246358306]</p>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p>All of the CoD games blow, they are all the same content with the same engine, with the same bugs. Or so it seems to me. Then again, I’m a <span class="bbcode-b">Halo geek</span>, what do I know?</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>halo sucks nigger balls<br>
[/quote]True story but the only good CoD-game was 2.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>The graphics on 1-4 sucked.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>WaW graphics are fucking terrible compared to Modern warfare, the fuck are you talking about you dumb gypsy.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>No, look at them. WaW’s graphics are clearly better. If you knew something about graphics, you’d shut up by now. Now stop talking, and stop your feud against me, since I’m still learning graphics, you took it here. I’ll report you to a moderator if you flame me again.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>You’re a retard for thinking WaW has better graphics. 'Sif graphics matter anyway, it’s the gameplay and experience that matters.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Did you actually look at them? WaW looks more real. Gameplay-wise, I guess COD4 could be better, not much of a difference, just the guns and the time.[/quote]</p>
<p>The WaW graphics look choppy, too sharp and not at all realistic.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/why-cod4-5-and-6-are-bad-games/284550/51">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/why-cod4-5-and-6-are-bad-games/284550/51</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 30 Jun 2009 20:59:44 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-284550-51</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/why-cod4-5-and-6-are-bad-games/284550.rss">Why cod4, 5 and 6 are bad games</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Why cod4, 5 and 6 are bad games</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Full_Metalst Full Metalst]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/full_metalst">@Full_Metalst</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote="`Rich, post:49, topic:284550"][quote author=slayer215 link=topic=376001.msg2847982#msg2847982 date=1246386682]<br>
COD5 in multiplayer is generally terrible compared to most other fpses. The teams are often really unbalanced and the MP40 nearly ruins the whole game, also tanks were the worst idea ever.</p>
<p>Nearly all the guns are overpowered, as in you can just be running and youll fall over within half a second of bullets being shot. Also I think prestiges take way too long, it should be lowered back to lvl 55 as the highest or something.</p>
<p>The best thing about the game is War, its so much fun. I dont even know how people can play team deathmatch when theres ground war and war now.<br>
[/quote]</p>
<p>When I played WaW, all I did was play Headquarters or Hardcore S&amp;D, because Team deathmatch sucks dick on that game (mostly because the guns are unbalanced as fuck, and the only gun anyone uses is MP40). Prestige didn’t take that long either, as I got 1-10 in about ~2months (inb4 tico comment).</p>
<p>I think CoD4 has the better game play though, as I seem to play Team deathmatch on that alot more then in CoD5.</p>
<p>The one thing I dislike about CoD4 is that there is no leaderboards for certain gametypes like in CoD5, hopefully that will be cleared up with tons of other things in MW2.[/quote]<br>
What really sucks about MW2 is you can only play with 2 players… I don’t think I’m gonna buy it, not sure yet though. November is close.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/why-cod4-5-and-6-are-bad-games/284550/50">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/why-cod4-5-and-6-are-bad-games/284550/50</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 30 Jun 2009 20:19:30 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-284550-50</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/why-cod4-5-and-6-are-bad-games/284550.rss">Why cod4, 5 and 6 are bad games</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Why cod4, 5 and 6 are bad games</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@_Rich Rich]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/_rich">@_Rich</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“slayer215, post:47, topic:284550”]COD5 in multiplayer is generally terrible compared to most other fpses. The teams are often really unbalanced and the MP40 nearly ruins the whole game, also tanks were the worst idea ever.</p>
<p>Nearly all the guns are overpowered, as in you can just be running and youll fall over within half a second of bullets being shot. Also I think prestiges take way too long, it should be lowered back to lvl 55 as the highest or something.</p>
<p>The best thing about the game is War, its so much fun. I dont even know how people can play team deathmatch when theres ground war and war now.[/quote]</p>
<p>When I played WaW, all I did was play Headquarters or Hardcore S&amp;D, because Team deathmatch sucks dick on that game (mostly because the guns are unbalanced as fuck, and the only gun anyone uses is MP40). Prestige didn’t take that long either, as I got 1-10 in about ~2months (inb4 tico comment).</p>
<p>I think CoD4 has the better game play though, as I seem to play Team deathmatch on that alot more then in CoD5.</p>
<p>The one thing I dislike about CoD4 is that there is no leaderboards for certain gametypes like in CoD5, hopefully that will be cleared up with tons of other things in MW2.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/why-cod4-5-and-6-are-bad-games/284550/49">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/why-cod4-5-and-6-are-bad-games/284550/49</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 30 Jun 2009 20:04:50 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-284550-49</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/why-cod4-5-and-6-are-bad-games/284550.rss">Why cod4, 5 and 6 are bad games</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Why cod4, 5 and 6 are bad games</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Full_Metalst Full Metalst]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/full_metalst">@Full_Metalst</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“Cowie`, post:46, topic:284550”][quote author=Full Metalst link=topic=376001.msg2846655#msg2846655 date=1246318299]</p>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p>All of the CoD games blow, they are all the same content with the same engine, with the same bugs. Or so it seems to me. Then again, I’m a <span class="bbcode-b">Halo geek</span>, what do I know?</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>halo sucks nigger balls<br>
[/quote]True story but the only good CoD-game was 2.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>The graphics on 1-4 sucked.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>WaW graphics are fucking terrible compared to Modern warfare, the fuck are you talking about you dumb gypsy.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>No, look at them. WaW’s graphics are clearly better. If you knew something about graphics, you’d shut up by now. Now stop talking, and stop your feud against me, since I’m still learning graphics, you took it here. I’ll report you to a moderator if you flame me again.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>You’re a retard for thinking WaW has better graphics. 'Sif graphics matter anyway, it’s the gameplay and experience that matters.[/quote]<br>
Did you actually look at them? WaW looks more real. Gameplay-wise, I guess COD4 could be better, not much of a difference, just the guns and the time.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/why-cod4-5-and-6-are-bad-games/284550/48">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/why-cod4-5-and-6-are-bad-games/284550/48</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 30 Jun 2009 19:31:02 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-284550-48</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/why-cod4-5-and-6-are-bad-games/284550.rss">Why cod4, 5 and 6 are bad games</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Why cod4, 5 and 6 are bad games</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@slayer215 slayer215]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/slayer215">@slayer215</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>COD5 in multiplayer is generally terrible compared to most other fpses. The teams are often really unbalanced and the MP40 nearly ruins the whole game, also tanks were the worst idea ever.</p>
<p>Nearly all the guns are overpowered, as in you can just be running and youll fall over within half a second of bullets being shot. Also I think prestiges take way too long, it should be lowered back to lvl 55 as the highest or something.</p>
<p>The best thing about the game is War, its so much fun. I dont even know how people can play team deathmatch when theres ground war and war now.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/why-cod4-5-and-6-are-bad-games/284550/47">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/why-cod4-5-and-6-are-bad-games/284550/47</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 30 Jun 2009 18:31:22 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-284550-47</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/why-cod4-5-and-6-are-bad-games/284550.rss">Why cod4, 5 and 6 are bad games</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
