<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Nurturing writers as well as programmers</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/nurturing-writers-as-well-as-programmers/136749</link>
    <description>This thought just came to me a minute ago.

The most important reason why you should have a community, rather than a website with nothing more than &quot;download cheat&quot; links, is for sharing knowledge, and training/recruiting more productive members (eg scripters).

Right now we do a lot to recognize and encourage programmers. For example, we give them &quot;scar scripter&quot; and &quot;Java guru&quot; status images. Perhaps we should also focus on nurturing a group of excellent documentation and tutorial writers. It would be a simple matter of handing out a &quot;writer&quot; status image, making a board or two for documentation/tutorial writing, and assigning a few moderators. Perhaps also creating a neatly organized repository for tutorials (like the old script dumps), that&#39;s maintained by a few mods would also be extremely useful.

The payoff for doing this could be quite great. We&#39;d be able to give beginners a smoother transition into cheating, rather than leaving them reading threads sprawled across a messy forum.

People like having roles. Right now there&#39;d be plenty of people out there who&#39;d happily become writers, if you simply offer some recognition for it.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 17 Sep 2007 05:27:44 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Community Inside Talk</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/nurturing-writers-as-well-as-programmers/136749.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Nurturing writers as well as programmers</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Brazen_Bull Brazen Bull]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/brazen_bull">@Brazen_Bull</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“Azeroth, post:26, topic:136749”](because, cow, seriously, you can’t be suggesting open wiki site after the last spectacular failure with open wiki RS cheating site).[/quote]I never suggested a wiki at all. I was more thinking of a board for posting tutorials, and a website similar to the old scar scriptdumps where mods can upload the good ones to.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/nurturing-writers-as-well-as-programmers/136749/27">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/nurturing-writers-as-well-as-programmers/136749/27</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 17 Sep 2007 05:27:44 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-136749-27</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/nurturing-writers-as-well-as-programmers/136749.rss">Nurturing writers as well as programmers</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Nurturing writers as well as programmers</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Azeroth Azeroth]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/azeroth">@Azeroth</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Personally, I’d suggest a hybrid system. Have writers with writer awards and have wikimen who have access to wiki site (because, cow, seriously, you can’t be suggesting open wiki site after the last spectacular failure with open wiki RS cheating site).<br>
Whenever people post something useful in forum, wikimen fish it out, decide where it fits in the wiki site and post it there. After that wikimen notify staff that the person who posted is eligible for writers award.<br>
If someone thinks he posted something worthy for wiki site, he can notify wikimen (with a single click, preferrably).<br>
Allow people to have both - wikiman and writer’s awards.<br>
Keep a list for all wiki site sections where the information came from.</p>
<p>Also, since it’s easy to check wikipedia user’s activity, wikiman award could be flexible and expire if for a certain period of time wikiman hasn’t updated wiki site with anything useful.  Make wikimen award common but easy to lose if user doesn’t contribute. Make this process automatic if possible.</p>
<p>But, indeed, a site that summarizes the useful from the forums would be most useful and welcome from both professionals and newbies.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/nurturing-writers-as-well-as-programmers/136749/26">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/nurturing-writers-as-well-as-programmers/136749/26</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 09 Sep 2007 20:32:44 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-136749-26</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/nurturing-writers-as-well-as-programmers/136749.rss">Nurturing writers as well as programmers</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Nurturing writers as well as programmers</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@moparisthebest Moparisthebest]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/moparisthebest">@moparisthebest</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>The point is that you came into the community for runescape cheating, mopman says there are people who come into it for other reasons, but I don’t really think there are.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/nurturing-writers-as-well-as-programmers/136749/25">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/nurturing-writers-as-well-as-programmers/136749/25</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 29 Aug 2007 02:31:42 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-136749-25</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/nurturing-writers-as-well-as-programmers/136749.rss">Nurturing writers as well as programmers</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Nurturing writers as well as programmers</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@jme jme]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/jme">@jme</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote no-group" data-post="23" data-topic="136749">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 frank_:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>it really depends what your involvemnt was, whether you may still have further contributions or are just hanging around for the next bot</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Most likely neither. I have no interest in any bots, I probably wont even test them.</p>
<p>Basically I would consider myself a prime example of the type of members we don’t exactly want around here. Me == a teen. Me being here == hanging out. Uh oh <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/expressionless.png?v=6" title=":expressionless:" class="emoji" alt=":expressionless:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/nurturing-writers-as-well-as-programmers/136749/24">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/nurturing-writers-as-well-as-programmers/136749/24</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 29 Aug 2007 02:20:09 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-136749-24</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/nurturing-writers-as-well-as-programmers/136749.rss">Nurturing writers as well as programmers</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Nurturing writers as well as programmers</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@frank frank_]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/frank">@frank</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>it really depends what your involvemnt was, whether you may still have further contributions or are just hanging around for the next bot</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/nurturing-writers-as-well-as-programmers/136749/23">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/nurturing-writers-as-well-as-programmers/136749/23</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 28 Aug 2007 16:42:37 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-136749-23</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/nurturing-writers-as-well-as-programmers/136749.rss">Nurturing writers as well as programmers</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Nurturing writers as well as programmers</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@jme jme]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/jme">@jme</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote no-group" data-post="20" data-topic="136749">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/user_avatar/forum.moparisthebest.com/mopman/40/33_2.png" class="avatar"> Mopman:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>There are people that have never cheated in Runescape. What are they doing on a Runescape cheating forum?</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I’m still trying to figure that out for myself. I mean, I <em>have</em> cheated in runescape, but not for ages. I’ve also lost my interest in programming. I was learning java, read 200 pages from an ebook, then just lost interest in it. Seriously, there is just no purpose for me to be here and yet here I am. I can’t help but feel like one of the people that we DON’T want around here.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/nurturing-writers-as-well-as-programmers/136749/22">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/nurturing-writers-as-well-as-programmers/136749/22</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 28 Aug 2007 10:28:39 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-136749-22</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/nurturing-writers-as-well-as-programmers/136749.rss">Nurturing writers as well as programmers</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Nurturing writers as well as programmers</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@moparisthebest Moparisthebest]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/moparisthebest">@moparisthebest</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p><a class="mention" href="/u/lothy">@Lothy</a>, Point taken, perhaps an instant 1 week mute on people that post moparscape questions on <a href="http://moparisthebest.com" rel="nofollow noopener">moparisthebest.com</a> would be fitting.</p>
<p><a class="mention" href="/u/mopman">@Mopman</a>, surely not, what would convince someone to come here if not for programming/runescape cheating?  I guarantee one search on google would bring up many sites that are much better at graphics than this one.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/nurturing-writers-as-well-as-programmers/136749/21">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/nurturing-writers-as-well-as-programmers/136749/21</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 28 Aug 2007 08:31:03 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-136749-21</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/nurturing-writers-as-well-as-programmers/136749.rss">Nurturing writers as well as programmers</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Nurturing writers as well as programmers</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Mopman Mopman]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/mopman">@Mopman</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Mopar: By teen forum, I didn’t mean people’s ages, I meant their mentalities and why they are here. There are people here that came here for graphics stuff, only post in the graphics section and do not care about Runescape. There are people that have never cheated in Runescape. What are they doing on a Runescape cheating forum?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/nurturing-writers-as-well-as-programmers/136749/20">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/nurturing-writers-as-well-as-programmers/136749/20</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 28 Aug 2007 06:56:24 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-136749-20</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/nurturing-writers-as-well-as-programmers/136749.rss">Nurturing writers as well as programmers</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Nurturing writers as well as programmers</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@lothy Lothy]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/lothy">@lothy</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Personally, no I don’t think the warning system needs to be changed to a permanent system. But it’s obvious that people who can think a little bit outside of the box can play the system like a fiddle. If I wanted to, I could go and make a dickhead of myself now in general discussion, get warned, wait until that warning disappears in a week, and do it all again.<br>
The line that shouldn’t be crossed is so obvious, and with static warning lengths it’s very easy to screw around and get away with it.<br>
As for strikes though, maybe something could be added where they are stored for a month or so. They don’t even need to be muted while the strikes are there. Say they get muted: 3 strikes (out of a maximum 5 or so, for the sake of leeway - you would of course keep that second figure private) added to their account, and when the mute runs out, they stay attached. If the person then gets up to moderated status again, then that should be it.</p>
<p>However, that bit on the warning system and the potential to abuse it was not as important as this:</p>
<blockquote>The next thing I'd like to mention is how some stuff is being taken care of - namely Moparscape related questions on these forums. I feel certain that most users don't appreciate said questions being posted on this website.
What I don't understand is why the culprits aren't either muted for a while or banned altogether. The request to post Moparscape questions on www.moparisthebest.com/smf is in two locations: the TOS page, and the description of the questions section.
If their posting of moparscape questions on this site is not blatant disregard for the rules, then frankly I don't know what is. I mean, it's only written there in CAPSLOCK.
These people are not the people that should be welcomed here. 
Failing to read the rules is never a mistake - it is nothing short of sheer disrespect for the community and rule abiding users who visit this website.</blockquote>
<p>Personally, I’m not like frank and the other people that want Moparscape gone altogether. Like many things, I’m fine with it - provided it’s done in the right place. As mentioned in that quote, people that post the questions here are blatantly disregarding rules, and in doing so they are disrespecting the members that make up this community.<br>
The rules are in the TOS, and it should be assumed that they read those. The request to not post server questions is also in capslock in the questions section description.</p>
<p>Anyway, I only left my big post because Kmb asked a few questions. =X Sorry for any possible derailment.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/nurturing-writers-as-well-as-programmers/136749/19">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/nurturing-writers-as-well-as-programmers/136749/19</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 28 Aug 2007 02:43:12 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-136749-19</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/nurturing-writers-as-well-as-programmers/136749.rss">Nurturing writers as well as programmers</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Nurturing writers as well as programmers</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@moparisthebest Moparisthebest]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/moparisthebest">@moparisthebest</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I apologize for not responding in a more timely fashion, I have not had internet for the last 8 days and just now got it back.</p>
<p>Alright, it seems that there are two distinct discussions going on in this thread, one discussing cow’s original idea, and another discussing the staff and site policies in general.  I will try to address all the issues here but there are many of them, if I miss one you want addressed just bring it up to me again.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-u"><span class="bbcode-b">Cow’s idea:</span></span></p>
<p>I do like that idea, it seems like it might be even better in today’s cheating environment where you need quite a bit more than general java knowledge to write a bot.  In <a href="http://kaitnieks.com" rel="nofollow noopener">kaitnieks.com</a>’s day and the early days of this forum, when you could simply download a working deob or the program to make one for you it was generally easy to work with, now you are basically forced to work with the bytecode or do some nasty hacks with reflection.</p>
<p>Someone already suggested a mediawiki installation that could be used for things like this, it would be easy to install and forum awards could be made for contributing to it.  All else that is needed are active members willing to moderate the wiki and then, as you say, there should be plenty who would be willing to contribute to it.  Suggestions/comments/criticisms?</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b"><span class="bbcode-u">Staff/site discussion:</span></span></p>
<p>I don’t believe I have ever claimed that this site was not a runescape cheating site, I have always viewed it with dual purposes, one for general programming, the other for runescape cheating.  The two really work well with each other in my opinion, you can’t cheat in runescape without programming knowledge.</p>
<p>I do not and never did want a ‘teen forum’, as mopman claims this forum is now, however it is inevitable as the average age of runescape players goes down that the average age of runescape cheaters will go down is it not?  I don’t really see a solution to this ‘problem’ as limiting the age of registration is not only unfair, but as we all know would simply not work.</p>
<p>Also, this is not the only thread where some have said that ‘mopar needs to make this more of a cheating forum’, but I have still yet to see suggestions on how one would go about doing this?  Are you saying I should release a bot (cherokee is nearing release)? or something else?  Please tell me what you have in mind.</p>
<p><a class="mention" href="/u/lothy">@Lothy</a>, then how do you suggest that the warning system should work?  Should we keep strikes on each user account and once they reach a set number issue a permanent ban? Should those ever expire? anything else?</p>
<p>[quote=“sdouble, post:13, topic:136749”][quote=Kmb]<br>
…most of them are from Kaitnieks…<br>
[/quote]</p>
<p>This is actually very not true anymore.[/quote]</p>
<p>kmb was referring to the rules when he said that, and it is true, most of the rules are from kaitnieks or close variants thereof.</p>
<p><a class="mention" href="/u/sdouble">@sdouble</a>, When this forum originally was started, it was meant to be a hang-out until <a href="http://kaitnieks.com" rel="nofollow noopener">kaitnieks.com</a> came back online and therefore an extension of the community (Think in java: <a href="http://Moparisthebest.com" rel="nofollow noopener">Moparisthebest.com</a> extends <a href="http://Kaitnieks.com" rel="nofollow noopener">Kaitnieks.com</a>) I tried to hand out all of the same awards to the same people, but as the forum got bigger it got harder to do, plus I don’t have the memory of an elephant, sorry about that.  Your idea about expiring awards would be the ideal solution, but like you said would be very hard for the staff to handle.  I wonder if putting some sort of timer on awards similar to those that are on warnings would work, such as once a certain award is given it would come up for renewal every month or so and the staff could then review the recent posts to see if it should be renewed or not, one problem with this system is that some awards should be permanent, staff/ex-staff/developer.  Also would that be fair? Isn’t programming somewhat like riding a bike? Once a java guru always a java guru?  Surely even though you or I have not actually scripted SCAR for a long time doesn’t mean that we couldn’t pick it back up in a few minutes.</p>
<p><a class="mention" href="/u/ruler">@ruler</a>, you have always been a conspiracy theorist of sorts, none of the staff here is out to get you or other contributors, I promise.</p>
<p>edit(I always forget certain points):</p>
<p>I never come to staff decisions lightly, I know many other forums do, but that is one of the reasons I don’t like them.  Some of the criteria is that they must be active, friendly, make honest attempts at correct grammer/spelling, and have been around for awhile.  I know quite a few programmers have the contention that good staff must be good at programming.  I have found this not to be necessarily true, some people who are excellent programmers make sorry staff.  Another difference between this and other forums is that I realize that the people who ask for staff positions, those that seem to not be able to think about anything else, are not the type of people you want as staff.  Instead of doing a good job, they are only interested in that little pikachu and the title of ‘Global Moderator’ next to their name.  The most blatant and recent example of someone like this just posted an “I quit.” thread after I flat out told him it was never going to happen.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/nurturing-writers-as-well-as-programmers/136749/18">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/nurturing-writers-as-well-as-programmers/136749/18</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 27 Aug 2007 21:34:38 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-136749-18</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/nurturing-writers-as-well-as-programmers/136749.rss">Nurturing writers as well as programmers</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Nurturing writers as well as programmers</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@yakman yakman]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/yakman">@yakman</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>yeah i think the writers is a good idea,<br>
a while ago i wrote a tutorial about bcel, I would have preferred if there was a ‘java tutorial section’ for me to post it in instead of java programming. scar has a tutorial section.</p>
<p>if you wanted to stop people racing for the cups, you could make the writers section, then released the cups three weeks later, by then, writing is already old</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/nurturing-writers-as-well-as-programmers/136749/17">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/nurturing-writers-as-well-as-programmers/136749/17</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 27 Aug 2007 19:32:40 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-136749-17</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/nurturing-writers-as-well-as-programmers/136749.rss">Nurturing writers as well as programmers</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Nurturing writers as well as programmers</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Freddy1990 Freddy1990]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/freddy1990">@Freddy1990</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Heh, well I for one think it’s a good idea <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=6" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/nurturing-writers-as-well-as-programmers/136749/16">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/nurturing-writers-as-well-as-programmers/136749/16</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 26 Aug 2007 15:48:55 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-136749-16</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/nurturing-writers-as-well-as-programmers/136749.rss">Nurturing writers as well as programmers</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Nurturing writers as well as programmers</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@lothy Lothy]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/lothy">@lothy</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“ruler, post:14, topic:136749”]People contributed at <a href="http://kaitnieks.com" rel="nofollow noopener">kaitnieks.com</a> not because kait was a great admin, it was because they respected him.</p>
<p>Contributors dont respect the staff here.  The staff loves to abuse contributors.  Hence why we see development at brach off sites like mine, <a href="http://srl-forums.com" rel="nofollow noopener">srl-forums.com</a>, <a href="http://rs-resources.com" rel="nofollow noopener">rs-resources.com</a>[/quote]<br>
Ugh, you’re still going on about that rubbish. That’s utter horse shit - nobody targets you, and nobody ever will.</p>
<p>Here’s a reality check: the world doesn’t revolve around ruler, nobody hangs onto every last word you type, nobody goes digging through your posts, nobody cares.</p>
<p>If you have gotten into trouble in the past, then that was your own fault. You certainly weren’t the first community member to be warned or higher, and you definitely weren’t the last.</p>
<p>Sdouble: you raise a good point, but it isn’t entirely true. While you yourself don’t really care about the awards, I’m sure that a whole heap of others do. Either way, it wouldn’t really hurt to experiment with Brazen Bull’s idea, would it? <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=6" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/nurturing-writers-as-well-as-programmers/136749/15">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/nurturing-writers-as-well-as-programmers/136749/15</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 26 Aug 2007 05:22:05 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-136749-15</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/nurturing-writers-as-well-as-programmers/136749.rss">Nurturing writers as well as programmers</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Nurturing writers as well as programmers</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@ruler ruler]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/ruler">@ruler</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>People contributed at <a href="http://kaitnieks.com" rel="nofollow noopener">kaitnieks.com</a> not because kait was a great admin, it was because they respected him.</p>
<p>Contributors dont respect the staff here.  The staff loves to abuse contributors.  Hence why we see development at brach off sites like mine, <a href="http://srl-forums.com" rel="nofollow noopener">srl-forums.com</a>, <a href="http://rs-resources.com" rel="nofollow noopener">rs-resources.com</a></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/nurturing-writers-as-well-as-programmers/136749/14">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/nurturing-writers-as-well-as-programmers/136749/14</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 26 Aug 2007 03:58:49 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-136749-14</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/nurturing-writers-as-well-as-programmers/136749.rss">Nurturing writers as well as programmers</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Nurturing writers as well as programmers</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@sdouble sdouble]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/sdouble">@sdouble</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <blockquote>...most of them are from Kaitnieks...</blockquote>
<p>This is actually very not true anymore.</p>
<p>Of the admins, 2 used to be moderators from Kait’s  Starblaster and Waffendennis (if you can count him, he hasn’t been active) and they were both upgraded to admin on this forum.  Of the global mods, I think 0 were staff on Kaitnieks.  Kmb, you may have been a mod on Kait’s during his final modding spree but I don’t recall.  It seems possible.</p>
<p>I do feel that the current staff is doing just fine.  I think there are way too many locked topics.  When people get the answer they’re looking for, they request that a topic gets locked.  What if someone runs across that in the future by using the search?  I’ve noticed some people don’t want old topics revived and even tell the “offender” to not revive old topics, but if it’s something that someone found because they actually used the search option but can no longer post in it, what’s the point of the search?  On Kait’s forum, locking topics was a no no.  Only if absolutely necesary.  If there was a “flame war” going on, you would take it to the individuals involved, not the thread.</p>
<p>But back to Brazen Bull’s original point:<br>
Cups and awards aren’t really enough to motivate the right people.  Here’s a scenario.  When people came over to this forum, they got their cups and awards.  I didn’t get mine.  Well, I was offered the Pikachu because I was an admin but turned it down.  But I also had a Scar Cup and Bat Cup over there (all cups were removed when you’re staff).  It doesn’t really matter to some people.  pplsuqbawlz has his cups and his ex-staff award.  xerxes had a java guru award basically for scripting with aryan on Kaitnieks forum yet I helped many more people learn how to script for aryan there.  Simple logic says I should have a scar, bat, and java cups as well as my ex-staff award.  This is the first time I’ve thought about it.  I’m gonna have to have some words with Moparisthebest!  But seriously:  People don’t really care about the awards.  With the lack of motivation we have here, and everyone not really caring about the community but mostly just about themselves, don’t expect people to release tutorials and such.  There have been a few people that have released portions of their own stuff in the client hacking section (Silver Lining, Ollie, pplsuqbawls, frank_, etc) but that’s about all you’ll get.  Over on rs-resources, ownagesbot released a small tutorial on writing a bcel bot.  You just don’t see that here.  While at first, it’ll be a race to get that new award, it will die off.  Once people start getting it, they’ll stop.  Now if it was tracked and if you didn’t do anything for awhile you lost it, that would be another story.  But this would be WAY too much for the staff to do.  If someone really wants the award, they might work on getting it and then stop after they do get it.  I like the awards, but I don’t like the way it works.</p>
<p>Do I deserve an award for being ex-staff?  No.  Especially since I was staff at an entirely different community.  I’ve never been staff here.<br>
Do I deserver the scar, bat, and java cup I mentioned earlier?  No.  I haven’t even opened SCAR for years.  I run linux now, incompatable.  I haven’t contributed anything to earn the others either.<br>
Should someone that was part of the “AutoRune Crew” get an award for that?  Not really.  It doesn’t really mean anything.<br>
How about the IRC Legend award.  If the forum and IRC are so tight knitted that there is an IRC award on the forum, shouldn’t the staff of each be exactly the same?</p>
<p>I understand some of these awards are simply a status symbol (AutoRune Crew, Ex-Staff, IRC Legend) since having one of those awards means absolutely nothing to anyone.  But it says “Hey, I was there.  I was part of that.”  But I think the awards that really matter should be given to contributing members.  If someone does a lot of writing of tutorials and stuff, sure.  Give them an award.  They’re contributing.  But once they stop contributing, take it away.  Just because you wrote a bunch of tutorials a year ago doesn’t mean anything now.  Same with the SCAR cup.  Things have changed since I last used SCAR.  There was even a new version released.  And now there’s SRL.  I know nothing about SCAR anymore.  It would be pointless for me to have a SCAR cup.  Sure, I may have been a great help to scar scripters long ago, but I couldn’t offer much assistance anymore.  There would be no reason for me to have one.  Hell, I even received a vote for “Greatest SCAR scripter of all time” over on the SRL forum.  I would say this person made a poor choice, but I’m going with it to prove my point.  I’ve posted less than 5 times on that forum.  That forum is geared more towards SCAR and SCAR scripting.  Yet do I deserve to keep the scar scripter award?  Absolutely not.</p>
<p>Currently, if someone was to write a bunch of java tutorials, they would get a java cup.  Same with scar.  Would the writing that you’re talking about be strictly for things like that?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/nurturing-writers-as-well-as-programmers/136749/13">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/nurturing-writers-as-well-as-programmers/136749/13</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 25 Aug 2007 23:41:18 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-136749-13</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/nurturing-writers-as-well-as-programmers/136749.rss">Nurturing writers as well as programmers</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Nurturing writers as well as programmers</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@lothy Lothy]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/lothy">@lothy</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“Mopman, post:11, topic:136749”]We already split the forum in two, ie Moparscape and MITB - why don’t we spawn a third forum, MoparSocial or something? This could contain the general, graphics, etc. sections, keeping mopar his ad money and allowing people who enjoy the teen hangout type stuff to continue with that, while seperating the development sections and stopping them being swamped with topics that others do not wish to sift through?</p>
<p>I realise splitting an entire forum is not an easy task and hardly the best solution, but really the better idea would have been not to allow the “teen” crowd to take over in the first place.[/quote]<br>
With regards to the whole teen taking over thing, it’s the morons that go around tlking liek dis mn that really get me.<br>
It’s just something that bugs the fuck out of me. I’ve banned a whole bunch of people for acting like that on IRC, on the grounds that this isn’t 4chan/similar. That isn’t enough though - it should be discouraged and shunned on the forums as well so people get the message.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/nurturing-writers-as-well-as-programmers/136749/12">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/nurturing-writers-as-well-as-programmers/136749/12</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 25 Aug 2007 19:29:25 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-136749-12</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/nurturing-writers-as-well-as-programmers/136749.rss">Nurturing writers as well as programmers</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Nurturing writers as well as programmers</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Mopman Mopman]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/mopman">@Mopman</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>We already split the forum in two, ie Moparscape and MITB - why don’t we spawn a third forum, MoparSocial or something? This could contain the general, graphics, etc. sections, keeping mopar his ad money and allowing people who enjoy the teen hangout type stuff to continue with that, while seperating the development sections and stopping them being swamped with topics that others do not wish to sift through?</p>
<p>I realise splitting an entire forum is not an easy task and hardly the best solution, but really the better idea would have been not to allow the “teen” crowd to take over in the first place.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/nurturing-writers-as-well-as-programmers/136749/11">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/nurturing-writers-as-well-as-programmers/136749/11</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 25 Aug 2007 19:20:12 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-136749-11</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/nurturing-writers-as-well-as-programmers/136749.rss">Nurturing writers as well as programmers</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Nurturing writers as well as programmers</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@lothy Lothy]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/lothy">@lothy</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote no-group quote-modified" data-post="2" data-topic="136749">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 frank_:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>…and selected staff that actually had half an idea what they are doing (at the moment only a couple do)…</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I’m not quite sure what you mean by that - do you mean they aren’t the best programmers the world has ever seen, or do you mean that can’t see a situation and react properly?</p>
<p>Personally, I think that most do a great job. However, I daresay some of them see all situations as completely black and white; they fail to take certain things into account.<br>
As for their programming ability, I don’t know. But forum staff are the face of the forums. They have to be nice, approachable (to an extent - I’m well aware of the messages they receive at times), and so on. A lot of people that ‘know what they’re doing’ when it comes to programming can be and often are arseholes - there are of course exceptions to this, and there are times when I’m certainly not one of them. <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=6" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
<p>[quote=“Kmb, post:6, topic:136749”][quote author=frank_ link=topic=188280.msg1700405#msg1700405 date=1188045198]<br>
try getting mopar to admit that this is a cheating website, though</p>
<p>i agree with you, though most people are reluctant to post anything worthwhile because it will be instantly leeched. if the community had less idiots, or was more private, i am almost certain that others would be willing to contribute</p>
<p>that said, if mopar were willing to make this more of a cheating community, <span class="bbcode-b">and selected staff that actually had half an idea what they are doing (at the moment only a couple do),</span> the cheating scene might possibly be able to pull itself out of this depression.</p>
<p>mopar, perhaps you could create another set of [private] forums, removed from these, with an integrated wiki or something, have required registration and admin validation, pick staff that actually know how things work…<br>
[/quote]<br>
This is a bit off topic, but:<br>
I’ve seen quite a lot of criticizing towards the staff recently from a couple of our members. I’d like to know<br>
a) What we do wrong.<br>
b) If you were a mod, what would you have done in those situations.<br>
c) Who would you suggest for new staff?<br>
d) What makes a good moderator? Is the moderator who doesn’t do anything if he faces obvious breaking of the rules better than the one who chooses to ignore the situation and therefore not doing his job?</p>
<p>Right now, I don’t know what the rest of staff here do, or what they should do, but I’m here to control that the rules are being followed. I didn’t come up with them, as you probably know, most of them are from Kaitnieks.</p>
<h2>I do agree with you (well, this isn’t exactly what you said, but the same idea) on the fact that this forum has become too much of a just another forum for pre-teens who have no motivation to contribute to the community cheat-wise. We simply do not encourage people enough to do what they should. That is learning programming and developing new cheats. Ditching some boards could do the thing.</h2>
<p>On topic, great ideas there Cow. I’d definitely like to see some of those suggestions realized.[/quote]<br>
I’ll do my best to answer those questions.</p>
<p>Firstly, I don’t think any of you do anything ‘wrong’, but there is often inconsistency; it’s definitely noticable at times.<br>
I daresay that some of you guys take a black and white approach to everything, and that isn’t always appropriate.<br>
On a happier note, it’s good to see that the cocky warn/moderated/mute messages have gone - that used to be a big problem, and frankly I think those messages did make the writers look absolutely stupid. Good to see the backs of them.</p>
<p>When it comes to moderating, I’ve been a sectional moderator and I’m an operator in both IRC channels - needless to say, I’ve been there and done that. It’s a lot harder then a lot of people would expect, and it really is impossible to win over the hearts of every single user. I always strive to be consistent though.</p>
<p>As for new staff, I’d say that anyone who has a decent attitude that is active would probably do a reasonable job. Having said that though, I do think that the current staff do a pretty good job, despite the things mentioned above. There’s always room for improvement though, and I’m sure you guys will take suggestions on board. <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=6" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
<p>The answer to the last question is obvious. However there are times when there is overzealous moderating, and times when not enough is being done to punish the user who is in the wrong.</p>
<p>The next thing I’d like to mention is how some stuff is being taken care of - namely Moparscape related questions on these forums. I feel certain that most users don’t appreciate said questions being posted on this website.<br>
What I don’t understand is why the culprits aren’t either muted for a while or banned altogether. The request to post Moparscape questions on <a href="http://www.moparisthebest.com/smf" rel="nofollow noopener">www.moparisthebest.com/smf</a> is in two locations: the TOS page, and the description of the questions section.<br>
If their posting of moparscape questions on this site is not blatant disregard for the rules, then frankly I don’t know what is. I mean, it’s only written there in CAPSLOCK.<br>
These people are not the people that should be welcomed here.<br>
Failing to read the rules is never a mistake - it is nothing short of sheer disrespect for the community and rule abiding users who visit this website.</p>
<p>The next thing is the warning system, and how it works. You get warned for a week for something. Warning ends. If you do the same thing again within the week, you may or may not get put up to moderated. If you do the same thing once the warning is removed, then you may or may not be rewarned.<br>
What’s the point. Quux made a very good point on freenode while we were still using the network: Why should something that is wrong in 6 days be less incriminating in 8 days? I look forward to any reasonable reply to that, because I think it’s senseless and impossible to justify.</p>
<p>Finally, there’s the questioning of this website and who it’s for. I really don’t know what it is: A programming website, a cheating website, a place for 10yr olds to hang out and act like dickheads at everyone else’s expense? I really do not know.<br>
I’ve actually asked Mopar on IRC (last week or something) about his opinion of what the forums were - I wasn’t sure if I was the right sort of person to operate the IRC channel (anyone that uses the channel can probably tell you that I aim to keep it idiot free, so you can rock up for a half decent discussion. I try to keep it in pristine condition for the older users, and the mature younger users).<br>
My question was something along the lines of “Am I the right person to be an operator for the channels - It’s meant to be a programming and cheating community, but sometimes I feel like I’m moderating a children’s playground.” He assured me that I was doing a good job, and that the site wasn’t just a teen’s hangout spot.</p>
<p>But then there’s the other side of the coin. I’ve had around half a dozen topics made about me and my apparent abuse of power in the IRC channels - someone even jokingly suggested that a section be made for the “I hate Lothy” topics. <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=6" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"><br>
I think I do a reasonable job - I keep the stupid behaviour and the stupid people out of the channel, and by doing so I make it a welcoming place for people to have real discussions. That being my belief, I wonder why the topics were left hanging around for so long, giving everyone that doesn’t know me this impression that I’m a real dickhead to anyone that passes by.<br>
The people who posted the topics not only provided pathetic reasoning, but they were also the same people that, ironically enough, manage to get into constant trouble on the forums too. One of the people who made a topic was Xerxes evading his permanent ban - the topic was left there for a long time regardless of that.<br>
I just don’t think it’s right to let rule breakers get away with slagging off other members. The maker of said topics should have been invited to contact Mopar if there was a genuine case of abuse, and the topic should have been removed a few hours later.<br>
Didn’t mean to make it personal, it was just the best example I could think of.</p>
<p>Sorry about going off topic - Had to reply to Kmb’s post. Excuse any errors too. <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=6" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/nurturing-writers-as-well-as-programmers/136749/10">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/nurturing-writers-as-well-as-programmers/136749/10</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 25 Aug 2007 19:05:10 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-136749-10</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/nurturing-writers-as-well-as-programmers/136749.rss">Nurturing writers as well as programmers</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Nurturing writers as well as programmers</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@kmb Kmb]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/kmb">@kmb</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Thanks for your answers.</p>
<p>The way I see it, when I warn a well-recognized member here, it’s absolutely nothing personal. As majority of the people here are quite young, things tend to get out hand very easily. It’s just a small reminder that one has crossed the line. I try to warn those who have constantly broken the rules. Although I do agree that I have done some arguable decisions in the past. In the end, we are all just humans.</p>
<p>I have never had a reason to warn you, as when you criticize someone, you tend to say it in a sophisticated manner. Most of us can see your frustration, but you don’t go around yelling, swearing and flaming him and everyone randomly on sight [no - I’m not kiss your arse. You are just a good example].</p>
<p>I guess it’s too much to ask people behaving maturely, though, when they’re kids trying to kill time. After all, “diz iz just da interwebs”.</p>
<p>I believe Katnieks once said something like “If you’re angry, don’t post at all. Take a deep breath and log out. Come back when you have calmed down.” That’s a suggestion I try to follow, also when warning. Although, I admit, I have snapped once on irc, which I’m ashamed of.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/nurturing-writers-as-well-as-programmers/136749/9">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/nurturing-writers-as-well-as-programmers/136749/9</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 25 Aug 2007 16:19:49 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-136749-9</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/nurturing-writers-as-well-as-programmers/136749.rss">Nurturing writers as well as programmers</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Nurturing writers as well as programmers</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Mopman Mopman]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/mopman">@Mopman</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote no-group" data-post="6" data-topic="136749">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/kmb/40/5_6259e4fa9dfe0dec282fb0955bb1974c.png" class="avatar"> Kmb:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>a) What we do wrong.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Some of you (let’s not mention names here) have a tendency to warn/ban/generally go apeshit at the silliest tiny rule violations, while ignoring blatent serious ones, especially if the person commiting the more serious ‘crime’ is a well-known member. Having said that, this seems to be improving lately. An even worse problem with the current staff team is that it seems you only care about “your job” rather than the community as a whole - the place is going down the shitter and all you’re doing is warning people for hating on a jew?</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-post="6" data-topic="136749">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/kmb/40/5_6259e4fa9dfe0dec282fb0955bb1974c.png" class="avatar"> Kmb:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>b) If you were a mod, what would you have done in those situations.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I realise that this applies to the members of the community as well, especially the CM’s I suppose, but you must see that it is easy to get disillusioned when the forum is in the state that it’s in. The same thing happened towards the end of Kaitnieks, the same thing happened to RSCN (well actually no, RSCN was full of retards from the start :P).</p>
<p>What is needed is some kind of drastic change in mopar’s thinking - does he want an earner, as the board is now, or does he want a real cheating forum? Now, I’m not looking down my nose here, I live off earnings from websites, it’s all I do, and if mopar is enjoying the same kind of freedom I do, then good for him. But it would be nice to admit this is a teen forum intended for generating ad revenue, rather than a cheating forum, if that’s his intention. Because at the moment, that’s what it is.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-post="6" data-topic="136749">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/kmb/40/5_6259e4fa9dfe0dec282fb0955bb1974c.png" class="avatar"> Kmb:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>c) Who would you suggest for new staff?</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I don’t want to get into the whole name-calling and bigging up your friends stuff. I actually don’t have a problem with most of the staff here already, I just think the site as a whole needs a bit of a shakeup, and that includes the mods.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-post="6" data-topic="136749">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/kmb/40/5_6259e4fa9dfe0dec282fb0955bb1974c.png" class="avatar"> Kmb:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>d) What makes a good moderator? Is the moderator who doesn’t do anything if he faces obvious breaking of the rules</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>A good moderator enforces the rules in a fair and unbiased manner, while showing a desire to be involved in the future of the forum. Is this what we are seeing?</p>
<p>I apologise for my incoherency, it’s pretty damn early. <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=6" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/nurturing-writers-as-well-as-programmers/136749/8">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/nurturing-writers-as-well-as-programmers/136749/8</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 25 Aug 2007 15:38:02 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-136749-8</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/nurturing-writers-as-well-as-programmers/136749.rss">Nurturing writers as well as programmers</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Nurturing writers as well as programmers</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Sean Sean]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/sean">@Sean</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>if you want to encourage people start sharing the ad revenue with contributors. Enough said.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/nurturing-writers-as-well-as-programmers/136749/7">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/nurturing-writers-as-well-as-programmers/136749/7</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 25 Aug 2007 15:28:42 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-136749-7</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/nurturing-writers-as-well-as-programmers/136749.rss">Nurturing writers as well as programmers</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Nurturing writers as well as programmers</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@kmb Kmb]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/kmb">@kmb</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“frank_, post:2, topic:136749”]try getting mopar to admit that this is a cheating website, though</p>
<p>i agree with you, though most people are reluctant to post anything worthwhile because it will be instantly leeched. if the community had less idiots, or was more private, i am almost certain that others would be willing to contribute</p>
<p>that said, if mopar were willing to make this more of a cheating community, <span class="bbcode-b">and selected staff that actually had half an idea what they are doing (at the moment only a couple do),</span> the cheating scene might possibly be able to pull itself out of this depression.</p>
<p>mopar, perhaps you could create another set of [private] forums, removed from these, with an integrated wiki or something, have required registration and admin validation, pick staff that actually know how things work…[/quote]<br>
This is a bit off topic, but:<br>
I’ve seen quite a lot of criticizing towards the staff recently from a couple of our members. I’d like to know<br>
a) What we do wrong.<br>
b) If you were a mod, what would you have done in those situations.<br>
c) Who would you suggest for new staff?<br>
d) What makes a good moderator? Is the moderator who doesn’t do anything if he faces obvious breaking of the rules better than the one who chooses to ignore the situation and therefore not doing his job?</p>
<p>Right now, I don’t know what the rest of staff here do, or what they should do, but I’m here to control that the rules are being followed. I didn’t come up with them, as you probably know, most of them are from Kaitnieks.</p>
<h2>I do agree with you (well, this isn’t exactly what you said, but the same idea) on the fact that this forum has become too much of a just another forum for pre-teens who have no motivation to contribute to the community cheat-wise. We simply do not encourage people enough to do what they should. That is learning programming and developing new cheats. Ditching some boards could do the thing.</h2>
<p>On topic, great ideas there Cow. I’d definitely like to see some of those suggestions realized.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/nurturing-writers-as-well-as-programmers/136749/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/nurturing-writers-as-well-as-programmers/136749/6</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 25 Aug 2007 15:20:41 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-136749-6</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/nurturing-writers-as-well-as-programmers/136749.rss">Nurturing writers as well as programmers</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Nurturing writers as well as programmers</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@ruler ruler]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/ruler">@ruler</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Evolution</p>
<p>programmer writes code<br>
programmer documents work<br>
programmer fired</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/nurturing-writers-as-well-as-programmers/136749/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/nurturing-writers-as-well-as-programmers/136749/5</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 25 Aug 2007 14:02:30 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-136749-5</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/nurturing-writers-as-well-as-programmers/136749.rss">Nurturing writers as well as programmers</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Nurturing writers as well as programmers</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@frank frank_]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/frank">@frank</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>i would, but i dont have the motivation, or the money</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/nurturing-writers-as-well-as-programmers/136749/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/nurturing-writers-as-well-as-programmers/136749/4</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 25 Aug 2007 13:36:08 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-136749-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/nurturing-writers-as-well-as-programmers/136749.rss">Nurturing writers as well as programmers</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Nurturing writers as well as programmers</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@sup000 sup000]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/sup000">@sup000</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>why are you suggesting mopar must do it frank_? many other people are big enough and ugly enough to do it if it is what they really wanted <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue_winking_eye.png?v=6" title=":stuck_out_tongue_winking_eye:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue_winking_eye:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/nurturing-writers-as-well-as-programmers/136749/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/nurturing-writers-as-well-as-programmers/136749/3</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 25 Aug 2007 13:29:34 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-136749-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/nurturing-writers-as-well-as-programmers/136749.rss">Nurturing writers as well as programmers</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
