<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Exercising and Getting Fit</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/exercising-and-getting-fit/444059</link>
    <description>I&#39;m just curious, but has anyone here made it a long-term goal to do so before (Note this isn&#39;t a question, but I want to see some discussion)? I&#39;ve been a lazy poor eater for a long time and I finally decided to do something about it (Not to mention my stomach doesn&#39;t look too attractive right now). It&#39;s been just over a week now with Sunday my only day off exercising and trying to eat right, and I haven&#39;t seen results. Granted, the first week it was more to get into the routine of working out and today was the first day I was really challenged.

I&#39;ve spent some time reading articles on the best eating and exercising patterns. I&#39;ve decided to follow [url=http://exercise.about.com/cs/exbeginners/l/blimplement.htm]This Guide[/url] with the schedule of the beginner&#39;s workout (except more cardio workouts) but intensity of the intermediate exercises. I currently weigh about 160 lbs and I&#39;d like to be around 140 lbs or more depending on my muscle gain, since I&#39;ll also be working out and not just doing cardio exercise. My goal is to make it happen by August.

So here&#39;s what I&#39;ve gathered in terms of proper eating: Start the day off with a proper breakfast, which includes pretty much what you&#39;d expect - banana, cereal, toast, etc... Eat a small snack somewhere between lunch, which basically includes... snacks - nuts, some form of chips, fruit, etc... For lunch, well, it&#39;s lunch. I haven&#39;t read on recommendations, but it&#39;s pretty obvious what to eat and what to avoid. I guess just look at the nutrition facts of what you&#39;re about to eat. A good dinner is really anything rich in protein, unsaturated fats, fiber, etc... Again, pretty obvious.

Honestly, I don&#39;t see how people have trouble with dieting. I used to drink multiple cans of pop (or soda for assholes) a day and almost never touch water, but I&#39;ve only drank 2 cans in almost 2 weeks - and there&#39;s my favorite kind readily available at this very moment. Now I drink about 3 water bottles a day and lay off the snacks and I don&#39;t have any trouble. I guess it&#39;s a matter of self control.

Now, the biggest issue I&#39;ve had with exercising is I don&#39;t know when to. I live in Arizona, and it&#39;s summer time, meaning the temperature is usually over 100F from 12PM til dusk. I&#39;m a teenager, so I sleep in late, but that doesn&#39;t matter. I&#39;ve performed all my exercises so far at 4-6PM every day - just after the hottest part. Again, I think it&#39;s a self control and motivation thing. But that&#39;s not at all what I wanted to address. Logically, when you burn calories, your body goes for what it just made, so if you exercise after you just ate, you&#39;re going to feel hungry and not burn any of the fat you have stored - seems pretty wasteful to me. Apparently, it&#39;s best to go exercising at least an hour since you last ate, depending on your metabolism, how much you ate, and what you ate. I think for these reasons, it&#39;s best to go exercising after breakfast. It gets your metabolism going, it&#39;s the only thing you&#39;ve eaten so far, there&#39;s enough time to drink at least a bottle of water and be fully hydrated, and there&#39;s some other reasons that are less significant.

So here&#39;s what I&#39;ve learned and plan on following for the next 2 months in a nutshell:
-Cardio exercise 5 times a week
-Upper body, lower body, and core workouts each once a week. Stretch the other days
-Exercise after breakfast
-Snacks are good, but not in large amounts and more than twice a day. They keep your metabolism going
-A meal with a big protein portion, along with some sort of green vegetable should be had after exercising to properly rebuild muscles
-Get a proper amount of sleep
-Avoid anything other than water, tea, milk, coffee, and anything that wasn&#39;t naturally made sweet
-Fats usually beat carbohydrates - you can read about it on page 2 of the Weight Loss Solutions article I linked below.
-If you&#39;re going for weight loss, weigh yourself in the morning and not throughout the day. Your body has burned up what you ate through the night, so in the morning is when you most likely weigh your true weight. I was 157 lbs early one day and 160 late the next.
-Don&#39;t skip out on exercising and get lazy. Don&#39;t look at what people have, and don&#39;t aim high. Set long-term goals, but bust your ass either way. You&#39;re not going to see an immediate change.

In case you&#39;re curious of where I got all of this stuff from, here are all of the articles I read.
http://www.menshealth.com/mhlists/curb-hunger/index.php
http://www.menshealth.com/weight-loss/weight-loss-solutions
http://askville.amazon.com/long-wait-eating-meal-work/AnswerViewer.do?requestId=9434591
http://www.mayoclinic.com/health/exercise/HQ00594_D
http://www.webmd.com/fitness-exercise/features/whats-the-best-time-to-exercise

Now, I&#39;m not at all an expert on any of this stuff, but I sort of wanted to summarize everything I learned not only so it was easier for me to comprehend, but so other people here could learn from it as well. I don&#39;t believe in the fast-acting eat-as-much-as-you-want weight loss and muscle gains. You have to work for things like these, and there&#39;s no such thing anyway. I also don&#39;t believe you need a gym or anything like that to get fit. Look at videos like P90X - doing what the videos show, you can work every single muscle in your body with only using something like a stool or rag occasionally (I was in a fitness class all 3 of my highschool years and we had to do these workouts from time to time).

So uuuh... Yeah, there&#39;s my late-at-night big article thing. Hope it was a good read and maybe inspired some of you looking to get in shape but don&#39;t know where to start.

~Lin</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 31 Aug 2012 02:18:06 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>General Discussion</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/exercising-and-getting-fit/444059.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Exercising and Getting Fit</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Frell Frell]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/frell">@Frell</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Im not sure what you mean.</p>
<p>Make sure they aren’t just core muscles.</p>
<p>Heres my core, as you can see, even my abs’ abs have their own abs:</p>
<p>None of these are ribs</p>
<p><img src="http://i.imgur.com/OG8qZ.png" alt width="295" height="363"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/exercising-and-getting-fit/444059/129">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/exercising-and-getting-fit/444059/129</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 31 Aug 2012 02:18:06 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-444059-129</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/exercising-and-getting-fit/444059.rss">Exercising and Getting Fit</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Exercising and Getting Fit</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@jc22493 Jc22493]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/jc22493">@jc22493</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Bump.</p>
<p>So I’ve been working out a lot and my body definitely looks much better than a few months ago. The problem now is that I feel like I can see my ribs even though I’m not skinny, etc. Anyone know why? I’ve heard that dumbbell pullovers are good for intercostals.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/exercising-and-getting-fit/444059/128">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/exercising-and-getting-fit/444059/128</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 31 Aug 2012 00:59:05 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-444059-128</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/exercising-and-getting-fit/444059.rss">Exercising and Getting Fit</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Exercising and Getting Fit</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Frell Frell]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/frell">@Frell</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>lol’d</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/exercising-and-getting-fit/444059/127">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/exercising-and-getting-fit/444059/127</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 31 Jul 2012 17:41:20 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-444059-127</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/exercising-and-getting-fit/444059.rss">Exercising and Getting Fit</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Exercising and Getting Fit</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@wildskiller wildskiller]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/wildskiller">@wildskiller</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Shakeweight.<br>
I don’t have one and probably wont. I move my arms extremely fast up and down like I’m running in place and I’ve seen awesome results. I don’t run much because of my asthma.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/exercising-and-getting-fit/444059/126">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/exercising-and-getting-fit/444059/126</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 31 Jul 2012 16:15:10 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-444059-126</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/exercising-and-getting-fit/444059.rss">Exercising and Getting Fit</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Exercising and Getting Fit</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Frell Frell]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/frell">@Frell</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>love you too</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/exercising-and-getting-fit/444059/125">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/exercising-and-getting-fit/444059/125</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 31 Jul 2012 13:52:47 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-444059-125</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/exercising-and-getting-fit/444059.rss">Exercising and Getting Fit</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Exercising and Getting Fit</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Yz85Racer Yz85Racer]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/yz85racer">@Yz85Racer</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“Frell, post:123, topic:444059”][quote author=Yz85Racer link=topic=546742.msg4063470#msg4063470 date=1343656247]<br>
Actually, I’d say supplements like protein powder are proven to be more effective than a multivitamin (assuming your diet means you consume ample amounts). There’s no proof backing the effectiveness of multivitamins, because usually you just excrete whatever you don’t absorb (and, too many vitamins causes toxicity)<br>
[/quote]<br>
Whey protein can hardly be considered a “supplement”[/quote]<br>
You know what I meant faggot</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/exercising-and-getting-fit/444059/124">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/exercising-and-getting-fit/444059/124</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 31 Jul 2012 10:49:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-444059-124</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/exercising-and-getting-fit/444059.rss">Exercising and Getting Fit</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Exercising and Getting Fit</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Frell Frell]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/frell">@Frell</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote quote-modified" data-post="121" data-topic="444059">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/yz85racer/40/5_e05bb34c421432ee4d40de30c10af3e5.png" class="avatar"> Yz85Racer:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Actually, I’d say supplements like protein powder are proven to be more effective than a multivitamin (assuming your diet means you consume ample amounts). There’s no proof backing the effectiveness of multivitamins, because usually you just excrete whatever you don’t absorb (and, too many vitamins causes toxicity)</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Whey protein can hardly be considered a “supplement”</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/exercising-and-getting-fit/444059/123">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/exercising-and-getting-fit/444059/123</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 31 Jul 2012 00:25:19 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-444059-123</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/exercising-and-getting-fit/444059.rss">Exercising and Getting Fit</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Exercising and Getting Fit</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Faded.Fear Faded.Fear]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/faded.fear">@Faded.Fear</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote quote-modified" data-post="121" data-topic="444059">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/yz85racer/40/5_e05bb34c421432ee4d40de30c10af3e5.png" class="avatar"> Yz85Racer:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Actually, I’d say supplements like protein powder are proven to be more effective than a multivitamin (assuming your diet means you consume ample amounts). There’s no proof backing the effectiveness of multivitamins, because usually you just excrete whatever you don’t absorb (and, too many vitamins causes toxicity)</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>When I say multivitamins. I’m saying, ONE pill a day…<br>
Diet, meaning watching what you eat, not eating too much, not eating too less, eating a proportionate amount each time I eat. Which is 5-7 times a day, but little rations at a time.<br>
I run 3-5 miles a day, 4-6 days a week. Weight-Resistance training 3-5 days a week. (Being sure to always switch it up every few weeks to prevent muscle plateaus.)<br>
That much cardio implemented with that much weight-resistance, and that diet.<br>
Will, no doubt, tone you up. Slim you down. While packing LEAN muscle mass on you, with the least amount of FAT.<br>
I know this, because I’ve done some Personal Training for others, and have seen nothing but results.<br>
Also, my Recruiters have also told me that is the best way to put on LEAN Muscle mass. (Lean, meaning the least amount of fat as possible)</p>
<p>I also would like to add: I do not look badly on supplementation, but I do not use them. Solely on the fact that I love the hard work and challenge it is to do what I have done, and do what I want to do with my body, without that “extra umph.” To know I did it Naturally. That is what makes me feel so great about my transformation.</p>
<p>I also recommend any and everyone, who truly cares about their fitness/health levels. To register on <a href="http://www.bodybuilding.com" rel="nofollow noopener">www.bodybuilding.com</a> and do your measurements and use that site. It is a great way to keep you motivated, keep track of yourself, and make goals on there with their goal trackers. They have tons of exercises, with guides, pics, and even videos on how to do them. Targeted exercises, etc. They have motivational photos and other stuff on their forums. It’s a great site, and great motivator.<br>
I promise you won’t be disappointed in it. <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/wink.png?v=5" title=":wink:" class="emoji" alt=":wink:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/exercising-and-getting-fit/444059/122">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/exercising-and-getting-fit/444059/122</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 30 Jul 2012 13:58:03 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-444059-122</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/exercising-and-getting-fit/444059.rss">Exercising and Getting Fit</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Exercising and Getting Fit</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Yz85Racer Yz85Racer]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/yz85racer">@Yz85Racer</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Actually, I’d say supplements like protein powder are proven to be more effective than a multivitamin (assuming your diet means you consume ample amounts). There’s no proof backing the effectiveness of multivitamins, because usually you just excrete whatever you don’t absorb (and, too many vitamins causes toxicity)</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/exercising-and-getting-fit/444059/121">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/exercising-and-getting-fit/444059/121</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 30 Jul 2012 13:50:47 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-444059-121</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/exercising-and-getting-fit/444059.rss">Exercising and Getting Fit</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Exercising and Getting Fit</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Faded.Fear Faded.Fear]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/faded.fear">@Faded.Fear</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Mehh you don’t need supplements.<br>
All you need at the minimum are multivitamins.</p>
<p>To healthily and successfully lose weight, it’s all about your mind-set.<br>
You have to want it.<br>
Cardio.Diet.Weight-Resistance Training. Hydration.(water)</p>
<p>You will see nothing but results.<br>
I was over 300 pounds last year.<br>
Now I’m 195-200 lbs.<br>
Me now:<br>
<div class="lightbox-wrapper"><a class="lightbox" href="http://i48.tinypic.com/351ivqx.jpg" title="351ivqx.jpg" rel="nofollow noopener"><img src="http://i48.tinypic.com/351ivqx.jpg" alt width="375" height="500"><div class="meta">
<svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-far-image svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#far-image"></use></svg><span class="filename">351ivqx.jpg</span><span class="informations">600×800</span><svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-discourse-expand svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#discourse-expand"></use></svg>
</div></a></div></p>
<p>Future Soldier in the United States Army.<br>
Hooah!</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/exercising-and-getting-fit/444059/120">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/exercising-and-getting-fit/444059/120</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 30 Jul 2012 13:36:09 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-444059-120</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/exercising-and-getting-fit/444059.rss">Exercising and Getting Fit</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Exercising and Getting Fit</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Yz85Racer Yz85Racer]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/yz85racer">@Yz85Racer</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Seriously, the best exercises for losing weight are compound exercises.</p>
<p>Jc, there’s nothing wrong with using BCAA’s. I personally use xTend. However I’d ditch the creatine… The only thing that’s proven with creatine is it makes it easier to achieve muscle hypertrophy. Might sound good, but if you’re not achieving it naturally, you’re not working hard enough.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/exercising-and-getting-fit/444059/119">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/exercising-and-getting-fit/444059/119</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 30 Jul 2012 13:07:25 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-444059-119</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/exercising-and-getting-fit/444059.rss">Exercising and Getting Fit</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Exercising and Getting Fit</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@jc22493 Jc22493]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/jc22493">@jc22493</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote" data-post="117" data-topic="444059">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 The Soul:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>jc22493 use metamyosyn</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Ehh, I’d rather buy casein along with whey, because that’s what metamyosyn basically is.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/exercising-and-getting-fit/444059/118">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/exercising-and-getting-fit/444059/118</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jul 2012 05:09:21 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-444059-118</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/exercising-and-getting-fit/444059.rss">Exercising and Getting Fit</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Exercising and Getting Fit</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@the_soul The Soul]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/the_soul">@the_soul</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>jc22493 use metamyosyn</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/exercising-and-getting-fit/444059/117">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/exercising-and-getting-fit/444059/117</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jul 2012 05:03:32 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-444059-117</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/exercising-and-getting-fit/444059.rss">Exercising and Getting Fit</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Exercising and Getting Fit</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@gothic_queen casey.]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/gothic_queen">@gothic_queen</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote" data-post="115" data-topic="444059">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/frell/40/5_e05bb34c421432ee4d40de30c10af3e5.png" class="avatar"> Frell:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>no supplements, build muscle like an old medieval farmer</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>^^^^^^^</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/exercising-and-getting-fit/444059/116">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/exercising-and-getting-fit/444059/116</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jul 2012 04:40:32 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-444059-116</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/exercising-and-getting-fit/444059.rss">Exercising and Getting Fit</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Exercising and Getting Fit</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Frell Frell]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/frell">@Frell</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“m1lkman, post:113, topic:444059”][quote author=Frell link=topic=546742.msg4060034#msg4060034 date=1343336881]<br>
Natural plateau is the best plateau.<br>
[/quote]</p>
<p>Natural plateau?[/quote]<br>
no supplements, build muscle like an old medieval farmer</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/exercising-and-getting-fit/444059/115">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/exercising-and-getting-fit/444059/115</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jul 2012 02:50:42 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-444059-115</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/exercising-and-getting-fit/444059.rss">Exercising and Getting Fit</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Exercising and Getting Fit</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@jc22493 Jc22493]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/jc22493">@jc22493</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote" data-post="110" data-topic="444059">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/frell/40/5_e05bb34c421432ee4d40de30c10af3e5.png" class="avatar"> Frell:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Its all mental. Good nutrition + whey protein will have the same results.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Yeah, but being vegetarian during summer class isn’t really that great. The dining halls suck right now, lol.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/exercising-and-getting-fit/444059/114">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/exercising-and-getting-fit/444059/114</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jul 2012 23:07:40 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-444059-114</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/exercising-and-getting-fit/444059.rss">Exercising and Getting Fit</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Exercising and Getting Fit</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@m1lkman m1lkman]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/m1lkman">@m1lkman</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote" data-post="112" data-topic="444059">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/frell/40/5_e05bb34c421432ee4d40de30c10af3e5.png" class="avatar"> Frell:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Natural plateau is the best plateau.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Natural plateau?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/exercising-and-getting-fit/444059/113">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/exercising-and-getting-fit/444059/113</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jul 2012 21:40:04 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-444059-113</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/exercising-and-getting-fit/444059.rss">Exercising and Getting Fit</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Exercising and Getting Fit</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Frell Frell]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/frell">@Frell</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Natural plateau is the best plateau.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/exercising-and-getting-fit/444059/112">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/exercising-and-getting-fit/444059/112</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jul 2012 21:08:01 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-444059-112</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/exercising-and-getting-fit/444059.rss">Exercising and Getting Fit</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Exercising and Getting Fit</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@m1lkman m1lkman]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/m1lkman">@m1lkman</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote" data-post="110" data-topic="444059">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/frell/40/5_e05bb34c421432ee4d40de30c10af3e5.png" class="avatar"> Frell:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Its all mental. Good nutrition + whey protein will have the same results.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>He probably broke his plateau.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/exercising-and-getting-fit/444059/111">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/exercising-and-getting-fit/444059/111</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jul 2012 21:02:38 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-444059-111</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/exercising-and-getting-fit/444059.rss">Exercising and Getting Fit</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Exercising and Getting Fit</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Frell Frell]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/frell">@Frell</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Its all mental. Good nutrition + whey protein will have the same results.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/exercising-and-getting-fit/444059/110">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/exercising-and-getting-fit/444059/110</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jul 2012 20:56:58 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-444059-110</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/exercising-and-getting-fit/444059.rss">Exercising and Getting Fit</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Exercising and Getting Fit</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@jc22493 Jc22493]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/jc22493">@jc22493</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote" data-post="108" data-topic="444059">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/frell/40/5_e05bb34c421432ee4d40de30c10af3e5.png" class="avatar"> Frell:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>If you just started working out you will feel larger pretty quick, and then it slows down.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I’ve been working out for months, but I just started taking supplements other than whey protein.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/exercising-and-getting-fit/444059/109">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/exercising-and-getting-fit/444059/109</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jul 2012 20:10:48 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-444059-109</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/exercising-and-getting-fit/444059.rss">Exercising and Getting Fit</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Exercising and Getting Fit</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Frell Frell]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/frell">@Frell</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>If you just started working out you will feel larger pretty quick, and then it slows down.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/exercising-and-getting-fit/444059/108">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/exercising-and-getting-fit/444059/108</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jul 2012 19:23:30 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-444059-108</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/exercising-and-getting-fit/444059.rss">Exercising and Getting Fit</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Exercising and Getting Fit</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@jc22493 Jc22493]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/jc22493">@jc22493</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote quote-modified" data-post="97" data-topic="444059">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/jc22493/40/5_e05bb34c421432ee4d40de30c10af3e5.png" class="avatar"> Jc22493:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Right now I’m taking a bit of whey, glutamine, BCAAs, and creatine pre-workout and the same (but more whey) post-workout. I’m just wondering what ‘pre-workout’ and ‘post-workout’ mean, with respect to the time frame before and after my workout.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Back to this, it’s been 3 days since I’ve been taking this combination of supplements, and I’ve already felt and seen results. My biceps definitely feel a bit larger, and I’ve been able to do more in the gym.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/exercising-and-getting-fit/444059/107">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/exercising-and-getting-fit/444059/107</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jul 2012 19:12:11 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-444059-107</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/exercising-and-getting-fit/444059.rss">Exercising and Getting Fit</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Exercising and Getting Fit</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Turmoilz1337x Turmoilz1337x]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/turmoilz1337x">@Turmoilz1337x</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p><span class="mention">@JC</span><br>
Pre- That’s good supplementation, I do similar. Try a powder called Jack3d, you can get it at Vitamin Shop. Makes me bench much more on “bench day”.<br>
After- I’m not sure creatine is the ebst fr you after your workout, from what I belive it’s best pre.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/exercising-and-getting-fit/444059/106">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/exercising-and-getting-fit/444059/106</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jul 2012 13:06:24 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-444059-106</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/exercising-and-getting-fit/444059.rss">Exercising and Getting Fit</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Exercising and Getting Fit</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@jc22493 Jc22493]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/jc22493">@jc22493</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Abraham, I already have the glutamine and BCAAs, so I’ll just stick with them for now. I also found that NO helps a lot.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/exercising-and-getting-fit/444059/105">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/exercising-and-getting-fit/444059/105</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 24 Jul 2012 23:01:21 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-444059-105</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/exercising-and-getting-fit/444059.rss">Exercising and Getting Fit</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
