<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>SEO - Search Engine Optimization</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/seo-search-engine-optimization/38178</link>
    <description>I work for a site which currently offers advertisment and bookings for hotels, restaurants, bars etc... We will soon be moving onto a bigger site where we will become an online travel agency. This doesnt matter but I thought I would share it. I had to read up and learn about SEO.
The defination of SEO:

[i]The term used to describe the marketing technique of preparing a website to enhance its chances of being ranked in the top results of a search engine once a relevant search is undertaken. A number of factors are important when optimising a website, including the content and structure of the website&#39;s copy and page layout, the HTML meta-tags and the submission process.[/i] (Taken from www.websearchworkshop.co.uk/glossary.htm)

Basically if your good at SEO your site will appear first on the top of search engines, have a higher page rank, and over all will be viewed more.

[b]Linking[/b]
Linking may be one of the biggest parts of SEO as without links there would be no world wide web, everything is linked together in someway, the more links a page will have going towards it then the more people will be able to find it/go to it.
Google’s own literature encourages us to think of links as votes of differing values. A link from a respected website is a powerful vote. A link from a small website is a weak vote but still a vote. 

Popular search engines like Google and Yahoo build up a database of the World Wide Web by reading web pages and exploring the links they find with automated programs called robots or spiders. Before a website can appear in Google it must be found by Googlebot (Google’s spider), before a website can appear in Yahoo it must be found by Yahoo!Slurp (Yahoo!’s spider) and before a website can appear in any other spider based search engine it must first be found by that spider. A site with many links pointing to it is likely to be found quickly by spiders. A website without any links pointing to it will not be found by spiders unless something else explicitly draws the attention of the spiders. 


The links visible on most web pages are hyperlinks. The two main components of a hyperlink are the anchor text and the destination link. Inbound links to your site are hyperlinks on external sites which have your site as their destination. The text displayed on a web page for the link is known as the anchor text. The text “anchors” the link in the visible side of the web page. 

For example,
	For more details – click here

The phrase “click here” is the anchor text. 

“Click here” is not good anchor text. A search engine optimised website will avoid using phrases like “Click here” for anchor text. 


The best pages to link to yours will be good quality pages, have a similar topic/theme to your website and will link to yours using keyword rich anchor text.

To count as a “back link” in Google (a page of note which links to yours) a web page must have PageRank™ of 4/10 or more. You can view a page’s PageRank by using the Google toolbar (http://toolbar.google.com) and selecting the PageRank option.

Having identified on-topic and quality web pages which would make beneficial inbound links the owner/administrator of the site must be approached politely and persuaded into adding the link. In truth the majority of such requests will go an answered, many refused and only a small number accepted. The significance of winning one quality link, every week or so, is so great that it is worth the link building effort and the high number of failures.

Well this is only the linking part of SEO, and this is all I have learned, if you know more about SEO then just say what you know! This also only briefly covers linking but I picked out the most important points. To sum it all up you want reciprocal links, the higher the page rank of the link going towards your site, the higher your pagerank will be.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 22 Dec 2006 16:17:08 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>General Programming</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/seo-search-engine-optimization/38178.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>SEO - Search Engine Optimization</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@wonderguy6 Doc. Booty]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/wonderguy6">@wonderguy6</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>sounds very nice cant wait to see it.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/seo-search-engine-optimization/38178/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/seo-search-engine-optimization/38178/2</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 22 Dec 2006 16:17:08 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-38178-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/seo-search-engine-optimization/38178.rss">SEO - Search Engine Optimization</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>SEO - Search Engine Optimization</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Kimber Kimber]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/kimber">@Kimber</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I work for a site which currently offers advertisment and bookings for hotels, restaurants, bars etc… We will soon be moving onto a bigger site where we will become an online travel agency. This doesnt matter but I thought I would share it. I had to read up and learn about SEO.<br>
The defination of SEO:</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-i">The term used to describe the marketing technique of preparing a website to enhance its chances of being ranked in the top results of a search engine once a relevant search is undertaken. A number of factors are important when optimising a website, including the content and structure of the website’s copy and page layout, the HTML meta-tags and the submission process.</span> (Taken from <a href="http://www.websearchworkshop.co.uk/glossary.htm" rel="nofollow noopener">www.websearchworkshop.co.uk/glossary.htm</a>)</p>
<p>Basically if your good at SEO your site will appear first on the top of search engines, have a higher page rank, and over all will be viewed more.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Linking</span><br>
Linking may be one of the biggest parts of SEO as without links there would be no world wide web, everything is linked together in someway, the more links a page will have going towards it then the more people will be able to find it/go to it.<br>
Google’s own literature encourages us to think of links as votes of differing values. A link from a respected website is a powerful vote. A link from a small website is a weak vote but still a vote.</p>
<p>Popular search engines like Google and Yahoo build up a database of the World Wide Web by reading web pages and exploring the links they find with automated programs called robots or spiders. Before a website can appear in Google it must be found by Googlebot (Google’s spider), before a website can appear in Yahoo it must be found by Yahoo!Slurp (Yahoo!’s spider) and before a website can appear in any other spider based search engine it must first be found by that spider. A site with many links pointing to it is likely to be found quickly by spiders. A website without any links pointing to it will not be found by spiders unless something else explicitly draws the attention of the spiders.</p>
<p>The links visible on most web pages are hyperlinks. The two main components of a hyperlink are the anchor text and the destination link. Inbound links to your site are hyperlinks on external sites which have your site as their destination. The text displayed on a web page for the link is known as the anchor text. The text “anchors” the link in the visible side of the web page.</p>
<p>For example,<br>
For more details – click here</p>
<p>The phrase “click here” is the anchor text.</p>
<p>“Click here” is not good anchor text. A search engine optimised website will avoid using phrases like “Click here” for anchor text.</p>
<p>The best pages to link to yours will be good quality pages, have a similar topic/theme to your website and will link to yours using keyword rich anchor text.</p>
<p>To count as a “back link” in Google (a page of note which links to yours) a web page must have PageRank™ of 4/10 or more. You can view a page’s PageRank by using the Google toolbar (<a href="http://toolbar.google.com" rel="nofollow noopener">http://toolbar.google.com</a>) and selecting the PageRank option.</p>
<p>Having identified on-topic and quality web pages which would make beneficial inbound links the owner/administrator of the site must be approached politely and persuaded into adding the link. In truth the majority of such requests will go an answered, many refused and only a small number accepted. The significance of winning one quality link, every week or so, is so great that it is worth the link building effort and the high number of failures.</p>
<p>Well this is only the linking part of SEO, and this is all I have learned, if you know more about SEO then just say what you know! This also only briefly covers linking but I picked out the most important points. To sum it all up you want reciprocal links, the higher the page rank of the link going towards your site, the higher your pagerank will be.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/seo-search-engine-optimization/38178/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/seo-search-engine-optimization/38178/1</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 22 Dec 2006 16:16:24 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-38178-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/seo-search-engine-optimization/38178.rss">SEO - Search Engine Optimization</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
