<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Moparcraft as a whole</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/moparcraft-as-a-whole/449647</link>
    <description>I&#39;d appreciate if you all read this topic in its entirety and then respond to each issue individually. All opinions are needed and appreciated. ;)

Right. Tom and I were discussing Moparcraft on the IRC and discussed a number of issues that we as a community and as a staff team need to target and fix. We are on the verge of advertising this server and at the moment I feel the current community and staff team aren&#39;t unified, which makes for a bad enviroment in which this community is supposed to develop in. We, the staff team, and also the community&#39;s members can decide what direction this community will take, and it must be the correct direction for us to survive. Below, I will highlight some key issues that we need to discuss, debate and come to a conclusion on. Feel free to say absolutely anything and suggest absolutely anything. Nobody will be judged.

I&#39;ll start off with this first issue: [u]Staff Image[/u]. At the moment, we feel that the members just view a lot of us as an &#39;oppressive force&#39;. As if we&#39;re just here to ruin their fun and their time online. Our staff image is reflected in our actions in the community, the punishments we deal and the warnings we give and we need to fix our current staff image for the better. An example of something bad recently is the Agl incident, where there was an uproar from him and his friends. This has since resulted in a bad attitude from him and perhaps his friends at times. We need to ensure our decisions are respected and aren&#39;t opposed in a public manner. This means that future public arguments should be completely out of the question. We should keep these issues to the PM system where we (the moderators) can clearly spell out the situation, our reasoning for the punishment handed out and any further discussion required. This also leads us onto another small, yet significant issue: clear communication.

We need to have clear, concise communication in the future to afford us the expense of misinterpretation. In turn this may prevent public arguments, misunderstanding of the rules and would hopefully lead to a happier community.

Another important issue we face is [u]staff initiative[/u]. At the moment this is a problem for a number of reasons. For one, the members currently go straight to Tom or Zuppers if they require assistance when it is actually our job to provide that assistance. The administrators have enough on their plate without the extra pressure of helping the community, a job which we are supposed to fulfill. This means helping out more on the server, even going out of your way to help somebody if they require assistance. If you see an established member on the server who is annoying a new one, we should step in and stop the problem. 

Another part of this issue is staff members responding to important topics in the staff section (I&#39;m also a culprit to this). If we want to develop as a staff team and actually become the definition of the word &#39;team&#39;, then we actually need to respond to, discuss and argue issues if necessary. By discussing and arguing issues, there is always the potential chance that the original suggestion may be bettered and any flaws be ironed out. Don&#39;t be afraid to suggest something and then back it up through controlled arguments and good logic. If you want something on the server changed, don&#39;t be afraid to make a topic about it. Trust me, if we do this, we&#39;ll be a much better and composed staff team. Communication and honesty should be a fundamental property to any staff team.

Another important issue are the [u]server reports[/u]. Since we&#39;re so close to advertising the server we need to be on the ball with our response times to server reports. We want the users to get the impression that we&#39;re always there for help and support and if we achieve this, it&#39;s a good way to entice the new traffic to stick around. This also ties in with another issue of staff reliability and whether they have the will and capability to fulfill the demands of the position.

Also, I *think* there is a need to shorten the rules and our explanations of them. We&#39;re not here to spell everything out to the members, if they can&#39;t read between the lines and use their common sense, then so be it. Users tend to search for loop-holes in the rules.

Last, for now, is our judgement on members when suggesting them for any position (badges and all) within the community. What we should be looking for and require in staff members is knowledge, will power and dependability. We each need to learn how to recognize these traits and also identify any bad traits in a member. In short, we need to look more in depth at our nominations and their capacities (for lack of a better term). We need to stay away from listening to only the friends opinion on the nomination (not that we have been doing this) and form our own personal opinion on him/her. Generally, most members will be biased when suggesting a friend.

Sorry for the essay, but it had to be done. I may have also missed a point or explained a point that Tom and I discussed incorrectly, so keep an eye out for any edits. Please feel free to highlight any other issues you feel are worth mentioning or further a point I may have mentioned. :)</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 17 Jul 2012 00:48:36 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Games</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/moparcraft-as-a-whole/449647.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Moparcraft as a whole</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@LilXCj LilXCj]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/lilxcj">@LilXCj</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“Si Force, post:11, topic:449647”][quote author=LilXCj link=topic=552537.msg4048708#msg4048708 date=1342296736]<br>
Adding in to my previous arguements though:<br>
I feel that once we start bringing the hammer down (if we do at all), people like Agl will start screaming communism or something similar in which I feel they just need to be removed from this side of the forum as well.<br>
[/quote]</p>
<p>Sorry for posting a bit late, I saw your post but didn’t have the time to reply on the weekend.</p>
<p>I don’t feel that they should simply be ‘removed’, but I do agree that the hammer should be brought down and their nonsense put to a stop. An example of a member getting away with something is Agl verbally abusing Tom on the forum basically. That’s a case in which it should of been stopped early, and I along with others are guilty of not stepping in really. I don’t really predict it’ll happen again, however if it does i’m sure all of us will step in.[/quote]</p>
<p>I agree. I suppose we all just lacked the will to step in.</p>
<p>I hope to help in anyway while I can.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/moparcraft-as-a-whole/449647/12">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/moparcraft-as-a-whole/449647/12</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jul 2012 00:48:36 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-449647-12</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/moparcraft-as-a-whole/449647.rss">Moparcraft as a whole</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Moparcraft as a whole</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@si_force Si Force]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/si_force">@si_force</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“LilXCj, post:5, topic:449647”]Adding in to my previous arguements though:<br>
I feel that once we start bringing the hammer down (if we do at all), people like Agl will start screaming communism or something similar in which I feel they just need to be removed from this side of the forum as well.[/quote]</p>
<p>Sorry for posting a bit late, I saw your post but didn’t have the time to reply on the weekend.</p>
<p>I don’t feel that they should simply be ‘removed’, but I do agree that the hammer should be brought down and their nonsense put to a stop. An example of a member getting away with something is Agl verbally abusing Tom on the forum basically. That’s a case in which it should of been stopped early, and I along with others are guilty of not stepping in really. I don’t really predict it’ll happen again, however if it does i’m sure all of us will step in.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/moparcraft-as-a-whole/449647/11">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/moparcraft-as-a-whole/449647/11</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 16 Jul 2012 23:14:46 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-449647-11</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/moparcraft-as-a-whole/449647.rss">Moparcraft as a whole</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Moparcraft as a whole</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Tom Tom]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/tom">@Tom</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Okay the suggestions board permissions should be sorted now, allow me to explain how the board works:</p>
<p>When people post there the post goes into moderation, this means it can only be viewed by staff members and not regular members. Staff can approve these posts by clicking the green icon where quote etc would be. The board works as followed: They post a topic, the staff review it, if the users is okay with it then it can be approved for public discussion.</p>
<p>Some people may wish to keep the topic moderated so it can be between staff -&gt; member only , if this is the case don’t approve it. Always ask a member if it’s okay to approve before doing it.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/moparcraft-as-a-whole/449647/10">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/moparcraft-as-a-whole/449647/10</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 15 Jul 2012 02:29:29 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-449647-10</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/moparcraft-as-a-whole/449647.rss">Moparcraft as a whole</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Moparcraft as a whole</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@LilXCj LilXCj]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/lilxcj">@LilXCj</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“Tom, post:8, topic:449647”]That’s true to an extent, if an established member griefs massively then there ban should be as long as a new players would be. But for the smaller incidents you should remember that everybody makes mistakes, and cracks under pressure. If a newer member joins straight of the bat and decides to break rules then the pure intent is to do bad for the community.</p>
<p>Having a pure intent to do bad is different from cracking under pressure. I’m not saying 6 months difference in the bans, but just a little more consideration. Of course repeat offenses can change all of that.</p>
<p>Good established players can be a hard thing to come by, if we go massively banning them straight off for making a mistake then it’s an issue, though, this is where staff opinion on a case by case basis comes in I guess  :)[/quote]</p>
<p>Of course I understand case by case issues and the gravity of each situation calls for different levels of punishments but a rule is still a rule.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/moparcraft-as-a-whole/449647/9">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/moparcraft-as-a-whole/449647/9</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 14 Jul 2012 21:11:58 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-449647-9</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/moparcraft-as-a-whole/449647.rss">Moparcraft as a whole</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Moparcraft as a whole</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Tom Tom]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/tom">@Tom</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>That’s true to an extent, if an established member griefs massively then there ban should be as long as a new players would be. But for the smaller incidents you should remember that everybody makes mistakes, and cracks under pressure. If a newer member joins straight of the bat and decides to break rules then the pure intent is to do bad for the community.</p>
<p>Having a pure intent to do bad is different from cracking under pressure. I’m not saying 6 months difference in the bans, but just a little more consideration. Of course repeat offenses can change all of that.</p>
<p>Good established players can be a hard thing to come by, if we go massively banning them straight off for making a mistake then it’s an issue, though, this is where staff opinion on a case by case basis comes in I guess  <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=5" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/moparcraft-as-a-whole/449647/8">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/moparcraft-as-a-whole/449647/8</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 14 Jul 2012 20:44:48 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-449647-8</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/moparcraft-as-a-whole/449647.rss">Moparcraft as a whole</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Moparcraft as a whole</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@LilXCj LilXCj]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/lilxcj">@LilXCj</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>If anything, we should make our bans harsh so “established players” wouldn’t be tempted to break the rules at all. Everyone is a player and should be treated equally regardless of their time here.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/moparcraft-as-a-whole/449647/7">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/moparcraft-as-a-whole/449647/7</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 14 Jul 2012 20:40:52 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-449647-7</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/moparcraft-as-a-whole/449647.rss">Moparcraft as a whole</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Moparcraft as a whole</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Tom Tom]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/tom">@Tom</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>We’re very lenient with a lot of things now, Agl is just being silly now, I’m sure you remember when he was arguing ingame about us going to easy on people breaking the rules and being idiots, he got banned now he’s saying we’re too harsh and I’m communist when he was the one arguing for such things.</p>
<p>His opinion on anything is about as constant as the changing weather. There is no bringing the hammer down as far as I can see, it’s more getting a few social changes to Moparcraft before we start advertising such as the entire staff team working together.</p>
<p>There is nothing wrong with giving more established players weaker bans, though. If they’re very active and they hardly do anything wrong then I don’t see why they shouldn’t be in comparison to somebody who just joined to break rules for example.</p>
<p>If you guys feel Agl needs to be removed I can do that no problem, but I’m not going to do that by my own vote because I’d just be feeding the fire. He doesn’t bring anything to Moparcraft, doesn’t cooperate with staff and just spams communism.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/moparcraft-as-a-whole/449647/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/moparcraft-as-a-whole/449647/6</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 14 Jul 2012 20:34:19 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-449647-6</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/moparcraft-as-a-whole/449647.rss">Moparcraft as a whole</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Moparcraft as a whole</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@LilXCj LilXCj]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/lilxcj">@LilXCj</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>My idea of when I became a staff member is that it was a job, albeit voluntary. I feel the staff need to treat it like such so that we need to establish that moparcraft is the way it is because the admins say so. If anyone acts outside the rules because they don’t like it, we simply punish them and that should be the end of it. No unbans, no second chances. They get one warning and that’s all. We have an entire thread which clearly explains the rules for each and every player of MoparCraft. I feel some of the staff gets attached to certain members they play with and soften up to the moparian community with things like 1 week bans, etc.</p>
<p>As far as people trying to make us look bad, why should we worry about them? We are trying to do our job as staff to the community in order to keep the game fresh and running smoothly for EVERYONE. Just because one or two people don’t like certain changes is no reason to falter and start trying to look for different solutions.</p>
<p>I don’t really have any comments towards staff unity because I am bad for not logging in here anymore due to my inability to play the game and moderate at all. It literally took me an hour to build an incomplete staircase in the creative world.</p>
<p>As far as badges go, I agree with Si Force and I don’t really have any further comments to make towards that subject.</p>
<p>Adding in to my previous arguements though:<br>
I feel that once we start bringing the hammer down (if we do at all), people like Agl will start screaming communism or something similar in which I feel they just need to be removed from this side of the forum as well.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/moparcraft-as-a-whole/449647/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/moparcraft-as-a-whole/449647/5</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 14 Jul 2012 20:12:16 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-449647-5</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/moparcraft-as-a-whole/449647.rss">Moparcraft as a whole</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Moparcraft as a whole</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Tom Tom]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/tom">@Tom</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Well we have 6 pages of discussion here in comparison to the admin section where there probably isn’t even a page. A lot of stuff is discussed here, and should be discussed here, usually it requires me to post it though (just look at the history of this section) if a staff member has an idea or concern then they should post it here. If you think I’m keeping you in the dark on something then post a topic, and we’ll talk, nobody ever said you couldn’t.</p>
<p>A lot of staff are afraid to perform to their full capability and say things they want to say because they’re afraid of getting put on the spot, or called out because of it. A lot of staff have been afraid to post their true, longer opinion because they’re afraid the admin might think they’re promotion hunting well that may be the case elsewhere but it isn’t here - I don’t care what you want albeit a promotion, an award, even a pet owl. If you have an opinion, even if its 4 posts long, post it.</p>
<p>I’ve only ever dealt with 3 matters in a section moderators can’t see (not always admin, either), and I’ve posted hundreds of topics. Those 3 matters were discussed in other places as well. What you have to realize is a lot of the stuff players are perceiving as decided on is just nothing but chatter from an administrator who logs on and can’t be found in either staff sections.</p>
<p>They want us to talk, we talk, then they misunderstand it ask a moderator who wants to know why they aren’t involved. Let’s face it a large portion of our players aren’t very smart, not to be rude but it’s just the truth. I regularly hold discussion on the server when people want to talk I’ve even made clear this isn’t decided on to them in the past. The only matters that were sort of decided on were the end, and the world changes.</p>
<p>Staff team in the past was just a bitching contest, I’m just as to blame as take Davidi2 for example, whoever decided that combination would work was either very smart or not thinking. Having 2 polar opposites is good for refined decision making but not on a minecraft server, as far as I’m concerned, Moparisthebest should of just told us both to shut up when we started bickering, though I don’t blame him for not doing that back then as he probably would of ended up in the firing line from both of us. As a general rule of thumb I’ve always said that staff should behave as if they were one, no drawing blood in public basically.</p>
<p>This idea of “I’ll just ask Tom” is due to many things, one reason would be that melon Agl who spams communism everywhere, according to him I’m the great British leader: Sir Tom. Who may I note, doesn’t take negative comments! Which is funny because I take about 4 hours of shit a day from Moparcraft alone, that doesn’t include being a MSCP moderator and dealing with that as well. Another reason is, a lot of the ideas that have come to be were posted by me, or at least contributed to a lot by me meaning people are aware I probably know more than most about changes and what’s going on. I’ve also been here as a staff member through a huge chunk of Moparcraft history, so people are well aware of who I am and how I operate. I’m by no means boasting. Everybody here is a good staff member it just comes down to reputation. This has been happening for ages it’s just only now everyone has started noticing.</p>
<p>I’ve never stood up and said “Don’t ask them, ask me! I know everything!” I’ve just answered questions, posted, and held discussions ingame when acceptable. All I’ve ever done is stand up and take the initiative, you can all do the same.</p>
<p>Just to address a few other points:</p>
<p><span class="mention">@cant</span> view suggestions properly: That’s an issue with the permission profile at the moment, I had Taharok add permissions so it’s like that of the MSCP where only MSCP moderators can view it (along with admins). I’ll go ahead and speak to him about giving every staff member here permission to see it, though I’ll have to work up a few guidelines on how the section is intended to work.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/moparcraft-as-a-whole/449647/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/moparcraft-as-a-whole/449647/4</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 14 Jul 2012 18:15:20 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-449647-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/moparcraft-as-a-whole/449647.rss">Moparcraft as a whole</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Moparcraft as a whole</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Phaze_One Fuscate]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/phaze_one">@Phaze_One</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>In regards to the staff image, yes, I completely agree with this. Multiple instances have and are occurring where the players are having this unnecessary public outcry against a single staff member (which almost 100% of the time is Tom). Obviously we need to put across the message that all changes are subject to debate however the way it is being done is not the way we want it. If multiple members wish to discuss something they disagree with then it should head to a private message or private IRC conversation to prevent it spiraling out of control on the forums and the server.</p>
<p>Going towards the initiative side we need to ensure members are aware that the moderators have almost the same capability of answering, discussing and debating with whatever issue they may have. From what I have observed the general consensus is that we have this hierarchy where the admins have the only say on what goes on behind the scenes, which is why we have groups attacking Tom about every single change. Multiple times I have been having a discussion with a member which just resolves with ‘I’ll just ask Tom’ , which is what I want to aim to prevent.</p>
<p>The staff unity one is a difficult subject. The fact that we are about to advertise is a little daunting considering the fact that only four of us regularly login to the server nowadays. Yes I would like to see more discussions on updates in the staff section (adding also I am a culprit to not always stating my opinion) but with such a limited amount of us a united decision cannot always come to the surface. Considering one of Moparcraft’s biggest updates was hidden to most of us which I believe all of us could’ve contributed to and came to a united decision about some aspects of the change (please note I am not picking holes here, everything that was changed was changed with logic and reason behind it and I personally would not have done anything differently).</p>
<p>With server reports, I can personally admit that I am not always as attentive as I should be with them. Most will be done within a few hours or a day however I will step on it and ensure they are a priority from now. This is another thing that falls under staff image that in the future we need to step up a notch.</p>
<p>In regards to nominations, as we see a rise in activity from when we begin advertising i’m sure this will become more relevant (the only nomination I have seen in months was the one posted by Tom from manbearpig (I cannot see the suggestions forum)) however I will bare this in mind for future nominations as I have often been accused of having tunnel vision.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/moparcraft-as-a-whole/449647/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/moparcraft-as-a-whole/449647/3</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 14 Jul 2012 18:00:11 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-449647-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/moparcraft-as-a-whole/449647.rss">Moparcraft as a whole</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Moparcraft as a whole</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@zuppers zuppers]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/zuppers">@zuppers</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I think the staff image will improve over time and it’s only a few people mainly agl who are going about and purposely trying to make us look bad. As for initiative I’m starting to think it’s going to kill me. Between trying to solve reports, play the actual game, new IRL responsibilities, make suggestions, picking new staff members and promoting old ones, just generally being active on the forums and in-game, finding time to work on xAuth and set up the server advertising, it’s getting kinda tough. And has much as I would like to. I don’t think I’ll be able to do it all alone anymore. We are going to need a few more staff members to be much more active here soon. As for rule shortening, having written most of them myself go for it. When something’s not on the list of rules and not clearly spelled out in front of their face, then we have to start constantly explaining the rules in-game which is annoying. You have to remember some users follow the rules down to the T. And when you punish someone for something that is just a general rule e.g No Griefing and <span class="bbcode-u">just because</span> you didn’t specify taking crops as griefing you can’t punish them for it without the user-base jumping on the hate the staff bandwagon and they start saying things like we’re just doing what ever we want and we’re making rules up. I’m not saying I do everything around here and I understand everyone else works to do stuff but my responsibilities are spread far and wide. And by saying “do it all alone” I mean purposely handling everything myself and not working as a team.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/moparcraft-as-a-whole/449647/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/moparcraft-as-a-whole/449647/2</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 14 Jul 2012 17:23:56 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-449647-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/moparcraft-as-a-whole/449647.rss">Moparcraft as a whole</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Moparcraft as a whole</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@si_force Si Force]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/si_force">@si_force</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I’d appreciate if you all read this topic in its entirety and then respond to each issue individually. All opinions are needed and appreciated. <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/wink.png?v=5" title=":wink:" class="emoji" alt=":wink:"></p>
<p>Right. Tom and I were discussing Moparcraft on the IRC and discussed a number of issues that we as a community and as a staff team need to target and fix. We are on the verge of advertising this server and at the moment I feel the current community and staff team aren’t unified, which makes for a bad enviroment in which this community is supposed to develop in. We, the staff team, and also the community’s members can decide what direction this community will take, and it must be the correct direction for us to survive. Below, I will highlight some key issues that we need to discuss, debate and come to a conclusion on. Feel free to say absolutely anything and suggest absolutely anything. Nobody will be judged.</p>
<p>I’ll start off with this first issue: <span class="bbcode-u">Staff Image</span>. At the moment, we feel that the members just view a lot of us as an ‘oppressive force’. As if we’re just here to ruin their fun and their time online. Our staff image is reflected in our actions in the community, the punishments we deal and the warnings we give and we need to fix our current staff image for the better. An example of something bad recently is the Agl incident, where there was an uproar from him and his friends. This has since resulted in a bad attitude from him and perhaps his friends at times. We need to ensure our decisions are respected and aren’t opposed in a public manner. This means that future public arguments should be completely out of the question. We should keep these issues to the PM system where we (the moderators) can clearly spell out the situation, our reasoning for the punishment handed out and any further discussion required. This also leads us onto another small, yet significant issue: clear communication.</p>
<p>We need to have clear, concise communication in the future to afford us the expense of misinterpretation. In turn this may prevent public arguments, misunderstanding of the rules and would hopefully lead to a happier community.</p>
<p>Another important issue we face is <span class="bbcode-u">staff initiative</span>. At the moment this is a problem for a number of reasons. For one, the members currently go straight to Tom or Zuppers if they require assistance when it is actually our job to provide that assistance. The administrators have enough on their plate without the extra pressure of helping the community, a job which we are supposed to fulfill. This means helping out more on the server, even going out of your way to help somebody if they require assistance. If you see an established member on the server who is annoying a new one, we should step in and stop the problem.</p>
<p>Another part of this issue is staff members responding to important topics in the staff section (I’m also a culprit to this). If we want to develop as a staff team and actually become the definition of the word ‘team’, then we actually need to respond to, discuss and argue issues if necessary. By discussing and arguing issues, there is always the potential chance that the original suggestion may be bettered and any flaws be ironed out. Don’t be afraid to suggest something and then back it up through controlled arguments and good logic. If you want something on the server changed, don’t be afraid to make a topic about it. Trust me, if we do this, we’ll be a much better and composed staff team. Communication and honesty should be a fundamental property to any staff team.</p>
<p>Another important issue are the <span class="bbcode-u">server reports</span>. Since we’re so close to advertising the server we need to be on the ball with our response times to server reports. We want the users to get the impression that we’re always there for help and support and if we achieve this, it’s a good way to entice the new traffic to stick around. This also ties in with another issue of staff reliability and whether they have the will and capability to fulfill the demands of the position.</p>
<p>Also, I <em>think</em> there is a need to shorten the rules and our explanations of them. We’re not here to spell everything out to the members, if they can’t read between the lines and use their common sense, then so be it. Users tend to search for loop-holes in the rules.</p>
<p>Last, for now, is our judgement on members when suggesting them for any position (badges and all) within the community. What we should be looking for and require in staff members is knowledge, will power and dependability. We each need to learn how to recognize these traits and also identify any bad traits in a member. In short, we need to look more in depth at our nominations and their capacities (for lack of a better term). We need to stay away from listening to only the friends opinion on the nomination (not that we have been doing this) and form our own personal opinion on him/her. Generally, most members will be biased when suggesting a friend.</p>
<p>Sorry for the essay, but it had to be done. I may have also missed a point or explained a point that Tom and I discussed incorrectly, so keep an eye out for any edits. Please feel free to highlight any other issues you feel are worth mentioning or further a point I may have mentioned. <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=5" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/moparcraft-as-a-whole/449647/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/moparcraft-as-a-whole/449647/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 14 Jul 2012 16:19:46 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-449647-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/moparcraft-as-a-whole/449647.rss">Moparcraft as a whole</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
