<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Join survivaldestiny.g.akliz.net its the best server</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/join-survivaldestiny-g-akliz-net-its-the-best-server/448698</link>
    <description>Welcome to Survival Destiny (1.2.5), the Owner is Yozee.

This is a dedicated server and we spend all are time trying to improve this server and we are needing people to come down and have fun on playing this server. This is a server with a lot of dedicated staff.

WE ARE ALSO LOOKING FOR SPECTACULAR BUILDERS TO MAKE CITY&#39;S, TOWN, HOTELS, HOUSES, SHOPS AND MORE.... FOR THAT THERE WILL BE A REWARD TO THIS. WE ARE ALSO LOOKING FOR A STAFF MEMBER,  BUT NEVER ASK FOR IT YOU WILL HAVE TO EARN IT.
We are very strict on the rules, you have to follow every rule that has been placed for you. if you oblige the rules then the results of this will be consider and will be taken through with staff seriosly. the best think to do if you want to get on well then have fun and enjoy your time that you have spent with us and hoping that you want to come back and gain a massive experience throughout this server.

We are also looking for someone who is experienced with all the plug-ins and the files and willing to help the server you will receive Mod/technician ONLY if I accept.

This server has many cities, villages and houses and many more, if you like building then this is your server to play where there is FLAT Land for you to build anything such as city&#39;s, houses villages. We also have a fast and easy shopping system. This is a type of server that if you work hard you will succeed into the game and will revive vast amount of rewards!!!!
Also we are looking For a Website Creator, by doing this you will receive the rank of forums owner or something such as this but i will need to approve of this before you receive the reward!!!

SO JOIN AND ENJOY THE VAST AMOUNT OF PLUGINGS WE HAVE THANKSS...</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 07 Jul 2012 21:29:42 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Minecraft</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/join-survivaldestiny-g-akliz-net-its-the-best-server/448698.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Join survivaldestiny.g.akliz.net its the best server</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@1wdvcxzaq12 1wdvcxzaq12]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/1wdvcxzaq12">@1wdvcxzaq12</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Welcome to Survival Destiny (1.2.5), the Owner is Yozee.</p>
<p>This is a dedicated server and we spend all are time trying to improve this server and we are needing people to come down and have fun on playing this server. This is a server with a lot of dedicated staff.</p>
<p>WE ARE ALSO LOOKING FOR SPECTACULAR BUILDERS TO MAKE CITY’S, TOWN, HOTELS, HOUSES, SHOPS AND MORE… FOR THAT THERE WILL BE A REWARD TO THIS. WE ARE ALSO LOOKING FOR A STAFF MEMBER,  BUT NEVER ASK FOR IT YOU WILL HAVE TO EARN IT.<br>
We are very strict on the rules, you have to follow every rule that has been placed for you. if you oblige the rules then the results of this will be consider and will be taken through with staff seriosly. the best think to do if you want to get on well then have fun and enjoy your time that you have spent with us and hoping that you want to come back and gain a massive experience throughout this server.</p>
<p>We are also looking for someone who is experienced with all the plug-ins and the files and willing to help the server you will receive Mod/technician ONLY if I accept.</p>
<p>This server has many cities, villages and houses and many more, if you like building then this is your server to play where there is FLAT Land for you to build anything such as city’s, houses villages. We also have a fast and easy shopping system. This is a type of server that if you work hard you will succeed into the game and will revive vast amount of rewards!!!<br>
Also we are looking For a Website Creator, by doing this you will receive the rank of forums owner or something such as this but i will need to approve of this before you receive the reward!!!</p>
<p>SO JOIN AND ENJOY THE VAST AMOUNT OF PLUGINGS WE HAVE THANKSS…</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/join-survivaldestiny-g-akliz-net-its-the-best-server/448698/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/join-survivaldestiny-g-akliz-net-its-the-best-server/448698/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 07 Jul 2012 21:29:42 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-448698-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/join-survivaldestiny-g-akliz-net-its-the-best-server/448698.rss">Join survivaldestiny.g.akliz.net its the best server</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
