<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Creating a server from scratch</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/creating-a-server-from-scratch/553675</link>
    <description>Hi,

I&#39;d like to learn how to write a server from scratch. First, I will say, my goals are rather grand, far-fetched, and perhaps unrealistic, but what isn&#39;t, is what I&#39;m asking. All I know, is if I can do this one thing I just said, I have a chance of bringing my visions to reality.

I want to know exactly how a server and client work from the ground up so that I can create my own custom server from my own understanding. I love being self-taught and do not want to leech anything. I know there is a lot involved in writing a server, many components to create, I would be grateful if anyone would be willing to help me learn what different parts there are to a server and how I should go about learning how to create each part to it.

I have many ideas of my own that I have not seen in a server, but I do not want to ask anyone to do it for me, so the only way would be to learn how to make a server completely from scratch and actually understanding how everything works and what each part is doing, so that when I create a feature of my own, I will know exactly how the server works in order to be able to add it. I do not want to write a server from scratch so that I can remake another version of RuneScape and emulate it, but rather, rethink the experience as a whole to another level, keeping to a simple fundamental value that I believe is the biggest drive of RuneScape that they never fully actualized and strayed further and further away from...

It&#39;s apparent not just in RuneScape, but every other successful mainstream game in existence to my knowledge. You can name any one, and I can tell you why it&#39;s successful, and why that is how I want to make my own game based off the philosophy. I can say as a student in game design and development, the one thing I&#39;ve always been interested in was the design of one that is prominent and successful, and I&#39;ve seen a common ground in all of them. The depth, the approach, and the realism of intuitivity being a key element. And it&#39;s my passion to bring that all together in a unified genre of game design. And I see the potential to sprout the seedling that&#39;s been germinating for decades from this very, simple, Java browser game.

I have been around Java and learning the basics for years, but never got into it seriously enough to be able to do everything on my own, always learning from others&#39; sources. I will still do that, but I want to be more serious in how I learn it, so I need to know exactly what I need to learn in every part of the server and also client from the ground up.

I&#39;ve taken the route of going to school and majoring in Software Engineering, but until you have a real application to develop (like this), you&#39;re just stuck learning bits and pieces of functional language that may be essential down the line, but doesn&#39;t serve an immediate purpose as such as this. I think this puts me way closer to my goal than just taking courses academically for years first, which doesn&#39;t even get me as close to where I want to be as this would. I just have to put more dedication into searching for the answers on my own and that&#39;s what I&#39;m doing. It&#39;s one way to learn everything before you know what you want to do with it, and another far more effective way, to know exactly what you want and learn it as you go in order to achieve it.

Now, actually getting to the technical aspect, I would like to start with a 525 to 530 revision because I think those were the best days of RuneScape, I have a very complete idea of what I have in mind for the server that is unlike any one else, with every single skill and feature in the game rethought of and re-imagined to create a completely different experience, but with the same game assets and models we all love. I plan to eventually create a standalone game with my base starting from RSPS, because I see so many elements in this game that would be reworked in a different way to make a game just like RuneScape, but a completely different focus to the game. I do not want to reveal too much as that is why I want to learn to do it myself altogether, just with some help and support from more experienced programmers that have already written their own servers and clients from scratch using Jagex&#39;s cache and game.

Once I have actually learned everything and begun writing my own source from scratch, I will create a project thread that details everything I plan to do to create a game that is unique to its core, just borrowing the assets of an already developed game, then eventually, if I can successfully host the server and gain a player base and expanded my knowledge of programming and game creation enough, I want to actually develop a full-blown game from scratch from the same concepts and ideas I have for the server.

I hope this would compel some experienced developers here to give some guidance and direction for me and others who I imagine might be wanting to know the same thing.

Thanks.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 28 Oct 2015 08:47:15 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/creating-a-server-from-scratch/553675.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Creating a server from scratch</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@xx_matty_xx Justin Bieber]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/xx_matty_xx">@xx_matty_xx</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I scanned through your post and it seems as though you have some great ideas and a lot of passion, but your programming skills are not yet advanced enough to fulfil your ambitions.</p>
<p>My advice would be to take a big step back and set some smaller, more realistic goals that you can achieve on your own. They definitely don’t have to be directly related to RSPS, just anything to do with networking and gaming that will build your experience. Basically just start writing shit that you know you can do, you’re setting yourself up for failure embarking on a project you have no idea how to start.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/creating-a-server-from-scratch/553675/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/creating-a-server-from-scratch/553675/4</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 28 Oct 2015 08:47:15 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-553675-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/creating-a-server-from-scratch/553675.rss">Creating a server from scratch</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Creating a server from scratch</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@shadow9903 shadow9903]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/shadow9903">@shadow9903</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I use to have this same idea of creating a server from scratch, it’s definitely a lot of work i’d say it’s possible though i didn’t have the motivation or the knowledge really to finish but then again i only messed around in java a little and I ended up switching to front end and back end web development anyways, I got a little off track you don’t see to many people actually complete this but I wish you the best of luck!</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/creating-a-server-from-scratch/553675/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/creating-a-server-from-scratch/553675/3</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 28 Oct 2015 04:32:23 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-553675-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/creating-a-server-from-scratch/553675.rss">Creating a server from scratch</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Creating a server from scratch</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@sinisoul sini]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/sinisoul">@sinisoul</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p><a href="https://github.com/Hadyn/mopar" class="onebox" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">https://github.com/Hadyn/mopar</a></p>
<p>The application you’re trying to develop is very complex. You need to have the mindset you’re trying to design and write a server, for a video game. There’s a lot of topics you will need to understand beyond the basics but if you can succeed to the best of your abilities you will have accomplished a huge deal.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/creating-a-server-from-scratch/553675/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/creating-a-server-from-scratch/553675/2</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 28 Oct 2015 00:26:19 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-553675-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/creating-a-server-from-scratch/553675.rss">Creating a server from scratch</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Creating a server from scratch</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@xSymmetry xSymmetry]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/xsymmetry">@xSymmetry</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Hi,</p>
<p>I’d like to learn how to write a server from scratch. First, I will say, my goals are rather grand, far-fetched, and perhaps unrealistic, but what isn’t, is what I’m asking. All I know, is if I can do this one thing I just said, I have a chance of bringing my visions to reality.</p>
<p>I want to know exactly how a server and client work from the ground up so that I can create my own custom server from my own understanding. I love being self-taught and do not want to leech anything. I know there is a lot involved in writing a server, many components to create, I would be grateful if anyone would be willing to help me learn what different parts there are to a server and how I should go about learning how to create each part to it.</p>
<p>I have many ideas of my own that I have not seen in a server, but I do not want to ask anyone to do it for me, so the only way would be to learn how to make a server completely from scratch and actually understanding how everything works and what each part is doing, so that when I create a feature of my own, I will know exactly how the server works in order to be able to add it. I do not want to write a server from scratch so that I can remake another version of RuneScape and emulate it, but rather, rethink the experience as a whole to another level, keeping to a simple fundamental value that I believe is the biggest drive of RuneScape that they never fully actualized and strayed further and further away from…</p>
<p>It’s apparent not just in RuneScape, but every other successful mainstream game in existence to my knowledge. You can name any one, and I can tell you why it’s successful, and why that is how I want to make my own game based off the philosophy. I can say as a student in game design and development, the one thing I’ve always been interested in was the design of one that is prominent and successful, and I’ve seen a common ground in all of them. The depth, the approach, and the realism of intuitivity being a key element. And it’s my passion to bring that all together in a unified genre of game design. And I see the potential to sprout the seedling that’s been germinating for decades from this very, simple, Java browser game.</p>
<p>I have been around Java and learning the basics for years, but never got into it seriously enough to be able to do everything on my own, always learning from others’ sources. I will still do that, but I want to be more serious in how I learn it, so I need to know exactly what I need to learn in every part of the server and also client from the ground up.</p>
<p>I’ve taken the route of going to school and majoring in Software Engineering, but until you have a real application to develop (like this), you’re just stuck learning bits and pieces of functional language that may be essential down the line, but doesn’t serve an immediate purpose as such as this. I think this puts me way closer to my goal than just taking courses academically for years first, which doesn’t even get me as close to where I want to be as this would. I just have to put more dedication into searching for the answers on my own and that’s what I’m doing. It’s one way to learn everything before you know what you want to do with it, and another far more effective way, to know exactly what you want and learn it as you go in order to achieve it.</p>
<p>Now, actually getting to the technical aspect, I would like to start with a 525 to 530 revision because I think those were the best days of RuneScape, I have a very complete idea of what I have in mind for the server that is unlike any one else, with every single skill and feature in the game rethought of and re-imagined to create a completely different experience, but with the same game assets and models we all love. I plan to eventually create a standalone game with my base starting from RSPS, because I see so many elements in this game that would be reworked in a different way to make a game just like RuneScape, but a completely different focus to the game. I do not want to reveal too much as that is why I want to learn to do it myself altogether, just with some help and support from more experienced programmers that have already written their own servers and clients from scratch using Jagex’s cache and game.</p>
<p>Once I have actually learned everything and begun writing my own source from scratch, I will create a project thread that details everything I plan to do to create a game that is unique to its core, just borrowing the assets of an already developed game, then eventually, if I can successfully host the server and gain a player base and expanded my knowledge of programming and game creation enough, I want to actually develop a full-blown game from scratch from the same concepts and ideas I have for the server.</p>
<p>I hope this would compel some experienced developers here to give some guidance and direction for me and others who I imagine might be wanting to know the same thing.</p>
<p>Thanks.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/creating-a-server-from-scratch/553675/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/creating-a-server-from-scratch/553675/1</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 28 Oct 2015 00:04:45 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-553675-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/creating-a-server-from-scratch/553675.rss">Creating a server from scratch</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
