<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Sl psww</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/sl-psww/80678</link>
    <description>Lorax or whoever else can help there are a few problems that i need help with. Is there some way to edit the script so it wont turn friends chat on. Also i turn it on it works and i come back later and it keeps telling me that it is the next players turn when i have it set to only one player. And i have the time limit set to 60 mins. Also it keeps passin up the bank. If nyone can help me with these problems ASAP i would appreciate it. this is a copy of my script:

if you can help me please do i need all the help i can get


thanks

bsballastro</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 16 Apr 2007 03:28:23 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/sl-psww/80678.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Sl psww</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@iluvrs iluvrs]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/iluvrs">@iluvrs</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>i have all the same problems + more besides the part when you start it it worls fine, mine works but only for a run or 2 always gets lots on the way to the bank. these are some of mine,<br>
Ok, whenever i start the script in the bank it fails at finding the best ax, i have a mithril ax in the first bank slot but it doesn’t pick it up, it just stays there till it loggs out do you nkow what the problem is? And lets just say my name on rs that i was useing is  g lil mee it’s not but would me nick just be lil?<br>
Basicaly, The script works different for me than it does for everyone else. I have folowed people that are useing the same script and they all walk the same path but if i let sl psww pick the colors it walks so weird and always ends up getting lost on the way ot the bank and logging off. and than it will say going to account 1 but i dont want it to logg on account 1. it dont have an account 1 i only wanted to use account 0 but if i set 0 where it says how many acounts do you want to use it says error on line 75.So are the people that are useing sl psww setting there own colors? if so will you show me how to set my own colors? pleas ehelp i just want this 1 script to wrok, and maybe a yew script oncei m lvl 60 wcing. please help im so mad that this isn;t working!</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/sl-psww/80678/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/sl-psww/80678/2</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 16 Apr 2007 03:28:23 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-80678-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/sl-psww/80678.rss">Sl psww</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Sl psww</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@bsballastro bsballastro]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/bsballastro">@bsballastro</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Lorax or whoever else can help there are a few problems that i need help with. Is there some way to edit the script so it wont turn friends chat on. Also i turn it on it works and i come back later and it keeps telling me that it is the next players turn when i have it set to only one player. And i have the time limit set to 60 mins. Also it keeps passin up the bank. If nyone can help me with these problems ASAP i would appreciate it. this is a copy of my script:</p>
<p>if you can help me please do i need all the help i can get</p>
<p>thanks</p>
<p>bsballastro</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/sl-psww/80678/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/sl-psww/80678/1</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 16 Apr 2007 01:31:50 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-80678-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/sl-psww/80678.rss">Sl psww</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
