<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>I Want To Learn Hard Shit</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/i-want-to-learn-hard-shit/256847</link>
    <description>Well, i got the basics down, been coding for about 6 months now. There&#39;s Stuff i still don&#39;t know though. Like Wtf is a static int, i just wanna learn all this void shit and what it means, i&#39;ve tryed that &quot;java coding conventions but it brings me to this page with like 100 words, and no explanation.So if your good at coding(very good) help me with the following.

[ul][li]Static ints[/li]
[li]Methods[/li]
[li]Booleans[/li][/ul]

I know you barely know what i mean, but i just wanna figure out what they mean, and how i can learn to use them.ive spent too lnog coding and i can&#39;t even make stuff like a duel arena, the best i can do is a quest, ipban codes typed out, and the best thing i&#39;ve ever done was make a clan chat.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2009 00:18:17 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/i-want-to-learn-hard-shit/256847.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>I Want To Learn Hard Shit</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@xray_veeo xray veeo]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/xray_veeo">@xray_veeo</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Well, i got the basics down, been coding for about 6 months now. There’s Stuff i still don’t know though. Like Wtf is a static int, i just wanna learn all this void shit and what it means, i’ve tryed that "java coding conventions but it brings me to this page with like 100 words, and no explanation.So if your good at coding(very good) help me with the following.</p>
<p>[ul][li]Static ints[/li]<br>
[li]Methods[/li]<br>
[li]Booleans[/li][/ul]</p>
<p>I know you barely know what i mean, but i just wanna figure out what they mean, and how i can learn to use them.ive spent too lnog coding and i can’t even make stuff like a duel arena, the best i can do is a quest, ipban codes typed out, and the best thing i’ve ever done was make a clan chat.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/i-want-to-learn-hard-shit/256847/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/i-want-to-learn-hard-shit/256847/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2009 00:18:17 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-256847-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/i-want-to-learn-hard-shit/256847.rss">I Want To Learn Hard Shit</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
