<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Making Commands</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/making-commands/233773</link>
    <description>Heya everyone im trying to make a command for my up comming server (my first one) I got Voule Command Generatore i took it from another source and put it in the source im using atm and umm i made the command and the coords where it will take me and i generated the code. Now i only got 1 question for you all, Where would i put that code so in-game i will be able to use that command to teleport to where i want to teleport...? just please anyone tell me where i put that code then ill thank you after im done with all my commands ill start editing npcs then eventually release my new server/client. then ill be releasing the source. first i need help with this one problem.

Thanks,

Masterth1ef</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2008 00:07:10 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/making-commands/233773.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Making Commands</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@MicroZoft MicroZoft]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/microzoft">@MicroZoft</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>ok when you got the code copied open client.java and search for any other code you have such as master etc. right below or above doesn’t really matter post the code.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/making-commands/233773/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/making-commands/233773/2</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2008 00:07:10 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-233773-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/making-commands/233773.rss">Making Commands</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Making Commands</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@MasterTh1ef MasterTh1ef]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/masterth1ef">@MasterTh1ef</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Heya everyone im trying to make a command for my up comming server (my first one) I got Voule Command Generatore i took it from another source and put it in the source im using atm and umm i made the command and the coords where it will take me and i generated the code. Now i only got 1 question for you all, Where would i put that code so in-game i will be able to use that command to teleport to where i want to teleport…? just please anyone tell me where i put that code then ill thank you after im done with all my commands ill start editing npcs then eventually release my new server/client. then ill be releasing the source. first i need help with this one problem.</p>
<p>Thanks,</p>
<p>Masterth1ef</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/making-commands/233773/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/making-commands/233773/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 28 Sep 2008 23:18:20 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-233773-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/making-commands/233773.rss">Making Commands</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
