<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Client Problems</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/client-problems/317791</link>
    <description>Hello, I&#39;m going to try to be descriptive as possible while explaining this. Please ask for additional details if you need them. So, for all clients I play, there is this little problem. When I first load the client and I start logging in, it takes forever to load. &quot;Loading please wait..&quot; For about 1-2 minutes. Now, this comes weird to me since I can play Webclients and Runescape just fine, without it loading slow. This is for any client, 317-525, and so forth. It just takes forever to load. If someone has a good fix for this, please post. Also, for 317&#39;s, this is where the major problem is. When I get onto a 317 client, I can&#39;t move without it crashing. As soon as I take a few steps in any direction it crashes. It does this for all 317 client&#39;s I have played. I really hope you guys can help me out. If you need more information on this then I will post it. Oh, and I have a 508, 525, Runesape, and 317 cache in my C:\ drive. I also have JDK downloaded and paths set. 

Thanks for reading,
Xx R A G 3 R.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 05 Dec 2009 18:35:58 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Game Development</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/client-problems/317791.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Client Problems</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Xx_R_A_G_3_R Xx R A G 3 R]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/xx_r_a_g_3_r">@Xx_R_A_G_3_R</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Hello, I’m going to try to be descriptive as possible while explaining this. Please ask for additional details if you need them. So, for all clients I play, there is this little problem. When I first load the client and I start logging in, it takes forever to load. “Loading please wait…” For about 1-2 minutes. Now, this comes weird to me since I can play Webclients and Runescape just fine, without it loading slow. This is for any client, 317-525, and so forth. It just takes forever to load. If someone has a good fix for this, please post. Also, for 317’s, this is where the major problem is. When I get onto a 317 client, I can’t move without it crashing. As soon as I take a few steps in any direction it crashes. It does this for all 317 client’s I have played. I really hope you guys can help me out. If you need more information on this then I will post it. Oh, and I have a 508, 525, Runesape, and 317 cache in my C:\ drive. I also have JDK downloaded and paths set.</p>
<p>Thanks for reading,<br>
Xx R A G 3 R.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/client-problems/317791/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/client-problems/317791/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 05 Dec 2009 18:35:58 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-317791-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/client-problems/317791.rss">Client Problems</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
