<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>[Discussion] &quot;I Play Games - Not Make &#39;Em&quot;</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/discussion-i-play-games-not-make-em/374851</link>
    <description>Hi there.

I have something on my mind. Now this next statement may seem a bit biased/prejudice so please have some sensitivity whilst reading it: When has anyone in the private server community ever been successful. I mean really successful. Please read on to fully understand what I mean.

Now there are some very clever people here. I don&#39;t know what you all do for jobs, maybe there are some official IT experts here? I don&#39;t know. Maybe there is some people here that can or have created something completely new, original, from scratch with all ideas of their own (game wise; not small programs). Maybe.

Now this is more of a personal quote, as it probably doesn&#39;t apply to you, but I thought to myself just a while ago &quot;I play games - not make them&quot;.

I play games. And I enjoy doing so, as do you I&#39;m sure, because you&#39;re here reading this. Now then, I enjoy to download a private server source, take a look at it and have a play around with it. It&#39;s fun to create your own custom RuneScape.

But who am I kidding? I can&#39;t impact the community by doing something amazing (coding wise), which I believe deep down we all strive to do. We all contribute in our own way, some more than others, to produce some something we can call our own, our release, our server. But is that what you really call success? Even the more approved servers out there, the more complexed ones, can you [b]REALLY[/B] call them a success?

It sounds like I&#39;m talking down to them right? I&#39;m not. I genuinely appreciate the people that made private servers possible. I appreciate the people that do post some really nice content for us to use and abuse.

What I mean is, sit back for a second and think about the word &quot;success&quot;. Can any of us become a success here in the private server community? Can any of us become anything more than a &quot;server-tinkerer&quot; (I know we&#39;re all different individuals; this does not apply to everyone). 

You may think I&#39;m just saying this becasue I can&#39;t do it myself or I don&#39;t have the right to say this. It&#39;s something I was wondering. I don&#39;t know jack-shit; that&#39;s why I&#39;m asking you.

I guess my real question is: if any of us were that great, would we be here?

But I will speak for myself.

Also, maybe there are successful people among the community, but have not yet come forward. I know if I really had done something special, I&#39;d be reluctant to just broadcast it and let it be ruined.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 24 Dec 2010 17:54:54 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>General Discussion</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/discussion-i-play-games-not-make-em/374851.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>[Discussion] &quot;I Play Games - Not Make &#39;Em&quot;</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Explisionist Explisionist]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/explisionist">@Explisionist</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>People come here to talk, and help most of the time. The ones who are posting downloads over and over of the same stuff are normally just people trying to gain respect over the internet.</p>
<p>The true creators are Jagex, and everyone knows it… No matter how hard you try to “change” the scripting it will still be made by Jagex… Sure everyone can flame me and say stupid crap, but you all know its true… Now a game made by someone from scratch or a 2d/3d engine and turned in to a big success is pretty good.<br>
Most people here claim to “know” Java… But really your tl;dr everything you work with on here.</p>
<p>To ensure that you can really “code” then read the doc’s for Java, C#, C+, C++, C, etc…<br>
Or find someone that is good with it and can help you… It may sound hard from the beginning but after you work with it, I’m sure you will understand that it’s easier.</p>
<p>In my own opinion I would have to say about 98% of this community only plays games, and downloads bases to make their own to play. The 2% actually try to make a unique game, and when they do normally no one try’s it out because its not a famous source…</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/discussion-i-play-games-not-make-em/374851/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/discussion-i-play-games-not-make-em/374851/4</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 24 Dec 2010 17:54:54 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-374851-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/discussion-i-play-games-not-make-em/374851.rss">[Discussion] &quot;I Play Games - Not Make &#39;Em&quot;</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Discussion] &quot;I Play Games - Not Make &#39;Em&quot;</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Muroth Muroth]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/muroth">@Muroth</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“k0 twin, post:1, topic:374867”][quote author=Ix Soulcist xI link=topic=470815.msg3443116#msg3443116 date=1293209111]<br>
a lot of the popular, great, talented programmers have been on R-S<br>
[/quote]<br>
Can you clarify? I don’t really get what you mean by this. You’re saying a lot of the great programmers out there have been involved with Runescape private servers?[/quote]</p>
<p>On rune server forums.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/discussion-i-play-games-not-make-em/374851/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/discussion-i-play-games-not-make-em/374851/3</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 24 Dec 2010 17:22:07 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-374851-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/discussion-i-play-games-not-make-em/374851.rss">[Discussion] &quot;I Play Games - Not Make &#39;Em&quot;</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Discussion] &quot;I Play Games - Not Make &#39;Em&quot;</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Ix_Soulcist_xI Soulcist]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/ix_soulcist_xi">@Ix_Soulcist_xI</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>There isn’t much to explain with that question but I can see that for some reason a lot of the popular, great, talented programmers have been on R-S for some reason. If I knew a lot about programming, then I would help turn MoparScape around or at least attempt to.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/discussion-i-play-games-not-make-em/374851/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/discussion-i-play-games-not-make-em/374851/2</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 24 Dec 2010 16:45:11 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-374851-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/discussion-i-play-games-not-make-em/374851.rss">[Discussion] &quot;I Play Games - Not Make &#39;Em&quot;</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Discussion] &quot;I Play Games - Not Make &#39;Em&quot;</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Mendorphins Mendorphins]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/mendorphins">@Mendorphins</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Hi there.</p>
<p>I have something on my mind. Now this next statement may seem a bit biased/prejudice so please have some sensitivity whilst reading it: When has anyone in the private server community ever been successful. I mean really successful. Please read on to fully understand what I mean.</p>
<p>Now there are some very clever people here. I don’t know what you all do for jobs, maybe there are some official IT experts here? I don’t know. Maybe there is some people here that can or have created something completely new, original, from scratch with all ideas of their own (game wise; not small programs). Maybe.</p>
<p>Now this is more of a personal quote, as it probably doesn’t apply to you, but I thought to myself just a while ago “I play games - not make them”.</p>
<p>I play games. And I enjoy doing so, as do you I’m sure, because you’re here reading this. Now then, I enjoy to download a private server source, take a look at it and have a play around with it. It’s fun to create your own custom RuneScape.</p>
<p>But who am I kidding? I can’t impact the community by doing something amazing (coding wise), which I believe deep down we all strive to do. We all contribute in our own way, some more than others, to produce some something we can call our own, our release, our server. But is that what you really call success? Even the more approved servers out there, the more complexed ones, can you <span class="bbcode-b">REALLY</span> call them a success?</p>
<p>It sounds like I’m talking down to them right? I’m not. I genuinely appreciate the people that made private servers possible. I appreciate the people that do post some really nice content for us to use and abuse.</p>
<p>What I mean is, sit back for a second and think about the word “success”. Can any of us become a success here in the private server community? Can any of us become anything more than a “server-tinkerer” (I know we’re all different individuals; this does not apply to everyone).</p>
<p>You may think I’m just saying this becasue I can’t do it myself or I don’t have the right to say this. It’s something I was wondering. I don’t know jack-shit; that’s why I’m asking you.</p>
<p>I guess my real question is: if any of us were that great, would we be here?</p>
<p>But I will speak for myself.</p>
<p>Also, maybe there are successful people among the community, but have not yet come forward. I know if I really had done something special, I’d be reluctant to just broadcast it and let it be ruined.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/discussion-i-play-games-not-make-em/374851/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/discussion-i-play-games-not-make-em/374851/1</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 24 Dec 2010 13:43:21 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-374851-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/discussion-i-play-games-not-make-em/374851.rss">[Discussion] &quot;I Play Games - Not Make &#39;Em&quot;</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
