<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>New rs 07 videos</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-rs-07-videos/520368</link>
    <description>RS07 User: Kr0nic Rng
Channel: https://www.youtube.com/user/k1dkr0nic

I made a new youtube channel when rs07 was released.
I already have a few videos up to be watched, and a lot more to come.
Let me know what type of videos you think would make my channel/videos better (preferably only if you already watched alteast a few of what I got)
I plan on showing more pking at the end of my progress videos for now on, just like my new path of a pker series shows, and complete pk montages and commentaries once my account if finished or closer to hitting my goals.
I have been told and do understand I need to work on my commentary so please don&#39;t spam that but I do plan on working on that as much as just getting up my stats and making more entertaining content.

If you like what you see, or just want to give it a chance for a while to see if it improves I will really appreciate some subscriptions, likes, and comments on my videos,
-Thanks for reading all this and giving the channel a chance (if you do lol) I hope you enjoy, sub, and continue watching future videos..

I wasn&#39;t sure if I could advertise my channel in this section tbh but since it is a rs07 channel with a lot of rs07 progress vids, bank vids, and pking, I didn&#39;t see why it would be a problems. (plus I couldn&#39;t find a rules thread in this section.) If this thread needs to be moved or something though then ight (:

RS07 User: Kr0nic Rng
Channel: https://www.youtube.com/user/k1dkr0nic</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 30 May 2013 05:53:48 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-rs-07-videos/520368.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>New rs 07 videos</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@trilogy-reborn trilogy-reborn]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/trilogy-reborn">@trilogy-reborn</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>RS07 User: Kr0nic Rng<br>
Channel: <a href="https://www.youtube.com/user/k1dkr0nic" rel="nofollow noopener">https://www.youtube.com/user/k1dkr0nic</a></p>
<p>I made a new youtube channel when rs07 was released.<br>
I already have a few videos up to be watched, and a lot more to come.<br>
Let me know what type of videos you think would make my channel/videos better (preferably only if you already watched alteast a few of what I got)<br>
I plan on showing more pking at the end of my progress videos for now on, just like my new path of a pker series shows, and complete pk montages and commentaries once my account if finished or closer to hitting my goals.<br>
I have been told and do understand I need to work on my commentary so please don’t spam that but I do plan on working on that as much as just getting up my stats and making more entertaining content.</p>
<p>If you like what you see, or just want to give it a chance for a while to see if it improves I will really appreciate some subscriptions, likes, and comments on my videos,<br>
-Thanks for reading all this and giving the channel a chance (if you do lol) I hope you enjoy, sub, and continue watching future videos…</p>
<p>I wasn’t sure if I could advertise my channel in this section tbh but since it is a rs07 channel with a lot of rs07 progress vids, bank vids, and pking, I didn’t see why it would be a problems. (plus I couldn’t find a rules thread in this section.) If this thread needs to be moved or something though then ight (:</p>
<p>RS07 User: Kr0nic Rng<br>
Channel: <a href="https://www.youtube.com/user/k1dkr0nic" rel="nofollow noopener">https://www.youtube.com/user/k1dkr0nic</a></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-rs-07-videos/520368/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-rs-07-videos/520368/1</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 30 May 2013 05:53:48 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-520368-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-rs-07-videos/520368.rss">New rs 07 videos</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
