<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>[PI] Clipping</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/pi-clipping/434377</link>
    <description>Well, to say it lightly, I&#39;m at a dead end. I&#39;ve put a lot of effort into a source that I&#39;d rather not release until the clipping is fixed, as it will just cause problems for the players.

I&#39;m looking for some help in fixing the player clipping, which is when the players can run through walls and objects when they attack another player, or another npc.. etc. I&#39;ve managed to fix the follow clip, but I&#39;m at a complete dead end with the player clipping.

Looking for some ideas maybe or any help. I&#39;ve looked for tutorials and searched through the entire forum basically, I can&#39;t find anything. I know it&#39;s probably pointless to ask for help since everyone expects you to know what you&#39;re doing, but what&#39;s the point of the help section if you can&#39;t ask questions right? Any help is really appreciated.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 27 Feb 2012 01:11:18 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/pi-clipping/434377.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>[PI] Clipping</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@DrummerDavex DrummerDavex]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/drummerdavex">@DrummerDavex</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Well, to say it lightly, I’m at a dead end. I’ve put a lot of effort into a source that I’d rather not release until the clipping is fixed, as it will just cause problems for the players.</p>
<p>I’m looking for some help in fixing the player clipping, which is when the players can run through walls and objects when they attack another player, or another npc… etc. I’ve managed to fix the follow clip, but I’m at a complete dead end with the player clipping.</p>
<p>Looking for some ideas maybe or any help. I’ve looked for tutorials and searched through the entire forum basically, I can’t find anything. I know it’s probably pointless to ask for help since everyone expects you to know what you’re doing, but what’s the point of the help section if you can’t ask questions right? Any help is really appreciated.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/pi-clipping/434377/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/pi-clipping/434377/1</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 27 Feb 2012 01:11:18 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-434377-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/pi-clipping/434377.rss">[PI] Clipping</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
