<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Can not run server</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/can-not-run-server/274196</link>
    <description>I&#39;ve recently switched to a 508 server and have been focusing a lot on that, but when I recently decided to release my 317 I began to encounter issues. When attempting to run the server, this message appears in the prompt:

[kernel]: machine is too slow to run this server!

This message appears repeatedly. I&#39;ve already considered the possibility that my computer may not be fast enough, but I&#39;ve found this is not true. When I attempt to run an older version of the same server, that actually has signifficantly larger file sizes, it runs perfectly. Another disproving factor is my 508 server, which runs just fine as well. My friend has actually attempted to run this server on his much faster, and, well better computer, and he encountered this same issue.

I&#39;ve been making some attempts correct this problem, for example I cleared almost 20 mbs of space, this included clearing out char files, all logs, deleting unneaded globalobjects, deleting unneaded npc spawns, deleting unneaded commands etc etc... but I&#39;ve come to a certain level of frustration and decided to simply ask for a solution.

If you know or may have a solution, I would really appreciate some feedback.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 18 Apr 2009 18:39:09 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/can-not-run-server/274196.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Can not run server</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@chadrocks13 chadrocks13]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/chadrocks13">@chadrocks13</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I’m not entirly sure… my friend actually hosts our servers. When I try to run it though it’s from a local host.[br][br][size=1]Posted on: April 18, 2009, 02:00:27 pm[/size][hr]I’d also like to note that it’s not instantaneous, the kernel doesn’t usually show up for a few minutes…</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/can-not-run-server/274196/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/can-not-run-server/274196/3</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 18 Apr 2009 18:39:09 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-274196-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/can-not-run-server/274196.rss">Can not run server</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Can not run server</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@NewbieNewty Newty]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/newbienewty">@NewbieNewty</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Do 508’s use MySQL, because I used to get that error when running my 317 through a free MySQL host.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/can-not-run-server/274196/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/can-not-run-server/274196/2</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 18 Apr 2009 18:36:47 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-274196-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/can-not-run-server/274196.rss">Can not run server</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Can not run server</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@chadrocks13 chadrocks13]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/chadrocks13">@chadrocks13</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I’ve recently switched to a 508 server and have been focusing a lot on that, but when I recently decided to release my 317 I began to encounter issues. When attempting to run the server, this message appears in the prompt:</p>
<p>[kernel]: machine is too slow to run this server!</p>
<p>This message appears repeatedly. I’ve already considered the possibility that my computer may not be fast enough, but I’ve found this is not true. When I attempt to run an older version of the same server, that actually has signifficantly larger file sizes, it runs perfectly. Another disproving factor is my 508 server, which runs just fine as well. My friend has actually attempted to run this server on his much faster, and, well better computer, and he encountered this same issue.</p>
<p>I’ve been making some attempts correct this problem, for example I cleared almost 20 mbs of space, this included clearing out char files, all logs, deleting unneaded globalobjects, deleting unneaded npc spawns, deleting unneaded commands etc etc… but I’ve come to a certain level of frustration and decided to simply ask for a solution.</p>
<p>If you know or may have a solution, I would really appreciate some feedback.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/can-not-run-server/274196/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/can-not-run-server/274196/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 18 Apr 2009 18:30:55 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-274196-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/can-not-run-server/274196.rss">Can not run server</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
