<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Mouse trouble?</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/mouse-trouble/16421</link>
    <description>Hello all. I&#39;m having trouble with my mouse.

I have a dell optical mouse, and recently the red light that it uses stops without warning, and I can&#39;t move the mouse. The mouse is pretty old, the things that bother me are as follows:

It often stops without warning, and I can&#39;t get it to work again for I don&#39;t know how long, BUT the mouse buttons(1, 2, 3) are still functional, I just can&#39;t move it. I recently had to format my pc so I&#39;m not sure if it&#39;s my computer or the mouse. It won&#39;t work in any other usb port, so again I&#39;m not sure if it&#39;s the pc or the mouse it&#39;s self.

I&#39;m not sure if it&#39;s a virus because, like I said my left, right and mouse wheel buttons still work, and the red light is turned off and I can&#39;t move it. Right now I&#39;m using my keyboard mouse keys to move it. :) 

Any help/suggestions is apprieated before I buy a new mouse.

*EDIT* I&#39;m now using my brothers mouse, I&#39;ll let you guys know if the same thing happens. *It&#39;s new so if it is I&#39;ll know it&#39;s the pc*.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 28 Sep 2006 16:52:46 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>General Discussion</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/mouse-trouble/16421.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Mouse trouble?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@jcs_double jcs_double]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/jcs_double">@jcs_double</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>its probably a loose connection either in the mouse, the usb/ps2 port or the cable unless its wireless my best bet would be to get a new one</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/mouse-trouble/16421/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/mouse-trouble/16421/2</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 28 Sep 2006 16:52:46 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-16421-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/mouse-trouble/16421.rss">Mouse trouble?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Mouse trouble?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@The_Un-Named The Un-Named]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/the_un-named">@The_Un-Named</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Hello all. I’m having trouble with my mouse.</p>
<p>I have a dell optical mouse, and recently the red light that it uses stops without warning, and I can’t move the mouse. The mouse is pretty old, the things that bother me are as follows:</p>
<p>It often stops without warning, and I can’t get it to work again for I don’t know how long, BUT the mouse buttons(1, 2, 3) are still functional, I just can’t move it. I recently had to format my pc so I’m not sure if it’s my computer or the mouse. It won’t work in any other usb port, so again I’m not sure if it’s the pc or the mouse it’s self.</p>
<p>I’m not sure if it’s a virus because, like I said my left, right and mouse wheel buttons still work, and the red light is turned off and I can’t move it. Right now I’m using my keyboard mouse keys to move it. <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=9" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
<p>Any help/suggestions is apprieated before I buy a new mouse.</p>
<p><em>EDIT</em> I’m now using my brothers mouse, I’ll let you guys know if the same thing happens. <em>It’s new so if it is I’ll know it’s the pc</em>.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/mouse-trouble/16421/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/mouse-trouble/16421/1</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 28 Sep 2006 16:11:44 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-16421-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/mouse-trouble/16421.rss">Mouse trouble?</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
