<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>317 Random Things I Need Assistance With :)</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/317-random-things-i-need-assistance-with/357134</link>
    <description>so im pretty new to java. i wanted to make a little thing in edgeville for me and 1-3 friends. i got a blank client and blank source, so i could just put little things here and there and some npcs as shops.

i reorganized what i was looking for help with so if you would like to help it&#39;s easier 

1. shops - below i was told &quot;shops.cfg&quot;. i see it, but i don&#39;t know what to do with it lol. i do see a shop handler class and java file but i dont know how to edit those so they will be shops. i think i have an idea and i will experiment with it, it could possibly work. --FAILED lol.
2. i have pking, it&#39;s in the wildy like normal, but i would like to make it everywhere except edge bank itself.
3. the spawn, i tried using coordinates but for some reason instead of edgeville im in burthope lol. i did double check and mine were right but its still in burthope.
4. is there a way i can put my own commands in? like ::money or ::teletome (name)? i would like commands but i dont know where they go.
5. since im using a blank client, where can i go to edit the background and the login buttons n stuff? im looking but i dont know where. - DONE FEW PROBLEMS
6. im using a blank server so do i have to add ancients and lunar and range? i want them to work (lol) and be able to go from a distance instead of running up to the person.
7. to add to magic, alters would be cool 
8. how to add items in the correct slots? i have bandos stuff going in the weapon slot with everything else, how do i prevent/fix that?
i do know this list is extensive and could take alot work but im willing to learn and take the time to do it. i tried to use blank sources and clients to do most of it myself ( with help) instead of just modifying somebody elses. i dont know if using a blank surce and client is considered leeching and im sorry if it is, but this is as much work as i can do, without making a whole runescape world myself and with the buildings and all.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 26 Aug 2010 19:38:53 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/317-random-things-i-need-assistance-with/357134.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>317 Random Things I Need Assistance With :)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@me_caveman me caveman]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/me_caveman">@me_caveman</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>so im pretty new to java. i wanted to make a little thing in edgeville for me and 1-3 friends. i got a blank client and blank source, so i could just put little things here and there and some npcs as shops.</p>
<p>i reorganized what i was looking for help with so if you would like to help it’s easier</p>
<ol>
<li>shops - below i was told “shops.cfg”. i see it, but i don’t know what to do with it lol. i do see a shop handler class and java file but i dont know how to edit those so they will be shops. i think i have an idea and i will experiment with it, it could possibly work. --FAILED lol.</li>
<li>i have pking, it’s in the wildy like normal, but i would like to make it everywhere except edge bank itself.</li>
<li>the spawn, i tried using coordinates but for some reason instead of edgeville im in burthope lol. i did double check and mine were right but its still in burthope.</li>
<li>is there a way i can put my own commands in? like ::money or ::teletome (name)? i would like commands but i dont know where they go.</li>
<li>since im using a blank client, where can i go to edit the background and the login buttons n stuff? im looking but i dont know where. - DONE FEW PROBLEMS</li>
<li>im using a blank server so do i have to add ancients and lunar and range? i want them to work (lol) and be able to go from a distance instead of running up to the person.</li>
<li>to add to magic, alters would be cool</li>
<li>how to add items in the correct slots? i have bandos stuff going in the weapon slot with everything else, how do i prevent/fix that?<br>
i do know this list is extensive and could take alot work but im willing to learn and take the time to do it. i tried to use blank sources and clients to do most of it myself ( with help) instead of just modifying somebody elses. i dont know if using a blank surce and client is considered leeching and im sorry if it is, but this is as much work as i can do, without making a whole runescape world myself and with the buildings and all.</li>
</ol>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/317-random-things-i-need-assistance-with/357134/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/317-random-things-i-need-assistance-with/357134/1</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 Aug 2010 19:38:53 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-357134-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/317-random-things-i-need-assistance-with/357134.rss">317 Random Things I Need Assistance With :)</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
