<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Strange Jarring Issue</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/strange-jarring-issue/420516</link>
    <description>Right, every single source and client I&#39;ve tried I&#39;ve had this problem. The problem being that whenever I change the client.java&#39;s IP to my own, then compile, Jarring fails. Don&#39;t tell me I&#39;m jarring wrong because I know I&#39;m not because I&#39;ve done it years ago on my old computer. Whenever I&#39;ve changed the IP and then Jar it, it comes up with the error &quot;Could not find the main class: client. Program will exit. Whereas if I don&#39;t change anything and I Jar it... It works. What is the problem with me changing my IP and compiling?</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 04 Nov 2011 08:39:24 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Game Development</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/strange-jarring-issue/420516.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Strange Jarring Issue</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@ProximityPlus ProximityPlus]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/proximityplus">@ProximityPlus</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Right, every single source and client I’ve tried I’ve had this problem. The problem being that whenever I change the client.java’s IP to my own, then compile, Jarring fails. Don’t tell me I’m jarring wrong because I know I’m not because I’ve done it years ago on my old computer. Whenever I’ve changed the IP and then Jar it, it comes up with the error "Could not find the main class: client. Program will exit. Whereas if I don’t change anything and I Jar it… It works. What is the problem with me changing my IP and compiling?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/strange-jarring-issue/420516/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/strange-jarring-issue/420516/1</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 04 Nov 2011 08:39:24 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-420516-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/strange-jarring-issue/420516.rss">Strange Jarring Issue</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
