<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Here are some classic PvP terms</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/here-are-some-classic-pvp-terms/534671</link>
    <description>Here are some general hints on playing hardcore PvP. Note that some of these hints apply only to playing on a dedicated PvP server but most can be applied to playing PvP on normal servers as well.Win the battle before it starts with the exception of Rogues, Warlock pets, and players laying an ambush you can see most threats coming. 

Knowing when to run is more than half the battle.There&#39;s safety in numbers. When travelling, round up a crew of faction friends despite their levels and stick together.Stay out of the open, stay on the move, and stay alert; especially when you&#39;re fighting NPC mobs.Casters and hunters need line of sight to execute their most powerful attacks. Grab some cover whenever possible, but don&#39;t get yourself backed into a corner.

Do what you do best, but do it big and fast - If you&#39;re specialty is damage, set up your talents to do lots of damage quickly. If you&#39;re a healer, heal big and buff big; worry less about mana consumption than being able to heal a few players fast and give them a better chance to resist mind-control spells. Most battles are less about winning than making your opponent lose. 

For example, snare a hunter&#39;s pet and close on him or her fast to minimize the hunter&#39;s ranged attack advantage. Silence/stifle/pummel a warlock so that they can&#39;t DoT and fear you. Root or snare a warrior to stay clear of their powerful melee attacks wow gold sale . Find a way to survive a rogue&#39;s initial barrage, mark them, and you should be in good shape to turn the tables. Player vs. Player servers are for a special kind of gamer. 

While nothing matches the satifaction you get from beating a tough human opponent, similarly nothing quite matches the depths of * you&#39;ll sink to if you meet up with players who&#39;ve turned griefing into an art form.Here are some classic PvP terms that you should be familiar with. If you feel a twinge of excitement from reading these definitions, you might find a home on a PvP server.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 26 Oct 2013 02:07:20 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>General Discussion</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/here-are-some-classic-pvp-terms/534671.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Here are some classic PvP terms</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@TabbyKiller TabbyKiller]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/tabbykiller">@TabbyKiller</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I suggest reading <a href="http://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php/topic,354311.0.html" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">the rules</a> carefully. Try rule 5 and rule 8</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/here-are-some-classic-pvp-terms/534671/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/here-are-some-classic-pvp-terms/534671/2</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 26 Oct 2013 02:07:20 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-534671-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/here-are-some-classic-pvp-terms/534671.rss">Here are some classic PvP terms</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Here are some classic PvP terms</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@sunchangping sunchangping]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/sunchangping">@sunchangping</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Here are some general hints on playing hardcore PvP. Note that some of these hints apply only to playing on a dedicated PvP server but most can be applied to playing PvP on normal servers as well.Win the battle before it starts with the exception of Rogues, Warlock pets, and players laying an ambush you can see most threats coming.</p>
<p>Knowing when to run is more than half the battle.There’s safety in numbers. When travelling, round up a crew of faction friends despite their levels and stick together.Stay out of the open, stay on the move, and stay alert; especially when you’re fighting NPC mobs.Casters and hunters need line of sight to execute their most powerful attacks. Grab some cover whenever possible, but don’t get yourself backed into a corner.</p>
<p>Do what you do best, but do it big and fast - If you’re specialty is damage, set up your talents to do lots of damage quickly. If you’re a healer, heal big and buff big; worry less about mana consumption than being able to heal a few players fast and give them a better chance to resist mind-control spells. Most battles are less about winning than making your opponent lose.</p>
<p>For example, snare a hunter’s pet and close on him or her fast to minimize the hunter’s ranged attack advantage. Silence/stifle/pummel a warlock so that they can’t DoT and fear you. Root or snare a warrior to stay clear of their powerful melee attacks wow gold sale . Find a way to survive a rogue’s initial barrage, mark them, and you should be in good shape to turn the tables. Player vs. Player servers are for a special kind of gamer.</p>
<p>While nothing matches the satifaction you get from beating a tough human opponent, similarly nothing quite matches the depths of * you’ll sink to if you meet up with players who’ve turned griefing into an art form.Here are some classic PvP terms that you should be familiar with. If you feel a twinge of excitement from reading these definitions, you might find a home on a PvP server.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/here-are-some-classic-pvp-terms/534671/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/here-are-some-classic-pvp-terms/534671/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 26 Oct 2013 02:01:27 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-534671-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/here-are-some-classic-pvp-terms/534671.rss">Here are some classic PvP terms</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
