<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Government</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/government/530619</link>
    <description>I had a dream last week that I logged into Moparscape Classic and there were several hundred players online. Having ran two RSC servers over a period of years, I realize how important it is going to be to devise a functional server team from the beginning as all eyes will be on MoparClassic. As this server will be tied to this forum being the official RSC server of Moparscape, players will flock in droves. Maybe not at first but given time, it can happen. 

Keep Jagex&#39;s invisible style of RSC days government in mind. We rarely saw jmods. I personally never enountered a pmod until RS2. A few screenshots of Mod Paul and Andrew may still survive still but for the most part, players did not interact with Jagex directly. This led to minimal confrontation, high integrity of the economy and production database, as well as a game where players could sort out their fights with other players themselves through conventional means - clan warfare in the wilderness. Without having the admin&#39;s ear, player #1 who accuses player #2 of botting when player #2 is simply far better at timing the rune ore rocks will not be able to convince their close friend who is in the role of admin to ban player #2. Player #2 will then not burn bridges by quitting in a fury and going on to post ranting insults about the server in general, causing new players to not give MoparClassic a chance and instead leave to play an alternative server. Often, it is the player mod who abuses their power and causes the series of events to unfold the same way.

The best government is a formal, nonserver-based government with a small number of player moderators in-game covering all time zones with very limited powers. The ability to mute and the ability to offer assistance to unstuck a player (with the player accepting on their end, similar to a trade window, before the teleport to Lumbridge can occur to prevent abuse for any reason) should be the only two powers assigned to a player moderator. Banning should be a formal process that a council vote on the forum should address. Kicking should not be permitted as it can be used as a form of player abuse. A player that is disruptive was never jailed for 20 minutes in RSC. That only serves to make them quit and it abuse of powers. 

The modroom was never furnished with a desk, a plant, and a jail cell as common RSC servers have. I recall a picture from around 2002 that showed a player teleported there with one of the jmods and it was simply an empty room for the screenshot. Things have changed with RS3 though. Take this photo, displayed on the Runescape website as a meeting place for player moderators to converse with Jagex moderators:
[img]http://services.runescape.com/m=rswikiimages/en/initialUpload/pmod_room.jpg[/img]

Botting should be handled through something resembling Jagex’s botwatch. Here is how we can solve the problem:
Step 1.) Create a website, tie it to the database, take weekly snapshots of all players and graph it. Show a graph for all players who are either over level 50 or have x amount of gp/high value items in their inventory+bank spanning three week snapshots. For any who have an abnormal overlay showing a much higher wealth or skill gain than the others that could only be indicative of botting, place them under surveillance. 

Step 2.) Utilize another form of player moderator account named invisimod that cannot engage in combat, trade any items, and is completely invisible to traditional players. Local chat should not be visible to traditional players either. Only private messaging should. The invisimods must remain as ghosts and not interrupt or interact with the game other than surveying suspected bots.

Step 3.) The invisimod should private message the suspected player and strike up a conversation with them, acting as if they are a regular player for all intents and purposes. If the suspect does not respond or does not make any reasonable human reply, the invisimod should take a screenshot and submit it to the council to vote on a ban. For players who might disable their private messages to appear offline, invisimods should be granted the power to override the player’s private message setting to enable it in order for their messages to reach the suspected player. This could be done through an in-game command or a menu overlay within the invisimod’s game client.

Step 4.) For players condemned to a ban, the punishment should be timed at two weeks with the player’s account name placed upon a list. Their tradelogs should be investigated utilizing a website connected to the database showing dates, times, trade partners, and items traded. Trade partners should be able to be clicked on to see a live view of their stats, bank, and inventory as well as IP addresses used. This information can be used to find all mule bot accounts which may also be given a two week ban at the discretion of the council. Upon the second documented attempt at botting with screenshot evidence by an invisimod, a permanent ban should be set in place for all associated accounts along with an IP ban for all IPs used in both account creation and last login.

By following the four step process outlined above, player moderators should not ever need to kick or ban players at their own discretion at any time. This will enable a timed response with just as much effectiveness but with much more accuracy and integrity than traditional methods.

I write from years of experience in dealing with this very problem tens, if not hundreds of times. It can and will be a server killer if the cancer is allowed to run rampant. We have all seen this time and time again and this can completely end that. The methods listed above, ranging from invisimods to functional website panels have all been created in one form or another over the years and are not difficult to implement. I still have the entire Lupus Regnum website that Elite created, as well as all of the DarkQuest features that can be shaped to cover everything listed above. I believe in a strong core game developed in an open source environment without a drive for monetization. MoparClassic is building on that foundation. Let us make that dream a reality!

These are screenshots of the website that Elite developed:
[IMG]http://i.imgur.com/ZWDQh78.png[/img]
[IMG]http://i.imgur.com/pBphG5U.png[/img]
[IMG]http://i.imgur.com/jy5cRZH.png[/img]
[IMG]http://i.imgur.com/IMsTHq5.png[/img]



This is an article written about the Runescape government and player moderators in RSC that contains a lot of relevant information:
http://djpailo.tripod.com/runescapemoderators.html


Lastly, here are some old pictures of things that we can make possible again:
[img]http://img.photobucket.com/albums/v406/cleako/runescape/noobscam1.jpg[/img][img]http://img.photobucket.com/albums/v406/cleako/runescape/sgrile11.jpg[/img]
[img]http://img.photobucket.com/albums/v406/cleako/runescape/noob8.jpg[/img][img]http://img.photobucket.com/albums/v406/cleako/runescape/fireswastika.jpg[/img]</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 18 Sep 2013 15:45:58 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/government/530619.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Government</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@JUMPHIM JUMPHIM]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/jumphim">@JUMPHIM</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“nacional, post:23, topic:530619”]fair point on the squabble part, but I think there’s still room for explaining rules and resorting scam claims. But muted mods<br>
are fine now I guess, we’ll see how it plays out.</p>
<p>I don’t think stuck was implemented at all since we had all those mining/fishing problems.[/quote]<br>
you the man bro you the man gl</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/government/530619/25">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/government/530619/25</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 18 Sep 2013 15:45:58 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-530619-25</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/government/530619.rss">Government</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Government</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@lil_devil420 lil devil420]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/lil_devil420">@lil_devil420</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“nacional, post:23, topic:530619”]fair point on the squabble part, but I think there’s still room for explaining rules and resorting scam claims. But muted mods<br>
are fine now I guess, we’ll see how it plays out.</p>
<p>I don’t think stuck was implemented at all since we had all those mining/fishing problems.[/quote]</p>
<p>::stuck was implemented near the end with a 5 minute wait .</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/government/530619/24">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/government/530619/24</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 18 Sep 2013 05:19:25 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-530619-24</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/government/530619.rss">Government</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Government</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@nacional nacional]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/nacional">@nacional</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>fair point on the squabble part, but I think there’s still room for explaining rules and resorting scam claims. But muted mods<br>
are fine now I guess, we’ll see how it plays out.</p>
<p>I don’t think stuck was implemented at all since we had all those mining/fishing problems.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/government/530619/23">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/government/530619/23</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 18 Sep 2013 04:35:55 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-530619-23</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/government/530619.rss">Government</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Government</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@CodeForFame CodeForFame]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/codeforfame">@CodeForFame</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“nacional, post:16, topic:530619”]invisible or not a mod shouldn’t do that. ‘invisimods’ would have the power to teleport and invisible right? So wouldn’t this account type<br>
reserve the right to chat to settle a squabble between two or more players or speak to a player who is stuck?[/quote]A moderator shouldn’t be getting involved in squabbles at all… Mute is for people being racist, spamming, etc. It’s not for muting people who are raging at one another.</p>
<p>Furthermore, don’t normal players have ::stuck? So, why is that an issue at all?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/government/530619/22">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/government/530619/22</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 18 Sep 2013 02:27:06 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-530619-22</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/government/530619.rss">Government</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Government</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@nacional nacional]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/nacional">@nacional</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Hmm so a typical mod would have one regular account for playing, one for surveillance and one for actual moderating.<br>
Seems a bit redundant but I’m sure we’ll figure out the kinks once the server is on a roll again.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/government/530619/21">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/government/530619/21</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2013 23:09:35 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-530619-21</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/government/530619.rss">Government</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Government</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@cleako cleako]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/cleako">@cleako</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“nacional, post:16, topic:530619”]invisible or not a mod shouldn’t do that. ‘invisimods’ would have the power to teleport and invisible right? So wouldn’t this account type<br>
reserve the right to chat to settle a squabble between two or more players or speak to a player who is stuck?[/quote]</p>
<p>There would be two different types of moderator accounts - one for traditional player moderating, and one for bot surveillance to verify and gather evidence with.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/government/530619/20">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/government/530619/20</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2013 23:05:22 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-530619-20</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/government/530619.rss">Government</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Government</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@nacional nacional]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/nacional">@nacional</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“CodeForFame, post:17, topic:530619”][quote author=nacional link=topic=649380.msg4364879#msg4364879 date=1379455404]<br>
I agree with it also but why not chat?<br>
[/quote]They could be following someone around and harassing them via chat.[/quote]</p>
<p>look at my post above yours.</p>
<aside class="quote quote-modified" data-post="18" data-topic="530619">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/user_avatar/forum.moparisthebest.com/lothy/40/51_1.png" class="avatar"> Lothy:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>The thing with the fatigue system is that you can anticipate when you’ll need to sleep. So someone knows that they might be able to mine for an hour before using the sleeping bag, so they go AWOL for an hour and come back in time to manually enter the captcha.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I like this idea.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/government/530619/19">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/government/530619/19</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2013 22:59:22 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-530619-19</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/government/530619.rss">Government</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Government</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@lothy Lothy]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/lothy">@lothy</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>The thing with the fatigue system is that you can anticipate when you’ll need to sleep. So someone knows that they might be able to mine for an hour before using the sleeping bag, so they go AWOL for an hour and come back in time to manually enter the captcha.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/government/530619/18">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/government/530619/18</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2013 22:54:05 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-530619-18</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/government/530619.rss">Government</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Government</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@CodeForFame CodeForFame]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/codeforfame">@CodeForFame</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“nacional, post:14, topic:530619”]I agree with it also but why not chat?[/quote]They could be following someone around and harassing them via chat.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/government/530619/17">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/government/530619/17</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2013 22:43:54 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-530619-17</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/government/530619.rss">Government</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Government</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@nacional nacional]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/nacional">@nacional</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>invisible or not a mod shouldn’t do that. ‘invisimods’ would have the power to teleport and invisible right? So wouldn’t this account type<br>
reserve the right to chat to settle a squabble between two or more players or speak to a player who is stuck?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/government/530619/16">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/government/530619/16</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2013 22:43:44 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-530619-16</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/government/530619.rss">Government</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Government</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@cleako cleako]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/cleako">@cleako</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Invisible player moderators hounding players who cannot see them except on the minimap as a form of harassment. Main point is that invisimods could only be there for one reason and no other.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/government/530619/15">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/government/530619/15</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2013 22:34:39 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-530619-15</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/government/530619.rss">Government</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Government</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@nacional nacional]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/nacional">@nacional</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I agree with it also but why not chat?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/government/530619/14">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/government/530619/14</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2013 22:03:24 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-530619-14</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/government/530619.rss">Government</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Government</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Loveandpower Loveandpower]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/loveandpower">@Loveandpower</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“cleako, post:12, topic:530619”][quote author=CodeForFame link=topic=649380.msg4364705#msg4364705 date=1379427011]<br>
I don’t like the idea of forcing captchas. People already need to sleep, and if it isn’t secure enough, we can always change it.</p>
<p>As for invisible and teleporting, accounts shouldn’t be able to interact with anything at all; they should be purely for observation. This includes anything that gives exp, interacting with objects/npcs, and even chat. Any account that can go invisible should be under these restrictions at all times, which means mods would need a special account to do this with.<br>
[/quote]</p>
<p>Absolutely agree with this.[/quote]I absolutely agree as well with this</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/government/530619/13">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/government/530619/13</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2013 17:48:46 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-530619-13</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/government/530619.rss">Government</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Government</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@cleako cleako]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/cleako">@cleako</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“CodeForFame, post:11, topic:530619”]I don’t like the idea of forcing captchas. People already need to sleep, and if it isn’t secure enough, we can always change it.</p>
<p>As for invisible and teleporting, accounts shouldn’t be able to interact with anything at all; they should be purely for observation. This includes anything that gives exp, interacting with objects/npcs, and even chat. Any account that can go invisible should be under these restrictions at all times, which means mods would need a special account to do this with.[/quote]</p>
<p>Absolutely agree with this.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/government/530619/12">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/government/530619/12</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2013 14:27:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-530619-12</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/government/530619.rss">Government</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Government</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@CodeForFame CodeForFame]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/codeforfame">@CodeForFame</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I don’t like the idea of forcing captchas. People already need to sleep, and if it isn’t secure enough, we can always change it.</p>
<p>As for invisible and teleporting, accounts shouldn’t be able to interact with anything at all; they should be purely for observation. This includes anything that gives exp, interacting with objects/npcs, and even chat. Any account that can go invisible should be under these restrictions at all times, which means mods would need a special account to do this with.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/government/530619/11">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/government/530619/11</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2013 14:10:11 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-530619-11</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/government/530619.rss">Government</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Government</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@latifundio latifundio]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/latifundio">@latifundio</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote quote-modified" data-post="5" data-topic="530619">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/user_avatar/forum.moparisthebest.com/lothy/40/51_1.png" class="avatar"> Lothy:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>For bot detection, one idea I’ve recently had (and liked) was an ability for moderators to occasionally force a captcha screen to appear. They would be notified that it had appeared, and if the captcha was ever completed they would be notified of how long the completion process took (a strong indicator that there’s nobody at the computer if the player has just gone from powermining iron to not solving the captcha for five minutes).</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>That looks good.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/government/530619/10">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/government/530619/10</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2013 13:45:28 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-530619-10</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/government/530619.rss">Government</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Government</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@lothy Lothy]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/lothy">@lothy</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Shit, I just edited my post thinking nobody would reply. Hurrr durrr.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/government/530619/9">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/government/530619/9</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2013 23:38:46 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-530619-9</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/government/530619.rss">Government</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Government</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Rodgerwilco Rodgerwilco]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/rodgerwilco">@Rodgerwilco</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote quote-modified" data-post="7" data-topic="530619">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 Miss Silabsoft:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>i don’t feel like getting in the IRC is this shit up yet?</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Moparisthebest needs to show signs of life or I’ll turn on my serber again…</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/government/530619/8">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/government/530619/8</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2013 23:34:22 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-530619-8</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/government/530619.rss">Government</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Government</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@silabsoft RuneAgent]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/silabsoft">@silabsoft</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>i don’t feel like getting in the IRC is this shit up yet?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/government/530619/7">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/government/530619/7</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2013 23:31:38 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-530619-7</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/government/530619.rss">Government</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Government</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Rodgerwilco Rodgerwilco]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/rodgerwilco">@Rodgerwilco</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“Lothy, post:5, topic:530619”]My in-game account is a staffer account? This is news to me. <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=5" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"><br>
Was it like that before when the server was first online?[/quote]</p>
<p>The way I had it set up was…</p>
<p>Every person on the stickied thread are ranked player moderators with the ability to mute.<br>
From that point if their showing activity and their player moderator position shows positive results they will be given access to the moderator centre where they can view a full in depth analysis of player accounts and then we can flag accounts and come to an agreement on which were bots.</p>
<p>So when moparisthebest is done updating the client and has free time. The four of us will have access to ban/mute while others will have access to moderate indirectly…</p>
<p>IRC</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/government/530619/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/government/530619/6</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2013 23:28:35 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-530619-6</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/government/530619.rss">Government</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Government</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@lothy Lothy]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/lothy">@lothy</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>My in-game account is a staffer account? This is news to me. <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=5" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"><br>
Was it like that before when the server was first online?</p>
<p>By the way, I’ve always believed their should be restrictions on moderator accounts. Namely the same restrictions that Jagex employees are subject to - no trade, no dueling, dropped items are immediately removed from the game, etc.<br>
For bot detection, one idea I’ve recently had (and liked) was an ability for moderators to occasionally force a captcha screen to appear. They would be notified that it had appeared, and if the captcha was ever completed they would be notified of how long the completion process took (a strong indicator that there’s nobody at the computer if the player has just gone from powermining iron to not solving the captcha for five minutes).</p>
<p>I would be happy with the following ‘powers’:</p>
<ol>
<li>Muting.</li>
<li>Forcing a captcha (with some arbitrary limit).</li>
<li>Invisibility.</li>
<li>Teleporting to a target player.</li>
<li>Teleporting to an arbitrary location (either co-ordinates, or a named location such as ‘varrock’).</li>
</ol>
<p>And the following limitations:</p>
<ol>
<li>No trading.</li>
<li>No teleporting other players.</li>
<li>No dueling.</li>
<li>No dropping items on the ground.</li>
</ol>
<p>Forcing a captcha could obviously be used to harass, so there needs to be limits. Specifically, a target player should only be able to (initially) only receive one every 30 to 60 minutes. The cooldown needs to be on the receiving side, otherwise two or three moderators could captcha-gank someone and bug the fuck out of them.</p>
<p>I like the sound of an account management system. At the end of the day tooling really matters. It’s the game changer when it comes to usability.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/government/530619/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/government/530619/5</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2013 23:19:42 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-530619-5</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/government/530619.rss">Government</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Government</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@CodeForFame CodeForFame]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/codeforfame">@CodeForFame</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p><a class="mention" href="/u/cleako">@cleako</a> Your invis idea is not very good, and requires people to be trustworthy. Also, making money and xp gain doesn’t mean anything. Play times and patterns are much more indicative of someone who is botting.</p>
<p>I’d like to mention that every single packet is logged, and therefore it can theoretically be replayed and viewed manually, but you can also run several types of analysis on the packet data itself.</p>
<p>[quote=“Kaibutzu, post:3, topic:530619”]sounds awesome but have to be watch out sounds like mods could abuse this</p>
<p>the big problem a lot of servers have is mods abuse invis tele all type of ways, and thats why when they started to do moparclassic years ago they had a vote and everyone voted that mods would have no powers, but muting[/quote]The only commands that are even possible to abuse with are tele to specified coordinates, and goto. Nobody can teleport another player, or do anything like that.</p>
<p>Furthermore, nobody should have access to goto or tele commands, so it’s not an issue.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/government/530619/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/government/530619/4</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2013 06:39:34 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-530619-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/government/530619.rss">Government</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Government</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Kaibutzu Kaibutzu]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/kaibutzu">@Kaibutzu</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>sounds awesome but have to be watch out sounds like mods could abuse this</p>
<p>the big problem a lot of servers have is mods abuse invis tele all type of ways, and thats why when they started to do moparclassic years ago they had a vote and everyone voted that mods would have no powers, but muting</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/government/530619/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/government/530619/3</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2013 05:39:57 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-530619-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/government/530619.rss">Government</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Government</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Rodgerwilco Rodgerwilco]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/rodgerwilco">@Rodgerwilco</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Since we are moving to mysql, a website like <a href="http://classic.moparisthebest.com" rel="nofollow noopener">classic.moparisthebest.com</a> is quite possible and will need to be arranged by Tom and Moparisthebest to allow ftp access and his/your php or whatever language you’re using work will need to be reviewed for exploits. Since we are using smf we will need to have tabs at the top like the moderator centre and highscores similar to how 3hit dot net was ran.</p>
<p>In game I believe the only staffer account known right now is my pker, Lothy and possibly nacional. The rest of the moderators are not public so technically we kinda do have ‘agents’ but it doesn’t really matter. In fact the moderator room isn’t even needed and won’t ever be used. The in game commands are limited and moderation will be done via the logged data we pull via a moderator centre. The bot detection end of things is not public and won’t be found on the github.</p>
<p>You’re pretty much on the same page we agreed on awhile back but it doesn’t hurt to discuss this issue. CodeForFame will most likely go into more detail on the subject on the analysis of bots since he basically is the top developer of these parts.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/government/530619/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/government/530619/2</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2013 03:48:52 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-530619-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/government/530619.rss">Government</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Government</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@cleako cleako]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/cleako">@cleako</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I had a dream last week that I logged into Moparscape Classic and there were several hundred players online. Having ran two RSC servers over a period of years, I realize how important it is going to be to devise a functional server team from the beginning as all eyes will be on MoparClassic. As this server will be tied to this forum being the official RSC server of Moparscape, players will flock in droves. Maybe not at first but given time, it can happen.</p>
<p>Keep Jagex’s invisible style of RSC days government in mind. We rarely saw jmods. I personally never enountered a pmod until RS2. A few screenshots of Mod Paul and Andrew may still survive still but for the most part, players did not interact with Jagex directly. This led to minimal confrontation, high integrity of the economy and production database, as well as a game where players could sort out their fights with other players themselves through conventional means - clan warfare in the wilderness. Without having the admin’s ear, player <span class="hashtag">#1</span> who accuses player <span class="hashtag">#2</span> of botting when player <span class="hashtag">#2</span> is simply far better at timing the rune ore rocks will not be able to convince their close friend who is in the role of admin to ban player <span class="hashtag">#2</span>. Player <span class="hashtag">#2</span> will then not burn bridges by quitting in a fury and going on to post ranting insults about the server in general, causing new players to not give MoparClassic a chance and instead leave to play an alternative server. Often, it is the player mod who abuses their power and causes the series of events to unfold the same way.</p>
<p>The best government is a formal, nonserver-based government with a small number of player moderators in-game covering all time zones with very limited powers. The ability to mute and the ability to offer assistance to unstuck a player (with the player accepting on their end, similar to a trade window, before the teleport to Lumbridge can occur to prevent abuse for any reason) should be the only two powers assigned to a player moderator. Banning should be a formal process that a council vote on the forum should address. Kicking should not be permitted as it can be used as a form of player abuse. A player that is disruptive was never jailed for 20 minutes in RSC. That only serves to make them quit and it abuse of powers.</p>
<p>The modroom was never furnished with a desk, a plant, and a jail cell as common RSC servers have. I recall a picture from around 2002 that showed a player teleported there with one of the jmods and it was simply an empty room for the screenshot. Things have changed with RS3 though. Take this photo, displayed on the Runescape website as a meeting place for player moderators to converse with Jagex moderators:<br>
<img src="http://services.runescape.com/m=rswikiimages/en/initialUpload/pmod_room.jpg" alt width="" height=""></p>
<p>Botting should be handled through something resembling Jagex’s botwatch. Here is how we can solve the problem:<br>
Step 1.) Create a website, tie it to the database, take weekly snapshots of all players and graph it. Show a graph for all players who are either over level 50 or have x amount of gp/high value items in their inventory+bank spanning three week snapshots. For any who have an abnormal overlay showing a much higher wealth or skill gain than the others that could only be indicative of botting, place them under surveillance.</p>
<p>Step 2.) Utilize another form of player moderator account named invisimod that cannot engage in combat, trade any items, and is completely invisible to traditional players. Local chat should not be visible to traditional players either. Only private messaging should. The invisimods must remain as ghosts and not interrupt or interact with the game other than surveying suspected bots.</p>
<p>Step 3.) The invisimod should private message the suspected player and strike up a conversation with them, acting as if they are a regular player for all intents and purposes. If the suspect does not respond or does not make any reasonable human reply, the invisimod should take a screenshot and submit it to the council to vote on a ban. For players who might disable their private messages to appear offline, invisimods should be granted the power to override the player’s private message setting to enable it in order for their messages to reach the suspected player. This could be done through an in-game command or a menu overlay within the invisimod’s game client.</p>
<p>Step 4.) For players condemned to a ban, the punishment should be timed at two weeks with the player’s account name placed upon a list. Their tradelogs should be investigated utilizing a website connected to the database showing dates, times, trade partners, and items traded. Trade partners should be able to be clicked on to see a live view of their stats, bank, and inventory as well as IP addresses used. This information can be used to find all mule bot accounts which may also be given a two week ban at the discretion of the council. Upon the second documented attempt at botting with screenshot evidence by an invisimod, a permanent ban should be set in place for all associated accounts along with an IP ban for all IPs used in both account creation and last login.</p>
<p>By following the four step process outlined above, player moderators should not ever need to kick or ban players at their own discretion at any time. This will enable a timed response with just as much effectiveness but with much more accuracy and integrity than traditional methods.</p>
<p>I write from years of experience in dealing with this very problem tens, if not hundreds of times. It can and will be a server killer if the cancer is allowed to run rampant. We have all seen this time and time again and this can completely end that. The methods listed above, ranging from invisimods to functional website panels have all been created in one form or another over the years and are not difficult to implement. I still have the entire Lupus Regnum website that Elite created, as well as all of the DarkQuest features that can be shaped to cover everything listed above. I believe in a strong core game developed in an open source environment without a drive for monetization. MoparClassic is building on that foundation. Let us make that dream a reality!</p>
<p>These are screenshots of the website that Elite developed:<br>
<div class="lightbox-wrapper"><a class="lightbox" href="http://i.imgur.com/ZWDQh78.png" title="ZWDQh78.png" rel="nofollow noopener"><img src="http://i.imgur.com/ZWDQh78.png" alt width="689" height="500"><div class="meta">
<svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-far-image svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#far-image"></use></svg><span class="filename">ZWDQh78.png</span><span class="informations">982×712</span><svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-discourse-expand svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#discourse-expand"></use></svg>
</div></a></div><br>
<div class="lightbox-wrapper"><a class="lightbox" href="http://i.imgur.com/pBphG5U.png" title="pBphG5U.png" rel="nofollow noopener"><img src="http://i.imgur.com/pBphG5U.png" alt width="690" height="486"><div class="meta">
<svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-far-image svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#far-image"></use></svg><span class="filename">pBphG5U.png</span><span class="informations">944×665</span><svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-discourse-expand svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#discourse-expand"></use></svg>
</div></a></div><br>
<div class="lightbox-wrapper"><a class="lightbox" href="http://i.imgur.com/jy5cRZH.png" title="jy5cRZH.png" rel="nofollow noopener"><img src="http://i.imgur.com/jy5cRZH.png" alt width="644" height="500"><div class="meta">
<svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-far-image svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#far-image"></use></svg><span class="filename">jy5cRZH.png</span><span class="informations">1001×776</span><svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-discourse-expand svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#discourse-expand"></use></svg>
</div></a></div><br>
<div class="lightbox-wrapper"><a class="lightbox" href="http://i.imgur.com/IMsTHq5.png" title="IMsTHq5.png" rel="nofollow noopener"><img src="http://i.imgur.com/IMsTHq5.png" alt width="690" height="486"><div class="meta">
<svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-far-image svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#far-image"></use></svg><span class="filename">IMsTHq5.png</span><span class="informations">991×699</span><svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-discourse-expand svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#discourse-expand"></use></svg>
</div></a></div></p>
<p>This is an article written about the Runescape government and player moderators in RSC that contains a lot of relevant information:<br>
<a href="http://djpailo.tripod.com/runescapemoderators.html" class="onebox" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">http://djpailo.tripod.com/runescapemoderators.html</a></p>
<p>Lastly, here are some old pictures of things that we can make possible again:<br>
<img src="http://img.photobucket.com/albums/v406/cleako/runescape/noobscam1.jpg" alt width="515" height="349"><img src="http://img.photobucket.com/albums/v406/cleako/runescape/sgrile11.jpg" alt width="493" height="327"><br>
<img src="http://img.photobucket.com/albums/v406/cleako/runescape/noob8.jpg" alt width="487" height="335"><img src="http://img.photobucket.com/albums/v406/cleako/runescape/fireswastika.jpg" alt width="513" height="351"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/government/530619/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/government/530619/1</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2013 03:47:20 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-530619-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/government/530619.rss">Government</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
