<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>|circagaming|-runeunlimited-|circagaming|</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/circagaming-runeunlimited-circagaming/295499</link>
    <description>/\/\&lt;&gt;THIS IS A CIRCAGAMING™ PRODUCT&lt;&gt;/\/\
*Circa gaming, was made/discovered by: y0u are y0u(brawler/mike), and created by him..
--RuneUnlimited--
Coder/Creator: Brawler (me)
Client Maker: Brawler (me)
Model[rs]: Brawler (me), J0j0z, SilentCJ &lt;----he didn&#39;t help me, just used some of his custom items. AFC, has no friends.
--------------------FOR PEOPLE THAT ASKED--------------------
i MADE my own base, i didn&#39;t download anything. i also custom-made my own client..don&#39;t like it? piss off.
YES, i did take some things out of dragon-history..didn&#39;t use it as the base
-------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------
--FEATURES--
*Full dragon platebody making, with all of the parts.
*to get the ability to wield &quot;dragon claws&quot;, you need to complete a quest
*full spirit shields, along with spirit shield making.
([TIMELINE])GodWars--&gt;Holy Elixr/Spirit shield--&gt;[HolyElixr+Spirit shield]--&gt;blessed spirit shield--&gt;Arcane(or any other sigils)sigil--&gt;ARCANE SPIRIT SHIELD!
*Construction - - - CREDITS 100% to Aintaro.
*Revenant minigame - - - CREDITS 100% Aintaro (IDEA)
*Dueling - - - thanks to * of *, for the guide.
*1 working quest - - - CREDITS 100% Aintaro
*Summoning - - - all me their.
*godwars, you can either get the 20 sara kills, or get 90 construction and build a warped door, and choose which boss you want to go to.
*Members/Donators are the same thing, you do NOT get a crown (AS OF NOW) but i am currently working on it..
*a random event, you need to bury a certian bone, and you will get this message that says &#39;please pick an item&#39;. as of now, only the rubber chicken button works..
++and more, but i am way to lazy to list them all++

--Things i&#39;m working on--
*Wilderness ditch, i added my map so it&#39;s on the map on the upper right handed corner. just need to make them up and add them in :]. their problay not going 
to have a gfx, their just going to work as a portal. you click it, and it teles you to the other side. walk one block, and you&#39;re in level 1.

*skill cape emotes - all 100% done.

*cleaned up home, mved thieving stalls, moved shops and more..it&#39;s not like dodian, you start off with a certian look. just talk to the make over mage to change
youi&#39;re look.

*all skills working. cept firemaking. just need to get around to finishing it..

*--HUNTER*--
*hunter, is something i wanted to add ever since i got 99 hunter on runescape..it&#39;s my own custom version of hunter, so let me explain it to ya. you need to have
a MEMBERS spot to enter the portal, and you need a donators ticket to start the skill. i don&#39;t have any of the hunter models or NPC&#39;s yet, any one who wants to
help plz post :). anyways, you kill monsters with the net you get. the monster i have so far is a imp[s]. you kill it, and depending on the monster, you either get
1-5 ecto-tokens. you can use the tokens to exchange for hunter items, supplies, etc.. the most expensive item you can save up for is the hunter cape. which you can
show off around :D!. this is my own, and i have yet to seen this idea..if i see it just give me creds. for the idea :).

*--RUNE CRAFTING GUILD*--
yer, castlewars just wasn&#39;t working for me. so i decided to turn it into the runecrafting guild. so i got to work with adding the models, and noticed that instead
of sitting their and adding in all of the robes, and staffs, i just turned my dragon&#39;hai robes in runecrafting robes. and i turned an extra one of my zuriels staffs,into
the &#39;elemental staff&#39; which is a runecrafting item :). i added all of the teletabs, and you click them and it will teleport you to the altar. it will delete one, but it&#39;s eaiser
to runecraft.

*--MAGIC--*
so i have yet to have seen, a delta server, or any server, with superheating, enchanting, or any of those spells. so, i brought up my own method of superheating.
what is says if, you use a fire rune on any ore, it will send the 2 gfx&#39;s of alching, and the dragon battleaxe spec thing. it&#39;s pretty cool, and i spent a shitload of time
editing this and making it look good..you don&#39;t like it? fuck you.

enchanting, i haven&#39;t starter it yet, but i have all the gfx&#39;s and all of the methods writen out. so not enofugh information yet.

--*SKILLS*--
Attack - 100%      }-------------&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;
Strength - 100%   }===========&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt; All         COMPLETE. no errors..
Defence - 100%   }===========&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;    100%
Hitpoints - 100%   }-------------&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;
Range - 100% - - i edited so that you can see you&#39;re arrow going through the air, and you can pick it up once u killed the player/monster.
Summoning - 100% - - it&#39;s all just basic commands, nothing special.
Construction - 100% - - again, creds. go to Aintaro
Hunter - 40% - - just need to edit the ticket exchange, and the models.
Fletching - 100% - - working stringing bows, and fletching bows, with the correct GFX&#39;s.
Prayer - 100% - - working using a bone on an altar, and bone burying.
Fishing - 100% - - all fishing items working, with feathers and BAIT.
Crafting - 100% - - all gems, and stringing gems working.
Herblore - 50% - - still need to fix it up..way to many errors to explain..
Slayer - 40% - - need to add all of the NPC&#39;s that he will assign.(vannaka) 
Agility - 30% - - again, to many errors to explain.
Thieving - 100% - - working pickpocketing, and stealing from stalls.
Farming - 100% - - working raking, and watering plants :).
Woodcutting - 80% - - for some reason, my dumb ass guy stops cutting..you have to keep clicking.
Mining - 100% - - and made a mining guild.
Smithing - 100% - - 100% now, with superheating!
Firemaking - 1% - - haven&#39;t even starter yet..

--*CITIES*--
-all varrok spawns.
-all falador spawns = with air running, can only tele into the altar if you have an air tiara, no talisman yet..also added mining guild. need 60+ mining to enter.
-all camelot spawns
-all al kally spawns
-all lumby spawns
*MY GOAL IS TO GET AL CITY SPAWNS..*

--*DELTA TELES*--
(NOTE: as of now, i&#39;m starting to make more NPC teleports, as of portal teleports)
--MINIGAMES--
=Clan wars
=Funpk
=Revenants
=KBD
=Barrows
=Fight pits - - 80%
=Pest Control - - working on original
=Bounty Hunter - - working on targets.
=Barbian Assauly - - wanna replace something with it, it&#39;s problay going to be WWE monday night raw thing :) for teh kidz.

--Monster Teleports--
=Balance train
=Dagg lair - - with Tormented Deamon
=Island
=Cave
=Slayer tower

--Begin Training--
=Ghost Training
=Island
=GodWars Chambre
=Herblore

--Pking places--
=Edgeville
=Varrok
=Magebank

UPDATE: 8/7/09
well i was working on my horde, and as of now i&#39;m going to make my own map for the location..UNLESS i can find somewere where it would
be a good location..

UPDATE: 8/7/09
yeah, the map making didn&#39;t go so well lmfao..though it was easy, turns out it&#39;s not..so what i did, was find a city that wasn&#39;t very useful..
not guna give away the name, but than i found another city, in the wilderness. i think you all know what i&#39;m talking about..so what it is, it&#39;s
set up like the FightCaves, it sends waves. before the last wave, it says that &quot;run! hide! the Zombie Champion is coming next wave!&quot; it&#39;s pretty
much just a bunch a waves of zombies, that i custom made..eventually it will get harder like dragons will come, etc..not only that, but on the
last wave, player will be able to kill other players. think it&#39;s gay? please post.


UPDATE: 8/8/09
finished all my portals, thus making this server non delta..the portals are set up like pwnscape, you choose where you want to teleport to.
click on it, and it shows a frame with all of the diffrent teleports. 

UPDATE: 8/9/09
i decided, i&#39;m pretty sick of the fightcave thing.. i have a question, or more of a poll to ask of you. i was playing gears of war, and i was
going to replace all of the jad waves, and the jad NPC&#39;s, and such, with zombies, zombie champions, and what not. i just think it will be
something diffrent..the sooner i get you&#39;re response, the sooner i can get this done..just wondering if you would like it :) kthxbi.

UPDATE: 8/10/09
finally finished my zombie minigame; sweat in tears put into that..

--NO MORE DELTA--
spawned a few portals, and made them so that they show and interface that comes up with a list of all of the diffrent teleports..as of now,
i&#39;m not going to finish them. when i release the soruce, they will problay not be finished. sup to you to fix dem ;)

*--NEED A PLACE FOR JAD--*
if i&#39;m going to add the horde..do you think people will still want jad :((?


-**UPDATE ON MY RANDOM EVENT**-
this was yet another thing i kept working on. i made it so that if you bury a bone in a CERTIAN place (it&#39;s a big place, it almost half of edgeville,
but you only get the event every 15 minutes..it was difficult, the item you get is bunny ears, or a basket of eggs.

--**UPDATE ON RANDOM EVENT (8/10/09)**--
k, so i decided to make this for every1..you can only do it once, you use a bone on my custom altar..than you get teleported somewhere
were you kill a monster, get the rubber chicken etc..than get teleported out..ya i know it&#39;s insainly gay..but my other one just kept
getting errors :(( sowwie.

**UPDATE ON SKILLS**
here is a 100% update on skills..
-----------------------------------------------------
*COMBAT*
Attack-
100%, with correct interfaces
(instert img.name(attack) in skills folder)

Strength-
100%, with correct animations/interfaces
(insert img.name(strength) in skills folder)

Range-
100%, the arrow WILL be in air, than dropped on ground, once done killing the NPC/player.
(insert img.name(range) in skills folder)

Prayer-
80%, you can not only bury the bones, but use them on a &#39;altar&#39;..it&#39;s 80% done, because not all of the bones work. and i wanna add some
of the prayer amour, and robes.
(insert img.name(prayer) in skills folder)
(insert img.name(prayer1) in skills folder)

Mage-
75%, full alching, low leve alching, and such..i&#39;m currently working on superheating (almost done) along with enchanting amulets.
that is something that will problay be the last thing i do.. all depends on if i get around to it..super boring..
(insert img.name(mage) in skills folder)

RuneCrafting-
100%, yeah the first skill i ever finished..the first thing that i added was the Zamorak mage, which will teleport you to the abyss where you
can runecraft. i also, made it so that aubury will teleport you to the rune essence mine (both pure/regular).
(insert img.name(runecrafting1) in skills folder)
(insert img.name(runecrafting2) in skills folder)
(insert img.name(runecrafting3) in skills folder)
(insert img.name(runecrafting4) in skills folder)

Agility-
95%, ok so once i make it so that you get tickets when you complete the coruse, than make the ticket exchange, it will be 1005 =)
(insert img.name(agility) in skills folder)

Herblore-
40%, i STILL need to make so much more things..didn&#39;t really focus on this skill that much because i thought i was going to replace it..
turns out, i like it :)
(insert img.name(herblore) in skills folder)

Thieving-
100%, you can not only steal from stalls, but you can also pickpocket NPC&#39;s.
(insert img.name(thieving) in skills folder)

Crafting-
80%, need to make it so that you get the &quot;cut&quot; stone, instead of the amulet.
(insert img.name(crafting) in skills folder)

Fletching-
50%, as of now, their are no GFX&#39;s and the only thing you can really do is string the bow.
(insert img.name(fletching) in skills folder)

Slayer-
0%, no pictures (lmfao)

Mining-
60%, um for somereason, whenever i swing my pick, it only swings once..need to fix that :P so i guess whenever i get around to it
i can finish that, but until than kthbi.
(insert img.name(mining) in skills folder)

Smithing-
80%, the only thing i need to fix is that when you use the bar on the anvil, it brings up the interface and you click on the thing and it gives
you the item..almost their :s.
(insert img.name(smithing) in skills folder)

Fishing-
100%, i really don&#39;t want to work on i usually don&#39;t spend that much on skills but this is pretty much good just how it is. you auto fish, it
only sends 1 gfx wich is at the beginning.
(insert img.name(fishing) in skills folder)
(insert img.name(fishing1) in skills folder

Cooking-
100%, &#39;perfect&#39; working with the range, AND it auto cooks! you don&#39;t need to keep clicking it will cook for you. on top of that, it will keep
sending the gfx and it will never stop. also, you can cook on fires!
(insert img.name(cooking) in skills folder)

Firemaking-
0%, no pictures what the point?

Woodcutting-
90%, it&#39;s just like fishing which i don&#39;t like i want the character to keep swining.it auto woodcuts, so you don&#39;t have to keep clicking.
(insert img.name(woodcutting) in skills folder)


Farming-
100%, i acutally just finished this skill, it&#39;s 100%, loads all of the gfx&#39;s and handels all of the packets. use the seed on the patch, you char.
will get a rake and send a gfx, than a herb will spawn in you&#39;re inventory.
(insert img.name(farming) in skills folder)


Summoning-
100%, ALL CREDITS GO TO AINTARO FOR THE IDEA &lt;33
(insert img.name(summoning) in skills folder)

*UPDATE*
Anti-leech in my client. goodluck fixing it?
(insert img.name(antileechinmyclient) in skills folder)
*UPDATE*
another anti-leech, this is my own client and i want to keep it that way, so i deleted some of the java files so you can&#39;t edit them..

--/future work\--
*as of now, im making my own client..what do i have so far?
(insert img.name(546bars) in skills folder)
(insert img.name(546bars2) in skills folder)
(insert img.name(newoption) in skills folder)

**-/\i will be releasing any time i get around to it..just need to finish/\-**
thanks,
Y0u Are Y0u† [no, i didn&#39;t take the name from that guy on runescape..didn&#39;t even know it was a name, it&#39;s my fav. thing to say]
(sponsored by: CircaGaming™ (owned by me/rhw co-ex. Circa))
NEWS:
CircaGaming™&#39;s RuneUnlimited 508 has BEEN RELEASED. please click the link below, to take you to the desired location..

UPDATE: 8/15/09
Finished my Zombie Horde, it&#39;s just the fight caves but instead of monster spawning that would usually spawn, it&#39;s just zombies. at the end,
you fight Zombie King (K&#39;ril Tsuraoth) and if u beat him, u get firecape. you can have only 5 players in the match, but each player needs to
kill the required amount of monsters per wave..still some glitches, but i&#39;ll fix it eventually.

*|UPDATE|*
well as of now, i wanna make it so that when you click on one of the skill buttons, under the skill tab, it will teleport you to the skill master were
you can get the skill cape of that skill. (to make it set up like a 508/bulby type thing :] )

EDITINg IN THE PICTURE THINGS LATER GOING TO BED ATM...</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 17 Aug 2009 02:10:51 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/circagaming-runeunlimited-circagaming/295499.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>|circagaming|-runeunlimited-|circagaming|</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Deathspirit Deathspirit]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/deathspirit">@Deathspirit</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“marcbob, post:2, topic:295499”]lol no pics and half stuff is crossed out[/quote]Ofcourse it is he’s planning to make that also good luck with it Y0u Are Y0u.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/circagaming-runeunlimited-circagaming/295499/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/circagaming-runeunlimited-circagaming/295499/3</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 17 Aug 2009 02:10:51 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-295499-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/circagaming-runeunlimited-circagaming/295499.rss">|circagaming|-runeunlimited-|circagaming|</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>|circagaming|-runeunlimited-|circagaming|</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@marcbob marcbob]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/marcbob">@marcbob</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>lol no pics and half stuff is crossed out</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/circagaming-runeunlimited-circagaming/295499/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/circagaming-runeunlimited-circagaming/295499/2</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 16 Aug 2009 02:01:26 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-295499-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/circagaming-runeunlimited-circagaming/295499.rss">|circagaming|-runeunlimited-|circagaming|</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>|circagaming|-runeunlimited-|circagaming|</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Y0u_Are_Y0u Y0u Are Y0u]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/y0u_are_y0u">@Y0u_Are_Y0u</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <h2>//&lt;&gt;THIS IS A CIRCAGAMING™ PRODUCT&lt;&gt;//<br>
*Circa gaming, was made/discovered by: y0u are y0u(brawler/mike), and created by him…<br>
–RuneUnlimited–<br>
Coder/Creator: Brawler (me)<br>
Client Maker: Brawler (me)<br>
Model[rs]: Brawler (me), J0j0z, SilentCJ &lt;----he didn’t help me, just used some of his custom items. AFC, has no friends.<br>
--------------------FOR PEOPLE THAT ASKED--------------------<br>
i MADE my own base, i didn’t download anything. i also custom-made my own client…don’t like it? piss off.<br>
YES, i did take some things out of dragon-history…didn’t use it as the base</h2>
<p>–FEATURES–<br>
*Full dragon platebody making, with all of the parts.<br>
*to get the ability to wield “dragon claws”, you need to complete a quest<br>
*full spirit shields, along with spirit shield making.<br>
([TIMELINE])GodWars–&gt;Holy Elixr/Spirit shield–&gt;[HolyElixr+Spirit shield]–&gt;blessed spirit shield–&gt;Arcane(or any other sigils)sigil–&gt;ARCANE SPIRIT SHIELD!<br>
*Construction - - - CREDITS 100% to Aintaro.<br>
*Revenant minigame - - - CREDITS 100% Aintaro (IDEA)<br>
*Dueling - - - thanks to * of *, for the guide.<br>
*1 working quest - - - CREDITS 100% Aintaro<br>
*Summoning - - - all me their.<br>
*godwars, you can either get the 20 sara kills, or get 90 construction and build a warped door, and choose which boss you want to go to.<br>
*Members/Donators are the same thing, you do NOT get a crown (AS OF NOW) but i am currently working on it…<br>
*a random event, you need to bury a certian bone, and you will get this message that says ‘please pick an item’. as of now, only the rubber chicken button works…<br>
++and more, but i am way to lazy to list them all++</p>
<p>–Things i’m working on–<br>
*Wilderness ditch, i added my map so it’s on the map on the upper right handed corner. just need to make them up and add them in :]. their problay not going<br>
to have a gfx, their just going to work as a portal. you click it, and it teles you to the other side. walk one block, and you’re in level 1.</p>
<p>*skill cape emotes - all 100% done.</p>
<p>*cleaned up home, mved thieving stalls, moved shops and more…it’s not like dodian, you start off with a certian look. just talk to the make over mage to change<br>
youi’re look.</p>
<p>*all skills working. cept firemaking. just need to get around to finishing it…</p>
<p><em>–HUNTER</em>–<br>
*hunter, is something i wanted to add ever since i got 99 hunter on runescape…it’s my own custom version of hunter, so let me explain it to ya. you need to have<br>
a MEMBERS spot to enter the portal, and you need a donators ticket to start the skill. i don’t have any of the hunter models or NPC’s yet, any one who wants to<br>
help plz post :). anyways, you kill monsters with the net you get. the monster i have so far is a imp[s]. you kill it, and depending on the monster, you either get<br>
1-5 ecto-tokens. you can use the tokens to exchange for hunter items, supplies, etc… the most expensive item you can save up for is the hunter cape. which you can<br>
show off around :D!. this is my own, and i have yet to seen this idea…if i see it just give me creds. for the idea :).</p>
<p><em>–RUNE CRAFTING GUILD</em>–<br>
yer, castlewars just wasn’t working for me. so i decided to turn it into the runecrafting guild. so i got to work with adding the models, and noticed that instead<br>
of sitting their and adding in all of the robes, and staffs, i just turned my dragon’hai robes in runecrafting robes. and i turned an extra one of my zuriels staffs,into<br>
the ‘elemental staff’ which is a runecrafting item :). i added all of the teletabs, and you click them and it will teleport you to the altar. it will delete one, but it’s eaiser<br>
to runecraft.</p>
<p><em>–MAGIC–</em><br>
so i have yet to have seen, a delta server, or any server, with superheating, enchanting, or any of those spells. so, i brought up my own method of superheating.<br>
what is says if, you use a fire rune on any ore, it will send the 2 gfx’s of alching, and the dragon battleaxe spec thing. it’s pretty cool, and i spent a shitload of time<br>
editing this and making it look good…you don’t like it? fuck you.</p>
<p>enchanting, i haven’t starter it yet, but i have all the gfx’s and all of the methods writen out. so not enofugh information yet.</p>
<p>–<em>SKILLS</em>–<br>
Attack - 100%      }-------------&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;<br>
Strength - 100%   }===========&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt; All         COMPLETE. no errors…<br>
Defence - 100%   }===========&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;    100%<br>
Hitpoints - 100%   }-------------&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;<br>
Range - 100% - - i edited so that you can see you’re arrow going through the air, and you can pick it up once u killed the player/monster.<br>
Summoning - 100% - - it’s all just basic commands, nothing special.<br>
Construction - 100% - - again, creds. go to Aintaro<br>
Hunter - 40% - - just need to edit the ticket exchange, and the models.<br>
Fletching - 100% - - working stringing bows, and fletching bows, with the correct GFX’s.<br>
Prayer - 100% - - working using a bone on an altar, and bone burying.<br>
Fishing - 100% - - all fishing items working, with feathers and BAIT.<br>
Crafting - 100% - - all gems, and stringing gems working.<br>
Herblore - 50% - - still need to fix it up…way to many errors to explain…<br>
Slayer - 40% - - need to add all of the NPC’s that he will assign.(vannaka)<br>
Agility - 30% - - again, to many errors to explain.<br>
Thieving - 100% - - working pickpocketing, and stealing from stalls.<br>
Farming - 100% - - working raking, and watering plants :).<br>
Woodcutting - 80% - - for some reason, my dumb ass guy stops cutting…you have to keep clicking.<br>
Mining - 100% - - and made a mining guild.<br>
Smithing - 100% - - 100% now, with superheating!<br>
Firemaking - 1% - - haven’t even starter yet…</p>
<p>–<em>CITIES</em>–<br>
-all varrok spawns.<br>
-all falador spawns = with air running, can only tele into the altar if you have an air tiara, no talisman yet…also added mining guild. need 60+ mining to enter.<br>
-all camelot spawns<br>
-all al kally spawns<br>
-all lumby spawns<br>
<em>MY GOAL IS TO GET AL CITY SPAWNS…</em></p>
<p>–<em>DELTA TELES</em>–<br>
(NOTE: as of now, i’m starting to make more NPC teleports, as of portal teleports)<br>
–MINIGAMES–<br>
=Clan wars<br>
=Funpk<br>
=Revenants<br>
=KBD<br>
=Barrows<br>
=Fight pits - - 80%<br>
=Pest Control - - working on original<br>
=Bounty Hunter - - working on targets.<br>
=Barbian Assauly - - wanna replace something with it, it’s problay going to be WWE monday night raw thing <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=5" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"> for teh kidz.</p>
<p>–Monster Teleports–<br>
=Balance train<br>
=Dagg lair - - with Tormented Deamon<br>
=Island<br>
=Cave<br>
=Slayer tower</p>
<p>–Begin Training–<br>
=Ghost Training<br>
=Island<br>
=GodWars Chambre<br>
=Herblore</p>
<p>–Pking places–<br>
=Edgeville<br>
=Varrok<br>
=Magebank</p>
<p>UPDATE: 8/7/09<br>
well i was working on my horde, and as of now i’m going to make my own map for the location…UNLESS i can find somewere where it would<br>
be a good location…</p>
<p>UPDATE: 8/7/09<br>
yeah, the map making didn’t go so well lmfao…though it was easy, turns out it’s not…so what i did, was find a city that wasn’t very useful…<br>
not guna give away the name, but than i found another city, in the wilderness. i think you all know what i’m talking about…so what it is, it’s<br>
set up like the FightCaves, it sends waves. before the last wave, it says that “run! hide! the Zombie Champion is coming next wave!” it’s pretty<br>
much just a bunch a waves of zombies, that i custom made…eventually it will get harder like dragons will come, etc…not only that, but on the<br>
last wave, player will be able to kill other players. think it’s gay? please post.</p>
<p>UPDATE: 8/8/09<br>
finished all my portals, thus making this server non delta…the portals are set up like pwnscape, you choose where you want to teleport to.<br>
click on it, and it shows a frame with all of the diffrent teleports.</p>
<p>UPDATE: 8/9/09<br>
i decided, i’m pretty sick of the fightcave thing… i have a question, or more of a poll to ask of you. i was playing gears of war, and i was<br>
going to replace all of the jad waves, and the jad NPC’s, and such, with zombies, zombie champions, and what not. i just think it will be<br>
something diffrent…the sooner i get you’re response, the sooner i can get this done…just wondering if you would like it <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=5" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"> kthxbi.</p>
<p>UPDATE: 8/10/09<br>
finally finished my zombie minigame; sweat in tears put into that…</p>
<p>–NO MORE DELTA–<br>
spawned a few portals, and made them so that they show and interface that comes up with a list of all of the diffrent teleports…as of now,<br>
i’m not going to finish them. when i release the soruce, they will problay not be finished. sup to you to fix dem <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/wink.png?v=5" title=":wink:" class="emoji" alt=":wink:"></p>
<p><em>–NEED A PLACE FOR JAD–</em><br>
if i’m going to add the horde…do you think people will still want jad :((?</p>
<p>-<strong>UPDATE ON MY RANDOM EVENT</strong>-<br>
this was yet another thing i kept working on. i made it so that if you bury a bone in a CERTIAN place (it’s a big place, it almost half of edgeville,<br>
but you only get the event every 15 minutes…it was difficult, the item you get is bunny ears, or a basket of eggs.</p>
<p>–<strong>UPDATE ON RANDOM EVENT (8/10/09)</strong>–<br>
k, so i decided to make this for every1…you can only do it once, you use a bone on my custom altar…than you get teleported somewhere<br>
were you kill a monster, get the rubber chicken etc…than get teleported out…ya i know it’s insainly gay…but my other one just kept<br>
getting errors :(( sowwie.</p>
<h2>
<strong>UPDATE ON SKILLS</strong><br>
here is a 100% update on skills…</h2>
<p><em>COMBAT</em><br>
Attack-<br>
100%, with correct interfaces<br>
(instert img.name(attack) in skills folder)</p>
<p>Strength-<br>
100%, with correct animations/interfaces<br>
(insert img.name(strength) in skills folder)</p>
<p>Range-<br>
100%, the arrow WILL be in air, than dropped on ground, once done killing the NPC/player.<br>
(insert img.name(range) in skills folder)</p>
<p>Prayer-<br>
80%, you can not only bury the bones, but use them on a ‘altar’…it’s 80% done, because not all of the bones work. and i wanna add some<br>
of the prayer amour, and robes.<br>
(insert img.name(prayer) in skills folder)<br>
(insert img.name(prayer1) in skills folder)</p>
<p>Mage-<br>
75%, full alching, low leve alching, and such…i’m currently working on superheating (almost done) along with enchanting amulets.<br>
that is something that will problay be the last thing i do… all depends on if i get around to it…super boring…<br>
(insert img.name(mage) in skills folder)</p>
<p>RuneCrafting-<br>
100%, yeah the first skill i ever finished…the first thing that i added was the Zamorak mage, which will teleport you to the abyss where you<br>
can runecraft. i also, made it so that aubury will teleport you to the rune essence mine (both pure/regular).<br>
(insert img.name(runecrafting1) in skills folder)<br>
(insert img.name(runecrafting2) in skills folder)<br>
(insert img.name(runecrafting3) in skills folder)<br>
(insert img.name(runecrafting4) in skills folder)</p>
<p>Agility-<br>
95%, ok so once i make it so that you get tickets when you complete the coruse, than make the ticket exchange, it will be 1005 =)<br>
(insert img.name(agility) in skills folder)</p>
<p>Herblore-<br>
40%, i STILL need to make so much more things…didn’t really focus on this skill that much because i thought i was going to replace it…<br>
turns out, i like it <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=5" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"><br>
(insert img.name(herblore) in skills folder)</p>
<p>Thieving-<br>
100%, you can not only steal from stalls, but you can also pickpocket NPC’s.<br>
(insert img.name(thieving) in skills folder)</p>
<p>Crafting-<br>
80%, need to make it so that you get the “cut” stone, instead of the amulet.<br>
(insert img.name(crafting) in skills folder)</p>
<p>Fletching-<br>
50%, as of now, their are no GFX’s and the only thing you can really do is string the bow.<br>
(insert img.name(fletching) in skills folder)</p>
<p>Slayer-<br>
0%, no pictures (lmfao)</p>
<p>Mining-<br>
60%, um for somereason, whenever i swing my pick, it only swings once…need to fix that <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=5" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"> so i guess whenever i get around to it<br>
i can finish that, but until than kthbi.<br>
(insert img.name(mining) in skills folder)</p>
<p>Smithing-<br>
80%, the only thing i need to fix is that when you use the bar on the anvil, it brings up the interface and you click on the thing and it gives<br>
you the item…almost their :s.<br>
(insert img.name(smithing) in skills folder)</p>
<p>Fishing-<br>
100%, i really don’t want to work on i usually don’t spend that much on skills but this is pretty much good just how it is. you auto fish, it<br>
only sends 1 gfx wich is at the beginning.<br>
(insert img.name(fishing) in skills folder)<br>
(insert img.name(fishing1) in skills folder</p>
<p>Cooking-<br>
100%, ‘perfect’ working with the range, AND it auto cooks! you don’t need to keep clicking it will cook for you. on top of that, it will keep<br>
sending the gfx and it will never stop. also, you can cook on fires!<br>
(insert img.name(cooking) in skills folder)</p>
<p>Firemaking-<br>
0%, no pictures what the point?</p>
<p>Woodcutting-<br>
90%, it’s just like fishing which i don’t like i want the character to keep swining.it auto woodcuts, so you don’t have to keep clicking.<br>
(insert img.name(woodcutting) in skills folder)</p>
<p>Farming-<br>
100%, i acutally just finished this skill, it’s 100%, loads all of the gfx’s and handels all of the packets. use the seed on the patch, you char.<br>
will get a rake and send a gfx, than a herb will spawn in you’re inventory.<br>
(insert img.name(farming) in skills folder)</p>
<p>Summoning-<br>
100%, ALL CREDITS GO TO AINTARO FOR THE IDEA &lt;33<br>
(insert img.name(summoning) in skills folder)</p>
<p><em>UPDATE</em><br>
Anti-leech in my client. goodluck fixing it?<br>
(insert img.name(antileechinmyclient) in skills folder)<br>
<em>UPDATE</em><br>
another anti-leech, this is my own client and i want to keep it that way, so i deleted some of the java files so you can’t edit them…</p>
<p>–/future work–<br>
*as of now, im making my own client…what do i have so far?<br>
(insert img.name(546bars) in skills folder)<br>
(insert img.name(546bars2) in skills folder)<br>
(insert img.name(newoption) in skills folder)</p>
<p><strong>-/\i will be releasing any time i get around to it…just need to finish/-</strong><br>
thanks,<br>
Y0u Are Y0u† [no, i didn’t take the name from that guy on runescape…didn’t even know it was a name, it’s my fav. thing to say]<br>
(sponsored by: CircaGaming™ (owned by me/rhw co-ex. Circa))<br>
NEWS:<br>
CircaGaming™’s RuneUnlimited 508 has BEEN RELEASED. please click the link below, to take you to the desired location…</p>
<p>UPDATE: 8/15/09<br>
Finished my Zombie Horde, it’s just the fight caves but instead of monster spawning that would usually spawn, it’s just zombies. at the end,<br>
you fight Zombie King (K’ril Tsuraoth) and if u beat him, u get firecape. you can have only 5 players in the match, but each player needs to<br>
kill the required amount of monsters per wave…still some glitches, but i’ll fix it eventually.</p>
<p><em>|UPDATE|</em><br>
well as of now, i wanna make it so that when you click on one of the skill buttons, under the skill tab, it will teleport you to the skill master were<br>
you can get the skill cape of that skill. (to make it set up like a 508/bulby type thing :] )</p>
<p>EDITINg IN THE PICTURE THINGS LATER GOING TO BED ATM…</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/circagaming-runeunlimited-circagaming/295499/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/circagaming-runeunlimited-circagaming/295499/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 16 Aug 2009 01:49:33 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-295499-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/circagaming-runeunlimited-circagaming/295499.rss">|circagaming|-runeunlimited-|circagaming|</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
