<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Stylex | 317 | Pk-Eco</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/stylex-317-pk-eco/512726</link>
    <description>Eventually I&#39;ll spend an hour or so making this thread nice, but i&#39;m in a hurry atm and would like to just get it out before I leave. (I apologize)

In a nutshell. I&#39;m 22 and can do pretty much anything with PI, I have a VPS and already started on the website

Once I feel the server is ready for players I&#39;m going to buy a space on the mopar toplist to get things rolling.

I&#39;ve read and actually made many threads here myself, and in the end I&#39;m here to have fun and have lots of players join my server. Some people think they will make $ or think its cool to be a &quot;coder, Co-coder, owner&quot; whatever noobs call themselves now-a-days. I&#39;m in it to have a good time.


I&#39;m way different then any owner you&#39;ve met before. I&#39;m relaxed. nice as hell. not pushy. and best of all get shit done and very dedicated to my work.

Theres no application, I will have a max of 5 staff at any time including myself, you can get accepted by convincing me I need you with a friendly chat on skype.

I usually have skype open on my phone if im not home so just add me and we can go from there.
Thanks for your time,
Skype username :  Ahndeey</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2013 19:24:52 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/stylex-317-pk-eco/512726.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Stylex | 317 | Pk-Eco</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@T_h_3 T h 3]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/t_h_3">@T_h_3</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“tyb97, post:2, topic:512726”](Unless the rule has changed) No putting your website in this section unless it’s approved.</p>
<p>Anyways, I want to see some more details, so I’ll wait around until then.[/quote]</p>
<p>edited my post a bit. removed my website. (don’t wanna cause any problems and didn’t know about that rule) I’ve had links here previously, ~Thanks for the warning just think it helps to show people I’m not a noob with <a href="http://webs.com" rel="nofollow noopener">webs.com</a> domain</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/stylex-317-pk-eco/512726/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/stylex-317-pk-eco/512726/3</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2013 19:24:52 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-512726-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/stylex-317-pk-eco/512726.rss">Stylex | 317 | Pk-Eco</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Stylex | 317 | Pk-Eco</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@tyb97 tyb97]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/tyb97">@tyb97</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>(Unless the rule has changed) No putting your website in this section unless it’s approved.</p>
<p>Anyways, I want to see some more details, so I’ll wait around until then.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/stylex-317-pk-eco/512726/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/stylex-317-pk-eco/512726/2</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 31 Mar 2013 19:17:03 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-512726-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/stylex-317-pk-eco/512726.rss">Stylex | 317 | Pk-Eco</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Stylex | 317 | Pk-Eco</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@T_h_3 T h 3]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/t_h_3">@T_h_3</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Eventually I’ll spend an hour or so making this thread nice, but i’m in a hurry atm and would like to just get it out before I leave. (I apologize)</p>
<p>In a nutshell. I’m 22 and can do pretty much anything with PI, I have a VPS and already started on the website</p>
<p>Once I feel the server is ready for players I’m going to buy a space on the mopar toplist to get things rolling.</p>
<p>I’ve read and actually made many threads here myself, and in the end I’m here to have fun and have lots of players join my server. Some people think they will make $ or think its cool to be a “coder, Co-coder, owner” whatever noobs call themselves now-a-days. I’m in it to have a good time.</p>
<p>I’m way different then any owner you’ve met before. I’m relaxed. nice as hell. not pushy. and best of all get shit done and very dedicated to my work.</p>
<p>Theres no application, I will have a max of 5 staff at any time including myself, you can get accepted by convincing me I need you with a friendly chat on skype.</p>
<p>I usually have skype open on my phone if im not home so just add me and we can go from there.<br>
Thanks for your time,<br>
Skype username :  Ahndeey</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/stylex-317-pk-eco/512726/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/stylex-317-pk-eco/512726/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 31 Mar 2013 19:14:58 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-512726-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/stylex-317-pk-eco/512726.rss">Stylex | 317 | Pk-Eco</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
