<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:discourse="http://www.discourse.org/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Community Suggestions - moparisthebest.com</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/c/community-suggestions</link>
    <description>Topics in the &#39;Community Suggestions&#39; category This board allows you to suggest changes, and discuss them with the rest of the community and staff, also for announcing changes.</description>
    
      <lastBuildDate>Tue, 09 Aug 2016 07:30:10 +0000</lastBuildDate>
      <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/c/community-suggestions.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
        <item>
          <title>Consider making the old &#39;internal&#39; cheating section public</title>
          <dc:creator><![CDATA[@lothy Lothy]]></dc:creator>
          <category>Community Suggestions</category>
          <description><![CDATA[
            <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/lothy">@lothy</a> wrote:</p>
            <blockquote>
              <p>This is primarily for Moparisthebest’s consideration.</p>
<p>Can you consider making the internal cheating section public? There’s no real benefit in continued secrecy given that the discussions/developments aren’t really ongoing, but there were a lot of interesting discussions that people might enjoy reading.</p>
<p>I also suspect that enough time has passed that the people who made the posts there won’t feel any kind of loss.</p>
            </blockquote>
            <p>Posts: 12</p>
            <p>Participants: 5</p>
            <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/consider-making-the-old-internal-cheating-section-public/555752">Read full topic</a></p>
          ]]></description>
          <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/consider-making-the-old-internal-cheating-section-public/555752</link>
          <pubDate>Tue, 09 Aug 2016 07:30:10 +0000</pubDate>
          <discourse:topicPinned>No</discourse:topicPinned>
          <discourse:topicClosed>No</discourse:topicClosed>
          <discourse:topicArchived>No</discourse:topicArchived>
          <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-topic-555752</guid>
          <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/consider-making-the-old-internal-cheating-section-public/555752.rss">Consider making the old &#39;internal&#39; cheating section public</source>
        </item>
        <item>
          <title>Adding old badges</title>
          <dc:creator><![CDATA[@doom_j doom_j]]></dc:creator>
          <category>Community Suggestions</category>
          <description><![CDATA[
            <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/doom_j">@doom_j</a> wrote:</p>
            <blockquote>
              <p>It would be cool if we could get the old Badges added into the forum. Badges if allowed to can be used as a title which is a nifty feature since as far as I can see this one doesn’t support custom titles?</p>
<p>If anyone else has some cool ideas please share!</p>
            </blockquote>
            <p>Posts: 23</p>
            <p>Participants: 9</p>
            <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/adding-old-badges/555750">Read full topic</a></p>
          ]]></description>
          <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/adding-old-badges/555750</link>
          <pubDate>Mon, 08 Aug 2016 21:19:35 +0000</pubDate>
          <discourse:topicPinned>No</discourse:topicPinned>
          <discourse:topicClosed>No</discourse:topicClosed>
          <discourse:topicArchived>No</discourse:topicArchived>
          <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-topic-555750</guid>
          <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/adding-old-badges/555750.rss">Adding old badges</source>
        </item>
        <item>
          <title>About the Community Suggestions category</title>
          <dc:creator><![CDATA[@system system]]></dc:creator>
          <category>Community Suggestions</category>
          <description><![CDATA[
            <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/system">@system</a> wrote:</p>
            <blockquote>
              <p>This board allows you to suggest changes, and discuss them with the rest of the community and staff, also for announcing changes.</p>
            </blockquote>
            <p>Posts: 1</p>
            <p>Participants: 1</p>
            <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/about-the-community-suggestions-category/142">Read full topic</a></p>
          ]]></description>
          <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/about-the-community-suggestions-category/142</link>
          <pubDate>Fri, 29 Jul 2016 18:21:48 +0000</pubDate>
          <discourse:topicPinned>Yes</discourse:topicPinned>
          <discourse:topicClosed>No</discourse:topicClosed>
          <discourse:topicArchived>No</discourse:topicArchived>
          <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-topic-142</guid>
          <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/about-the-community-suggestions-category/142.rss">About the Community Suggestions category</source>
        </item>
        <item>
          <title>10 years! Wow. A brief History of the Forums</title>
          <dc:creator><![CDATA[@moparisthebest Moparisthebest]]></dc:creator>
          <category>Community Suggestions</category>
          <description><![CDATA[
            <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/moparisthebest">@moparisthebest</a> wrote:</p>
            <blockquote>
              <p>It’s been slightly over or under 10 years since these forums were started, depending on where you count from.  I first installed the forums on a shady PHP host I met on IRC and paid via paypal for a month, I set up <a href="http://moparisthebest.com/smf/">moparisthebest.com/smf/</a> and it ran for a few weeks, then the host disappeared off the face of the earth along with the database and everything else, so I set it up on a new host on February 22nd, 2006.  I know that date exactly because it’s the date my account shows for a creation date.  Don’t worry, 2006 moparisthebest was an idiot, 2016 moparisthebest has backups, RAID, security, and all the other things you’d expect from a host. <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=5" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
<p>For some more background, I started playing runescape (RS2) in late 2004 or early 2005.  When I started I couldn’t even touch type, I only hunted and pecked, I was forced into learning to touch type by the need to talk faster in runescape in order to cooperate with other players and be able to sell/buy things.  I quickly got tired of the monotony of grinding experience points, and since I had just taken my first intro to programming course, on my way to a mechanical engineering degree, in college (university for you European folks), I naturally thought maybe I could automatically program a mouse to do this for me.  Some searching brought me to a website with something called SCAR scripts on it, to <a href="http://sythe.org">sythe.org</a>, and eventually to the home of the creator of SCAR, the kaitnieks forums.  I liked these forums far more than <a href="http://sythe.org">sythe.org</a>, there was no buying or selling allowed, and therefore no scammers.  Additionally it appeared to be a meritocracy, anyone who could contribute positively to a conversation was welcomed, anyone who could program could share their work, and be recognized and thanked for it.  From the script repository website, I had a few scripts that mined ore in parts of fallador, and smithed it, and did some other things.  I improved on them, combined them, used them myself and shared them with the community.  I had never programmed anything other than Java, so Turbo Pascal was much different, but procedural programming was procedural programming so I figured it out by example and trial and error.  These scripts were so well liked I received 50 reputation points and magically saw a new board restricted to ‘Community Members’, there were some interesting discussions there, but most everything still happened in public.  I even got a ‘SCAR Scripter’ badge which I thought was the coolest thing ever.</p>
<p>Around that time, someone named Waffendennis was releasing these things called ‘deobs’, which stood for deobfuscated, decompiled, java source code for the runescape client.  You could modify it however you want, recompile it, and play runescape with it.  At the time, runescape released new versions every few weeks or so, so you had plenty of time to play around with it before it changed.  I used my knowledge of Java, and combined some tutorials posted on kaitnieks to create ‘MoparScape’, a custom client that made it easier to cheat on runescape with SCAR.  It supported things such as stripping out the randomization of colors (something Jagex added to make SCAR cheating harder), locking the view north and high (again, Jagex had it randomly rotate), and some other awesome things like replacing all strings of ‘RuneScape’ to ‘MoparScape’ and of course awesome MIDI music from Doom!  Probably some other things I don’t even remember as well.  People seemed to like it quite a bit too, and it kept me busy manually updating it every few weeks.  I wrote an automatic updater which has to be some of the worst Java code ever written, I didn’t know about parsers or regular expressions, so it consisted almost entirely of .indexOf(), .lastIndexOf(), and .substring(), it was so fragile I ended up writing more code and manually fixing it for almost every release, but I did end up learning a lot!  It was fairly popular because it made it so much easier and more reliable to cheat with SCAR, as much as I hate to admit, I doubt people played it for the Doom music…</p>
<p>Sometime afterwards a guy named Winterlove, who had taken a version 317 deob, removed the encryption, studied and modified it, released a rudimentary server for it.  You didn’t even have a character and you couldn’t move around, it was just a flyover of some of the landscape, and additionally, though we didn’t know it at the time, it was some of the worst code and code structure you’d ever see, but it worked!  Well that unleashed a firestorm, suddenly the possibility of playing on your own private runescape server was real, you could go anywhere, do anything, and see everything you couldn’t get to either because you didn’t have money to pay the $5/month membership fee or didn’t have the levels required or equipment to get there, it was a dream come true.  As I remember it, someone named Daiki made the first modifications needed to actually log in with a character and walk around.  I applied my MoparScape changes to the 317 client, along with modifications to type a custom server and port to connect to, and the first private server MoparScape version was released.  At some point I even bundled a server so all you needed was the client to play your own server, but honestly I don’t remember when.</p>
<p>Around the same time, keep in mind this was still 2005, some java wizards, I remember RegeX, eXemplar, SeanWT, and some others (I know Mopman got involved later) created a JAVA bot based off of Waffendennis’ deobs, this was called Aryan.  This changed EVERYTHING!!! You have to understand, SCAR worked by scraping your screen, clicking on colors, and typing things.  It took over your whole computer while automating a single bot.  You couldn’t even use the computer for anything else while SCAR was running.  Aryan, however, emulated the mouse and keyboard in java on a per-client level, so the number of bots you could run simultaneously while still using your computer was limited only by your RAM and CPU.  Runescape cheating exploded.  Jagex started updating more frequently, and everytime they did, you needed an update to Aryan before you could cheat again.  ‘Noobs’ as we called them would flood kaitnieks with requests for updates, indignant that the creators of Aryan doing all this work for them for free didn’t do it faster.  Jagex kept adding things to break Aryan, Aryan devs kept coding fixes, it was awesome.  Aryan has a much richer and deeper story I won’t fully cover here, we’ll leave that for another post (perhaps by Mopman), and get back to the forum.</p>
<p>In late December 2005, or early January 2006, the kaitnieks forums abrubtly shut down with no warning.  Kaitnieks had had a child, and had no more time to deal with the now far too busy forum, some of the community still hung out on IRC, and most of us talked over MSN messenger as well.  For awhile, we held out hope someone might bring it back, but no one did, and no one wanted to go back to <a href="http://sythe.org">sythe.org</a>.  I had purchased <a href="http://moparisthebest.com">moparisthebest.com</a> the year before and had some SCAR scripts on there, so I figured why not install a temporary forum for the kaitnieks community to hang out until kaitnieks came back?  I rebuilt the forum with the same category/board structure as kaitnieks, as retrieved from <a href="http://archive.org">archive.org</a>. The plan was to lure some original kaitnieks staff back, give them full control, and then revert myself to a regular member again.  But the staff came back too slowly, and soon it was popular, clear that kaitnieks would probably never come back, and people seemed to want me as admin, so here we are.</p>
<p>The forums went through some crazy changes, at first it was just SCAR scripts and Aryan, the Aryan devs had abandoned updates and released their (broken) updater in the wild.  It was crazy complicated with many regular expressions and even some perl, yuck.  Other slimeballs on the internet started releasing updates for money, that didn’t sit well with me, so I started releasing updates for it for free, along with my whole updater, so anyone could just click it and spit out a fully updated Aryan. (at that point, actually releasing an updated Aryan was legally questionable, releasing code to generate that from jagex’s original runescape.jar was fine)  This made the forums insanely popular towards the end of 2006, it quickly went from a hobby to something I spent 8+ hours a day on.  I realized I’d be just as happy programming as doing mechanical engineering work, and that more jobs were available and it paid more, I switched my major to Computer Science and graduated in 2009, later that same year I was married. <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=5" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
<p>During the same time period, private servers were making amazing strides, different people came out with different features, copied/pasted them between servers, and things worked despite not being able to support many clients simultaneously and mostly being coded as a giant case statement in one large method, it was terrible code-wise.  The forums were filled with ‘moparscape’ questions, the cheaters hated it.  I registered <a href="http://moparisthebest.com">moparisthebest.com</a> (some asshole had taken <a href="http://moparscape.com">moparscape.com</a>), copied the forum PHP files over there, and did terrible hacks to run 2 different forums on the same database.  We banished all moparscape and private server talk go to moparscape, and moparisthebest was reserved for cheating.  I personally focused almost entirely on cheating and <a href="http://moparisthebest.com">moparisthebest.com</a>, and unfortunatly <a href="http://moparisthebest.com">moparisthebest.com</a> turned into a craphole of spam, flaming, and all the other stuff you don’t want in a forum.  Then, Jagex released an update completely killing Aryan, it would have required a complete rewrite, and everyone was either too busy or didn’t know enough how to do it.  Even if you did manage it, updating was almost an insurmountable nightmare with the new setup.  The golden age of runescape cheating was over.  Runescape as a game started to decline as well, and with it, runescape cheating and <a href="http://moparisthebest.com">moparisthebest.com</a>.</p>
<p>Meanwhile and almost under the radar, <a href="http://moparisthebest.com">moparisthebest.com</a> was exploding.  I released version 3 of MoparScape which was Aryan, back-ported to 317, with MoparScape features.  The private server people didn’t care for it because they didn’t support cheating, I was surprised by this because I thought we were all cheaters, but I was wrong.  I should have firmly taken the reigns and molded <a href="http://moparisthebest.com">moparisthebest.com</a> into the awesome community that <a href="http://moparisthebest.com">moparisthebest.com</a> was, unfortunatly I was busy with life, college, meeting my future wife, getting married etc.  We had some less than great staff who got a head too big for their shoulders, treated everyone poorly, and even ended up creating a competing forum and encouraging everyone to go there.  Different staff members tried multiple times to ‘fix’ the problem, some more successful than others.  We created new forums, <a href="http://moparcraft.net">moparcraft.net</a> dedicated to minecraft, <a href="http://gamedev.moparisthebest.com">gamedev.moparisthebest.com</a> dedicated to game development, <a href="http://android.moparisthebest.org">android.moparisthebest.org</a> dedicated to android development.  This required horrible SMF hacks to maintain, and moparcraft was the only one that achieved any measurable success.  <a href="http://moparisthebest.com">moparisthebest.com</a> continued it’s decline, and before long, it was more work maintaining seperate forums than it was worth, and the decision was made to just move everything to <a href="http://moparisthebest.com">moparisthebest.com</a> and a vanilla SMF.  As runescape continues to decline so does moparscape, and I also don’t have the time I wish I could put into it as a married 30 year old, with a full time programming job, a 4 year old, a 2 year old, and one on the way.  I am still happy with what the forum was and still is, and it continues to be the absolute best community I’ve ever been a part of.  It’s still great and I think it can only get better in the future, so we should celebrate the past 10 years for what they were, and look forward to the next 10 years for what they can be.  Most of us started this journey as teenagers, and now 10+ years later we can raise a glass together as we continue down this road!  That’s a solid 1/3rd of my life, and even more than that for most of you!</p>
<p>Congratulations to the kaitnieks/moparisthebest/moparcraft/moparscape community!  Thanks for sticking together for an amazing 10 years!  Let’s keep it up!</p>
            </blockquote>
            <p>Posts: 130</p>
            <p>Participants: 71</p>
            <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/10-years-wow-a-brief-history-of-the-forums/554644">Read full topic</a></p>
          ]]></description>
          <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/10-years-wow-a-brief-history-of-the-forums/554644</link>
          <pubDate>Fri, 05 Feb 2016 04:57:36 +0000</pubDate>
          <discourse:topicPinned>No</discourse:topicPinned>
          <discourse:topicClosed>No</discourse:topicClosed>
          <discourse:topicArchived>No</discourse:topicArchived>
          <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-topic-554644</guid>
          <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/10-years-wow-a-brief-history-of-the-forums/554644.rss">10 years! Wow. A brief History of the Forums</source>
        </item>
        <item>
          <title>New Admin Suggestion</title>
          <dc:creator><![CDATA[@gothic_queen casey.]]></dc:creator>
          <category>Community Suggestions</category>
          <description><![CDATA[
            <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/gothic_queen">@gothic_queen</a> wrote:</p>
            <blockquote>
              <p>I would like to nominate Greeny to be the next Admin.</p>
<p>He has done a great job as the general discussion moderator and I feel like he could really benefit the site.</p>
            </blockquote>
            <p>Posts: 13</p>
            <p>Participants: 10</p>
            <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-admin-suggestion/554380">Read full topic</a></p>
          ]]></description>
          <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-admin-suggestion/554380</link>
          <pubDate>Wed, 13 Jan 2016 20:26:49 +0000</pubDate>
          <discourse:topicPinned>No</discourse:topicPinned>
          <discourse:topicClosed>No</discourse:topicClosed>
          <discourse:topicArchived>No</discourse:topicArchived>
          <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-topic-554380</guid>
          <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-admin-suggestion/554380.rss">New Admin Suggestion</source>
        </item>
        <item>
          <title>Merry Christmas, MoparScape!</title>
          <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Tom Tom]]></dc:creator>
          <category>Community Suggestions</category>
          <description><![CDATA[
            <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/tom">@Tom</a> wrote:</p>
            <blockquote>
              <p>On behalf of the staff team here at MoparScape I’d like to wish everyone in the community a very Merry Christmas, and best of luck for the new year! I hope we’ve all enjoyed the festive season and will make the most of what remains. <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=5" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
<p>Merry Christmas,</p>
<p>The MoparScape staff team.</p>
            </blockquote>
            <p>Posts: 26</p>
            <p>Participants: 22</p>
            <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/merry-christmas-moparscape/554200">Read full topic</a></p>
          ]]></description>
          <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/merry-christmas-moparscape/554200</link>
          <pubDate>Thu, 24 Dec 2015 23:33:06 +0000</pubDate>
          <discourse:topicPinned>No</discourse:topicPinned>
          <discourse:topicClosed>No</discourse:topicClosed>
          <discourse:topicArchived>No</discourse:topicArchived>
          <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-topic-554200</guid>
          <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/merry-christmas-moparscape/554200.rss">Merry Christmas, MoparScape!</source>
        </item>
        <item>
          <title>Should we pull an Ikilki on Sini?</title>
          <dc:creator><![CDATA[@gothic_queen casey.]]></dc:creator>
          <category>Community Suggestions</category>
          <description><![CDATA[
            <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/gothic_queen">@gothic_queen</a> wrote:</p>
            <blockquote>
              <p>Thornefall should be treated as Rune—Locus was.</p>
            </blockquote>
            <p>Posts: 42</p>
            <p>Participants: 17</p>
            <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/should-we-pull-an-ikilki-on-sini/553942">Read full topic</a></p>
          ]]></description>
          <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/should-we-pull-an-ikilki-on-sini/553942</link>
          <pubDate>Wed, 25 Nov 2015 05:59:10 +0000</pubDate>
          <discourse:topicPinned>No</discourse:topicPinned>
          <discourse:topicClosed>No</discourse:topicClosed>
          <discourse:topicArchived>No</discourse:topicArchived>
          <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-topic-553942</guid>
          <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/should-we-pull-an-ikilki-on-sini/553942.rss">Should we pull an Ikilki on Sini?</source>
        </item>
        <item>
          <title>Server status callback</title>
          <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Fridder Fridder]]></dc:creator>
          <category>Community Suggestions</category>
          <description><![CDATA[
            <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/fridder">@Fridder</a> wrote:</p>
            <blockquote>
              <p>Might be too late to suggest this, but I think we should have a callback on the server status page.</p>
            </blockquote>
            <p>Posts: 7</p>
            <p>Participants: 6</p>
            <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/server-status-callback/553730">Read full topic</a></p>
          ]]></description>
          <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/server-status-callback/553730</link>
          <pubDate>Tue, 03 Nov 2015 02:59:49 +0000</pubDate>
          <discourse:topicPinned>No</discourse:topicPinned>
          <discourse:topicClosed>No</discourse:topicClosed>
          <discourse:topicArchived>No</discourse:topicArchived>
          <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-topic-553730</guid>
          <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/server-status-callback/553730.rss">Server status callback</source>
        </item>
        <item>
          <title>Mandatory HTTPS!</title>
          <dc:creator><![CDATA[@moparisthebest Moparisthebest]]></dc:creator>
          <category>Community Suggestions</category>
          <description><![CDATA[
            <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/moparisthebest">@moparisthebest</a> wrote:</p>
            <blockquote>
              <p><a href="http://MoparScape.org">MoparScape.org</a> has supported TLS/HTTPS for years now, but I’ve finally flipped the switch and now it is mandatory.  I’ve also added it to the chrome preload list and enabled the Public-Key-Pins HPKP header so if you’ve visited the site before, your browser will not allow you to be man-in-the-middled.</p>
<p>If you have any questions, go ahead and ask them, but you really shouldn’t notice a difference except maybe a slight increase in speed. <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=5" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
            </blockquote>
            <p>Posts: 59</p>
            <p>Participants: 15</p>
            <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/mandatory-https/553635">Read full topic</a></p>
          ]]></description>
          <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/mandatory-https/553635</link>
          <pubDate>Fri, 23 Oct 2015 20:42:57 +0000</pubDate>
          <discourse:topicPinned>No</discourse:topicPinned>
          <discourse:topicClosed>No</discourse:topicClosed>
          <discourse:topicArchived>No</discourse:topicArchived>
          <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-topic-553635</guid>
          <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/mandatory-https/553635.rss">Mandatory HTTPS!</source>
        </item>
        <item>
          <title>After Posting, Return To Thread, Not the Section</title>
          <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Nucleon Nucleon]]></dc:creator>
          <category>Community Suggestions</category>
          <description><![CDATA[
            <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/nucleon">@Nucleon</a> wrote:</p>
            <blockquote>
              <p>As a new user of this forum software.</p>
<p>I find it very annoying that after creating a post I’m re-directed to the section of the forum where the thread is contained.</p>
<p>My suggestion is to revert/change this behavior.</p>
            </blockquote>
            <p>Posts: 3</p>
            <p>Participants: 2</p>
            <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/after-posting-return-to-thread-not-the-section/553582">Read full topic</a></p>
          ]]></description>
          <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/after-posting-return-to-thread-not-the-section/553582</link>
          <pubDate>Fri, 16 Oct 2015 17:39:40 +0000</pubDate>
          <discourse:topicPinned>No</discourse:topicPinned>
          <discourse:topicClosed>No</discourse:topicClosed>
          <discourse:topicArchived>No</discourse:topicArchived>
          <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-topic-553582</guid>
          <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/after-posting-return-to-thread-not-the-section/553582.rss">After Posting, Return To Thread, Not the Section</source>
        </item>
        <item>
          <title>New Administrator: zuppers</title>
          <dc:creator><![CDATA[@moparisthebest Moparisthebest]]></dc:creator>
          <category>Community Suggestions</category>
          <description><![CDATA[
            <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/moparisthebest">@moparisthebest</a> wrote:</p>
            <blockquote>
              <p>zuppers is our latest humble administrator, congrats!  <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/smiley.png?v=5" title=":smiley:" class="emoji" alt=":smiley:"></p>
            </blockquote>
            <p>Posts: 73</p>
            <p>Participants: 32</p>
            <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-administrator-zuppers/553508">Read full topic</a></p>
          ]]></description>
          <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-administrator-zuppers/553508</link>
          <pubDate>Mon, 05 Oct 2015 19:09:16 +0000</pubDate>
          <discourse:topicPinned>No</discourse:topicPinned>
          <discourse:topicClosed>No</discourse:topicClosed>
          <discourse:topicArchived>No</discourse:topicArchived>
          <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-topic-553508</guid>
          <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-administrator-zuppers/553508.rss">New Administrator: zuppers</source>
        </item>
        <item>
          <title>I&#39;m sorry to announce</title>
          <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Tom Tom]]></dc:creator>
          <category>Community Suggestions</category>
          <description><![CDATA[
            <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/tom">@Tom</a> wrote:</p>
            <blockquote>
              <p>That the Official MoparScape server has taken a serious set back.</p>
<p>Namely, we’ve lost our main and only developer: Sini (sinisoul). He worked alone on the server, putting in many hours to create the most efficient and time compatible solutions to problems. It’s safe to say his work will be sorely missed, even more so because it will be unfinished. Our ex-developer, Sini, has his prospects set on a new game entirely called Thornefall founded by a reputable member, and ex-administrator Taharok (Avail). I’d like to personally thank sini for his dedication, and ask others to respect his decision to focus on another project instead.</p>
<p>The show must go on, there was recently a small staff meeting regarding the situation and I’d like to personally invite the thoughts of the community too. It’s always very disappointing and familiar when community projects fail, I funded this one myself without the assistance of moparisthebest and I feel a deep sense of loss for all the time and money I’ve invested but we mustn’t let this set us back. Already a plan has been drawn up to host another server where content is a lot more existent and updates for this will be due within the next few weeks, others may complain this isn’t an achievable dream but consistency is key with anything.</p>
<p>We do need your help, gathering data such as drops and NPC locations, so if you’re able to do even the most basic of tasks please drop me a PM! <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=5" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"> Once again, you’ve my sincerest apologies for this, but there is only so much I’m able to do. <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/frowning.png?v=5" title=":frowning:" class="emoji" alt=":frowning:"></p>
<p>You can find sini’s personal reasoning below:</p>
<p>[quote=“sini, post:1, topic:553212”]I’m sorry to announce publicly that after today I will no longer be involved with the official server or any serious Runescape emulation projects. I say that with a heavy heart, and I’m grateful to Tom and Davidi2 for the chance and time we spent together trying to create an emulator for the community. I’ve been apart of many projects over the years and I’ve met a lot of great people but I feel as if my time with Runescape emulation has grown beyond that of what can help me grow as a programmer and that I need to move on. Notably I had a great time working on the Moparscape server, both the original and my rendition, PRS06, my creations, and Silabgarza. I wouldn’t be the programmer I am today without this community and I don’t regret the hundreds of hours I spent trying to push the boundaries of emulators or research new topics.</p>
<p>I think this post, as dramatic as it may sound, is speaking to the community. Runescape is growing old, and the excitement that came with trying to discover how Jagex as a company operated at least for me died two years ago with the decline in the games popularity. My passion these past few years were driven by my taste to try and see a rise in the community, and have these adventures once more but I know now that isn’t plausible.</p>
<p>I was content on working on the server until recently I became involved with a project outside of Runescape emulation. This opportunity opened my eyes to the skills I could possess that are outside of emulation and the choice was simple. I have found that in the past year I have decided I want to get into game development so I can create a similar feeling to how I felt when I first loaded into Runescape about ten years ago with everyone.</p>
<p>I suggest to you that you try not to take this all as serious as some of you may, although taking this seriously is wise, I think everyone is really sensitive about how their image stands among people. I wish I spent more of my time instead of getting offended by how people saw me had more fun, and just enjoyed the ride. It went by fast, six years now I’ve been developing servers since the age of 14 and now looking back I know at least I accomplished much. I had a lot of feuds, I made a lot of friends. Making emulators can lead to skills to land you a job but it’s very limited because of the limitations of creativity you constrain yourself to. I found it hard to advance past the level I reached because I simply didnt understand all the nuances of the game client and the architecture of design.  People still are learning things today, and I think those skills are better applied to creating instead of emulating. There is a lot of talent here, it just needs better focus instead of wasting effort on something that is too niche.</p>
<p>With those remarks, thank you seriously to the following people. Silabsoft for providing a good bounty of information and security testing the server, Tom for helping me get the server to the point it was, Davidi2 for ideas and your dedication to trying to help me move my work forward, Taharok for giving me helpful advice on programming when I needed it, Lothy for bouncing ideas back and forth when we had nothing to do, Zuppers for testing and providing critical information for the server.</p>
<p>Thanks.[/quote]</p>
            </blockquote>
            <p>Posts: 82</p>
            <p>Participants: 32</p>
            <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/im-sorry-to-announce/553213">Read full topic</a></p>
          ]]></description>
          <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/im-sorry-to-announce/553213</link>
          <pubDate>Mon, 07 Sep 2015 01:31:58 +0000</pubDate>
          <discourse:topicPinned>No</discourse:topicPinned>
          <discourse:topicClosed>No</discourse:topicClosed>
          <discourse:topicArchived>No</discourse:topicArchived>
          <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-topic-553213</guid>
          <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/im-sorry-to-announce/553213.rss">I&#39;m sorry to announce</source>
        </item>
        <item>
          <title>Community Update [25/08/2015]</title>
          <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Tom Tom]]></dc:creator>
          <category>Community Suggestions</category>
          <description><![CDATA[
            <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/tom">@Tom</a> wrote:</p>
            <blockquote>
              <p>Hey guys,</p>
<p>Just a few small changes and updates to let you know about today, as I’ve posted around the forums recently I am now openly allowing name changes, please drop me a private message with all the relevant information and why you want your name changed and I’ll review it. If you’ve had your name changed already, I cannot guarantee I’ll do it again. That being said think long and hard before messaging me. <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=6" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
<p>On another note I’ve stumbled across a cool feature of simpleportal which allows the creation of new pages with cool designs, in the past people have suggested reworking the help tab to include more relevant information, we can now do that and once this page is complete I’ll link it on the homepage. You can find the under construction version of the page here:</p>
<aside class="onebox whitelistedgeneric">
  <header class="source">
      <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/uploads/default/original/2X/1/1f0dc167bcf798bdbd70b03bf0fd1bc836e54e1a.png" class="site-icon" width="32" height="32">
      <a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/" target="_blank">moparisthebest.com</a>
  </header>
  <article class="onebox-body">
    <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/default-apple-touch-icon.png" class="thumbnail onebox-avatar" width="144" height="144">

<h3><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/" target="_blank">moparisthebest.com</a></h3>

<p>programming, irc, cars</p>


  </article>
  <div class="onebox-metadata">
    
    
  </div>
  <div style="clear: both"></div>
</aside>

<p>If you’d like to help please let me know, I’d appreciate that a lot! <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=6" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
<p>Finally onto the elephant in the topic, I’m polling the return of the reputation system, while this poll doesn’t determine anything it’s merely to grasp the communities view on the matter. The results will be available after the poll has expired, I’d suggest everyone vote.</p>
<p>Thanks <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=6" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
            </blockquote>
            <p>Posts: 34</p>
            <p>Participants: 23</p>
            <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/community-update-25-08-2015/553083">Read full topic</a></p>
          ]]></description>
          <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/community-update-25-08-2015/553083</link>
          <pubDate>Tue, 25 Aug 2015 00:35:46 +0000</pubDate>
          <discourse:topicPinned>No</discourse:topicPinned>
          <discourse:topicClosed>No</discourse:topicClosed>
          <discourse:topicArchived>No</discourse:topicArchived>
          <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-topic-553083</guid>
          <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/community-update-25-08-2015/553083.rss">Community Update [25/08/2015]</source>
        </item>
        <item>
          <title>[RESOLVED - DENIED] New Server Advertisement Mod</title>
          <dc:creator><![CDATA[@system system]]></dc:creator>
          <category>Community Suggestions</category>
          <description><![CDATA[
            <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/system">@system</a> wrote:</p>
            <blockquote>
              <p>The current moderator for that is John, and he was last active in November, 2014.<br>
<span class="bbcode-b">Nothing major</span>, but it’d be good if there was a new moderator for the Server Advertisements  <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=5" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"></p>
            </blockquote>
            <p>Posts: 6</p>
            <p>Participants: 6</p>
            <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/resolved-denied-new-server-advertisement-mod/552685">Read full topic</a></p>
          ]]></description>
          <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/resolved-denied-new-server-advertisement-mod/552685</link>
          <pubDate>Wed, 29 Jul 2015 13:17:24 +0000</pubDate>
          <discourse:topicPinned>No</discourse:topicPinned>
          <discourse:topicClosed>No</discourse:topicClosed>
          <discourse:topicArchived>No</discourse:topicArchived>
          <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-topic-552685</guid>
          <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/resolved-denied-new-server-advertisement-mod/552685.rss">[RESOLVED - DENIED] New Server Advertisement Mod</source>
        </item>
        <item>
          <title>Mopar Weekly (#7)</title>
          <dc:creator><![CDATA[@pure2ownage Pure_]]></dc:creator>
          <category>Community Suggestions</category>
          <description><![CDATA[
            <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/pure2ownage">@pure2ownage</a> wrote:</p>
            <blockquote>
              <p>[size=24pt]News (for the week 27/07/2015)[/size]</p>
<p>[size=18pt]<a href="https://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php/board,272.0.html" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">MoparScape Official Server</a>[/size]</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Sini makes server, crowd cheers!</span> (as sinisoul puts it)<br>
It has been publically announced for a while now so the board has been made public again. Make sure you <a href="https://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php/topic,671436.0.html" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">keep up</a> with it.</p>
<p>[hr]</p>
<p>[size=18pt]Game Development[/size]</p>
<p>[size=14pt]<a href="https://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php/topic,646683.msg4490365.html#msg4490365" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">Blackwake’s Recent Success</a> (by <a href="https://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php?action=profile;u=110175" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">Frell</a>)[/size]<br>
It seems that since the last update the game has found somewhat of a following. Some big streamers have demoed the game which has helped gain it a little buzz.<br>
If you didn’t catch the streams live you can always watch the VODs on twitch. The links to said streamers is in the thread, you just need to dig a little <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=5" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"></p>
<p>[hr]</p>
<p>[size=18pt]Games[/size]</p>
<p>[size=14pt]<a href="https://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php/topic,660374.msg4489991.html#msg4489991" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener"><span class="bbcode-b">play</span>rust</a> (by <a href="https://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php?action=profile;u=284102" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">Tom</a>)[/size]<br>
Recently a few MoparScapers decided to give it <span class="bbcode-i">real</span> good (ayy lmao) to Rust. Tom, Pure and Albi (amongst others) have been playing together for a while now and await any one of you who wishes to join them on their adventures!</p>
<p><img src="http://i.imgur.com/JkBbKin.png" alt width="400" height="300"> <img src="http://i.imgur.com/rvRse3i.png" alt width="400" height="300"> <img src="http://i.imgur.com/QEDItVT.png" alt width="400" height="300"></p>
<p>[hr]</p>
<p>[size=18pt]General Programming[/size]</p>
<p>[size=14pt]<a href="https://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php/topic,671253.0.html" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">Creating a 2d game map? (Brainstorming Ideas)</a> (by <a href="https://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php?action=profile;u=695663" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">my-swagger</a>)[/size]<br>
The community at its finest, brainstorming programming ideas. We love to see threads like this one.</p>
<p>[size=14pt]<a href="https://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php/topic,671381.0.html" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">Introduction to C++ Metaprogramming: Lists, apply, and lambda</a> (by <a href="https://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php?action=profile;u=505043" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">justaguy</a>)[/size]<br>
Justaguy is back with part two of his mini-series of tutorials on C++ meta-programming. If you read the first one you have only seen the tip of the iceberg - <a data-bbcode="true">enter now</a> into the power of C++!</p>
<p>[size=16pt]Java Programming[/size]</p>
<p>[size=14pt]<a href="https://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php/topic,671355.0.html" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">RS Voice Chat</a> (by <a href="https://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php?action=profile;u=547809" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">Rodgerwilco</a>)[/size]<br>
Some more brainstorming of ideas regarding how voice chat could be implemented within an RS server.</p>
<p>[hr]</p>
<p>[size=18pt]Senior Member Feature - <a href="https://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php?action=profile;u=31237" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">Lothy</a>[/size]<br>
This week we have managed to dig up <a href="https://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php?action=profile;u=31237" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">Lothy</a> - an RSC guru and ex-staff member!</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">The “before” MoparScape?</span><br>
There wasn’t really a ‘before’ so to speak. I was in high school at the time and addicted to the game. By chance I happened to stumble upon the website after someone mentioned private servers on another forum.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">What was the appeal of RuneScape to you?</span><br>
In hindsight I’m not sure. Probably the illusion of achievement that comes with progression in the game mixed with the social aspect. Having said that I wouldn’t actively participate in another MMORPG nowadays.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Why would you not participate in another MMORPG nowadays?</span><br>
It’s just a massive time sink.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Sidebar: Was you here when Kaitnieks was a thing?</span><br>
No, I wasn’t around for kaitnieks. I came across MoparScape and MoparIsTheBest late 2006, so I missed that boat.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">What were the first things you did on MoparScape?</span><br>
The same as every new guy that comes along really. I jumped into developing a server by grabbing one of the “bases” (CheezScape, Project 16, and TestScape IIRC) and hacking together example code.<br>
I think my first “innovation” was to get player immobilisation (for spells like entangle/ice barrage) working. It was through asking this question that I first met javacisnotrecognized (<em>^</em> on IRC). Except I also saw it as an opportunity to develop my programming skills for the sake of employment, so I studied the language as well.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">You mentioned triangle explicitly, why so?</span><br>
Oh, just because. We had some good times back in the day, with the occasional frivolous kickbannings from IRC. XD But yeah, he did try to help me with that one. It was a case of the blind leading the blind though.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">What did you think of the atmosphere in early MSCP, was it friendly, how were the ‘senior’ members, etc?</span><br>
I always found it fine. Mind you, as a new member it’s often quite impersonal anyway. You join and have a clean slate and that remains the case until you prove your worth. Then you either excel in the community or you make it clear that you’re not really worth having around. Many people over the years have bleated about so-called elitism. But what they don’t realise is that seeing the same questions over and over, and bearing witness to the same pitfalls, is tiring.<br>
A new guy poses a question or something, and to him it’s a novel idea that he has had and trying to resolve. The new guy however doesn’t appreciate the larger context of the community, and the fact that their ideas or problems mightn’t be so unique after all. That invariably frustrates some people, and ultimately leads to what some perceive as mean and unreasonable behaviour. Are they right about some users being mean? Yeah, sometimes. But I can emphasise with people who do get frustrated with new users.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">How did you manage to become a staff member, and later an Admin?</span><br>
Well, good question. If I had to summarise I would say that I was of good character and standing within the community, at least to the extent expected of forum staff. I started as a MoparScape moderator, did good work in that role and was asked to moderate both sites as a global moderator.<br>
At one point there was a guy who went by the alias The Real JDB (or something along those lines). He discovered that he could create new global moderator accounts and decided to do just that. Moparisthebest was unaware of this functionality and frankly the SMF team shouldn’t have had such functionality built into their forum software. So this guy went about creating maybe a half dozen other global moderator accounts for his buddies, and there was a bit of a mess. It culminated in me wildcard IP banning everyone until Moparisthebest could come online and resolve the issue.<br>
So I guess somewhere between that incident and receiving Administrator was when I proved myself credible and trustworthy.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Was there at any point power-struggles within MITB? IIRC you banned Ikiliki to that extent, mind elaborating?</span><br>
Well the situation with Ikiliki was that he wanted to have his own website. That’s fair enough, right, you can’t fault someone for that. But he leveraged his standing in the community, and his privileges as a staff member, to actively pursue MoparScape members and lead them to his site. I took issue with that. In my eyes it was a form of unjust profiteering from our community’s work. As you say, that particular story culminated in me removing him from the community.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">What are you known for in MoparScape now or perhaps a while ago?</span><br>
Well nowadays probably not much. I have RSC-related software on my <a href="http://github.com/Lothy" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">GitHub account</a> and that’s still there to this day. I haven’t contributed a great deal to the MoparClassic project but my own Elysium server is a functioning RSC game.<br>
In my hay-day I provided a few cool features. Things like combat zones and the ability to toggle combat modes within the game. That’s one of the more memorable ones anyway.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">What kind of work have you done regarding RSPS (public or private)?</span><br>
Nothing particularly outstanding. Silabsoft and I worked on HybridScape for a while privately but it never really had the impact we wanted. Elysium, as mentioned, is a working RSC server that was designed to provide a high performance and highly concurrent server underpinned by Netty. There’s now a single-threaded version as well which is more easy for programmers who aren’t sufficiently experienced with concurrent software development. I provide the occasional technical guidance to people as well.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">How did the Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles first draft you as Dongatello - aka “the real Dongatello”?</span><br>
Well the Dongatello costume was an 18th birthday present. There was an inside joke with a couple of friends about me not being “turtley” enough for the turtle club. This resulted in my very own turtle costume.<br>
It goes without saying that it’s good manners to use things you receive as gifts, so I did - I took my costume and put it on. This led to many laughs and one of my friends took photos on her phone. Of course it was a child-sized costume, so it was a tight fit. I can’t find a link to it. You used to be able to google ‘lothy’ or my full name to find a nice picture of my arse in a turtle outfit.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">How is your personal life going?</span><br>
My personal life is good. I work professionally as a software developer for the state government here and recently received a promotion to Senior Software Developer.  I work on a variety of software applications used across different government departments, such as software used by schools for managing students and software used by hospitals for reporting on patients who present with legally notifiable diseases. We also have our bastard child that nobody likes, which is a piece of software that property developers use for receiving approvals and submitting plans. It goes without saying that this particular application makes grown men cry.  Still forever alone, but it’s fine</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">What advice do you have for those who want to be software developers, any insight into the industry, maybe about working for the government too, hows the pay like, etc?</span><br>
If I had to make one suggestion when it comes to succeeding in any endeavour, including computer science, I would say read voraciously. Consume educational material like it’s going out of fashion.<br>
If you’re looking to be a software developer then my advice is to spend the time practicing. Practice means both reading and writing code, reading books about writing good code, and undertaking a variety of projects that cover the many aspects of computing. If you want to truly excel then, just like any craft, you’ll probably want to do your ten thousand hours to go from zero to hero.<br>
The industry is sometimes hard to describe. Here in Australia, from where I’m standing, it’s good. But there are many others who go on about the sky falling down, about how outsourcing is killing the local industry, and so on.<br>
I mentioned that I currently work in government. Australia has (or had) a two-speed economy driven by our mining boom. I moved to Canberra and took a government job because the company I worked for, which relied on mining clients, basically went under. My hometown essentially had two kinds of software industry: Mining related, and banking related. So that situation was untenable for a software developer coming out of university, and I had little choice but to move - thus my current position in government. It’s a nice job. I work hard, but I could probably get away with doing less. I won’t though because I play to win and want to climb the corporate ladder just for the sake of it.<br>
I wouldn’t necessarily recommend government or the public sector over the private sector though. If there’s one thing that can be said for sure, the grass is not always greener on the other side. Sometimes there’s cool stuff in the private sector, sometimes in the public sector. It depends more on the particular company you work for than the industry you choose.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">What is your advice to newcomers, particularly those who want to learn how to code?</span><br>
My advice to newcomers is to be aware of the credibility and standing of the material you consume. Like any educational material, not all software-related literature is equal. Some books are better than others, some online tutorial sites are better than others.<br>
Secondly, you need to branch out. Too many people seem to want to niche too soon, and while they become quite adept at solving particular problem domain they lack the more generalised skills to take an arbitrary problem and methodically solve it.<br>
I can’t stress enough that software development is the art of problem solving. It’s not just about languages, syntax, tooling and environments. Don’t lose sight of this fact.<br>
​And if you’re currently considering programming as a profession but haven’t quite made the jump from RSPS-specific software then I would strongly start thinking outside of the RSPS box.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Do you have any advice to programmers relating specifically to RSPS?</span><br>
RSPS stuff is fun. For me back in 2006 it was a blend of a game that I enjoyed and a new hobby that I enjoyed. Ultimately where you go with it is up to you. If it’s all about RuneScape and programming is just the means to the end then enjoy yourself and build your server. If it’s about RuneScape but writing the code is the part that matters then keep doing that too. If you’re playing 20 questions with the community then try to do so in a reasonable manner. People will like you a lot more, and want to help you a lot more, if you demonstrate that you’ve made the effort to overcome the hurdles yourself. Similarly, do your research - there’s a good chance that your question is not unique and has been resolved.<br>
But otherwise, just have fun. Finally, if you’ve happened upon programming through RSPS by chance and concluded that you could see yourself doing it professionally then make the leap from RSPS and take on other projects. Practice, practice, practice! Study hard, and consider some form of tertiary education. Depending on where you live you can probably get into IT without tertiary education. However it’s invariably a hard slog to climb the ladder in contemporary society without some form of certification.</p>
<p>[hr]</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Contributing</span><br>
I would like to remind everybody that the authoring of this weekly article can be done by anybody who wants to. You can either contribute a section or the entire article - contact <a href="https://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php?action=profile;u=284102" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">Tom</a> for more information.</p>
            </blockquote>
            <p>Posts: 7</p>
            <p>Participants: 7</p>
            <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/mopar-weekly-7/552657">Read full topic</a></p>
          ]]></description>
          <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/mopar-weekly-7/552657</link>
          <pubDate>Mon, 27 Jul 2015 16:24:10 +0000</pubDate>
          <discourse:topicPinned>No</discourse:topicPinned>
          <discourse:topicClosed>No</discourse:topicClosed>
          <discourse:topicArchived>No</discourse:topicArchived>
          <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-topic-552657</guid>
          <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/mopar-weekly-7/552657.rss">Mopar Weekly (#7)</source>
        </item>
        <item>
          <title>[RESOLVED - ACCEPTED] Removal of 20,000 character limit in some cases</title>
          <dc:creator><![CDATA[@asshole_rule asshole_rule]]></dc:creator>
          <category>Community Suggestions</category>
          <description><![CDATA[
            <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/asshole_rule">@asshole_rule</a> wrote:</p>
            <blockquote>
              <p>Well for basically ANY tutorial that I post, they all have too much code to be posted with code tags. So I end up always needing to use pastebin. It’s not a real problem, I just don’t see a reason to have the limit, in the tutorial section at least.</p>
<p>Examples:<br>
<aside class="onebox whitelistedgeneric">
  <header class="source">
      <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/uploads/default/original/2X/1/1f0dc167bcf798bdbd70b03bf0fd1bc836e54e1a.png" class="site-icon" width="32" height="32">
      <a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/" target="_blank">moparisthebest.com</a>
  </header>
  <article class="onebox-body">
    <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/default-apple-touch-icon.png" class="thumbnail onebox-avatar" width="144" height="144">

<h3><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/" target="_blank">moparisthebest.com</a></h3>

<p>programming, irc, cars</p>


  </article>
  <div class="onebox-metadata">
    
    
  </div>
  <div style="clear: both"></div>
</aside>
<br>
<aside class="onebox whitelistedgeneric">
  <header class="source">
      <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/uploads/default/original/2X/1/1f0dc167bcf798bdbd70b03bf0fd1bc836e54e1a.png" class="site-icon" width="32" height="32">
      <a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/" target="_blank">moparisthebest.com</a>
  </header>
  <article class="onebox-body">
    <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/default-apple-touch-icon.png" class="thumbnail onebox-avatar" width="144" height="144">

<h3><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/" target="_blank">moparisthebest.com</a></h3>

<p>programming, irc, cars</p>


  </article>
  <div class="onebox-metadata">
    
    
  </div>
  <div style="clear: both"></div>
</aside>
<br>
<aside class="onebox whitelistedgeneric">
  <header class="source">
      <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/uploads/default/original/2X/1/1f0dc167bcf798bdbd70b03bf0fd1bc836e54e1a.png" class="site-icon" width="32" height="32">
      <a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/" target="_blank">moparisthebest.com</a>
  </header>
  <article class="onebox-body">
    <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/default-apple-touch-icon.png" class="thumbnail onebox-avatar" width="144" height="144">

<h3><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/" target="_blank">moparisthebest.com</a></h3>

<p>programming, irc, cars</p>


  </article>
  <div class="onebox-metadata">
    
    
  </div>
  <div style="clear: both"></div>
</aside>
</p>
<p>And those are just the ones I remember needing to use pastebin for.</p>
<p>I wouldn’t be opposed to completely removing it, because I honestly don’t see the point. But if we can just remove it for sections which require a pretty big amount of text EG(Server tutorials, Server development, Server Help, Private server client hacking) it would be convenient.</p>
            </blockquote>
            <p>Posts: 48</p>
            <p>Participants: 16</p>
            <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/resolved-accepted-removal-of-20-000-character-limit-in-some-cases/552427">Read full topic</a></p>
          ]]></description>
          <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/resolved-accepted-removal-of-20-000-character-limit-in-some-cases/552427</link>
          <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jul 2015 16:33:31 +0000</pubDate>
          <discourse:topicPinned>No</discourse:topicPinned>
          <discourse:topicClosed>No</discourse:topicClosed>
          <discourse:topicArchived>No</discourse:topicArchived>
          <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-topic-552427</guid>
          <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/resolved-accepted-removal-of-20-000-character-limit-in-some-cases/552427.rss">[RESOLVED - ACCEPTED] Removal of 20,000 character limit in some cases</source>
        </item>
        <item>
          <title>Mopar Weekly (#6)</title>
          <dc:creator><![CDATA[@pure2ownage Pure_]]></dc:creator>
          <category>Community Suggestions</category>
          <description><![CDATA[
            <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/pure2ownage">@pure2ownage</a> wrote:</p>
            <blockquote>
              <p>[size=24pt]News (for the week 06/07/2015)[/size]</p>
<p>[size=18pt]General Programming[/size]</p>
<p>[size=14pt]<a href="https://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php/topic,671203.0.html" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">Increasing your productivity by hot swapping classes</a> (by <a href="https://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php?action=profile;u=28549" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">Taharok</a>)[/size]<br>
Taharok was experimenting with JRebel alternatives and the like and stumbled onto this piece of code. This generated a discussion about class hot-swapping and its uses (such as updating classes on the fly, i.e. during runtime).</p>
<p>[size=14pt]<a href="https://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php/topic,671206.0.html" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">Introduction to C++ Metaprogramming: Basics</a> (by <a href="https://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php?action=profile;u=505043" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">justaguy</a>)[/size]<br>
This week justaguy decided to post about meta-programming in C++. Make sure you check it out and contribute to the discussion of the shenanigans which ensued!</p>
<p>[hr]</p>
<p>[size=18pt]Server Downloads[/size]</p>
<p>[size=14pt]<a href="https://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php/topic,671275.0.html" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">Asteria 3.0</a> (by <a href="https://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php?action=profile;u=490965" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">lare96</a>)[/size]<br>
The long wait for Asteria 3.0 is finally over. Lare has reworked some of the design in favour of stability and has added some new content and patches.<br>
We have seen him grow over the duration of this project which is very sweet to witness! If you are a user of the previous version(s) make sure you update to this one as soon as possible!</p>
<p><img src="http://i.imgur.com/d7vJdQJ.png" alt width="400" height="200"> <img src="http://i.imgur.com/VdjJoL2.png" alt width="400" height="200"> <img src="http://i.imgur.com/FrXz4Yl.png" alt width="400" height="200"> <img src="http://i.imgur.com/iORj3If.png" alt width="400" height="200"></p>
<p>[hr]</p>
<p>[size=18pt]Server Tutorials[/size]</p>
<p>[size=14pt]<a href="https://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php/topic,671172.0.html" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">Custom Music Player for 317 clients</a> (by <a href="https://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php?action=profile;u=695663" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">my-swagger</a>)[/size]<br>
My-swagger contributed a snippet which allows you to load music for the 317 client from a raw input folder. It’s useful for those who don’t know how to use the cache properly.<br>
Make sure you check it out if you have issues implementing it the correct way yourself, he pasted the entire code-base to make its usage as easy as possible for newbies <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=5" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
<p>[hr]</p>
<p>[size=18pt]RSC Server Tutorials[/size]<br>
It was apparent that the RSC boards were not getting any love in the news posts due to the lack of activity <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/frowning.png?v=5" title=":frowning:" class="emoji" alt=":frowning:"><br>
This all changed when Rodgerwilco decided to post a couple of snippets to add some regularly wanted features to RSC, make sure you implement them to give your server the edge <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/wink.png?v=5" title=":wink:" class="emoji" alt=":wink:"></p>
<p>[size=14pt]<a href="https://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php/topic,671223.0.html" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">[Release] Notes</a> (by <a href="https://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php?action=profile;u=547809" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">Rodgerwilco</a>)[/size]<br>
This snippet adds a sprite and functionality for noted items.</p>
<p>[size=14pt]<a href="https://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php/topic,671222.0.html" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">[Release] 99 Capes</a> (by <a href="https://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php?action=profile;u=547809" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">Rodgerwilco</a>)[/size]<br>
This snippet adds skillcapes to RSC - something regularly requested!</p>
<p>[hr]</p>
<p>[size=18pt]Senior Member Feature - <a href="https://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php?action=profile;u=28549" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">Taharok</a> (aka Avail)[/size]<br>
This week we have managed to get a hold of <a href="https://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php?action=profile;u=28549" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">Taharok</a> - a game programmer and ex-staff member! This interview contains a lot of interesting forum history so buckle up!</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">The “before” MoparScape?</span><br>
Hmm, before MoparScape…  I suppose around early 2005 it starts for me. I was introduced to RuneScape by a friend of mine and I became hooked pretty fast. This led me to wanting to learn programming so I could build my own game, since that’s the coolest thing ever at that age!<br>
So I started reading a dated C++ book from '97. It was a horrible book and it definitely didn’t stick for me at the time.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">What was the appeal of RuneScape to you?</span><br>
I’m not really sure. It was just an interesting game with a lot of fun things to do. It was more interesting than any other game I had played up to that point. I wasn’t really used to RPGs before then.<br>
But at one point around Fall 2006 I was getting a bit bored with RS. I recalled my brother’s friend telling me once about World of Warcraft private servers. I wondered if there were RS private servers, and I searched Google. First stop was MoparScape.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">What kind of game did you have in mind when you began to learn how to write games? What were your influences?</span><br>
Well at that time, the game I was “inventing” was basically just RuneScape with a lot of changes, haha. I dunno, I wasn’t a super creative child as far as coming up with new ideas is concerned. But I had a lot of fun looking at RS and thinking about how cool it would be to change it. Thinking up ideas was more interesting than figuring out how to do it at that point.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">What were the first things you did on MoparScape?</span><br>
I perused the forums for a few months without registering, I just wanted to try and figure out how this whole thing worked. It took a while to figure out how to play the servers and even longer on how to run one and change them.<br>
I can’t even remember what the servers were called back then. They were pretty small though. I think Xerocheez was a huge influence at that point and everyone kind of just used his code. I eventually created my own server called FreeScape and decided to register on MoparScape to advertise it. After that, I started helping people with their server issues.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">What kind of skills did you gain while creating Fre? Do you have anything in hindsight you would have done differently?</span><br>
Haha, I don’t know if I gained any lasting skills. I learned how to throw together spaghetti code, compile it, realize it doesn’t work and then do it over again. I had no real background in programming before MoparScape, so I was learning programming alongside this horrific private server scene.<br>
I don’t think I would have done anything differently, though. I became keenly aware of how bad the code was once I started venturing to <a href="http://moparisthebest.com" rel="nofollow noopener">moparisthebest.com</a> and that was good for me. Seeing the juxtaposition is what made me so critical of my own code, which led me to care so much more about doing a good job.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">What are you known for in MoparScape now?</span><br>
No clue honestly. I don’t really talk to people about what I’m known for. I’d be surprised if many people even remember me anymore. I stepped down as admin a few years ago now.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">What kind of work have you done regarding RSPS (public or private)? you said you created Fre did you ever release it?</span><br>
FreeScape was released, but it sort of got absorbed into the monlothic chimera that servers were at that time. This is back when there was no server organization, thus all class files were at the default package. There was a client.java file which was so large that it actually sometimes led to the compiler not being able to compile it due to some methods being too large to compile. Everything sort of got absorbed into one “base” at that time and people would make a few changes and re-release it under a new name. That pattern hasn’t really changed over the years.<br>
Other work includes a really obnoxious batch file I wrote called the “perfect compiler” which still tends to haunt me over the years. It was a batch file to avoid people having to modify their path to include the Java runtime. I think I tend to be known for that, since I always had the “contact mod taharok” echo in there.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Did you ever feel competition from the “mendacious nitwit” mdog’s compiler? <a href="https://community.oracle.com/thread/1520983?start=0&amp;tstart=0" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">Reference.</a></span><br>
Haha, that is a funny story actually. He just took mine and renamed it without changing my name in any of the batch echos.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Could you elaborate on your programming prowess, what kind of stuff do you do now?</span><br>
Well, I’m currently interning at a company and this has been going on since last year. I just received my undergraduate degree from DigiPen focusing on software engineering in game development.<br>
I have experience working in a wide variety of topics of software engineering, including game dev, web development and production server stacks.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">What do you think about the current state of MoparScape, any observations or suggestions? i.e. People have been trying to ‘revive’ the site or otherwise diagnose the reason why traffic has decreased so much.</span><br>
I stand by my <a href="https://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php/topic,670595.msg4484750.html#msg4484750" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">post</a> on this as I think it covers the answer well.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">How does your activity fare on MoparScape nowadays?</span><br>
I stopped being active for about two years now. I poped in and out, but once I got past Freshman year at DigiPen, I did not have enough time to do anything on the forums. I think it was the summer after that I resigned.<br>
I started being more active in the last few weeks because I’m in a temporary living situation and often bored; it gives me something to do and is close to socializing with people. Plus, sometimes people post interesting programming things. Not too often anymore, though. <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/frowning.png?v=5" title=":frowning:" class="emoji" alt=":frowning:"></p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">How did you become a staff member and establish your position in the community?</span><br>
As I mentioned earlier, my rough experiences of trying to learn programming and private servers at the same time led me to realize it’s hard to do for beginners. Hence, people had a lot of questions and I wanted to help them. Once you answer the same question enough times you begin to see a pattern. This led me to the tutorials section of the site, which was exceedingly popular then. It was getting very run down around October, 2006 though. People were posting a ton of spam, prawns, flaming people etc.<br>
You have to understand that the staffing model in 2006 was very, very different than it is now. There weren’t many staff members and they didn’t stick around for long. Nor did they usually care at all about MoparScape (which has always required the most moderation).<br>
After writing a few tutorials that started becoming popular, I decided I didn’t want to put up with the spamming anymore (report to moderator only goes so far…). So I emailed Starblaster100 at the time (admin) and he made me a board moderator of tutorials and I turned it around.  It’s up to you if you want to dive deeper into the staffing history of MoparScape; I have years of stuff to talk about there <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=5" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"> I was a board moderator over tutorials and I ended up rewriting the rules for it, etc.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">What proceeded to cement you as an administrator?</span><br>
So I did that (what was mentioned last post) for a couple of months. Then at the end of December 2006, a few other forum members were fed up with the garbage of the site overall. Moparisthebest decided to create a new staff position which was essentially a global moderator across all MoparScape boards. I was among the first to be added to this, along with God of Ikiliki and I think a third person I don’t remember currently.<br>
Then many years passed by, a lot of drama, and a lot of power changing. I sort of took charge on running the MoparScape moderators once God of Ikiliki was banned and Moparisthebest respected my decisions on a lot of stuff during those years.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">For those who aren’t up to date with the forum’s history, can you elaborate on who Ikiliki was and why he got banned? Preceded or followed by this said drama?</span><br>
Eventually, Lothy and Niall were made administrators and other noteworthy MITB members were promoted to global moderator (GM).  I think it was around then Mopar asked me to go to GM as well. I think Tico was GM before me, though. He was the other major moparscape moderator earlier on.<br>
Ikiliki rose in popularity on the forum doing a lot of work with his own private server. People seemed to really enjoy it and they respected all that he had to say. I believe he was Dutch so there was some translation barrier there.  As a result, he got flamed pretty badly in <span class="hashtag">#mopar</span> (IRC), on <a href="http://moparisthebest.com" rel="nofollow noopener">moparisthebest.com</a>, etc. To be fair, so did I and the rest of the MoparScape staff, but Ikiliki got it worse I think.<br>
Then there was a bit of a power play, but I honestly can’t remember the details right now. All I remember is he did something in response to all the hate that ended up going against his position in the community and Lothy banned him I think. He ended up being very angry toward the community for many years after that. I was able to make up with him later on, but it was an unfortuante series of events that shouldn’t have happened.<br>
note: This is expanded upon in next week’s interview - so make sure you catch that!</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">May you also elaborate on Tico’s role? He hasn’t been around for a while unfortunately.</span><br>
Tico was one of the most amazing staff members we ever had. Tom actually reminds me a lot of him. He was extremely active, helpful, and patient. He rose through the ranks faster than anyone I remember and he wasn’t power hungry. He also was respected quickly across both sites, but eventually his patience seemed to wear off after some of the <span class="hashtag">#mopar</span> stuff started getting to him, not to mention the day-in day-out unsolvable problems of MoparScape. He eventually became inactive and later resigned.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">What kind of <span class="hashtag">#mopar</span> stuff?</span><br>
Oh, nothing in particular. People on MITB just loved to flame MoparScape moderators though. Despite them being douchebags about it, it was sort of funny in retrospect. We were young kids hell bent on moderating and keeping the forum clean. They were just people who were hanging out and weren’t as serious as us.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">And what would these day-in, day-out unsolvable problems of MoparScape be?</span><br>
There was always a scalability issue. We didn’t have enough hands on the staff to manage all the problems that were going on. There was the aggression issue. MoparScapers that thought they knew stuff would be overly aggressive towards newcomers, arguing they shouldn’t be spoonfed. There was the helping issue. More people were asking for help than receiving it, many more. There was clarification issues. Tutorials being written weren’t helping enough people. There were security concerns, both with server downloads and advertised servers. Then there was just plain old spam and flaming.<br>
Too many things for the small staff to manage and we ended up doing some ridiculous things to try and fix them, but never successfully. I think we just eventually drove too many people from the site, possibly leading to what it is now. I’m not sure.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Can you speak a little of Starblaster100 since you mentioned him earlier? He has faded away <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/frowning.png?v=5" title=":frowning:" class="emoji" alt=":frowning:"></span><br>
I think he was one of the most active admins the site has seeen. He designed the first staff structure and created most of the forum layout. He was an admin on kaitnieks and a website that post-dated SCAR, but I can’t remember what it’s called at the moment. We felt like he was driven out of the community due to hate from <span class="hashtag">#mopar</span>, but he had a thicker skin than that. There was some strange drama and he ended up creating a shadow admin account, then Mopar banned him. We really have no clue why he did that, though.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">How do you feel about your time as a staff member? e.g. proud, happy</span><br>
It was life-changing, I think, and a good experience (not necessarily positive). I’m glad I did it, but I’m not really proud or happy about any of the things I did. I sort of became emotionally dulled with any of my accomplishments as staff.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">How is your personal life going? You mentioned you got a degree recently?</span><br>
Good, I’m currently contributing to an open-source project called Oppia, which aims to provide a personal tutoring experience to people, helping them learn better and be able to learn anything. I think it’s a huge game changer for the world. Besides that, I’m just pursuing full time employment and seeing where that goes.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Did you enjoy your CS course at uni, any insight into the life of an undergrad?</span><br>
Try to look at every topic as interesting and something you can pull something from. Universities are filled with sparse and high-level pieces of information that are supposed to form some sort of cohesive picture. They don’t succeed at this all the time, but they are much more effective at teaching the overall picture when the student is actually trying to figure out how everything relates together. This goes pretty far in not skipping classes, falling asleep, etc. If CS is something you really want to pursue, then it starts with your first day as an undergraduate.<br>
Actively pursue it, always. Even after you graduate; becoming a Computer Scientist is a life-long pursuit and it never ends. It’s the pursuit that’s interesting. And again, do not feel bad about asking questions. <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=5" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">What is your advice to those pursuing degrees in CS/internships/working in CS?</span><br>
Hmmm… Pretty much everything that you need to learn to do a job can be learned without a degree, but it’s really hard to get the structure or support of a degree. I think both are necessary to be successful in CS. Having some sort of structure to push your limits of what you can learn while also pushing your own limits by going beyond your classes, researching things on your own, and always working on projects will only lead to success; plus, it’s great for the resume.<br>
I think people should pursue CS if it is something they love or are passionate about; all else seems to follow after that. It’s pretty easy to experiment and get deep into some interesting topic. Follow your interests and see where they take you.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">What is your advice to newcomers, particularly those who want to learn how to code?</span><br>
Ah, a topic I debate commonly with my brother and others. I’m still working on a good answer to that question, but here’s what I have now: I think people just need a reason to code. Once you have some sort of motivation to learn something, just continuing along that thread will do wonders for you. Ah, and don’t be afraid to ask questions. Being prideful will destroy your ability to thrive.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Do you have any advice to programmers relating specifically to RSPS? i.e. a cool design pattern you saw somewhere or a nifty library?</span><br>
Sure, get out of RSPS and go do something that is either more interesting or more useful. RSPS strangles developers.</p>
            </blockquote>
            <p>Posts: 37</p>
            <p>Participants: 23</p>
            <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/mopar-weekly-6/552362">Read full topic</a></p>
          ]]></description>
          <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/mopar-weekly-6/552362</link>
          <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jul 2015 22:02:50 +0000</pubDate>
          <discourse:topicPinned>No</discourse:topicPinned>
          <discourse:topicClosed>No</discourse:topicClosed>
          <discourse:topicArchived>No</discourse:topicArchived>
          <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-topic-552362</guid>
          <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/mopar-weekly-6/552362.rss">Mopar Weekly (#6)</source>
        </item>
        <item>
          <title>Mopar Weekly (#5)</title>
          <dc:creator><![CDATA[@pure2ownage Pure_]]></dc:creator>
          <category>Community Suggestions</category>
          <description><![CDATA[
            <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/pure2ownage">@pure2ownage</a> wrote:</p>
            <blockquote>
              <p>[size=24pt]News (for the week 29/06/2015)[/size]</p>
<p>[size=18pt]General Discussion[/size]</p>
<p>[size=14pt]<a href="https://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php?topic=671102.0" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">US Same-Sex Marriage Legal Nationwide</a> (by <a href="https://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php?action=profile;u=547809" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">Rodgerwilco</a>)[/size]<br>
In recent news, the U.S. federal government decided to legalise same-sex marriage throughout! Make sure you contribute to the discussion we have been having at some point.<br>
Some feel like it’s a decision that should not have been taken by the federal government but rather on a state-by-state basis.</p>
<p>[hr]</p>
<p>[size=18pt]Game Development[/size]</p>
<p>[size=14pt]<a href="https://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php/topic,646683.0.html" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">Blackwake</a> (by <a href="https://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php?action=profile;u=110175" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">Frell</a>)[/size]<br>
Frell has been working on his game for a while now and implied in a post that it should be included in the news, so why not! His thread gets updated often so make sure you keep up if you aren’t already. His game is a pirate PVP multiplayer, one with ship battle and weapon physics - it sums up to some really entertaining and unique gameplay.</p>
<p><img src="http://i.imgur.com/fvGJHDP.png" alt width="400" height="200"> <img src="http://i.imgur.com/Qi6zh5m.png" alt width="400" height="200"> <img src="http://i.imgur.com/CkVVyKI.png" alt width="400" height="200"> <img src="http://i.imgur.com/QI0AnsR.png" alt width="400" height="200"></p>
<p>[hr]</p>
<p>[size=18pt]Server and Client Development Showoff[/size]</p>
<p>[size=14pt]<a href="https://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php/topic,671121.0.html" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">Mopar - Emulation Framework</a> (by <a href="https://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php?action=profile;u=449007" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">sini</a>)[/size]<br>
Sini has been working on a separate official server from David for a while which you might have caught a glimpse of on the last <a href="https://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php/topic,671061.0.html" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">member feature</a>.<br>
He has done enough to be able to show off the code now. Make sure you check out the design because it seems to show some promise and sini is definitely proud of it! He has recently finished up the cache updating and thus a cache library which you can find on github.</p>
<p>[size=14pt]<a href="https://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php/topic,668337.0.html" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">Skarred Lands</a> (by <a href="https://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php?action=profile;u=341531" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">sk8rdude461</a>)[/size]<br>
Sk8rdude has been making consistent progress on his server for months now, so it’s definitely worth a mention. He suggested that it was far off a beta stage however he has plenty of updates to read through.</p>
<p><img src="http://i.imgur.com/9nZgSdP.png" alt width="400" height="200"> <img src="http://i.imgur.com/tYBzAbS.png" alt width="400" height="200"> <img src="http://i.imgur.com/t2AZVHJ.png" alt width="400" height="200"></p>
<p>[hr]</p>
<p>[size=18pt]Web Design/Development[/size]</p>
<p>[size=14pt]<a href="https://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php/topic,671160.msg4488336.html" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">An Introduction to PHP</a> (by <a href="https://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php?action=profile;u=698227" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">EcoPS GM</a>)[/size]<br>
Wow a full tutorial! It’s still being redesigned but Eco did a wonderful job on the basics to PHP. This is definitely recommended to new programmers who want to dabble in a bit of server-sided stuff. It’s quite thorough and easy to follow.</p>
<p>[size=14pt]<a href="https://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php/topic,670894.0.html" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">Extending JavaScript using sweet.js</a> (by <a href="https://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php?action=profile;u=505043" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">justaguy</a>)[/size]<br>
Never fear it’s here!! Make sure you check out the syntactical “sugar” of sweet.js shown off by justaguy! It makes your stay with JS much more pleasant <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/wink.png?v=5" title=":wink:" class="emoji" alt=":wink:"></p>
<p>[hr]</p>
<p>[size=18pt]Senior Member Feature - <a href="https://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php?action=profile;u=340939" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">t4</a>[/size]<br>
This week we have managed to get a hold of <a href="https://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php?action=profile;u=340939" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">t4</a> - a competent veteran programmer among our ranks.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Initiating dialogue like a true autist using secure TLS handshake</span></p>
<blockquote> ur being drafted for the moparscape news ~~~
 ~~~ ok</blockquote>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">The “before” MoparScape?</span><br>
I hung out on <a href="http://www.swiftirc.net/" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">SwiftIRC</a> with a few RuneScape clans, this was back in 2005 or so. Around that time i got slightly bored of the grind and felt like cheating.<br>
I remember trying different software like SCAR and some other bad color detection bots. That didn’t work out too well. After a while I gave up and found private servers, I lurked MoparScape and other related forums and eventually got my own going.<br>
At that point I started to learn Java already haven worked with children’s languages like QBASIC. Then around (I think) 2008 I decided to register on MITB. Hence me being here now!</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">What was the appeal of RuneScape to you? It was clearly powerful enough to motivate you to learn to program.</span><br>
A lot of my friends at school used to play and we would compete against each other for wealth and stats. I was probably one of the last to abandon ship because I got the farthest.<br>
I played from about 2003 to 2011 or so with large breaks between. Near the end it was just me proving to myself I could accomplish the prestige (and by that time I had written custom private bots with some help).<br>
It was a curiosity that fuelled my endeavors of how far could I push by the botting method before getting banned. The game became more about botting than playing the game. A meta-game if you will.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">What were the first things you did on MoparScape?</span><br>
If I recall I mostly talked in the debate, general and operating systems child boards of MITB. I wasn’t as competent a programmer as I am now and I knew I would get my ass wrecked by some of the older members.<br>
I tried starting a MITB linux group (LUG). I was very fond of learning about linux and systems engineering stuff back then.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">How did you end up on IRC?</span><br>
I jumped on IRC around the time I registered on the forums, it seemed like the best way to become a part of the MITB community.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">What are you known for in MoparScape now?</span><br>
Don’t know really, most people probably think I’m an asshole. To answer the question more directly, probably my posts in the general programming child board. I’d post more, but the forum has been a little dead in those sections. <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/frowning.png?v=5" title=":frowning:" class="emoji" alt=":frowning:"> . I’d love to see those sections turn into a stackoverflow.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">What kind of work have you done regarding RSPS (public or private)? I know you had documented some of the 377 protocol, etc.</span><br>
I’ve written a few server bases in the past and was a big fan of using Netty for Java. I’ve written some basic proof of concept C servers, but never bothered releasing any.<br>
The only thing that saw the light of day that has any sort of impact is my work documenting the 377 protocol (one of my favorite revisions). An older member, whom I’m not sure wants to be mention, was kind enough to supply me with a near completely refactored 377 client.<br>
I also recall writing a deobfuscator for J-Shrink (lol). It was always fun running that on the shitty Java botnets kids used to distribute here.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Could you elaborate on your programming prowess, since you haven’t displayed it too much on the forums?</span><br>
I’ve been programming in Java for a long time and as I already mentioned had an early start with procedural languages. Shortly after Java I picked up on Python, C, and C++ and around that time enrolled in a Computer Science program at university.<br>
Since then I have completed the degree. Over the years I have seen many different technologies, languages, and paradigms that I can’t even begin to list. Some academic favorites include Haskell, x86 and MIPS assembly, algorithms, and operating systems design.<br>
I’ve also held many internships positions at various international companies. I am currently employed full time post-graduation on a research and development team.<br>
I specialize mostly with C and C++ programming on Linux platforms and am known to be anal about code correctness, documentation, and optimization.<br>
If you are interesting in picking up C and C++ the right way, I highly recommend reading K&amp;R C and Effective C++.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">How is your personal life going, you mentioned you got a degree recently? etc</span><br>
Great, I’ve got my own place, a few cars, great entertainment system that spans the whole house, etc. I love work.<br>
I love the people there and the stuff I am able to work on (a lot of super scalale C++ server software that span many nodes and is able to eat hexa-core CPUs and hundreds of gigabytes of memory). I also love the benefits of being a software engineer.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">May you expand on these benefits? Surely that includes playboy bunnies?</span><br>
Comfortable work environment, freedom to go out to lunch, to come in/leave when I want, to take off when I want, and of course the pay. The stipulation is of course you need to deliver</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">What is your advice to newcomers, particularly those who want to learn how to code?</span><br>
Don’t try learning from RSPS. It’s okay for it to spark your interest, but I suggest learning software architecting and a language before you sit down and go for the gold.<br>
There is a lot involved in creating scalable, efficient, and readable software. Hacking the client doesn’t lend itself to the aforementioned pitfall, so I’d recommend checking that out. There’s a lot to learn there and you just might spark interest in other members.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Do you have any advice to programmers relating specifically to RSPS? i.e. a cool design pattern you saw somewhere or a nifty library?</span><br>
A trick for developing a C++ server would be using the select() system call to allow for a non-blocking accept/recv loop (meaning you can accept new player connections and read incoming data from existing players synchronously).<br>
How select() works is it tells you when a given socket is ready. So you could pass the socket (file descriptor) to an event callback to produce a design similar to Netty.<br>
Combine that with some sexy C++11 features like threading and atomic variables and you’re well on your way to do some asynchronous processing (like player updating, server events, etc). If you’re interested in POSIX networking I highly suggest checking out <a href="http://beej.us/guide/bgnet/output/html/multipage/index.html" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">this</a>.</p>
<p>You could use Protobuf to declare language independent structure that get sent over the network (packets, like one of the <a href="https://github.com/moparisthebest/rswiki/wiki/317-Protocol#stage-3-client---server" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">login blocks</a>).<br>
There is an official tutorial/guide provided by Google for <a href="https://developers.google.com/protocol-buffers/docs/tutorials" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">C++, Java, and Python</a>.</p>
            </blockquote>
            <p>Posts: 17</p>
            <p>Participants: 10</p>
            <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/mopar-weekly-5/552241">Read full topic</a></p>
          ]]></description>
          <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/mopar-weekly-5/552241</link>
          <pubDate>Tue, 30 Jun 2015 22:00:27 +0000</pubDate>
          <discourse:topicPinned>No</discourse:topicPinned>
          <discourse:topicClosed>No</discourse:topicClosed>
          <discourse:topicArchived>No</discourse:topicArchived>
          <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-topic-552241</guid>
          <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/mopar-weekly-5/552241.rss">Mopar Weekly (#5)</source>
        </item>
        <item>
          <title>Mopar Weekly (#4)</title>
          <dc:creator><![CDATA[@pure2ownage Pure_]]></dc:creator>
          <category>Community Suggestions</category>
          <description><![CDATA[
            <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/pure2ownage">@pure2ownage</a> wrote:</p>
            <blockquote>
              <p>[size=24pt]News (for the week 22/06/2015)[/size]</p>
<p>[size=18pt]<a href="https://rswiki.moparisthebest.com/" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">RS Wiki</a> Rework[/size]<br>
The recent work on the Wiki hasn’t been finalised yet, so please be patient while we sort it all out!</p>
<p>[hr]</p>
<p>[size=18pt]Game Development[/size]</p>
<p>It seems that recently our game development board has taken off quite a bit, hosting projects such as <a href="https://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php/topic,646683.0.html" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">Blackwake</a> and <a href="https://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php/topic,669617.0.html" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">Codename::World</a>.<br>
This week was no exception to the recent trend of activity!</p>
<p>[size=14pt]<a href="https://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php/topic,670898.0.html" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">Da Magic Schoolbus</a> (by <a href="https://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php?action=profile;u=2685" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">Tree</a>)[/size]<br>
Tree recently made a small game demo to mess around with C and OpenGL. He gave us a screenshot to highlight his accomplishment, make sure you check it out and say rude things about him <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/wink.png?v=5" title=":wink:" class="emoji" alt=":wink:"></p>
<p><img src="http://i.imgur.com/Tz66zPT.png" alt width="400" height="200"></p>
<p>[size=14pt]<a href="https://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php/topic,670672.0.html" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">Shard Master 3D</a> (by <a href="https://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php?action=profile;u=635209" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">Limits</a>)[/size]<br>
Another member who has been messing with the RuneScape Classic client recently is Limits. He has managed to create a game kind of based on RSC (the general consensus) which is still in development.<br>
He is making rapid progress on it so I would advise you all to bookmark his thread! He now also has a link to a demo in his thread.</p>
<p><img src="http://i.imgur.com/0Y71s22.png" alt width="400" height="200"> <img src="http://i.imgur.com/DrJHWfo.png" alt width="400" height="200"></p>
<p>[hr]</p>
<p>[size=18pt]<span class="bbcode-s">Senior</span> Member Feature - <a href="https://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php?action=profile;u=449007" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">sinisoul</a>[/size]<br>
This week we have managed to get a hold of <a href="https://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php?action=profile;u=449007" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">sinisoul</a> - the co-developer of the official server. We have tons of server updates within this member feature!</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">The “before” MoparScape?</span><br>
I joined Moparscape about 5 years, before Moparscape I honestly wasn’t into programming. I touched on Alice (a 3D Java game environment) a bit. But beyond that I had no programming knowledge.<br>
I was just a kid coming out of middle school, for those of you who don’t live in the US I was about 13 at the time. I played sports, particularly Hockey and was just aspiring to be an engineer. I didn’t get involved with Moparscape/MITB until I played a server and thought “Wow I really want to make one too!”.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">How did you find MoparScape/MITB and what were the first things you did on here?</span><br>
I actually didn’t get very involved in Moparscape until The Wanderer, a friend of mine, and I were shooting crap about how it was better than r-l. I decided to branch out and joined!<br>
I was involved with the r-l community for the first 3 years of my time in the RSPS scene. Moparscape drew me in because it’s a more niche community. It has a lot of interesting characters and of course it’s the birthplace of modern RS emulation/botting.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">You mentioned you spent a lot of time on r-l, what kind of stuff did you do there? Anything interesting?</span><br>
On r-l no, I don’t think I did anything worth mentioning. I spent my first 4 years getting a good grasp on Java and a lot of the projects I did fell into obscurity.<br>
But then I found a passion for developing bases and I spent a lot of time trying to be innovative. A lot of it felt like wasted time, but I learned a lot about designing server applications and applications in general.<br>
I left r-l about two years ago because of some turmoil I had with Ikiliki. As much as I wanted to help the community he prioritised his top-list and would neglect the forums. He banned me, and a few others whom I’d consider knowledgeable members.<br>
I’m still banned there - to this day! I guess that’s why I never go back even though I had a lot of friends and good memories there. So all in all the politics turned me off. I much prefer the way the administration at Mopar handles their behavioral expectations and runs the community.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">What are you known for in Moparscape now?</span><br>
WELL. I am the curator of the original Moparscape server source. I guess that’s something. People more or less associate my name with “failed projects” and “can’t finish a project”. Well hell, I can’t disagree! My span of knowledge about emulation however is vast. I think in the recent year I’ve nailed down some very efficient emulation strategies. All topped off with my work on deciphering the the client to support these ideas. Shoutout to the Jmods who post Runescript! A lot of that information is very valuable to understanding a working approach to how you should write content. Which I consider the what you should invest most of your development time in.<br>
Back when we were in a tad bit of infancy I wrote plenty of articles detailing some protocols and file structures that are still on the Wiki today. I think only a few people can rival or come close to the amount of RS client hacking experience I have. Those being of course Veer (super), Method, Speljohan and MITB. All whom I respect greatly and thank for their help with filling in blanks I couldn’t figure out on my client hacking adventures.<br>
All of my “failures” actually re-appear in projects, however the priority of which shift constantly and as my interests change. I understand a point where I need to throw in the towel and reapproach a project from a different angle which I think is where people draw that conclusion. In the new server base you will be seeing an accumulation of my past projects this last few years (content system, system oriented design, scripting).</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">What news can you tell us about the new server? David is working on a distinct server too and what about your current progress?</span><br>
That is a long story and history which I’m sure a lot of people may have followed, however if you didn’t it boils down to this: I was approached a few years back to use my ScapeEmulator derivative for the official server. I told David from the get go that I had rushed plenty of features and didn’t expect it to be of the quality I’d expect an official server to be. He put a ton of work into it though and I’m very happy he did! We had an alpha which was a success and from there interest sort of tapered off.<br>
I wanted this project to be a revival of Moparscape as a whole, and I had a certain idea of how we’d get there. I wanted for the source to be an example of a well designed platform that people could use generally and my derivative didn’t provide that. I was given the chance to revisit and redesign everything, and I’m currently doing that.<br>
The current source is usable, but no one except David is working on it. I have a new design in place. I’m currently hammering out the kinks to make sure people can develop for it efficiently.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">So, you were caught on the forum talking about your implementation of protobufs, how will this affect the server you are currently designing?</span><br>
I’ve been eyeing protobuf for quite some time, and I think it’s important to mention I’ve also been eyeing gRPC (Google RPC framework) which uses protobuf to encode and decode messages over HTTP.<br>
I was toying with this in my recent design because I wanted to separate the role of responsibility for services which to give some background any Runescape emulation platform must feature nuances of the updating, game, and login services . However it doesn’t have to specifically be designed to be a service container. The result in a service-oriented design and a PI server is the same except obviously a service-oriented design is easier to manage and develop as a whole. I’m sure most of you have experience those growing pains! At least once or twice.<br>
Apollo is the best example of a base that first tried to organize specific server responsibilities by their services and services client sessions based upon indicated interest. It paved the way for this new way of thinking I foster today, however this current design for the official server was aimed at creating separate applications for each service. That’s not a bad practice but recently I took a new direction and instead worked on a service-oriented framework where the communication layer could be dictated by an internal application or communicating over sockets, even both if you needed to.<br>
I may implement gRPC to wrap services, however it’s still up in the air. I’m more worried about getting the gears in motion so people can develop content, login, save player profiles, and obviously connect to the server before I even worry about that but that may be included in the process somewhere in between. It just depends on what I logically find fit to support.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">You were messing around with the bootstrapping for scripting a little earlier, care to elaborate on how that system will work?</span><br>
With this design I’ve drawn a lot of inspiration from NodeJS and Redis. However of course both are not applicable in a 1:1 abstraction for a server. For all services, you submit requests with a callback. After the request is a process which updates the internal state of the service (for applicable status conditions) you receive a response and further process it to chain together various requests to complete goals. Currently the game service  has a Lua script environment which people are <span class="bbcode-b">expected</span>, not <span class="bbcode-b">encouraged</span> to use.<br>
I may hear a few groans for that but there is a reason. Frankly the Lua environment just wraps the service and has built in helpers to make your coding more efficient. Currently (at this very moment) I’m working on bootstrapping scripts and binding required data to the service in order to handle action callbacks and other data.<br>
The scripting system as a whole supports a few service requests, one to evaluate a script, one to load a script, and one to call a script by its namespace which you pass as an argument when you load a script into memory. With these you can do a variety of tasks remotely, or at least that’s the hope. It’s just a way to give people more control, and hopefully implement the functionality they require for their emulation implementation.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">So enough of that boring stuff, how are you? How is your personal life going, are you in uni? etc</span><br>
Yep. I’m at university right now heading into my 2nd year. I’m a computer science major, duh. I am just enjoying the summer with my girlfriend and family.<br>
As much as I want to spend my time outside, I spend about 3-6 hours a day designing and working on the Moparscape server source. I really want to see it done you know! Like I just want that one project I can sit back and look in awe at and think, wow this is an accumulation of everything you’ve done in the past 5 years. I think once we get everything up and running we’d see a surge in activity. Maybe not actual development, but new people joining and it’d give us a new initiative to actually be active for. It’s exciting, but its a long road and everyday its one step after the next.<br>
I think about quitting RSPS as a whole all the time but I want something to be remembered by and I think this may be the ticket. But who knows, it may flop. But at least I gained the experience I did along the way you know? I’m doing this for the community and I hope once it comes out everyone in the community has a chance to enjoy it. I have a lot of pride in being a member of Mopar, it’s been a fun ride and if I didn’t have Mopar I probably wouldn’t be in the place in my life I am now. So I am very grateful, to MITB, the admins, and everyone who has helped teach me what they could.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">To wrap this session up - What is your advice to newcomers, particularly those who want to learn how to code?</span><br>
My advice to anyone wanting to learn how to program is to be humble and don’t be afraid to ask for help. Learning to program is a long process regardless of choice of language. You have to keep an open mind and don’t get discouraged if it gets tough.<br>
If you get frustrated step back and come back later. It’ll always be there for you to pick up again. If you want to get to the best of your ability, set your goals high and don’t be afraid to fail.<br>
Start with Java, Ruby, or Python and have fun! Don’t do boring dribble, make a program that prints out cat facts or a client that receives cat facts from a server.<br>
Also if Pure is giving you programming advice, chance is its BAD programming advice. <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/wink.png?v=5" title=":wink:" class="emoji" alt=":wink:"> .</p>
            </blockquote>
            <p>Posts: 14</p>
            <p>Participants: 11</p>
            <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/mopar-weekly-4/552145">Read full topic</a></p>
          ]]></description>
          <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/mopar-weekly-4/552145</link>
          <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jun 2015 18:01:08 +0000</pubDate>
          <discourse:topicPinned>No</discourse:topicPinned>
          <discourse:topicClosed>No</discourse:topicClosed>
          <discourse:topicArchived>No</discourse:topicArchived>
          <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-topic-552145</guid>
          <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/mopar-weekly-4/552145.rss">Mopar Weekly (#4)</source>
        </item>
        <item>
          <title>Mopar Weekly (#3)</title>
          <dc:creator><![CDATA[@pure2ownage Pure_]]></dc:creator>
          <category>Community Suggestions</category>
          <description><![CDATA[
            <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/pure2ownage">@pure2ownage</a> wrote:</p>
            <blockquote>
              <p>[size=24pt]News (for the week 15/06/2015)[/size]</p>
<p>[size=14pt]<a href="https://rswiki.moparisthebest.com/" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">RS Wiki Update</a>[/size]<br>
You might have noticed that recently the wiki was in the process of being reworked and was constantly being cleaned up. We finally migrated to a system backed by Git which uses <a href="https://github.com/gollum/gollum" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">Gollum</a>.<br>
This version is still in the works and you can contribute to it using <a href="https://github.com/moparisthebest/rswiki" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">github</a> - we hope that this way it will be more powerful and easier to manage than ever.</p>
<p>[size=14pt]IRC Management - <a href="https://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php/topic,670840.0.html" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">#1</a>. <a href="https://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php/topic,670868.0.html" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">#2</a>.[/size]<br>
Some issues were ignited regarding the IRC management. I am happy to say that we have resolved all of them and usage of the IRC network can resume as normal.</p>
<p>[hr]</p>
<p>[size=18pt]Client Hacking[/size]</p>
<p>[size=14pt]<a href="https://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php/topic,670230.0.html" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">RuneTek 3+ - MIDI Compression Format</a> (by <a href="https://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php?action=profile;u=449007" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">sini</a>)[/size]<br>
Sini has refactored the MIDI compression class used in modern RuneTek engines. It is worth checking out if you are interested in such affairs regarding the client.</p>
<p>[size=14pt]<a href="https://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php/topic,670870.html" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">RuneScript to Lua Compiler</a> (by <a href="https://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php?action=profile;u=449007" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">sini</a>)[/size]<br>
Sini is not done just yet though! He has also been working on a RuneScript to Lua compiler recently which is starting to get together. The purpose of this is to be able to port client-sided RuneScript bytecodes to Lua (a source code format).<br>
A few members have also chimed together some ideas which are definitely worth the read.</p>
<p>[hr]</p>
<p>[size=18pt]Senior Member Feature - <a href="https://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php?action=profile;u=374" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">Mopman</a>[/size]<br>
This week we have managed to get a hold of <a href="https://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php?action=profile;u=374" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">Mopman</a> - the very foundation of our community <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=5" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Before MoparScape/MoparIsTheBest what did you do?</span><br>
Well, before mitb/moparscape i was on other runescape communities, rscn, kaitnieks etc. I never did anything of value there though, just leeched off of others <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/wink.png?v=5" title=":wink:" class="emoji" alt=":wink:"> I played runescape too up til RS2 came out, but i haven’t really played since the beta (a little on and off, but not seriously).<br>
I also used to be into the genesis3d community which was a free game engine, sort of a clone of the quake 3/unreal engines but when those were closed source and expensive. I would link you to my profile at g3d, but it’s super embarrassing, I was even less smart 15 years ago <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/wink.png?v=5" title=":wink:" class="emoji" alt=":wink:"></p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">How did you find MoparScape/MITB and what were the first things you did on here?</span><br>
I knew who moparisthebest was before he started the forum, he was at the time a big figure in the scar community on kaitnieks, which I wasn’t really a part of as I preferred other ways to bot.<br>
When he started his forum (moparisthebest, no moparscape yet, that came later!) I signed up though because I knew he was well known and very active. I assumed there’d be some good stuff on there and I guess I was right, since when kaitnieks died it basically became our new home.</p>
<p>I should also add everyone thought me and moparisthebest were the same fudgeing person so I couldn’t really not know who he was <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=5" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"><br>
When I posted Aryan updates on my site I had to put a notice saying I wasn’t moparisthebest because everyone kept private messaging him (and thus me) for help. In hindsight I should have just let them [private message me].</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">What are you known for in the community and how did you rise to power?</span><br>
Hm good question. I guess I’m not really known for anything in the sense that some people are - I never wrote any awesome bots or anything. In the early days I did a lot of public scripting/helping people with scripts and issues.<br>
After Aryan died I provided updates &amp; support for a while after the team stopped, basically just because I happened to have access to the private channels and such (despite not being a dev, contrary to belief) and could bug the devs with annoying questions when their shit broke.</p>
<p>As for ‘rising to power’ it basically just came through being here ages and being well known. iIwas a ‘community member’ on kaitnieks (I think that’s what it was called anyway - the rep-based rank). I only got gmod/admin after MITB - he just needed another gmod and asked.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">What made you decide to stick around for all this time, on the forums and IRC?</span><br>
Honestly at this point its just because I have friends here. I have known some people here longer than I have known my real life friends at this point!<br>
I still think botting/private servers are awesome and interesting and I want to see the community keep doing cool stuff, but I lost interest in the game itself years ago, so it’s just about keeping the community alive and keeping in touch with friends now.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">But surely I am the reason you stick around ^.^</span><br>
Oh of course, It’s all about pure! Everyone else is unimportant <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/smiley.png?v=5" title=":smiley:" class="emoji" alt=":smiley:"></p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">What do you think of the quality of content nowadays? Are you impressed by the evolution of rsps/botting?</span><br>
I must admit I haven’t kept up to date with servers - though last time I looked at them I was sincerely impressed! I like that eventually we moved away (somewhat) from copy-pasting all day and people started doing interesting things with custom content and stuff.<br>
Do more of that. (where is my tower defense in the runetek engine, bitches?) As for botting I’m like anti-impressed with it. we have a couple of profit oriented companies selling bots to gold farmers and that’s it - yawn.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">What do you think about the fragmentation of the RSPS communities nowadays and the inevitable decline?</span><br>
It sucks, but it’s probably, as you say, inevitable - the game itself is dropping off too of course. It’s a shame since as I said above people make good friends through this. After Aryan died we kept the private channel alive for a few years, with no Aryan related content, just to hang out.<br>
Now I don’t really speak to any of them other than exemplar. if you let the ‘community’ part die, eventually everyone will drift away, this is just the way it is. If you don’t like that, you have to find other things to keep people together.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">In more recent news, do you wish to make a statement on the IRC drama that was had or the shutting down of SoulSplit?</span><br>
Haha, I think enough has been said about the IRC drama, needless to say it was a clusterfudge and I apologise for my part in it. I think we have managed to do what is best for the community though even if it bruised some egos for all involved.<br>
As for soulsplit, I’m surprised they were not shut down sooner. The guy who runs it always seemed like a pretty OK guy to me, but he was being crazy, lol. I just hope whatever happened doesn’t ruin his chances at whatever other projects him/his company end up doing and that nobody got fudgeed over personally by losing their income etc.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">What do you do today, i.e. what’s a typical day like for Mopman <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=5" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"> ?</span><br>
HARD DRUGS. Wait no don’t put that. Uh, this is a family friendly post? <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/wink.png?v=5" title=":wink:" class="emoji" alt=":wink:"></p>
<p>Typical day for Mopeman… I work for a web hosting company here in the UK, but I work remotely, so my typical day involves waking up, eating cornflakes with bananas on it because it’s the breakfast of champions.<br>
Then I tend to broken servers or angry customers… On off days I ride a motorcycle which I’m pretty sure is going to fall apart any minute, berate pure for a few hours, and try to pick up women on IRC (rarely successful, but has been known to work).</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Wait, you said it has been known to work. Care to elaborate?</span><br>
Haha yeah, I met my current girlfriend on IRC… On <span class="hashtag">#mopar</span>, actually. Some of you know her as baristaTam… I recommend against IRC relationships though, airfare is expensive.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Any advice to newcomers on how to be pro coders etc/Final statements</span><br>
Just make stuff. Anytime you think a project would be cool, or you have a problem you want to solve, if you cant find anyone else who is solving the same problem who you can work with, it’s your job. <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/wink.png?v=5" title=":wink:" class="emoji" alt=":wink:"><br>
Too many programmers (inside and outside the community) get this mentality where they feel there is such a thing as an ‘elite’ programmer who is far better than them and knows everything, and they dedicate their time to becoming this elite programmer instead of doing shit.<br>
They don’t really exist though, so if you’re ever going to get anywhere you need to get used to going from ‘I don’t know anything about what I need to do’ -&gt; ‘research/exploration’ -&gt; ‘just doing it’ - That’s really what everyone else is doing too, you just only see the end results.<br>
I think that skill is far more important to being a great programmer than any sort of technical skill.</p>
<p>Seeing as it is exam season, good luck on exams everyone who has them currently, and don’t drop out like I did, it’s bad for health!</p>
<p>INSIDE JOKE ALERT: Also, go in pure - I’ll follow up <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/wink.png?v=5" title=":wink:" class="emoji" alt=":wink:"><br>
ps What the fudge a camper van just went past with Tom Cruise written on it. I assume Tom Cruise isn’t in it.</p>
            </blockquote>
            <p>Posts: 18</p>
            <p>Participants: 11</p>
            <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/mopar-weekly-3/551998">Read full topic</a></p>
          ]]></description>
          <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/mopar-weekly-3/551998</link>
          <pubDate>Sun, 14 Jun 2015 18:58:06 +0000</pubDate>
          <discourse:topicPinned>No</discourse:topicPinned>
          <discourse:topicClosed>No</discourse:topicClosed>
          <discourse:topicArchived>No</discourse:topicArchived>
          <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-topic-551998</guid>
          <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/mopar-weekly-3/551998.rss">Mopar Weekly (#3)</source>
        </item>
        <item>
          <title>Mopar Weekly (#2)</title>
          <dc:creator><![CDATA[@pure2ownage Pure_]]></dc:creator>
          <category>Community Suggestions</category>
          <description><![CDATA[
            <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/pure2ownage">@pure2ownage</a> wrote:</p>
            <blockquote>
              <p>[size=24pt]News (for the week 08/06/2015)[/size]</p>
<p>[size=14pt]<a href="https://rswiki.moparisthebest.com/" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">RS Wiki</a> <a href="https://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php/topic,670758.0.html" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">Cleanup</a>[/size]<br>
We have recently decided to update the official RS wiki by adding <a href="https://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php?action=profile;u=350406" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">Pure_</a> and <a href="https://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php?action=profile;u=449007" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">sini</a> as admins. Our hope is that sini can contribute his invaluable knowledge in the form of concise articles.<br>
This has also led to a massive purge of spam by Pure_ (somewhere around 1,500 posts were deleted and many accounts blocked permanently). While we will keep up this work we hope that the higher-level management can help us out by implementing spam filters soon!</p>
<p>[hr]</p>
<p>[size=18pt]Tutorials/Snippets[/size]</p>
<p>[size=14pt]<a href="https://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php/topic,670791.0.html" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">Groovy Scripting for Beginners</a> (by <a href="https://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php?action=profile;u=350406" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">Pure_</a>)[/size]<br>
As a part of a new scheme to encourage activity in the tutorial board, Pure_ has taken it upon himself to post and explain some general ideas which can be implemented into any server regardless of revision or language.<br>
This week he decided upon a simple plugin system, with the point of such threads being to encourage discussion about good practices and as such improvements upon the original post.</p>
<p>[hr]</p>
<p>[size=18pt]Game Development[/size]</p>
<p>[size=14pt]<a href="https://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php/topic,669617.0.html" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">Codename::World</a> (by <a href="https://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php?action=profile;u=67436" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">Lin</a>)[/size]<br>
Lin had began his project a couple of months ago to accomplish his dream, of building a sandbox environment where the player is not constrained by the programming.<br>
In recent updates his project has really taken off, prompting this highlight of his amazing project! We are certain of his individual ability as well as his amazing idea and wish him the best, make sure you give him some feedback and keep up with the development!</p>
<p><img src="http://i.imgur.com/VHK7N1m.png" alt width="" height=""> <img src="http://i.imgur.com/AWVhgz6.png" alt width="" height=""> <img src="http://i.imgur.com/dRyasFT.png" alt width="" height=""> <img src="http://i.imgur.com/TnK7SbP.png" alt width="" height=""></p>
<p>[hr]</p>
<p>[size=18pt]General Discussion[/size]</p>
<p>[size=14pt]<a href="https://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php/topic,670678.0.html" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">How fast can you type?</a> (by <a href="https://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php?action=profile;u=697625" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">WarTusk-RSPS</a>)[/size]<br>
This thread has really taken off recently with several members chiming in to compete with each other’s typing speeds <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=5" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"> Make sure you try your hand at it and post the results!</p>
<p>[hr]</p>
<p>[size=18pt]Senior Member Feature - <a href="https://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php?action=profile;u=19676" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">Archer</a>[/size]<br>
This is the first in hopefully many senior member features, a series which was masterminded by the old front-page project (now deceased, rip). This week we have managed to get a hold of <a href="https://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php?action=profile;u=19676" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">Archer</a>.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">A little about yourself?</span><br>
I was a graphics designer and posted my work on the MoparScape forums for a long period time. This line of work included modelling and other general art. You can still find my doodles here and there <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=5" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">How did you find the community?</span><br>
I joined due to the FreeScape server back in 2006.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">What are you known for?</span><br>
I was a moderator for a while on the forums. My graphics posts also attracted a lot of attention and you can always find me on IRC!</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">What makes you stay here?</span><br>
Once you’re in, you can’t leave.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Advice to newcomers trying to become better programmers/artists/etc?</span><br>
Make sure you aren’t arrogant, it will get you nowhere. Use google before asking anything, it was really helpful for me in picking up the basics and finding solutions to a lot of problems. Last but not least try to use some level of formal english on the forums, we can’t help you if we can’t understand you <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=5" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"></p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">What do you do nowadays?</span><br>
I am in University seeking an AA and AS degree in video game development. You can still catch me on IRC talking about my hobbies, which include being a Tae Kwan Doe black-belt and collecting firearms.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Inspiration!</span><br>
If you stick around, follow the rules and contribute to the community you will gain respect from the veteran members and learn valuable skills that will aid you in your future, on and off the forums.</p>
            </blockquote>
            <p>Posts: 18</p>
            <p>Participants: 13</p>
            <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/mopar-weekly-2/551885">Read full topic</a></p>
          ]]></description>
          <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/mopar-weekly-2/551885</link>
          <pubDate>Mon, 08 Jun 2015 14:50:08 +0000</pubDate>
          <discourse:topicPinned>No</discourse:topicPinned>
          <discourse:topicClosed>No</discourse:topicClosed>
          <discourse:topicArchived>No</discourse:topicArchived>
          <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-topic-551885</guid>
          <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/mopar-weekly-2/551885.rss">Mopar Weekly (#2)</source>
        </item>
        <item>
          <title>Forum software</title>
          <dc:creator><![CDATA[@pure2ownage Pure_]]></dc:creator>
          <category>Community Suggestions</category>
          <description><![CDATA[
            <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/pure2ownage">@pure2ownage</a> wrote:</p>
            <blockquote>
              <p>Any suggestions, ideas, etc</p>
<p><a href="http://try.discourse.org/" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">Discourse</a> seems to be a fore runner to me and some other people (incl. mitb).</p>
<p><img src="http://i.imgur.com/06GSNNL.png" alt width="" height=""></p>
            </blockquote>
            <p>Posts: 13</p>
            <p>Participants: 11</p>
            <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/forum-software/551834">Read full topic</a></p>
          ]]></description>
          <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/forum-software/551834</link>
          <pubDate>Fri, 05 Jun 2015 19:30:32 +0000</pubDate>
          <discourse:topicPinned>No</discourse:topicPinned>
          <discourse:topicClosed>No</discourse:topicClosed>
          <discourse:topicArchived>No</discourse:topicArchived>
          <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-topic-551834</guid>
          <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/forum-software/551834.rss">Forum software</source>
        </item>
        <item>
          <title>Mopar Weekly (#1)</title>
          <dc:creator><![CDATA[@pure2ownage Pure_]]></dc:creator>
          <category>Community Suggestions</category>
          <description><![CDATA[
            <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/pure2ownage">@pure2ownage</a> wrote:</p>
            <blockquote>
              <p>[size=24pt]News (for the week 01/06/2015)[/size]<br>
[size=18pt]Chat Server Upgrades[/size]<br>
Some of you have be aware that recently the IRC server was hit by a string of DDOS attacks. This has been the reason for any downtime/connection issues experienced.<br>
This has led to a host migration and t4 is now responsible for the server. We now have two nodes with one in Europe and one in America which is set to launch soon.</p>
<p>[hr]</p>
<p>[size=18pt]Tutorials/Snippets[/size]</p>
<p>[size=14pt]<a href="https://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php/topic,669365.0.html" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">Clan Chat for Hyperion</a> (by <a href="https://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php?action=profile;u=540458" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">Dan0194</a>)[/size]<br>
Dan recently posted a comprehensive copy+paste style tutorial on how to add fully functional clan chats to the Hyperion base. He covers both the client and server aspects of the feature. All topped off with a video of the final product which looks amazing!</p>
<p><img src="http://i.imgur.com/LReYQFg.png" alt width="" height=""></p>
<p>[size=14pt]<a href="https://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php/topic,669926.0.html" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">Item Definitions for Asteria 2.0</a> (by <a href="https://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php?action=profile;u=438237" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">Fridder</a>)[/size]<br>
This is an awesome contribution which features 20,000+ item definitions for the popular Asteria base, alongside how to implement it.</p>
<p><img src="http://i.imgur.com/xcvMYa4.png" alt width="" height=""></p>
<p>[hr]</p>
<p>[size=18pt]Client Hacking[/size]</p>
<p>[size=14pt]<a href="https://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php/topic,670167.0.html" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">RuneTek 4 Engine Rewrite</a> (by <a href="https://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php?action=profile;u=449007" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">sini</a>)[/size]<br>
Sini has recently began rewriting the RuneTek 4 engine for use in the offcial private server. Make sure you keep up with his progress!</p>
<p><img src="http://i.imgur.com/4hUvsSs.png" alt width="" height=""></p>
<p>[hr]</p>
<p>[size=18pt]Downloads[/size]</p>
<p>[size=14pt]<a href="https://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php/topic,670032.0.html" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">RS838 Emulation</a> (by <a href="https://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php?action=profile;u=609368" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">Sir James1996</a>)[/size]<br>
James is back with another emulation of the current RuneScape protocol. Although not complete, it has quite a bit of basic functionality and should serve as a good base for those wanting to dabble in this protocol.</p>
            </blockquote>
            <p>Posts: 20</p>
            <p>Participants: 12</p>
            <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/mopar-weekly-1/551785">Read full topic</a></p>
          ]]></description>
          <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/mopar-weekly-1/551785</link>
          <pubDate>Tue, 02 Jun 2015 19:00:41 +0000</pubDate>
          <discourse:topicPinned>No</discourse:topicPinned>
          <discourse:topicClosed>No</discourse:topicClosed>
          <discourse:topicArchived>No</discourse:topicArchived>
          <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-topic-551785</guid>
          <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/mopar-weekly-1/551785.rss">Mopar Weekly (#1)</source>
        </item>
        <item>
          <title>The continual decline of activity felt throughout the forum, what do you do?</title>
          <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Tom Tom]]></dc:creator>
          <category>Community Suggestions</category>
          <description><![CDATA[
            <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/tom">@Tom</a> wrote:</p>
            <blockquote>
              <p>Hey guys, I hope you’re all well. <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=5" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
<p>It’s been a well established trend for many years that activity is in decline. It’s publicly available information and if you’ve missed Tree’s biannual topics regarding it you can find forum activity data at the bottom of the forum. We’ve really been around the roundabout with this one, I’ve read every single topic in this board and the old one tonight and I’ve come across members suggesting the forums “death” can be attributed to poor management, runescape’s decline and a plethora of other reasons, some more bizarre than others.</p>
<p>It’s very hard to pinpoint a sole cause for every misfortune this community has had (Apart from the obvious reason of Classic) and while I do hold my own opinions regarding the reason activity has declined those opinions aren’t what I want this topic to be about. Instead of looking for something in the past to type and talk about I’d like the community to step into the shoes of the sole owner of this community and tell me about what they’d do.</p>
<p>Maybe you’d divert funds from the SSP into an advertising campaign? Or focus more on the SEO of the website? Perhaps you’d even change the theme, or push harder for an official server? <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=5" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"> I genuinely want to see things through the frustrated eyes of those who post in this section, and instead of arguing about themes or reputation systems I’d like to discuss meaningful advances on a higher level than forum modifications.</p>
            </blockquote>
            <p>Posts: 337</p>
            <p>Participants: 63</p>
            <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-continual-decline-of-activity-felt-throughout-the-forum-what-do-you-do/551680">Read full topic</a></p>
          ]]></description>
          <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-continual-decline-of-activity-felt-throughout-the-forum-what-do-you-do/551680</link>
          <pubDate>Tue, 26 May 2015 23:13:15 +0000</pubDate>
          <discourse:topicPinned>No</discourse:topicPinned>
          <discourse:topicClosed>No</discourse:topicClosed>
          <discourse:topicArchived>No</discourse:topicArchived>
          <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-topic-551680</guid>
          <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-continual-decline-of-activity-felt-throughout-the-forum-what-do-you-do/551680.rss">The continual decline of activity felt throughout the forum, what do you do?</source>
        </item>
        <item>
          <title>Remove our own topics</title>
          <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Spades Spades]]></dc:creator>
          <category>Community Suggestions</category>
          <description><![CDATA[
            <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/spades">@Spades</a> wrote:</p>
            <blockquote>
              <p>Tired of seeing “MOD REMOVE PLEASE” or “NEVERMIND” can we just remove our own topics?</p>
            </blockquote>
            <p>Posts: 20</p>
            <p>Participants: 8</p>
            <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/remove-our-own-topics/551563">Read full topic</a></p>
          ]]></description>
          <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/remove-our-own-topics/551563</link>
          <pubDate>Mon, 18 May 2015 01:19:38 +0000</pubDate>
          <discourse:topicPinned>No</discourse:topicPinned>
          <discourse:topicClosed>No</discourse:topicClosed>
          <discourse:topicArchived>No</discourse:topicArchived>
          <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-topic-551563</guid>
          <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/remove-our-own-topics/551563.rss">Remove our own topics</source>
        </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
