<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>- Pedant Blog #1 -</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/pedant-blog-1/555826</link>
    <description>&lt;img src=&#39;/uploads/default/original/2X/2/2b1d84f0ef5ed44d50020cbf8303fa8e2722347b.png&#39;&gt;

This week on Pedant blog, we take a look at this awful clickbait-esqe image I found on Facebook.

In this most likely made up story, the &quot;dumb blonde&quot; rhetoric is used for comedic effect; her alternative &quot;simple&quot; interpretation of the password restriction results in the creation of a strong password, in a ironic fashion. But, what if, she understood these restrictions when she read them and coincidentally chose the mentioned password. The password contains more than 8 characters and several capital letters - her statement is logically correct both when referring to glyphs and Disney characters/US state capitals.

Maybe this employee was well aware of the restrictions, recognised the &quot;joke&quot; in the password restriction and formed this satirical password for her own **personal** amusement, not expecting anyone to question her decision.

After pondering away at these possibilities, the real joke emerges - this employee just took part in a &quot;Password Audit&quot;. The fact that her own company knows her password undermines the whole idea of a &quot;Password Audit&quot; - her I.D. is clearly not safe if her employer can see it in plaintext.

The creator of this image is either incredibly stupid, or an absolute genius - 10/10.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 15 Sep 2016 18:16:16 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Uncategorized</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/pedant-blog-1/555826.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>- Pedant Blog #1 -</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@sini]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/sini">@sini</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Your senses of humor are dulled Lothy by the excess of women and liquor in your life.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/pedant-blog-1/555826/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/pedant-blog-1/555826/3</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 15 Sep 2016 18:16:16 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-555826-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/pedant-blog-1/555826.rss">- Pedant Blog #1 -</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>- Pedant Blog #1 -</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@lothy Lothy]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/lothy">@lothy</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>So what’s the point of this topic? If it’s click bait then just ignore it like any other click bait?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/pedant-blog-1/555826/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/pedant-blog-1/555826/2</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 15 Sep 2016 08:02:32 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-555826-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/pedant-blog-1/555826.rss">- Pedant Blog #1 -</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>- Pedant Blog #1 -</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Fat_Cookies Fat Cookies]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/fat_cookies">@Fat_Cookies</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p><img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/uploads/default/original/2X/2/2b1d84f0ef5ed44d50020cbf8303fa8e2722347b.png" width="557" height="396"></p>
<p>This week on Pedant blog, we take a look at this awful clickbait-esqe image I found on Facebook.</p>
<p>In this most likely made up story, the “dumb blonde” rhetoric is used for comedic effect; her alternative “simple” interpretation of the password restriction results in the creation of a strong password, in a ironic fashion. But, what if, she understood these restrictions when she read them and coincidentally chose the mentioned password. The password contains more than 8 characters and several capital letters - her statement is logically correct both when referring to glyphs and Disney characters/US state capitals.</p>
<p>Maybe this employee was well aware of the restrictions, recognised the “joke” in the password restriction and formed this satirical password for her own <strong>personal</strong> amusement, not expecting anyone to question her decision.</p>
<p>After pondering away at these possibilities, the real joke emerges - this employee just took part in a “Password Audit”. The fact that her own company knows her password undermines the whole idea of a “Password Audit” - her I.D. is clearly not safe if her employer can see it in plaintext.</p>
<p>The creator of this image is either incredibly stupid, or an absolute genius - 10/10.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/pedant-blog-1/555826/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/pedant-blog-1/555826/1</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 14 Sep 2016 19:50:01 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-555826-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/pedant-blog-1/555826.rss">- Pedant Blog #1 -</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
