<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Running a 317 rsps on a Linux server ( need help)</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/running-a-317-rsps-on-a-linux-server-need-help/530899</link>
    <description>Hello,


I recently got a linux vps and it&#39;s causing a few problems for me..it&#39;s a big change from windows vps.
So far my problem is, I can&#39;t figure out how to run my server.

I&#39;ve looked at a countless amount of tutorials but I just don&#39;t understand it..

So far I&#39;ve uploaded the source folder into the root of the vps
I&#39;ve also edited the contents of the run.bat as well as changed the extension to run.sh
the run.sh file contains the following...

screen -A -m -d -S rsps java -Xmx800m -classpath bin:deps/poi.jar:deps/netty.jar:deps/mysql.jar:deps/slf4j.jar:deps/slf4j-nop.jar:deps/jython.jar:log4j-1.2.15.jar: server.Server




Right, so basically the source is uploaded, the run.sh file is sorted out..but how do I run the server? is there any way of implementing an auto restarter in Linux?

Oh and, I also set up NO-IP but I was wondering, do I need to somehow add an exception in the Linux firewall for NO-IP?

Please try and explain in detail as I&#39;m not experienced with this sort of stuff

Thanks a lot.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2013 22:16:01 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/running-a-317-rsps-on-a-linux-server-need-help/530899.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Running a 317 rsps on a Linux server ( need help)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@sk8rdude461 sk8rdude461]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/sk8rdude461">@sk8rdude461</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p><a href="http://www.rune-server.org/runescape-development/rs2-server/tutorials/309503-running-rsps-centos-linux.html" class="onebox" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">http://www.rune-server.org/runescape-development/rs2-server/tutorials/309503-running-rsps-centos-linux.html</a></p>
<p>[quote author=LinkAbove][CENTER]<br>
<span class="bbcode-b"><span class="bbcode-u">Running your RuneScape private server on CentOS (Linux)</span></span></p>
<p>Hello and welcome to my tutorial on how to run RSPS in CentOS.<br>
I don’t know if this has been posted before, even if it was, it must be quite different.<br>
I found this way myself and I think it’s quite easy one. Anyway, it took me a while to figure out.<br>
So here it is, post replies and feel free to ask questions.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b"><span class="bbcode-u">1. Connecting to our VPS with “Secure Shell Client”</span></span></p>
<p>Well I find this program quite easy to use. It’s quite simple and it has file manager included.</p>
<p>First off, download and intall this program. Here is quite huge list for it:<br>
<a href="http://www.filewatcher.com/m/SSHSecureShellClient-3.2.9.exe.5517312.0.0.html" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">SSHSecureShellClient-3.2.9.exe - FTP Mirror Search (Downloads)</a></p>
<p>Start the program, and click quick connect.</p>
<p><img src="http://i.imgur.com/g1TAV.png" alt width="583" height="467"></p>
<p>Fill in your VPS information and click connect.<br>
If connection is successful, a box for password should pop-up.</p>
<p><img src="http://i.imgur.com/jUsd2.png" alt width="588" height="466"></p>
<p>Enter password and click ok. Then a table for “Add to profiles” will pop-up.<br>
You can add it to profiles so it will be easier to connect next time.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b"><span class="bbcode-u">2. Installing the JDK</span></span></p>
<p>Ok so now you are connected to your VPS. Here is the hard part.<br>
What you want to do now, is to get latest JDK for linux.</p>
<p>Go to: <a href="http://www.oracle.com/technetwork/java/javase/downloads/index.html" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">Java SE Downloads</a><br>
Click on “Download JDK” and select platform Linux.</p>
<p><img src="http://i.imgur.com/8a3YD.png" alt width="407" height="127"></p>
<p>Then you will see 2 downloads available.<br>
Click the one with RMP in it’s filename. (The first one in the image)</p>
<p><img src="http://i.imgur.com/HIxaM.png" alt width="567" height="98"></p>
<p>When you got your linux JDK downloaded, on your Secure Shell Client click the file transfer icon. ( <img src="http://i.imgur.com/Ab5Hf.png" alt width="24" height="20"> )</p>
<p><img src="http://i.imgur.com/WinNS.png" alt width="587" height="473"></p>
<p>And just drag your downloaded JDK to the right side of file manager.<br>
Wait for it to finish uploading.</p>
<p><img src="http://i.imgur.com/bk1lY.png" alt width="591" height="470"></p>
<p>Right click the jdk install and hit Properties.<br>
Set permission mode to 777.</p>
<p><img src="http://i.imgur.com/v3WcM.png" alt width="583" height="466"></p>
<p>Now you can minimize the file transfer window and go back to Secure Shell Client.<br>
Copy the file name of your JDK you downloaded and type in: ./FILENAME<br>
And wait for JDK to install.</p>
<p><img src="http://i.imgur.com/GUB1Y.png" alt width="553" height="204"></p>
<p>That’s it for JDK installation.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b"><span class="bbcode-u">3. Running your RSPS</span></span></p>
<p>For runing we will be using program called “SCREEN”.<br>
It allows you to run your program in background, so server will be online after you close the Secure Shell Client.<br>
I know JAVAW launcher allows you to do that, but somehow I couldn’t get it to work on CentOS.</p>
<p>To get “SCREEN” you basicly have to type: yum install screen<br>
Just wait until it downloads and installs it.</p>
<p>Well now open file transfer window again. Delete all those jdk files, it’s just for installation they are uneeded now.<br>
Now upload your source, just drag all folder with your source in. Wait for it to upload.</p>
<p><img src="http://i.imgur.com/KPh7D.png" alt width="299" height="78"></p>
<p>Alright, now when you got your source uploaded, close file transfer window.<br>
On Secure Shell Client, go to your source folder by typing: cd FOLDERNAME</p>
<p><img src="http://i.imgur.com/Zr3Ns.png" alt width="237" height="41"></p>
<p>Now in your source just open your run.bat and look for the line with “java” command.<br>
It should look something like this:</p>
<pre><code class="lang-auto"></code></pre>
<p>Well now what you need to do is to convert that line to LINUX format.<br>
Just change all ; to : and -cp to -classpath. This line converted looks like that:</p>
<pre><code class="lang-auto"></code></pre>
<p>Ok so now you could run your server just by typing this in Secure Shell Client.<br>
But if you would do so, after you close the Secure Shell Client your server would turn off also.<br>
So what we want to do is run it with “SCREEN”, the program we downloaded earlier.</p>
<p>In order to run it with screen you have add this before your command: screen -A -m -d -S NAME<br>
Well for name just use something obvious, like RSPS. So my example would be:</p>
<p><code>screen -A -m -d -S rsps java -classpath bin:deps/poi.jar:deps/mysql.jar:deps/mina.jar:deps/slf4j.jar:deps/slf4j-nop.jar:deps/jython.jar:log4j-1.2.15.jar server.Server
</code></p>
<p>So just type the line in your Secure Shell Client and your server will start up.<br>
To make sure that your server started up, type “free -m” before and after you run your server.<br>
You will see huge ram boost when you run it.</p>
<p>In order to shutdown your server. Type in: killall java<br>
Use “free -m” to make sure you have done it successfully.</p>
<p>Well that’s it I hope I was clear enough. Post all your questions.<br>
Good luck. <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/wink.png?v=5" title=":wink:" class="emoji" alt=":wink:"><br>
[/CENTER][/QUOTE]</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/running-a-317-rsps-on-a-linux-server-need-help/530899/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/running-a-317-rsps-on-a-linux-server-need-help/530899/2</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2013 22:16:01 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-530899-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/running-a-317-rsps-on-a-linux-server-need-help/530899.rss">Running a 317 rsps on a Linux server ( need help)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Running a 317 rsps on a Linux server ( need help)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Djibreel Djibreel]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/djibreel">@Djibreel</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Hello,</p>
<p>I recently got a linux vps and it’s causing a few problems for me…it’s a big change from windows vps.<br>
So far my problem is, I can’t figure out how to run my server.</p>
<p>I’ve looked at a countless amount of tutorials but I just don’t understand it…</p>
<p>So far I’ve uploaded the source folder into the root of the vps<br>
I’ve also edited the contents of the run.bat as well as changed the extension to run.sh<br>
the run.sh file contains the following…</p>
<p>screen -A -m -d -S rsps java -Xmx800m -classpath bin:deps/poi.jar:deps/netty.jar:deps/mysql.jar:deps/slf4j.jar:deps/slf4j-nop.jar:deps/jython.jar:log4j-1.2.15.jar: server.Server</p>
<p>Right, so basically the source is uploaded, the run.sh file is sorted out…but how do I run the server? is there any way of implementing an auto restarter in Linux?</p>
<p>Oh and, I also set up NO-IP but I was wondering, do I need to somehow add an exception in the Linux firewall for NO-IP?</p>
<p>Please try and explain in detail as I’m not experienced with this sort of stuff</p>
<p>Thanks a lot.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/running-a-317-rsps-on-a-linux-server-need-help/530899/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/running-a-317-rsps-on-a-linux-server-need-help/530899/1</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2013 14:23:57 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-530899-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/running-a-317-rsps-on-a-linux-server-need-help/530899.rss">Running a 317 rsps on a Linux server ( need help)</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
