<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Desire-X [317 loading 562+]</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/desire-x-317-loading-562/451321</link>
    <description>Hey guys. Desire-X will be a server where people won&#39;t go like &quot;Oh.. Another hybrid base&quot;. It&#39;s not. We are going to try to make a rsps where you start playing and discover new stuff. It&#39;s going to be like an adventure. Not like other servers. We do not have a source yet so I cannot post any pictures at the moment. We are also not going to be like the servers that go like &quot;FIRST ONE THAT JOINS GETS STAFF&quot;. No. We will pick staff fair. This server will be a unique server. Also, all staff will have &quot;Mod&quot; in front of their name to represent them (The crown will be there too.)If you&#39;re interested in programming, Follow this format.

Name:
Hours Dedicated:
Position:
Skype:
Why&#39;d you want to join:


Professional Java Programmer: 0/1 I think a professional programmer can program a good server by himself :P.

Web Developer: 1/1[Fragz10] Can make a good website. Not a professional website but good enough to catch someones attention and make it look cool.

Host: 1/1[George] The host has about $150+ of investment in this server. He is also going to purchase a custom domain. He is really dedicated. 

If you guys want a spot not mentioned in here, or expand a spot (Professional Programmer and Web Designer.) Feel free to leave it in the comments

What we are looking to do with the server-
Add lot&#39;s of bosses, minigames, and monsters to fight.
Custom place where monsters drop rare item (this way people can interact with each other and have fun)
Make a custom open skilling place (Not catherby)
Make a friendly community
More will be added later.

Our goal is to make a good server and not make it like others.. We just want to make a community and have fun. 
Our source will be chosen through skype.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 26 Jul 2012 02:45:12 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/desire-x-317-loading-562/451321.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Desire-X [317 loading 562+]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Fragz10 Fragz10]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/fragz10">@Fragz10</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Hey guys. Desire-X will be a server where people won’t go like “Oh… Another hybrid base”. It’s not. We are going to try to make a rsps where you start playing and discover new stuff. It’s going to be like an adventure. Not like other servers. We do not have a source yet so I cannot post any pictures at the moment. We are also not going to be like the servers that go like “FIRST ONE THAT JOINS GETS STAFF”. No. We will pick staff fair. This server will be a unique server. Also, all staff will have “Mod” in front of their name to represent them (The crown will be there too.)If you’re interested in programming, Follow this format.</p>
<p>Name:<br>
Hours Dedicated:<br>
Position:<br>
Skype:<br>
Why’d you want to join:</p>
<p>Professional Java Programmer: 0/1 I think a professional programmer can program a good server by himself :P.</p>
<p>Web Developer: 1/1[Fragz10] Can make a good website. Not a professional website but good enough to catch someones attention and make it look cool.</p>
<p>Host: 1/1[George] The host has about $150+ of investment in this server. He is also going to purchase a custom domain. He is really dedicated.</p>
<p>If you guys want a spot not mentioned in here, or expand a spot (Professional Programmer and Web Designer.) Feel free to leave it in the comments</p>
<p>What we are looking to do with the server-<br>
Add lot’s of bosses, minigames, and monsters to fight.<br>
Custom place where monsters drop rare item (this way people can interact with each other and have fun)<br>
Make a custom open skilling place (Not catherby)<br>
Make a friendly community<br>
More will be added later.</p>
<p>Our goal is to make a good server and not make it like others… We just want to make a community and have fun.<br>
Our source will be chosen through skype.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/desire-x-317-loading-562/451321/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/desire-x-317-loading-562/451321/1</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jul 2012 02:45:12 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-451321-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/desire-x-317-loading-562/451321.rss">Desire-X [317 loading 562+]</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
