<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Need somebody who can make me a client for my server! (Non-rs related)</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/need-somebody-who-can-make-me-a-client-for-my-server-non-rs-related/550710</link>
    <description>This feels like the wrong section for what I&#39;m after but I&#39;m looking for somebody to work so here goes!

I need somebody who can make a client for me that can run well with a server that I&#39;ve created. I can already create a base for this however I need somebody who can work on the front-end view so that the client can be flexible with any project (such as games, control panels and other apps). The client needs to be able to perform things such as rendering. 

The goal of my project is to making a framework that can be customized to work in most scenarios that involve client/server. I&#39;ll make it plugin based so that you can individually install scripts and services to extend functionality e.g. you can choose to install a file server, messaging server, dispatchers etc. 

If anybody wants to help out, throw me a message, reply to this thread or add me on Skype (ashi.mscp).</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 23 Mar 2015 18:03:55 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/need-somebody-who-can-make-me-a-client-for-my-server-non-rs-related/550710.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Need somebody who can make me a client for my server! (Non-rs related)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Ashi Ashi]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/ashi">@Ashi</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>This feels like the wrong section for what I’m after but I’m looking for somebody to work so here goes!</p>
<p>I need somebody who can make a client for me that can run well with a server that I’ve created. I can already create a base for this however I need somebody who can work on the front-end view so that the client can be flexible with any project (such as games, control panels and other apps). The client needs to be able to perform things such as rendering.</p>
<p>The goal of my project is to making a framework that can be customized to work in most scenarios that involve client/server. I’ll make it plugin based so that you can individually install scripts and services to extend functionality e.g. you can choose to install a file server, messaging server, dispatchers etc.</p>
<p>If anybody wants to help out, throw me a message, reply to this thread or add me on Skype (ashi.mscp).</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/need-somebody-who-can-make-me-a-client-for-my-server-non-rs-related/550710/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/need-somebody-who-can-make-me-a-client-for-my-server-non-rs-related/550710/1</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 23 Mar 2015 18:03:55 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-550710-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/need-somebody-who-can-make-me-a-client-for-my-server-non-rs-related/550710.rss">Need somebody who can make me a client for my server! (Non-rs related)</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
