<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>RS2 sandbox server (read please :P)</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rs2-sandbox-server-read-please-p/539650</link>
    <description>Hello :)

I have engaged myself into a great endeavor... to create something that&#39;s missing in online games.

An online game with no directions... a world where everything does something regardless of your progress in quests/levels or whatever. I find some games are too combat centric, to the point where it just becomes boring grind.
While I agree that Runescape (at least, the old version) used to do this somewhat well; I simply didn&#39;t enjoy the pacing.
So imagine... you log into the server, customize your character and that&#39;s it... Do whatever you want.

[b]So what am I setting out to do?[/b]
I am working to change the mechanics to how items are found/obtained in RS2 and create a server where, if you kill a monster; it will not drop pants... rather it will drop an item piece which will aid you in creating said pants.
The crafting system will be completely different... there will be no &quot;5 bars to create a rune chest piece&quot;, there will be no steel armor... Iron armor, then next one up is mithril... and the way to obtain mithril is to take an iron ore and enchant it in a magical location :) e.t.c.

[b][i]An example, please?[/i][/b]
Dragon square shield will be the best shield in the game, as it will heal you whenever a dragon breath hits you, it is one hell of an awesome shield... In my server, one half will be guarded by an iron dragon, the other half will be guarded by a steel dragon... if you pick up the piece before killing this dragon; it will enrage and burn your nuts off.
To merge the two halves of this shield; you need to have the two halves in your inventory and you need to engage a normal dragon without any dragon-fire protection (dragonfire shield/dragon square shield/anti-fire potion), the two halves of the shield will begin to tremble under the dragonfires magical properties and will merge together (the player must equip the shield immediately or they are in great danger of death).

OR

To a lesser extent... imagine you have a set of shears... and you want those equippable flowers... Just use the shears on some flowers on the ground... voilá.

And that is just one of the things... The end idea is... Create a sandbox of difficult progress; awesome boss fights; exploration and rewards... craftsmanship, player professions and interaction.

This will be done in an un-modded 317 client (Moparscape client) for accessibility and simplicity.

CURRENT PROGRESS:
Crafting framework (and basic smithing) - done.
Smelting framework - done.
Scribe system (only used for certain things in the game) - in progress.

Notes:
This is still an idea in progress :) I am writing myself a &quot;DIRECTION&quot; document to have a clear, un-changing goal in mind.
All skills will be utilized in some respects.

Let me know what you think :) Would you play it?
I am looking for peoples opinions to see if there&#39;s any point in me attempting to host this... If you don&#39;t have anything you can think of to say, just put a score like... out of 10. :)</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 10 Feb 2014 02:58:44 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rs2-sandbox-server-read-please-p/539650.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>RS2 sandbox server (read please :P)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@furyking50 furyking50]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/furyking50">@furyking50</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>All the ideas are great I would totally play.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rs2-sandbox-server-read-please-p/539650/9">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rs2-sandbox-server-read-please-p/539650/9</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 10 Feb 2014 02:58:44 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-539650-9</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rs2-sandbox-server-read-please-p/539650.rss">RS2 sandbox server (read please :P)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>RS2 sandbox server (read please :P)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@fuzzout fuzzout]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/fuzzout">@fuzzout</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote" data-post="7" data-topic="539650">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/docent/40/5_e05bb34c421432ee4d40de30c10af3e5.png" class="avatar"> Docent:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Vain_, what you are describing is multiplayer survival minecraft (on a good server).</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Not necessarily; albeit a similar element <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=5" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
<p>Running out of resources to promote interaction among players (good idea!); it is an MMO-style game after all; interaction is everything. A game where you can be a master blacksmith discussing trades with a master crafter… THAT is a good game.</p>
<p>He refers to a similar situation… world runs out of resources to give you incentive to do things outside of combat or searching for items… Things like farming (planting a tree) e.t.c.</p>
<p>P.S. I am looking for one person to have access to the server at all times <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=5" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"> To just randomly come on and test out the connection + random crap I’ve shoved into it. A play-tester if you will.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rs2-sandbox-server-read-please-p/539650/8">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rs2-sandbox-server-read-please-p/539650/8</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2014 00:19:05 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-539650-8</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rs2-sandbox-server-read-please-p/539650.rss">RS2 sandbox server (read please :P)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>RS2 sandbox server (read please :P)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Docent Limits]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/docent">@Docent</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Vain_, what you are describing is multiplayer survival minecraft (on a good server).</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rs2-sandbox-server-read-please-p/539650/7">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rs2-sandbox-server-read-please-p/539650/7</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2014 00:10:22 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-539650-7</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rs2-sandbox-server-read-please-p/539650.rss">RS2 sandbox server (read please :P)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>RS2 sandbox server (read please :P)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@fuzzout fuzzout]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/fuzzout">@fuzzout</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Actually, Vain you have a very awesome idea indeed… I completely didn’t think about the “supply &amp; demand” aspect of it in that much detail… it was a different setup… However, I will try to apply your methods to what I implement <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=5" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
<p>However; many of the mechanics in my server… like gathering of items… work differently.</p>
<p>Runite ore, for instance CAN be mined; but it is also a drop from a monster of high difficulty.<br>
Pickaxes break very often, thus needing to be repaired (by those who chose to invest into finding an item that does that; which in itself is something that must be assembled); this would promote interaction among players who have different items/specialties to help each other.<br>
You might think at this point: “But how will players trust each other when trading items(to fix) and then to get the items back?”; I solve this problem by the magic of glowing circles.<br>
A player uses the repair tool (repairs anything damaged); this tool creates a glowing circle in front of the caster, if anyone steps into this circle - their broken items are fixed. The helper gets money (from the server, not the player), the one in need of help gets their pickaxe back!</p>
<p>ta-da!<br>
Edit: I just finished up a code for the repair tool; and it works 100% ^^. Was pretty simple to create too!</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rs2-sandbox-server-read-please-p/539650/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rs2-sandbox-server-read-please-p/539650/6</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2014 21:06:17 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-539650-6</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rs2-sandbox-server-read-please-p/539650.rss">RS2 sandbox server (read please :P)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>RS2 sandbox server (read please :P)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Vain1 Vain_]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/vain1">@Vain1</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I always thought of making a dynamic base, but never put any effort towards it. I wrote out a lot of ideas, if anyone cares to find the post.</p>
<p>a few would be like: all objects have singular instances. once a tree is cut down, it is gone. if a tree is not cut (or cared for) after so long, it dies. and a dead tree appears. dead trees can be cut but won’t yield the same amount of resources, if any.</p>
<p>this makes demand for farmers to go around and replant tree seeds as well as tend to the trees available.</p>
<p>fishing bodies of water (mainly rivers) can deplete after so long. once depleted, there will be no fishing spots (or spots remain but no yield) available. this drives the player to further adventure the game.</p>
<p>ores do not respawn after a few seconds. all rocks in the game are randomly transformed into different ores (such as the iron in the rimmington mine, might turn into adamant.) and once that ore is mined, it’s gone forever (or a few days/hours however you want to do it.).<br>
this will drive players to travel around the game in search of the rarest ores, and spots to mine to train. this makes smithing and mining both highly sought after (having a cape would stand out) it also makes the ores a decent method for cash as they wouldn’t be very populated.<br>
also, instead of each rock only giving one ore, they would randomly collect amounts of the ore (think oak trees)</p>
<p>I’m too lazy to keep typing more. so if someone wants to find my ideas then post it, also if anyone wants custom ideas for their server: shoot me a pm with your thoughts/what you need and I’ll try my best.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rs2-sandbox-server-read-please-p/539650/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rs2-sandbox-server-read-please-p/539650/5</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2014 20:33:29 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-539650-5</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rs2-sandbox-server-read-please-p/539650.rss">RS2 sandbox server (read please :P)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>RS2 sandbox server (read please :P)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Clawz_fury lare69]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/clawz_fury">@Clawz_fury</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“fuzzout, post:3, topic:539650”][quote author=Clawz fury link=topic=658490.msg4404597#msg4404597 date=1391532655]<br>
hate to be so blunt about it but I doubt anyone cares, just go for it dude do whatever makes you happy. you don’t need our judgement<br>
[/quote]</p>
<p>Well, I was just asking to see how people would receive such a thing <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=5" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"> To see if I could host this for people to play it.[/quote]<br>
oh my mistake, yeah id play it. I’m open to anything (not retarded) though</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rs2-sandbox-server-read-please-p/539650/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rs2-sandbox-server-read-please-p/539650/4</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2014 17:22:29 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-539650-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rs2-sandbox-server-read-please-p/539650.rss">RS2 sandbox server (read please :P)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>RS2 sandbox server (read please :P)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@fuzzout fuzzout]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/fuzzout">@fuzzout</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote" data-post="2" data-topic="539650">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 Clawz fury:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>hate to be so blunt about it but I doubt anyone cares, just go for it dude do whatever makes you happy. you don’t need our judgement</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Well, I was just asking to see how people would receive such a thing <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=5" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"> To see if I could host this for people to play it.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rs2-sandbox-server-read-please-p/539650/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rs2-sandbox-server-read-please-p/539650/3</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2014 16:52:27 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-539650-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rs2-sandbox-server-read-please-p/539650.rss">RS2 sandbox server (read please :P)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>RS2 sandbox server (read please :P)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Clawz_fury lare69]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/clawz_fury">@Clawz_fury</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>hate to be so blunt about it but I doubt anyone cares, just go for it dude do whatever makes you happy. you don’t need our judgement</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rs2-sandbox-server-read-please-p/539650/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rs2-sandbox-server-read-please-p/539650/2</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2014 16:50:55 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-539650-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rs2-sandbox-server-read-please-p/539650.rss">RS2 sandbox server (read please :P)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>RS2 sandbox server (read please :P)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@fuzzout fuzzout]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/fuzzout">@fuzzout</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Hello <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=5" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
<p>I have engaged myself into a great endeavor… to create something that’s missing in online games.</p>
<p>An online game with no directions… a world where everything does something regardless of your progress in quests/levels or whatever. I find some games are too combat centric, to the point where it just becomes boring grind.<br>
While I agree that Runescape (at least, the old version) used to do this somewhat well; I simply didn’t enjoy the pacing.<br>
So imagine… you log into the server, customize your character and that’s it… Do whatever you want.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">So what am I setting out to do?</span><br>
I am working to change the mechanics to how items are found/obtained in RS2 and create a server where, if you kill a monster; it will not drop pants… rather it will drop an item piece which will aid you in creating said pants.<br>
The crafting system will be completely different… there will be no “5 bars to create a rune chest piece”, there will be no steel armor… Iron armor, then next one up is mithril… and the way to obtain mithril is to take an iron ore and enchant it in a magical location <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=5" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"> e.t.c.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b"><span class="bbcode-i">An example, please?</span></span><br>
Dragon square shield will be the best shield in the game, as it will heal you whenever a dragon breath hits you, it is one hell of an awesome shield… In my server, one half will be guarded by an iron dragon, the other half will be guarded by a steel dragon… if you pick up the piece before killing this dragon; it will enrage and burn your nuts off.<br>
To merge the two halves of this shield; you need to have the two halves in your inventory and you need to engage a normal dragon without any dragon-fire protection (dragonfire shield/dragon square shield/anti-fire potion), the two halves of the shield will begin to tremble under the dragonfires magical properties and will merge together (the player must equip the shield immediately or they are in great danger of death).</p>
<p>OR</p>
<p>To a lesser extent… imagine you have a set of shears… and you want those equippable flowers… Just use the shears on some flowers on the ground… voilá.</p>
<p>And that is just one of the things… The end idea is… Create a sandbox of difficult progress; awesome boss fights; exploration and rewards… craftsmanship, player professions and interaction.</p>
<p>This will be done in an un-modded 317 client (Moparscape client) for accessibility and simplicity.</p>
<p>CURRENT PROGRESS:<br>
Crafting framework (and basic smithing) - done.<br>
Smelting framework - done.<br>
Scribe system (only used for certain things in the game) - in progress.</p>
<p>Notes:<br>
This is still an idea in progress <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=5" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"> I am writing myself a “DIRECTION” document to have a clear, un-changing goal in mind.<br>
All skills will be utilized in some respects.</p>
<p>Let me know what you think <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=5" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"> Would you play it?<br>
I am looking for peoples opinions to see if there’s any point in me attempting to host this… If you don’t have anything you can think of to say, just put a score like… out of 10. <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=5" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rs2-sandbox-server-read-please-p/539650/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rs2-sandbox-server-read-please-p/539650/1</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2014 16:20:13 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-539650-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rs2-sandbox-server-read-please-p/539650.rss">RS2 sandbox server (read please :P)</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
