<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Skill Problems</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/skill-problems/336547</link>
    <description>hello guys =D
I have an little problem... and I need that someone explain what I must do.
well when someone create an acount... it will be added in the inventory 5k bronze arrows.. and when some one wield it and shot in some npc&#39;s, the arrows in the inventory will never lose...
example :
I have 5000 arrows in my bag, i shot 100 in npc&#39;s, but it stays in 5000 arrows... with the runes is different, I have 500 rune but when I shot 100 at then It will stay 400 runes.
How do I fix that ?
and another problem.
my members says that is annoying buying arrows and runes 1 each of the time... i wanted to put the &quot;X&quot; marker for them to buy whatever the number of runes and arrows they wanted... how do I fix that too ?
I really Apreciate the help.


Cumpz.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 11 Apr 2010 21:37:49 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Game Development</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/skill-problems/336547.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Skill Problems</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Balazyo94 Balazyo94]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/balazyo94">@Balazyo94</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>hello guys =D<br>
I have an little problem… and I need that someone explain what I must do.<br>
well when someone create an acount… it will be added in the inventory 5k bronze arrows… and when some one wield it and shot in some npc’s, the arrows in the inventory will never lose…<br>
example :<br>
I have 5000 arrows in my bag, i shot 100 in npc’s, but it stays in 5000 arrows… with the runes is different, I have 500 rune but when I shot 100 at then It will stay 400 runes.<br>
How do I fix that ?<br>
and another problem.<br>
my members says that is annoying buying arrows and runes 1 each of the time… i wanted to put the “X” marker for them to buy whatever the number of runes and arrows they wanted… how do I fix that too ?<br>
I really Apreciate the help.</p>
<p>Cumpz.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/skill-problems/336547/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/skill-problems/336547/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 11 Apr 2010 21:37:49 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-336547-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/skill-problems/336547.rss">Skill Problems</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
