<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Battle-Ages</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/battle-ages/540597</link>
    <description>[CENTER][URL=http://&quot;http://battle-ages.cf&quot;][IMG]http://i62.tinypic.com/w2k12s.png[/img][/URL]

I&#39;d like to give you all a first welcome to the first step in reviving our server, Battle-Ages. We are using Project Insanity as the servers base I am currently using a free webhost (unlimited) their may be some downtime, the web hosts will be changed to .net soon.

We will also have slight usergroup changes, I&#39;ll have the whole hierarchy of the staff and their roles in a thread. With all of that said, as you can tell, even though the forums are completed, to an extent, the server is currently in development. I got the forum up running earlier for you guys so you can sit around, chat, give feedback and suggestions, and all of that good stuff. This way we can also have a little place for all of the excited members waiting to play the server again all collaborate here.[/CENTER]

[B]Development Team[/B]
[img]http://www.rune-server.org/static/crown/admin.gif[/img][B][COLOR=#b22222]Mod Nick[/COLOR][/B]

[B]Updates Log[/B]
[SPOILer]Client music
XP Counter[/SPOILer]

[B]Media[/B]
[SPOILer][img]http://gyazo.com/f3c56ea79e6d2fea0b64d64736df1fc8.png[/img][/SPOILer]</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2014 01:43:51 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Uncategorized</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/battle-ages/540597.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Battle-Ages</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@battleages battleages]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/battleages">@battleages</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[CENTER][URL=http://“<a href="http://battle-ages.cf" rel="nofollow noopener">http://battle-ages.cf</a>”]<img src="http://i62.tinypic.com/w2k12s.png" alt width="" height="">[/URL]</p>
<p>I’d like to give you all a first welcome to the first step in reviving our server, Battle-Ages. We are using Project Insanity as the servers base I am currently using a free webhost (unlimited) their may be some downtime, the web hosts will be changed to .net soon.</p>
<p>We will also have slight usergroup changes, I’ll have the whole hierarchy of the staff and their roles in a thread. With all of that said, as you can tell, even though the forums are completed, to an extent, the server is currently in development. I got the forum up running earlier for you guys so you can sit around, chat, give feedback and suggestions, and all of that good stuff. This way we can also have a little place for all of the excited members waiting to play the server again all collaborate here.[/CENTER]</p>
<p>[B]Development Team[/B]<br>
<img src="http://www.rune-server.org/static/crown/admin.gif" alt width="" height="">[B][COLOR=#b22222]Mod Nick[/COLOR][/B]</p>
<p>[B]Updates Log[/B]<br>
[SPOILer]Client music<br>
XP Counter[/SPOILer]</p>
<p>[B]Media[/B]<br>
[SPOILer]<img src="http://gyazo.com/f3c56ea79e6d2fea0b64d64736df1fc8.png" alt width="" height="">[/SPOILer]</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/battle-ages/540597/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/battle-ages/540597/1</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2014 01:43:51 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-540597-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/battle-ages/540597.rss">Battle-Ages</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
