<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>How this system is intended to work [Updated 06/08/2012] - Added protocol</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-this-system-is-intended-to-work-updated-06-08-2012-added-protocol/444079</link>
    <description>Basically, we just discuss stuff that&#39;s not approved. If something is denied, throw it in this board (for now). You can keep it disapproved for now. We have no feature that allows us to disapprove an approved topic, but I will push for that to be added to the forum in the future.

As far as banning members from this board is concerned, there is no system currently in place for that. I will add it when we need it. If someone needs to be banned from the board, just post their name in this topic and I will get around to doing that. There&#39;s no easy way to allow you guys as a whole team to add and remove people from that group yet, so this is the alternative (and hopefully temporary) solution.

Edit: Move expired topics to the expired board. Make sure they remain hidden. Users can still see their topics but cannot post in them. Move them back if they are to reopen for discussion. We want the main suggestions board to be as empty as possible, so we can continually discuss queued topics.

Just added a new rule called the three day rule. Since I&#39;m one of the only moderators making use of the expired section, I figure this would be good to add. Basically, take the one following actions depending on what&#39;s going on, after 3 days:


[ul][li]If most of the moderators have sided to a single decision, it can be solved (read below).[/li]
[li]If one of you asked a question that the user has not answered within those three days, say that it has expired and mark it as resolved by moving it to the resolved section.[/li]
[li]If no moderators have responded to the topic, please try to respond to it so decision can be made. [b]The three-day rule applies after the last mod posts, not when the topic is created.[/b][/li]
[li]If you guys are collectively unsure about what do with a topic, say that it is being discussed by the staff members and post it in the MoparScape staff section to discuss.[/li][/ul]


How to handle a topic: if none of the above apply and a topic can genuinely be solved, try to solve it yourselves. If you need a global moderator or administrate to do it, message one (or me) with the link and someone will get to it as soon as possible. You can optionally let the user know that it&#39;s being handled by another staff member. That staff member is expected to move it to the expired section after solving it.

Post any concerns with this protocol if you have any. :P</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 06 Jun 2012 20:37:21 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Community Suggestions</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-this-system-is-intended-to-work-updated-06-08-2012-added-protocol/444079.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>How this system is intended to work [Updated 06/08/2012] - Added protocol</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@mod_taharok Taharok]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/mod_taharok">@mod_taharok</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I just thought of another idea for posting. If it’s too sensitive and may harm someone if it were to accidentally go public, then it’s better off not in the topics. Heaven forbid a moderator gets exploited and goes rogue, they could easily publicize every single thread in both of the sections. If they aren’t sensitive, then it does little harm.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-this-system-is-intended-to-work-updated-06-08-2012-added-protocol/444079/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-this-system-is-intended-to-work-updated-06-08-2012-added-protocol/444079/5</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 06 Jun 2012 20:37:21 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-444079-5</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-this-system-is-intended-to-work-updated-06-08-2012-added-protocol/444079.rss">How this system is intended to work [Updated 06/08/2012] - Added protocol</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>How this system is intended to work [Updated 06/08/2012] - Added protocol</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@mod_taharok Taharok]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/mod_taharok">@mod_taharok</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote quote-modified" data-post="3" data-topic="444079">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/user_avatar/forum.moparisthebest.com/davidi2/40/2579_1.png" class="avatar"> Davidi2:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Yea I tried to keep my reply pretty ambiguous to that thread, but I can’t tell if I did it enough and you are directing that towards me <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/expressionless.png?v=5" title=":expressionless:" class="emoji" alt=":expressionless:"></p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I was actually referring to myself. <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=5" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"> I find it difficult not to disclose any more information than is necessary for the member to know. You did a better job than me, so I figured I’d post about it here.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-this-system-is-intended-to-work-updated-06-08-2012-added-protocol/444079/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-this-system-is-intended-to-work-updated-06-08-2012-added-protocol/444079/4</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 06 Jun 2012 05:22:35 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-444079-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-this-system-is-intended-to-work-updated-06-08-2012-added-protocol/444079.rss">How this system is intended to work [Updated 06/08/2012] - Added protocol</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>How this system is intended to work [Updated 06/08/2012] - Added protocol</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@davidi2 Davidi2]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/davidi2">@davidi2</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Yea I tried to keep my reply pretty ambiguous to that thread, but I can’t tell if I did it enough and you are directing that towards me <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/expressionless.png?v=5" title=":expressionless:" class="emoji" alt=":expressionless:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-this-system-is-intended-to-work-updated-06-08-2012-added-protocol/444079/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-this-system-is-intended-to-work-updated-06-08-2012-added-protocol/444079/3</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 06 Jun 2012 00:05:43 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-444079-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-this-system-is-intended-to-work-updated-06-08-2012-added-protocol/444079.rss">How this system is intended to work [Updated 06/08/2012] - Added protocol</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>How this system is intended to work [Updated 06/08/2012] - Added protocol</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@mod_taharok Taharok]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/mod_taharok">@mod_taharok</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Just an addendum: be careful with how you reply to the topics. For example, the topic posted about raising the rep limit is very involved with our discussion of changing/removing rep, but that doesn’t mean that we can disclose that information (obviously). My personal policy is, if their change is not directly related to what we are talking about in the staff sections, we cannot disclose anything. I don’t agree that the rep limit should be changed, but I do agree rep in itself should be changed. He can’t know that, though.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-this-system-is-intended-to-work-updated-06-08-2012-added-protocol/444079/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-this-system-is-intended-to-work-updated-06-08-2012-added-protocol/444079/2</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 05 Jun 2012 23:20:37 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-444079-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-this-system-is-intended-to-work-updated-06-08-2012-added-protocol/444079.rss">How this system is intended to work [Updated 06/08/2012] - Added protocol</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>How this system is intended to work [Updated 06/08/2012] - Added protocol</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@mod_taharok Taharok]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/mod_taharok">@mod_taharok</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Basically, we just discuss stuff that’s not approved. If something is denied, throw it in this board (for now). You can keep it disapproved for now. We have no feature that allows us to disapprove an approved topic, but I will push for that to be added to the forum in the future.</p>
<p>As far as banning members from this board is concerned, there is no system currently in place for that. I will add it when we need it. If someone needs to be banned from the board, just post their name in this topic and I will get around to doing that. There’s no easy way to allow you guys as a whole team to add and remove people from that group yet, so this is the alternative (and hopefully temporary) solution.</p>
<p>Edit: Move expired topics to the expired board. Make sure they remain hidden. Users can still see their topics but cannot post in them. Move them back if they are to reopen for discussion. We want the main suggestions board to be as empty as possible, so we can continually discuss queued topics.</p>
<p>Just added a new rule called the three day rule. Since I’m one of the only moderators making use of the expired section, I figure this would be good to add. Basically, take the one following actions depending on what’s going on, after 3 days:</p>
<p>[ul][li]If most of the moderators have sided to a single decision, it can be solved (read below).[/li]<br>
[li]If one of you asked a question that the user has not answered within those three days, say that it has expired and mark it as resolved by moving it to the resolved section.[/li]<br>
[li]If no moderators have responded to the topic, please try to respond to it so decision can be made. <span class="bbcode-b">The three-day rule applies after the last mod posts, not when the topic is created.</span>[/li]<br>
[li]If you guys are collectively unsure about what do with a topic, say that it is being discussed by the staff members and post it in the MoparScape staff section to discuss.[/li][/ul]</p>
<p>How to handle a topic: if none of the above apply and a topic can genuinely be solved, try to solve it yourselves. If you need a global moderator or administrate to do it, message one (or me) with the link and someone will get to it as soon as possible. You can optionally let the user know that it’s being handled by another staff member. That staff member is expected to move it to the expired section after solving it.</p>
<p>Post any concerns with this protocol if you have any. <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=5" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-this-system-is-intended-to-work-updated-06-08-2012-added-protocol/444079/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-this-system-is-intended-to-work-updated-06-08-2012-added-protocol/444079/1</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 05 Jun 2012 15:30:39 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-444079-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-this-system-is-intended-to-work-updated-06-08-2012-added-protocol/444079.rss">How this system is intended to work [Updated 06/08/2012] - Added protocol</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
