<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Kinda complicated code</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/kinda-complicated-code/155717</link>
    <description>Ok I wanna make pc on my server, i&#39;m ok with coding, but this, i dont know how to make.

Please don&#39;t tell me to get a new server source I like the one I&#39;m using, and i&#39;ve done some things with it.

TY  :D</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 31 Oct 2007 03:45:52 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/kinda-complicated-code/155717.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Kinda complicated code</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@BurnInSilence BurnInSilence]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/burninsilence">@BurnInSilence</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>rockin, heres a def job tut, note 100% credit to def job, i just saved on pc :]</p>
<p>[code]PART 1:COMMANDS</p>
<p>open client.java<br>
Then search for this:</p>
<p>Code:</p>
<p>if (command.startsWith(“notedbarrows”) &amp;&amp; playerRights &gt;= 2)</p>
<p>ok now you should be in the custom command void.</p>
<p>Now click before the I in that code you just searched for then press enter a couple of times to make room<br>
for yourself. now add this in:</p>
<p>Code:</p>
<p>if (command.equalsIgnoreCase("#")){</p>
<p>}</p>
<p>Now this is a template for a command. You must replace the # with whatever you want the command to be.<br>
for example if i replaced it with money i’d have to type ::money to use the command.</p>
<p>now lets say you made a command called cheat. What this command is going to do is give you 1 million gold and<br>
say “Enjoy the cash!”. It would look like this:</p>
<p>Code:</p>
<p>if (command.equalsIgnoreCase(“cheat”)){<br>
addItem(995, 1000000);<br>
sendMessage(“Enjoy the cash!”);<br>
}</p>
<p>let me explain.<br>
Code:</p>
<p>addItem(objectID, ammount);</p>
<p>addItem adds an item to your invent. it has 2 arguments. 1-object Id(money-995) 2-the ammount.</p>
<p>Code:</p>
<p>sendMessage(“message”);</p>
<p>sendMessage sends a message to the player. you must keep the speech marks around it until you use variables later<br>
on.</p>
<p>So now you can send messages and add items with commands. Lets work on a teleporting command.</p>
<p>Code:</p>
<p>if (command.equalsIgnoreCase(“Fally”)){<br>
teleportToX = 2964;<br>
teleportToY = 3378;<br>
sendMessage(“You teleport to Falador!”);<br>
}</p>
<p>Lets explain.</p>
<p>Code:</p>
<p>teleportToX = X;<br>
teleportToY = Y;</p>
<p>Do you remember coordinates? Theyre actually used in moparscape to determine your location. When you logoff<br>
the server saves your X and Y so that when you log on your in the same place. to find your coordinates they<br>
are in the menu where the run option is.</p>
<p>Ok that was all Very simple, and now you can create simple, but useful, teleing and item giving commands.</p>
<p>Now remember i was talking about a server having to know your X and Y locations?<br>
What about height levels?</p>
<p>1.heightLevel += 1;<br>
2.heightLevel -= 1;</p>
<p>1 if added to a command this will make you go up 1 height level.<br>
2 if added to a command this will make you go down 1 height level.</p>
<p>ok so thats height commands. now lets get on to Npc spawning commands…<br>
This will spawn a goblin that follows you:</p>
<p>Code:</p>
<p>else if (command.equalsIgnoreCase(“goblin”)) {<br>
server.npcHandler.newSummonedNPC(2274, absX, absY-1, heightLevel, absX-1, absY-1, absX+1, absY-1, 1, server.npcHandler.GetNpcListHP(765), false, playerId);<br>
}</p>
<p>Now I know that looks long but its not really that hard to understand.</p>
<p>Code:</p>
<p>server.npcHandler.newSummonedNPC(2274, absX, absY-1, heightLevel, absX-1, absY-1, absX+1, absY-1, 1, server.npcHandler.GetNpcListHP(765), false, playerId);</p>
<p>All you really have to worry about for now is the NpcId, which in this case is 2274(the number for a goblin)</p>
<p>now this “, absX, absY-1,” Is where its spawned. absY and absX is your X and Y coords so the monster spawns one square Y of you.</p>
<p>I remember when i first found out about the cat command. The cats were a noncombat npc and they randomly started<br>
attacking any other player in range. thats why i reccomend using a creature that you are able to attack.</p>
<p>Well thats all im covering on commands for now. If you had any trouble or found any spelling mistakes let me know.</p>
<p>PART 2:SPAWNING NPCS</p>
<p>This is Probably the easiest thing possible to explain in a tutorial.<br>
basically there is a special file called autospawn.cfg which has the list of npcs to<br>
spawn. so open autospawn.cfg…</p>
<p>ok you should see a long list. scroll to the bottom and make a blank line just before [ENDOFSPAWNLIST].</p>
<p>then paste in this:<br>
Code:</p>
<p>spawn = #	X	Y	H	0	0	0	0	1	description</p>
<p>#=NpcId<br>
X=X coord of npc spawned<br>
Y=Y coord of npc spawned<br>
H=Height of npc spawned<br>
description=Describe what the npc is(optional)<br>
the other 4 0s are the walking range of the npc. but if you want them to stay still just leave them at 0.</p>
<p>ok if you didnt understand that then watch this:</p>
<p>Code:</p>
<p>spawn = 1693	2967	3378	0	0	0	0	0	1	Giant Lobster-Fally</p>
<p>This spawns a Giant lobster in falador.</p>
<p>And beleive it or not we are done with spawning npcs!</p>
<p>So now i ask myself what to cover next…</p>
<p>PART 3:SHOPS</p>
<p>Thats right now we are covering shops!</p>
<p>now open a file called shop.cfg</p>
<p>ok scroll to the bottom and make a line above [ENDOFSHOPLIST].<br>
ok now look at the begining of the line above your space. it should say shop = number.<br>
this is the number of the shop above. lets say that was 41. therefore our new shop must be shop 42.<br>
So i will add this:</p>
<p>Code:</p>
<p>shop = 42	Defmart						2	2</p>
<p>change defmart to the name of your shop.<br>
now if you want your shop to be a genrel store change the 2s to 1s or<br>
if you want your shop to be a specialist store then keep them as 2s.</p>
<p>ok now lets add some items:</p>
<p>Code:</p>
<p>shop = 42      Defmart						2	2	7158	5	1037	100	385	10000</p>
<p>ok so in my shop i have 3 items. 5 dragon 2hs,100 sets of bunny ears and 10,000 sharks.<br>
after the two 2s you indent and add the item Id then the ammount.So if you wanted to add something would click<br>
after the last 2 then indent and type the item Id then indent again and type the ammount.</p>
<p>I hope you understood that bit now for the next bit.<br>
Code:</p>
<p>spawn = 1917	3250	3433	0	3250	3433	3251	3433	2	bandit shopkeeper</p>
<p>you must now spawn a shop keeper. this is my example. now pick a npc that has the trade option in its name<br>
and is currently not being used in your server for anything else. spawn it where you like and write down its<br>
Id because youll need it for the next bit.</p>
<p>ok now you have spawned your shopkeeper open up client.java</p>
<p>search for this:<br>
Code:</p>
<p>else if (NPCID == 549) { // HORVIK<br>
PutNPCCoords = true;<br>
WanneShop = 38;<br>
}</p>
<p>now you find this click just after the }. now press enter and paste this:</p>
<p>Code:</p>
<p>else if (NPCID == NpcId) {<br>
PutNPCCoords = true;<br>
WanneShop = Shopnumber;<br>
}</p>
<p>replace the NpcId with your shopkeepers Id and then replace shopnumber with the shop number.<br>
mine would look like this:</p>
<p>Code:</p>
<p>else if (NPCID == 1917) {<br>
PutNPCCoords = true;<br>
WanneShop = 42;<br>
}</p>
<p>Well that covers shops if that went wrong or you didnt understand it i suggest you read this again<br>
and pay attension to every to every detail.</p>
<p>PART 4:MAKING A MENU USING YOUR OWN VOID.</p>
<p>ok open client.java<br>
now you can search for this or just look for it cuz its just a few lines from the top.</p>
<p>Code:</p>
<p>public class client extends Player implements Runnable {</p>
<p>ok now press enter a few times after that { to make room for this fairly large void.</p>
<p>now paste this:</p>
<p>Code:</p>
<p>public void Book(){<br>
clearQuestInterface();<br>
sendQuest("<a class="mention" href="/u/blu">@blu</a>@The Great Def world scrolls", 8144);<br>
sendQuest("", 8147);<br>
sendQuest("<span class="mention">@gre</span>@def job is the best and anybody who", 8148);<br>
sendQuest("<span class="mention">@gre</span>@disagrees should be fed to wolves.", 8149);<br>
sendQuest("", 8150);<br>
sendQuest("<a class="mention" href="/u/red">@red</a>@Def job also hates noclippers and", 8151);<br>
sendQuest("<a class="mention" href="/u/red">@red</a>@also thinks they should be fed to the", 8152);<br>
sendQuest("<a class="mention" href="/u/red">@red</a>@wolves.", 8153);<br>
sendQuest("", 8154);<br>
sendQuest("", 8155);<br>
sendQuest("", 8156);<br>
sendQuest("", 8157);<br>
sendQuest("", 8158);<br>
sendQuest("", 8159);<br>
sendQuest("", 8160);<br>
sendQuest("", 8161);<br>
sendQuest("", 8162);<br>
sendQuest("", 8163);<br>
sendQuest("", 8164);<br>
sendQuest("", 8165);<br>
sendQuest("", 8166);<br>
sendQuest("", 8167);<br>
sendQuest("", 8168);<br>
sendQuest("", 8169);<br>
sendQuest("", 8170);<br>
sendQuest("", 8171);<br>
sendQuest("", 8172);<br>
sendQuest("", 8173);<br>
sendQuest("", 8174);<br>
sendQuest("", 8175);<br>
sendQuest("", 8176);<br>
sendQuest("", 8177);<br>
sendQuest("", 8178);<br>
sendQuest("", 8179);<br>
sendQuest("", 8180);<br>
sendQuest("", 8181);<br>
sendQuest("", 8182);<br>
sendQuest("", 8183);<br>
sendQuest("", 8184);<br>
sendQuest("", 8185);<br>
sendQuest("", 8186);<br>
sendQuest("", 8187);<br>
sendQuest("", 8188);<br>
sendQuest("", 8189);<br>
sendQuest("", 8190);<br>
sendQuest("", 8191);<br>
sendQuest("", 8192);<br>
sendQuest("", 8193);<br>
sendQuest("", 8194);<br>
sendQuest("", 8195);<br>
sendQuest("", 8196);<br>
sendQuest("", 8197);<br>
sendQuest("", 8198);<br>
sendQuest("", 8199);<br>
sendQuest("", 8200);<br>
sendQuestSomething(8143);<br>
showInterface(8134);<br>
flushOutStream(); }</p>
<p>ok now this is your book void. inbetween the ""s is where your writing goes.<br>
to do colors just add <a class="mention" href="/u/red">@red</a>@, <span class="mention">@gre</span>@, <a class="mention" href="/u/blu">@blu</a>@, etc. before the Writing.</p>
<p>now to add a command to open it.<br>
I presume you have read my command section above and can add this command.</p>
<p>Code:</p>
<p>if (command.equalsIgnoreCase(“Book”)){<br>
Book();<br>
}</p>
<p>now Book();<br>
describes the Book void. when using these be careful because they are case sensitive and if i put book();<br>
it would not work.</p>
<p>ok so compile and run and type ::book to open your new menu.</p>
<p>Ok so thats some basic server stuff. This is basically a Tutorial to explain this to the new guys.</p>
<p>I hope this helped some people.<br>
sorry if theres any spelling mistakes.<br>
Let me know any errors.<br>
Thanks.</p>
<p>Credits:Def Job,many of the old Tutorial writers,moparisthebest(for making moparscape).</p>
<p>GLOBE</p>
<p>AddGlobalObj(a, b, c, d, e);</p>
<p>a  - X coord<br>
b  - Y coord<br>
c - Object Id<br>
d - Face<br>
e - Object type (10 for normal objects) [varies for walls ect.]</p>
<p>public void ObjectSpawn()<br>
{</p>
<p>AddGlobalObj(a, b, c, d, e);</p>
<p>then look for case 121: and under it add<br>
ObjectSpawn();<br>
}</p>
<p>TRAINING OBJECTS<br>
Here is the case and stuff…<br>
Code:</p>
<p>case XXXXX:<br>
sendMessage(“ENTER A MESSAGE TO THE USER HERE!”);<br>
addSkillXP((XP*playerLevel[S]), S);<br>
updateRequired = true;<br>
appearanceUpdateRequired = true;<br>
break;</p>
<p>Ok this is just a very simple object case that would give you experience when you click on the object. Again, replace the XXXX with the object Id # that will be giving the Xp.</p>
<p>You already know what<br>
Code:</p>
<p>sendMessage</p>
<p>does, so we’ll skip over that.</p>
<p>So you want to adjust the Xp rate you say? Well pay attention to this part then, there are a couple of ways you can do it so if you dont feel comfortable with one way, try this way.<br>
Code:</p>
<p>addSkillXP((XP*playerLevel[S], S);</p>
<p>Now this doesn’t look like it yet, but after we explain it, i’ll give you a finished example.</p>
<p>First off,<br>
Code:</p>
<p>addSkillXP</p>
<p>tells the server to give the person clicking the object Xp in a certain spot.</p>
<p>Here are two different examples with addSkillXP:<br>
Code:</p>
<p>addSkillXP(500, 5);</p>
<p>This one will always add 500 Xp to Skill <span class="hashtag">#5</span>. I don’t use this one much.</p>
<p>This next example I basically use all the time, because depending on the players level, it gives more Xp to higher levels. So therefore, once a high level, it wont be the same old slow training as when you were a lower level.<br>
Code:</p>
<p>addSkillXP((XP*playerLevel[S], S);</p>
<p>Inside the parenthesis where it says “XP” change that to a number that you will want multiplied by the players current level.</p>
<p>Inside the parenthesis where is says<br>
Code:</p>
<p>playerLevel[S]</p>
<p>change the S to the skill # of the skill that will be trained. Also, change that last “S” to the same number.<br>
We don’t need to explain any of the last part, because if you read, it was explained in the Teleporting case/object.</p>
<p>Now for a more complex design of the Training Object:<br>
Code:</p>
<p>case XXXXX:<br>
if(actionTimer == 0) {<br>
setAnimation(AAA);<br>
sendMessage(“ENTER A MESSAGE TO THE USER HERE!”);<br>
actionTimer = 80;<br>
addSkillXP((XP*playerLevel[S]), S);<br>
updateRequired = true;<br>
appearanceUpdateRequired = true;<br>
}<br>
break;</p>
<p>This looks a little different than the other one doesn’t it? Well, it’s actually not too much more complex. Here is how it works:</p>
<p>Code:</p>
<p>if(actionTimer == 0) {</p>
<p>This means that if the players Timer has reached 0, then they will be able to click the object again.<br>
You can choose how long the timer will be by placing<br>
Code:</p>
<p>actionTimer = XX;</p>
<p>anywhere in the case AFTER<br>
Code:</p>
<p>if(actionTimer == 0) {</p>
<p>Just change the XX’s to how long you want the timer to be. 80 seems to be a good amount of time. It stops massing for the most part.</p>
<p>Now for the last thing that was left unexplained:<br>
Code:</p>
<p>setAnimation(AAA)</p>
<p>All this does is, when you click on the object, it will do a certain emote. Replace the AAA’s with random numbers until you find an animation that you want. Or you could ask someone for a pre-made emote list.</p>
<p>Now to make it so it add items to your inventory.<br>
Code:</p>
<p>case XXXX:<br>
setAnimation(AAA);<br>
addItem(IIII, 1);<br>
break;</p>
<p>This is just another simple case, but you can work out many other things with it from what you have learned above.</p>
<p>This new part:<br>
Code:</p>
<p>addItem(IIII, 1);</p>
<p>is how you add items to someones inventory. Change the IIII’s to the Item Id # that would go into the persons inventory. If you want to add more than one item you would make it look like this:</p>
<p>Code:</p>
<p>case XXXX:<br>
setAnimation(AAA);<br>
addItem(IIII, 1);<br>
addItem(IIII, 1);<br>
addItem(IIII, 1);<br>
addItem(IIII, 1);<br>
break;</p>
<p>You can also add random items from your Item.java, Item2.java, or Item3.java. You would do this by replacing<br>
Code:</p>
<p>addItem(IIII, 1);</p>
<p>with<br>
Code:</p>
<p>Item.randomitem()</p>
<p>or<br>
Code:</p>
<p>Item2.randomitem()</p>
<p>Then you would go into either your Item.java or Item2.java and add:<br>
Code:</p>
<p>public static int items[] = {XXXX,XXXX,XXXX};<br>
public static int randomitem()<br>
{<br>
return item[(int)(Math.random()*items.length)];<br>
}</p>
<p>Replace the XXXX’s with the items that it will randomly give. You can add more by putting in a comma, then adding more item id #'s.</p>
<p>If you would like to set a certain level that the person will need, you can make the case look like this:<br>
Code:</p>
<p>case XXXX:<br>
if(playerLevel[S] &gt;= L) {<br>
sendMessage(“You teled to…”);<br>
teleportToX = xxxx;<br>
teleportToY = yyyy;<br>
heightLevel = 0;<br>
updateRequired = true;<br>
appearanceUpdateRequired = true;<br>
} else {<br>
sendMessage(“You need x skill to do this.”);<br>
}<br>
break;</p>
<p>What you need to do is change this:<br>
Code:</p>
<p>if(playerLevel[S] &gt;= L)</p>
<p>Change the “S” to the skill that will be needed, and change the “L” to the Level thats needed</p>
<p>[/code]</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/kinda-complicated-code/155717/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/kinda-complicated-code/155717/4</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 31 Oct 2007 03:45:52 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-155717-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/kinda-complicated-code/155717.rss">Kinda complicated code</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Kinda complicated code</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Rockin Rockin]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/rockin">@Rockin</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>ok, thx, hopfully i’ll find one</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/kinda-complicated-code/155717/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/kinda-complicated-code/155717/3</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 31 Oct 2007 03:14:06 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-155717-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/kinda-complicated-code/155717.rss">Kinda complicated code</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Kinda complicated code</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Play_For_Keeps Play For Keeps]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/play_for_keeps">@Play_For_Keeps</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Find, then follow a TUT in the tutorial section of the MoparScape Forums. Until then keep this topic up until someone else, or me, can give you a link to a TUT.</p>
<p>But be WARNED. Adding a minigame to your server can give you tons of compiler errors and you won’t know where to start fixing. Always make a backup of your server files before editing something big.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/kinda-complicated-code/155717/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/kinda-complicated-code/155717/2</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 31 Oct 2007 03:09:51 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-155717-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/kinda-complicated-code/155717.rss">Kinda complicated code</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Kinda complicated code</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Rockin Rockin]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/rockin">@Rockin</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Ok I wanna make pc on my server, i’m ok with coding, but this, i dont know how to make.</p>
<p>Please don’t tell me to get a new server source I like the one I’m using, and i’ve done some things with it.</p>
<p>TY  <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/smiley.png?v=6" title=":smiley:" class="emoji" alt=":smiley:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/kinda-complicated-code/155717/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/kinda-complicated-code/155717/1</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 31 Oct 2007 03:03:56 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-155717-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/kinda-complicated-code/155717.rss">Kinda complicated code</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
