<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Number of Uninsured Americans Soars To Over 50 Million</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/number-of-uninsured-americans-soars-to-over-50-million/375653</link>
    <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;Less than a year ago, Francis Campos-Dunn was still working at a county hospital in the San Francisco Bay Area, helping patients navigate the often-maddening bureaucracy required to draw on their health insurance. These days, she has a new set of problems to navigate: how to manage her own care without any insurance of her own, having slipped into an unfortunate but fast-growing slice of the population--Americans who have lost their jobs and now lack health coverage.

Back when she was still working, Campos-Dunn, 42, earned $4,000 a month, enough to make her co-payments for regular medical care. These days, she depends on $300 a month contributions from her 16-year-old son--money he earns at a part-time job--just to pay to the rent. When a recent seizure left her with two broken teeth, she skipped the required treatment and opted to have the teeth pulled instead, because she lacked the funds--a choice that would have previously seemed unthinkable.

As the Great Recession has sown unemployment and downgraded work even for those people who have held on to their jobs, the number of Americans lacking healthcare has swelled beyond 50 million, according to a sobering new report from the Kaiser Foundation.

Among the report&#39;s most troubling findings: The number of Americans without any health care coverage grew by more than four million in 2009. That left almost one-fifth of non-elderly people uninsured. Among those between 19 and 29 years old, nearly one-third lacked coverage.

The study underscores the degree to which the recession has accelerated the loss of basic elements once viewed as inextricable pieces of a middle class life. The number of Americans lacking medical coverage now exceeds the population of Spain.

Nearly all Americans over 65 are insured by Medicare, the government-run health care plan, but those beneath that age are increasingly vulnerable to losing health care once provided by their employers or finding themselves unable to afford private coverage, according to the report, &quot;The Uninsured: A Primer.&quot;

As those lacking health insurance grow in number, so do those missing out on necessary medical attention. About one-in-four uninsured adults have forgone care in the past year because of costs, compared to only 4 percent of those who have private coverage, according to the report.

Those lacking health coverage are vulnerable to what has become a commonplace financial calamity: confronting a medical emergency, and having to pay for care entirely out of pocket. This year, 27% of uninsured adults used up most or all of their savings paying medical bills, according to the study. Half of these uninsured households had total assets of $600 or less.

Medicaid covers Americans with the lowest incomes, but that fact merely mitigates conditions for people in abysmal circumstances: Medicaid beneficiaries are typically in much worse health than those with private coverage. They are likely to have incomes that place them well below the poverty line, and to suffer health conditions that impede their ability to work, exacerbating their difficulties.

Under the health reforms championed by President Obama, Medicaid is set to expand in 2014 to cover almost all people under 65 with incomes up to 138% of the federal poverty line. That would provide health care to many more Americans who now lack coverage. But until then, many Americans will continue to shoulder the burden of unaffordable health care costs.

The soaring number of people falling through the cracks and going without health insurance is in large part the result of the recession, which has eliminated millions of jobs, along with employer-sponsored coverage. Roughly half of all working age Americans with insurance have it through their employer.

Even among those who have avoided unemployment, millions have been forced to take temporary or part-time positions for lack of available full-time work, often surrendering their benefits in the process.

More than half of those who are officially unemployed have no health coverage whatsoever, according to a Rutgers University study, &quot;The Shattered American Dream: Unemployed Workers Lose Ground, Hope, and Faith in their Future.&quot; Those numbers increase to nearly 60% for those who have been unemployed for over six months. Six in ten unemployed Americans have been unemployed for over a year.

Yet even if the economy soon adds more jobs and lowers the ranks of the unemployed, the scarcity of health coverage is likely to endure, argues one of the study&#39;s authors, Carl Van Horn, Professor of Public Policy at Rutgers University and Director of the John J. Heldrich Center for Workforce Development. Long before the recession, he noted, having a job conveyed no guarantee of coverage.

&quot;Just recovery of jobs isn&#39;t sufficent to address the issue,&quot; he said. &quot;A lot of the jobs that people are getting are part-time jobs and/or don&#39;t have healthcare benefits attached to them.&quot;

And even those who are eligible for healthcare in the wake of job loss cannot always take advantage of what is available to them.

&quot;It&#39;s pretty obvious that government policies are confusing,&quot; Van Horn said. &quot;A lot of folks are losing their jobs for the first time and they don&#39;t know what they&#39;re even entitled to.&quot;

Paying for healthcare can be one of the first things to go for families dealing with constrained finances. Over 50% of those surveyed said that healthcare was one of the expenses they could not afford to pay.

&quot;We have an employer-based healthcare system,&quot; Van Horn said. &quot;And if your lose your job, unless you&#39;re old or very poor, you have no health care insurance.&quot;

In San Mateo, California, just south of San Francisco, Francis Campos-Dunn understands this fact all too well. For years, she has contended with a variety of often-expensive health problems, making her insurance situation particularly crucial.

Her administrative job at the San Mateo County Hospital provided for her needs and also delivered insurance for her son and a granddaughter. But late last year, she was laid off, and so began a painful and bewildering lesson in the particularities of the American health care system.

Kaiser, the giant health maintenance organization, offered her the option to continue her health insurance for $1,500 dollars a month. But that outstripped her total income-- a disability payment of $1,300 a month.

So Campos-Dunn turned to Medical, California&#39;s state-run health insurance--the state&#39;s version of Medicaid. But they told her that her income exceeded the allowable limit by $32 a month and denied her claim, she says. Undeterred, she appealed, was granted a hearing and was subsequently approved for the state insurance.

But three weeks later, another letter arrived informing her that once again, she made too much money to qualify for the state&#39;s health insurance. Since her unemployment, she has struggled with this ceaseless back and forth with the bureaucracy, going without care for weeks in between.

&quot;I never thought I&#39;d be in this position,&quot; she said. &quot;I used to help families get on insurance. I used to hear all these problems. I used to think anything was possible to try to figure out a way around it so they could get health insurance. Now I have no health insurance.&quot;

With her medical condition continuing to require care, her battle to keep up has worn her down past the point where she can even muster the effort to continue fighting.

&quot;It got up to a point where I didn&#39;t even try to deal with them anymore,&quot; she said. &quot;If I ended up in the hospital I&#39;d just pay the bill.&quot;

She now owes Kaiser over $55,000, she says. She owes the San Mateo County Hospital--her old employer-- over $22,000.

&quot;I just don&#39;t think it&#39;s right,&quot; she said. &quot;I&#39;ve been working since I was 15 years old and now I can&#39;t access what I need because I make 32 dollars too much.&quot;&lt;/blockquote&gt;

http://www.huffingtonpost.com/2010/12/27/uninsured-americans-50-million_n_801695.html

That number isn&#39;t far off the population of the UK!</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 11 Jan 2011 18:50:45 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>General Discussion</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/number-of-uninsured-americans-soars-to-over-50-million/375653.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Number of Uninsured Americans Soars To Over 50 Million</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@bootnecklad bootnecklad]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/bootnecklad">@bootnecklad</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote no-group quote-modified" data-post="88" data-topic="375653">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/greeny/40/5_1887921562df0dabfae55079ddabeb03.png" class="avatar"> Greeny:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>My brother has the same problem Scoliosis (less severe) so he’s only on the NHS.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>So we won’t have another blob? <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/frowning.png?v=5" title=":frowning:" class="emoji" alt=":frowning:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/number-of-uninsured-americans-soars-to-over-50-million/375653/89">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/number-of-uninsured-americans-soars-to-over-50-million/375653/89</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jan 2011 18:50:45 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-375653-89</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/number-of-uninsured-americans-soars-to-over-50-million/375653.rss">Number of Uninsured Americans Soars To Over 50 Million</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Number of Uninsured Americans Soars To Over 50 Million</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Greeny Greeny]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/greeny">@Greeny</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I’ve skim read the past few pages, seems to be a lot of waiting time talk. As someone whose experienced first hand the NHS GPs, NHS hospitals and a private hospital. I can definitely say most are right about the GP waiting times being non-existent. You’ll pretty much always get the appointment on the day, just have to wait when you get there because they’re always running 5-10 mins late.</p>
<p>Hospitals are a totally different story, ER waiting times are prioritised, so if you don’t have a head injury you’re not going to be seen for like an hour. So the trick is, even if you only broke your leg to mention the “throbbing pain” in your head <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/wink.png?v=5" title=":wink:" class="emoji" alt=":wink:"> ) In terms of specialists at hospitals, or specialist clinics - these take GP referrals to get into because there are waiting lists. For instance Orthopaedics (for my spine) required a referral then about 2-3 months waiting before I could see a surgeon. When I saw the surgeon I had to wait around 1-2 hours for Xrays (again, xrays always have long ass waiting times) so eventually we just went private, which here in the UK is holy shit fast. A surgery that would have waited 2-3 years on the NHS or maybe not even happened took 1 year at a private hospital (by 1 year, I mean it took 1 year of meeting the orthopaedic surgeon before he decided I needed the surgery, then he booked it straight away).</p>
<p>My brother has the same problem Scoliosis (less severe) so he’s only on the NHS. He goes every year for a checkup and waits around 3 hours for Xrays then sees the doctor. I used to go every 6 months privately, upon arriving had Xrays within 20-30 minutes- then saw the surgeon. Like I said I only had to go twice (1 year) before they decided surgery.</p>
<p>NHS has good GP practices, but the hospitals could definitely be a little better.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/number-of-uninsured-americans-soars-to-over-50-million/375653/88">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/number-of-uninsured-americans-soars-to-over-50-million/375653/88</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jan 2011 14:56:20 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-375653-88</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/number-of-uninsured-americans-soars-to-over-50-million/375653.rss">Number of Uninsured Americans Soars To Over 50 Million</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Number of Uninsured Americans Soars To Over 50 Million</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@SETO SETO]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/seto">@SETO</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote no-group quote-modified" data-post="8" data-topic="375653">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/user_avatar/forum.moparisthebest.com/moparisthebest/40/30_1.png" class="avatar"> Moparisthebest:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>I feel their pain, I haven’t been insured since I graduated college (may 09) and my wife hasn’t been insured since we got married.  …, which works alright (heartburn about once a week, on average).  I’m sure other people have an even harder time.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>are we really living in a modern society?, i know of third world countries, where education is free from grade 1 to University, and heathcare is also free. Also their emergency wait time it very very low, if you had to wait, they would attend to you and make sure you are given comfort, ex painkiller or etc.</p>
<p>I went to the emergency department last year, my fingers got cut by a machinery and i was in great pain, i had to wait for 5 hours, before they treated me to stop the pain. then another 1 hour to get treated.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-post="85" data-topic="375653">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 la­wl:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>as a canadian, ive never had any issues with health care here. the only case ive experienced long waits in is to see specialists, ie dermatologist/urologist</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>but not when the dermatologist is a close family friend lol, i find that very helpful, i often go to them, so i don’t have to wait that long.</p>
<p>by did you hear about the Calgary man, who died because no one attended to him in the Emergency department for few days. Not to say Canadian health care system is bad, but it could be better.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/number-of-uninsured-americans-soars-to-over-50-million/375653/87">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/number-of-uninsured-americans-soars-to-over-50-million/375653/87</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 08 Jan 2011 21:04:24 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-375653-87</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/number-of-uninsured-americans-soars-to-over-50-million/375653.rss">Number of Uninsured Americans Soars To Over 50 Million</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Number of Uninsured Americans Soars To Over 50 Million</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@jme jme]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/jme">@jme</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote no-group" data-post="85" data-topic="375653">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 la­wl:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>as a canadian, ive never had any issues with health care here. the only case ive experienced long waits in is to see specialists, ie dermatologist/urologist</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Specialists are long waits yes. My eyebrows are falling out (alopecia), so I’m going to see a dermatologist. I have to wait until May and I made the appointment months ago.</p>
<p>I waited like 8 months because of knee problems once.</p>
<p>But I’d rather that, then some bill I absolutely could never afford.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/number-of-uninsured-americans-soars-to-over-50-million/375653/86">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/number-of-uninsured-americans-soars-to-over-50-million/375653/86</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 08 Jan 2011 19:27:09 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-375653-86</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/number-of-uninsured-americans-soars-to-over-50-million/375653.rss">Number of Uninsured Americans Soars To Over 50 Million</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Number of Uninsured Americans Soars To Over 50 Million</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@lawl lawl]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/lawl">@lawl</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>as a canadian, ive never had any issues with health care here. the only case ive experienced long waits in is to see specialists, ie dermatologist/urologist</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/number-of-uninsured-americans-soars-to-over-50-million/375653/85">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/number-of-uninsured-americans-soars-to-over-50-million/375653/85</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 08 Jan 2011 19:21:37 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-375653-85</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/number-of-uninsured-americans-soars-to-over-50-million/375653.rss">Number of Uninsured Americans Soars To Over 50 Million</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Number of Uninsured Americans Soars To Over 50 Million</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@jme jme]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/jme">@jme</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote no-group" data-post="28" data-topic="375653">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/frell/40/5_1887921562df0dabfae55079ddabeb03.png" class="avatar"> Frell:</div>
<blockquote>
<p><a href="http://www.city-journal.org/html/17_3_canadian_healthcare.html">http://www.city-journal.org/html/17_3_canadian_healthcare.html</a></p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I find that ridiculous personally. As a Canadian who has been the the ER many times, I can say it’s not that bad.</p>
<blockquote>My health-care prejudices crumbled not in the classroom but on the way to one. On a subzero Winnipeg morning in 1997, I cut across the hospital emergency room to shave a few minutes off my frigid commute. Swinging open the door, I stepped into a nightmare: the ER overflowed with elderly people on stretchers, waiting for admission. Some, it turned out, had waited five days. The air stank with sweat and urine.</blockquote>
<p>I’ve never even heard of such things. I do not know anyone with bad experiences even close to that. This isn’t a fair representation of Canadian health care. Sweat and urine? Maybe he was standing beside a fat guy who pissed himself. But hospitals are ALWAYS very clean.</p>
<p>3 days ago, I went to the ER because I have a flu and had breathing problems later at night. They took me instantly and prescribed me antibiotics because it turns out I have a lung infection.</p>
<p>One time when I was hit in the eye by a hockey puck, I had to wait a full 20 minutes. That kind of sucked I guess. But thankfully vision returned by that time anyways.</p>
<p>If you’re going because you have a sore finger, you can expect to wait a few hours. I broke both my wrists and had x-rays almost immediately and was fixed up within a few hours.</p>
<p>A few years ago I had a stomach ache. I went to the ER and told them that i had this horrible nauseating cramp for the past day. I saw the doctor instantly and it turned out I had appendicitis, which progressed into peritonitis. It was life threatening, so I got surgery, tonnes of drugs, and walked out for free 3 days later. Interestingly, my grandma in Florida had the exact same problem near the same time. She is a Canadian citizen but lives in Florida 6 months a year. When she went to the doctor in Florida, they didn’t diagnose her properly and she lived with it for a whole week. My 1 day was hell and became life threatening, so I can’t even imagine what she went through.</p>
<p>While in the hospital we thought she was on her death bed. Well they finally decided it was appendicitis, and wanted to charge her $700,000 dollars for surgery. Instead she was flown back to Canada by helicopter, which costed $20,000 and was later paid for by OHIP. She got her surgery done, but because of the fuck up in Florida, she had to get a large portion of her bowels removed, her ovaries, and many more. She had to recover in the hospital for a few months.</p>
<p>Horror stories are bound to exist for every system. But it’s honestly not that damn bad here.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/number-of-uninsured-americans-soars-to-over-50-million/375653/84">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/number-of-uninsured-americans-soars-to-over-50-million/375653/84</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 08 Jan 2011 19:16:06 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-375653-84</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/number-of-uninsured-americans-soars-to-over-50-million/375653.rss">Number of Uninsured Americans Soars To Over 50 Million</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Number of Uninsured Americans Soars To Over 50 Million</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@yakman yakman]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/yakman">@yakman</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“Mopman, post:81, topic:375653”][quote author=Niall link=topic=471586.msg3458634#msg3458634 date=1294269173]<br>
Cept when you phone up and there’s no slots that day, technically making it a multiday wait to see a gp.<br>
[/quote]</p>
<p>That hasn’t happened to me, though to be fair I’m rural, it might be different in bigger practices.[/quote]</p>
<p>Never happened to me and I live in the middle of a city. Although I’ve only needed to go about 5 times in the last 10 years.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/number-of-uninsured-americans-soars-to-over-50-million/375653/83">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/number-of-uninsured-americans-soars-to-over-50-million/375653/83</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 08 Jan 2011 14:21:41 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-375653-83</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/number-of-uninsured-americans-soars-to-over-50-million/375653.rss">Number of Uninsured Americans Soars To Over 50 Million</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Number of Uninsured Americans Soars To Over 50 Million</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Frell Frell]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/frell">@Frell</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“R.I.P RSC, post:80, topic:375653”][quote author=Lothy link=topic=471586.msg3458674#msg3458674 date=1294270888]<br>
Actually, you’re right about the rubbish approach to organ donations. I’ve agreed to donate my organs on death (and this is listed on my driver’s licence), but plenty of people don’t.</p>
<p>It’s a big problem, because everyone that needs a transplant expects it soon enough to avoid death, yet they’re the same people (usually older and conservative people) who wouldn’t donate organs themselves.<br>
[/quote]</p>
<p>Some part in me says that the following would be a good rule: If you don’t donate, you don’t get a transplant yourself either.[/quote]<br>
Could possibly interfere with some gay religion. Or the risk of reusing a reused organ… ew</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/number-of-uninsured-americans-soars-to-over-50-million/375653/82">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/number-of-uninsured-americans-soars-to-over-50-million/375653/82</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 06 Jan 2011 21:36:02 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-375653-82</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/number-of-uninsured-americans-soars-to-over-50-million/375653.rss">Number of Uninsured Americans Soars To Over 50 Million</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Number of Uninsured Americans Soars To Over 50 Million</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Mopman Mopman]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/mopman">@Mopman</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote no-group quote-modified" data-post="76" data-topic="375653">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 Niall:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Cept when you phone up and there’s no slots that day, technically making it a multiday wait to see a gp.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>That hasn’t happened to me, though to be fair I’m rural, it might be different in bigger practices.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/number-of-uninsured-americans-soars-to-over-50-million/375653/81">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/number-of-uninsured-americans-soars-to-over-50-million/375653/81</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 06 Jan 2011 18:00:57 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-375653-81</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/number-of-uninsured-americans-soars-to-over-50-million/375653.rss">Number of Uninsured Americans Soars To Over 50 Million</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Number of Uninsured Americans Soars To Over 50 Million</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@R.I.P_RSC R.I.P RSC]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/r.i.p_rsc">@R.I.P_RSC</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“Lothy, post:79, topic:375653”]Actually, you’re right about the rubbish approach to organ donations. I’ve agreed to donate my organs on death (and this is listed on my driver’s licence), but plenty of people don’t.</p>
<p>It’s a big problem, because everyone that needs a transplant expects it soon enough to avoid death, yet they’re the same people (usually older and conservative people) who wouldn’t donate organs themselves.[/quote]</p>
<p>Some part in me says that the following would be a good rule: If you don’t donate, you don’t get a transplant yourself either.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/number-of-uninsured-americans-soars-to-over-50-million/375653/80">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/number-of-uninsured-americans-soars-to-over-50-million/375653/80</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 06 Jan 2011 17:57:38 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-375653-80</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/number-of-uninsured-americans-soars-to-over-50-million/375653.rss">Number of Uninsured Americans Soars To Over 50 Million</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Number of Uninsured Americans Soars To Over 50 Million</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@lothy Lothy]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/lothy">@lothy</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Actually, you’re right about the rubbish approach to organ donations. I’ve agreed to donate my organs on death (and this is listed on my driver’s licence), but plenty of people don’t.</p>
<p>It’s a big problem, because everyone that needs a transplant expects it soon enough to avoid death, yet they’re the same people (usually older and conservative people) who wouldn’t donate organs themselves.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/number-of-uninsured-americans-soars-to-over-50-million/375653/79">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/number-of-uninsured-americans-soars-to-over-50-million/375653/79</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 05 Jan 2011 23:41:28 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-375653-79</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/number-of-uninsured-americans-soars-to-over-50-million/375653.rss">Number of Uninsured Americans Soars To Over 50 Million</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Number of Uninsured Americans Soars To Over 50 Million</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@The_Un-Named The Un-Named]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/the_un-named">@The_Un-Named</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote no-group" data-post="77" data-topic="375653">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/frell/40/5_1887921562df0dabfae55079ddabeb03.png" class="avatar"> Frell:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>So the wait times are pretty much a myth?</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>somewhat, the majority of complaining is blown out of proportion</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/number-of-uninsured-americans-soars-to-over-50-million/375653/78">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/number-of-uninsured-americans-soars-to-over-50-million/375653/78</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 05 Jan 2011 23:23:21 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-375653-78</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/number-of-uninsured-americans-soars-to-over-50-million/375653.rss">Number of Uninsured Americans Soars To Over 50 Million</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Number of Uninsured Americans Soars To Over 50 Million</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Frell Frell]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/frell">@Frell</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>So the wait times are pretty much a myth?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/number-of-uninsured-americans-soars-to-over-50-million/375653/77">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/number-of-uninsured-americans-soars-to-over-50-million/375653/77</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 05 Jan 2011 23:18:01 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-375653-77</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/number-of-uninsured-americans-soars-to-over-50-million/375653.rss">Number of Uninsured Americans Soars To Over 50 Million</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Number of Uninsured Americans Soars To Over 50 Million</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@The_Un-Named The Un-Named]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/the_un-named">@The_Un-Named</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote no-group quote-modified" data-post="75" data-topic="375653">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/user_avatar/forum.moparisthebest.com/mopman/40/33_1.png" class="avatar"> Mopman:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>So multiday wait times for GP’s are a myth, at least in my area. Because you can’t do that.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Cept when you phone up and there’s no slots that day, technically making it a multiday wait to see a gp.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/number-of-uninsured-americans-soars-to-over-50-million/375653/76">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/number-of-uninsured-americans-soars-to-over-50-million/375653/76</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 05 Jan 2011 23:12:53 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-375653-76</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/number-of-uninsured-americans-soars-to-over-50-million/375653.rss">Number of Uninsured Americans Soars To Over 50 Million</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Number of Uninsured Americans Soars To Over 50 Million</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Mopman Mopman]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/mopman">@Mopman</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>My GP doesn’t even make advance appointments (except as a followup) - you HAVE to book the day you call.</p>
<p>So multiday wait times for GP’s are a myth, at least in my area. Because you can’t do that.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/number-of-uninsured-americans-soars-to-over-50-million/375653/75">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/number-of-uninsured-americans-soars-to-over-50-million/375653/75</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 05 Jan 2011 22:07:45 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-375653-75</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/number-of-uninsured-americans-soars-to-over-50-million/375653.rss">Number of Uninsured Americans Soars To Over 50 Million</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Number of Uninsured Americans Soars To Over 50 Million</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@R.I.P_RSC R.I.P RSC]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/r.i.p_rsc">@R.I.P_RSC</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“Lothy, post:73, topic:375653”]When I call my GP, I either get in on the day (the majority of the time), or in on the following day.<br>
We do have waiting lists in this country for things such as transplants and very specialist surgery.[/quote]</p>
<p>Our waiting lists for transplants are very high, but that’s mostly due to the law and people not signing up as a donor. In the Netherlands you have to say ‘Yes I want to be a donor’, instead of the much better ‘No, I don’t want to be a donor’. If you are automatically a donor, and have to fill in a form to get yourself off the list, you are forced to consider it.</p>
<p>But there’s also a problem with the law. Last time I checked, relatives are asked if they want to donate the organs of a (almost) deceased person. Even if the dead person enlisted as a donor. People usually say no when they have to decide over the organs of relatives.</p>
<p>If you need specialist surgery, and it’s not available in the Netherlands, you are allowed to go to a different country and be operated there. It’s even (partially) compensated by insurance companies.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/number-of-uninsured-americans-soars-to-over-50-million/375653/74">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/number-of-uninsured-americans-soars-to-over-50-million/375653/74</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 05 Jan 2011 18:57:03 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-375653-74</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/number-of-uninsured-americans-soars-to-over-50-million/375653.rss">Number of Uninsured Americans Soars To Over 50 Million</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Number of Uninsured Americans Soars To Over 50 Million</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@lothy Lothy]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/lothy">@lothy</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>When I call my GP, I either get in on the day (the majority of the time), or in on the following day.<br>
We do have waiting lists in this country for things such as transplants and very specialist surgery.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/number-of-uninsured-americans-soars-to-over-50-million/375653/73">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/number-of-uninsured-americans-soars-to-over-50-million/375653/73</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 05 Jan 2011 14:01:06 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-375653-73</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/number-of-uninsured-americans-soars-to-over-50-million/375653.rss">Number of Uninsured Americans Soars To Over 50 Million</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Number of Uninsured Americans Soars To Over 50 Million</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@R.I.P_RSC R.I.P RSC]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/r.i.p_rsc">@R.I.P_RSC</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>If you are in a life threatening situation, you get aid immediately (obviously). If not, then depending on your symptoms you might have to wait a few hours, or days if it doesn’t need immediate care. You can get free pain killers if you want, though, so the problems aren’t that big.</p>
<p>Besides, many diseases need testing to confirm, so you have to wait nonetheless. If you need a test that involves depositing a bottle of urine, you can do that and know the results tomorrow. A doctor doesn’t need to receive the cup in person, and he doesn’t do the tests either. Same with blood-tests. There are a lot of things people with lower educations than a doctor can do, which is cheaper and allows the doctor to do things only he can do.</p>
<p>If we feel ill all of the sudden, we have four options. We either call the doctor, and he’ll come by when he has time or we visit him. When it’s a bit more serious, there is a doctor waiting at the hospital, and when you give him a call you’re added to a list, and you’ll be visited the same day. You usually call this guy at night too. If you have problems that need immediate attention, you go to the ER yourself. If you feel like you are about to die, or any other serious problems, you ring 112 (European 911) and an Ambulance will arrive within 6-7 minutes.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/number-of-uninsured-americans-soars-to-over-50-million/375653/72">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/number-of-uninsured-americans-soars-to-over-50-million/375653/72</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 05 Jan 2011 13:23:27 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-375653-72</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/number-of-uninsured-americans-soars-to-over-50-million/375653.rss">Number of Uninsured Americans Soars To Over 50 Million</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Number of Uninsured Americans Soars To Over 50 Million</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@The_Un-Named The Un-Named]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/the_un-named">@The_Un-Named</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote no-group quote-modified" data-post="65" data-topic="375653">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/frell/40/5_1887921562df0dabfae55079ddabeb03.png" class="avatar"> Frell:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>If you are having headaches for a week, and you call the doctors in the UK or Aus for an appointment, how long are you waiting? (Serious question) 3-5 or more days? Even if its less, this number will not be proportional to the US at all. Its hard to believe it, but homeless people will hurt themselves for to be admitted to hospitals for free food and rest (prisoners already do it, because they’re healthcare is paid for by the government). Not to mention with the shortage of a new generation of doctors, this will leave a smaller professor generation. So in all you get more people in the hospitals, with less people to treat them.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>ill make a proper post later but, if you call your local gp you USUALLY can be seen the same day, and everytime we’ve had to go up we called 7-8am and were able to be seen by 12-1pm</p>
<p>and <span class="mention">@er</span> heh things are definitely different here, from the few times I’ve been to the er what will usually happen is if it needs immediate attention you’ll get it, then you’ll proceed to wait several hours(we were up there 6 hours when I broke my arm, inb4 shitstorm), when my brother was last up the er he was waiting about 10 mins(for me and my mum to arrive) before he got pain meds, maybe half an hour until an xray and got surgery the next day and this was for a particularly bad cut to the face which required several stitches and a few paper stitches. Granted our particular er is always pretty busy, I doubt it will be like that across much of the uk.</p>
<p>eEEEEEEEDeit: I imagine a lot of the complaining about wait times are the of the very long 2-4 week or more kind for specialized surgery, rather than 2-3 days for a gp appointment(which happens over busy times of the year).</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/number-of-uninsured-americans-soars-to-over-50-million/375653/71">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/number-of-uninsured-americans-soars-to-over-50-million/375653/71</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 05 Jan 2011 12:48:44 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-375653-71</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/number-of-uninsured-americans-soars-to-over-50-million/375653.rss">Number of Uninsured Americans Soars To Over 50 Million</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Number of Uninsured Americans Soars To Over 50 Million</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@PaulT PaulT]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/pault">@PaulT</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Here in my home state you can be uninsured, walk into any hospital, and still get treatment. The hospital will then retroactively sign you up for the state subsidized insurance and you will most likely be covered for any basic treatment and only have to pay a small copay. I think it’s a good thing. The more socialization of medicine the better; society only moves as fast as its slowest member. Life is destined to work with itself to improve the lot of all living things as much as competition allows.</p>
<p>In the United States many poor people can’t afford insurance or people choose to go uninsured; that’s not the biggest problem with healthcare though. I think the current “Disease=Symptom” model of the Medicinal Field and how old age and death are looked upon as unnatural is a more serious problem. Care for the elderly and disabled such as Dialysis and hospice care represent a huge portion of medical expenses for the US, as do Administrative costs (most estimate at least 80% industry spending is on Administration).</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/number-of-uninsured-americans-soars-to-over-50-million/375653/70">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/number-of-uninsured-americans-soars-to-over-50-million/375653/70</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 05 Jan 2011 02:39:05 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-375653-70</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/number-of-uninsured-americans-soars-to-over-50-million/375653.rss">Number of Uninsured Americans Soars To Over 50 Million</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Number of Uninsured Americans Soars To Over 50 Million</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Frell Frell]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/frell">@Frell</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“Thug-life, post:68, topic:375653”]I don’t know. But I can only imagine it is for very specialist stuff, even in surgery - I don’t hear of these waits. And having been under for quite a few, I haven’t experienced them either.</p>
<p>You have such a warped view on this whole thing. Emergency room, go in and they’ll sort you, the exact same way as you would.[/quote]<br>
I probably do have a warped view on the wait times, as to the whole thing, watch doctor interviews from here in America, and also see how “warped” Obamas policy is. Remember, im fighting HIS policy, not universal healthcare. His policy is probably different than European universal healthcare systems</p>
<aside class="quote no-group quote-modified" data-post="67" data-topic="375653">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/frell/40/5_1887921562df0dabfae55079ddabeb03.png" class="avatar"> Frell:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Ive heard longer wait times always being discussed everywhere, but I’ve never actually known about the actual time (other than the commercial about the canadian who was told to wait 3 months for surgery for her brain tumor, so she came here). If the wait times aren’t actually as long as im thinking, ill happily rearrange my thoughts.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/number-of-uninsured-americans-soars-to-over-50-million/375653/69">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/number-of-uninsured-americans-soars-to-over-50-million/375653/69</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 05 Jan 2011 02:34:45 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-375653-69</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/number-of-uninsured-americans-soars-to-over-50-million/375653.rss">Number of Uninsured Americans Soars To Over 50 Million</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Number of Uninsured Americans Soars To Over 50 Million</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@tL tL]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/tl">@tL</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I don’t know. But I can only imagine it is for very specialist stuff, even in surgery - I don’t hear of these waits. And having been under for quite a few, I haven’t experienced them either.</p>
<p>You have such a warped view on this whole thing. Emergency room, go in and they’ll sort you, the exact same way as you would.</p>
<p>I am not sure on how the Canadian system works, but wait times aren’t top of the list when it comes to problems with our healthcare system. It is usually them being overcrowded (which could lead to longer wait times, but it is usually just overcrowing on wards - people waiting in over night, not surgery), which is a fair and valid point - it is hard to keep on top of it, but there is a reason why we in Britain mostly, fiercely defend the NHS against foreign criticism, because many of us have benefitted greatly from it, and for what it is, it works pretty damn well.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/number-of-uninsured-americans-soars-to-over-50-million/375653/68">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/number-of-uninsured-americans-soars-to-over-50-million/375653/68</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 05 Jan 2011 02:29:49 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-375653-68</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/number-of-uninsured-americans-soars-to-over-50-million/375653.rss">Number of Uninsured Americans Soars To Over 50 Million</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Number of Uninsured Americans Soars To Over 50 Million</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Frell Frell]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/frell">@Frell</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote no-group quote-modified" data-post="66" data-topic="375653">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/thug-life/40/5_1887921562df0dabfae55079ddabeb03.png" class="avatar"> Thug-life:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>3-5 days? I’ve never had to wait for longer than a day. Its usually the very same day, as you go in. I’ve NEVER heard of such waits in this country. I’m not sure where you get that from.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Then what is the whole deal about longer wait times regarding? The ER? Wait, IIRC it only really shows up in surgery appointments.</p>
<p>Ive heard longer wait times always being discussed everywhere, but I’ve never actually known about the actual time (other than the commercial about the canadian who was told to wait 3 months for surgery for her brain tumor, so she came here). If the wait times aren’t actually as long as im thinking, ill happily rearrange my thoughts.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/number-of-uninsured-americans-soars-to-over-50-million/375653/67">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/number-of-uninsured-americans-soars-to-over-50-million/375653/67</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 05 Jan 2011 02:28:42 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-375653-67</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/number-of-uninsured-americans-soars-to-over-50-million/375653.rss">Number of Uninsured Americans Soars To Over 50 Million</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Number of Uninsured Americans Soars To Over 50 Million</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@tL tL]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/tl">@tL</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>3-5 days? I’ve never had to wait for longer than a day. Its usually the very same day, as you go in. I’ve NEVER heard of such waits in this country. I’m not sure where you get that from.</p>
<p>Most of the time, call up your local GP, tell them you need to see a doctor and they’ll have you in the very same day.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/number-of-uninsured-americans-soars-to-over-50-million/375653/66">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/number-of-uninsured-americans-soars-to-over-50-million/375653/66</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 05 Jan 2011 02:26:23 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-375653-66</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/number-of-uninsured-americans-soars-to-over-50-million/375653.rss">Number of Uninsured Americans Soars To Over 50 Million</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Number of Uninsured Americans Soars To Over 50 Million</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Frell Frell]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/frell">@Frell</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote no-group" data-post="63" data-topic="375653">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/frell/40/5_1887921562df0dabfae55079ddabeb03.png" class="avatar"> Frell:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Not a very accurate statement</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>This was to thug’s comment at the end of page 3, missed nialls entire post</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-post="61" data-topic="375653">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 Niall:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>expanding on personal freedoms, you contradicted yourself by saying healthy people will have to support people who live unhealthy life styles, and go on to say its wrong to increase taxes on unhealthy substances because that restricts their freedoms</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I dont recall ever being against taxes on such substances. In fact, I 100% support any ridiculous tax amount the government can dish out on everything from cigarettes to alcohol.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group quote-modified" data-post="61" data-topic="375653">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 Niall:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>you’re also against healthcare because from the way I read this, free healthcare is anti-competitive etc, this really isn’t the case because if private insurance is better(and from your no list I’m sure you think free health care will be terribad which only contributes to this argument, ) people will pay for it, which is why private insurance firms like bupa can operate in countries like the UK because they can specialize and give better treatment than a free option, get paid well for it, contribute to r&amp;d and all that good stuff without going bankrupt</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I dont think im understanding this. This is where my idea of a blanket layer comes in, where buying private insurance is optional but still readily available. Obama wants to cut out private insurance companies and cap doctor salaries(are they capped in the UK?), and pretty much re-do the system to cover illegal immigrants also, along with more crap that makes this far from pure “universal healthcare”</p>
<p>[quote=“Niall, post:61, topic:375653”]4, 8, how so</p>
<p>also 10, 12, supply and demand bitch<br>
also 15 p. sure it doesnt work like that[/quote]</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">4</span> " Government-controlled health care would lead to a decrease in patient flexibility. At first glance, it would appear universal health care would increase flexibility. After all, if government paid for everything under one plan, you could in theory go to any doctor. However, some controls are going to have to be put in to keep costs from exploding. For example, would “elective” surgeries such as breast implants, wart removal, hair restoration, and lasik eye surgery be covered? Then you may say, that’s easy, make patients pay for elective surgery. Although some procedures are obviously not needed, who decides what is elective and what is required? What about a breast reduction for back problems? What about a hysterectomy for fibroid problems? What about a nose job to fix a septum problem caused in an accident? Whenever you have government control of something, you have one item added to the equation that will most definitely screw things up–politics. Suddenly, every medical procedure and situation is going to come down to a political battle. The compromises that result will put in controls that limit patient options. The universal system in Canada forces patients to wait over 6 months for a routine pap smear. Canada residents will often go to the U.S. or offer additional money to get their health care needs taken care of. "</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">8</span> “Government-mandated procedures will likely reduce doctor flexibility and lead to poor patient care. When government controls things, politics always seep into the decision-making. Steps will have to be taken to keep costs under control. Rules will be put in place as to when doctors can perform certain expensive tests or when drugs can be given. Insurance companies are already tying the hands of doctors somewhat. Government influence will only make things worse, leading to decreased doctor flexibility and poor patient care.”</p>
<p>10&amp;12, how is that supply and demand?</p>
<p>15 is more of an opinionated one, not sure what thats about.</p>
<p>[quote=“Niall, post:61, topic:375653”][quote author=Frell link=topic=471586.msg3456853#msg3456853 date=1294099038]</p>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p>Hard to take it seriously when it uses long wait times as a reason.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>How is that not a valid reason?<br>
[/quote]</p>
<p>because people who are dying or seriously injured/ill take priority obviously, and everyone who has to wait <span class="bbcode-u">waits because they can wait</span>, it’s not the other way around where people who cant wait end up waiting and suffer ill effects because of it</p>
<p>for example(I know you’re probably talking about weeks to months here but a small scale example works just as well), a person who cuts their arm visits an er, they get it patched up immediately so there’s no immediate medical issue, they then wait until a proper doctor is free to look at it and send them on their way, meaning if someone comes in with a serious head injury there will be doctors on hand so the other doctors wouldn’t have had to drop everything</p>
<p>also what thug says about long waits also very much applies</p>
<p>ps this was sort of a long post anyway but oh well I was originally planning on expanding into more detail and shit</p>
<p>pps waiters waiting to serve in the waiting area[/quote]<br>
Im not sure if we’re on the same boat. Here, yes in the ER there are priorities, but the longest waiting time is porbably a few minutes depending on how much of an emergency it is. My mother was having stomach pains and got a normal doctors appointment in a day, went there and they suspected the “possibility” of having gallstones (This was about when I left for school, so about 8). I was aware she was at a doctors appointment, but then i got a text message at lunch of my dad saying she just got out of surgery. Thats fast. Sure, her gallbladder may not have exploded for a week or a few more hours, but why risk it?</p>
<p>As for normal appointments, people usually arrange them themselves depending on how serious it is. Last year I had a severe sore throat and was able to get an appointment an hour after calling, simply by asking if you have any times available today.</p>
<p>If you are having headaches for a week, and you call the doctors in the UK or Aus for an appointment, how long are you waiting? (Serious question) 3-5 or more days? Even if its less, this number will not be proportional to the US at all. Its hard to believe it, but homeless people will hurt themselves for to be admitted to hospitals for free food and rest (prisoners already do it, because they’re healthcare is paid for by the government). Not to mention with the shortage of a new generation of doctors, this will leave a smaller professor generation. So in all you get more people in the hospitals, with less people to treat them.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/number-of-uninsured-americans-soars-to-over-50-million/375653/65">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/number-of-uninsured-americans-soars-to-over-50-million/375653/65</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 05 Jan 2011 02:24:21 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-375653-65</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/number-of-uninsured-americans-soars-to-over-50-million/375653.rss">Number of Uninsured Americans Soars To Over 50 Million</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
