<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Www.rscdedication.com</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/www-rscdedication-com/541469</link>
    <description>hey all my RSC lovers! I would highly suggest hopping on this server and spending some time! Our admin/owner is in a 1 year contract for the server so we will be around for the long run! If you want to add me if you create an account feel free and ill help get you started with some items and show you a couple of the add-ons the programmers have implemented to help make RSC a little more convenient. I think there voting on reducing the XP rate soon so take advantage now while theres time! ive played every big RSC private server in the last 3 years and I highly suggest this one. You wont regret it, and that&#39;s a promise, A BIG PROMISE. www.rscdedication.com
-----add me 
-Burger-</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 23 Mar 2014 21:19:56 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/www-rscdedication-com/541469.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Www.rscdedication.com</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@burger1990 burger1990]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/burger1990">@burger1990</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>hey all my RSC lovers! I would highly suggest hopping on this server and spending some time! Our admin/owner is in a 1 year contract for the server so we will be around for the long run! If you want to add me if you create an account feel free and ill help get you started with some items and show you a couple of the add-ons the programmers have implemented to help make RSC a little more convenient. I think there voting on reducing the XP rate soon so take advantage now while theres time! ive played every big RSC private server in the last 3 years and I highly suggest this one. You wont regret it, and that’s a promise, A BIG PROMISE. <a href="http://www.rscdedication.com" rel="nofollow noopener">www.rscdedication.com</a><br>
-----add me<br>
-Burger-</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/www-rscdedication-com/541469/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/www-rscdedication-com/541469/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 23 Mar 2014 21:19:56 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-541469-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/www-rscdedication-com/541469.rss">Www.rscdedication.com</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
