<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Server issues// adding shops - eclipse 317 source</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/server-issues-adding-shops-eclipse-317-source/433231</link>
    <description>I have searched high and low, even going through 20 pages of tuts and guides and still can&#39;t figure out my problem. my problem is that I don&#39;t know what goes wrong when I add a shop to the shops.cfg I edited it slightly, just adding another line with ny info instead. compiled just fine. but when I ran the server, it never started up. just went through this cmd prompt loop. forceclosed itself, and did it continuously. at first I thought it was just the shops.cfg, but world-objects.cfg made it loop as well. this all started with the want to make a custom donors shop, then downgraded to a regular shop in the donor zone, to just wanting to know what&#39;s happening. I want to also add a bank and skill area to my donorzone, but if I can&#39;t even find out how to correctly edit the files, I&#39;m stuck with a useless command that takes me to tutorial island. I would appreciate some help, I am fairly new to java, but am learning fairly quickly. 

other info: 
I am able toedit server-spawn.cfg fine, I have the npc where I want, just need to know how to connect a shop to him. I looked in src&gt;server&gt;models&gt;PLAYER:client.java and couldn&#39;t even find wanneshop or anything like that. editing shophandler.java left me with a bunch of errors and most of it seemed to be connected to the skillcape shop. id offer pics but I&#39;m on my phone atm. ill post a link to the source I&#39;m using.
change google to runel0cus
 www.google.com/forums/showthread.php?58699-Eclipse-Rsps-317-562-Dicing-Frosts-Gamble-zone
this is the source and client I&#39;ve been editing. credits to eclipse for source and coding apparently. 
I am not positive on linking, but if I need to change it I will. or delete.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 17 Feb 2012 05:31:07 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/server-issues-adding-shops-eclipse-317-source/433231.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Server issues// adding shops - eclipse 317 source</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@thedolphin thedolphin]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/thedolphin">@thedolphin</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I have searched high and low, even going through 20 pages of tuts and guides and still can’t figure out my problem. my problem is that I don’t know what goes wrong when I add a shop to the shops.cfg I edited it slightly, just adding another line with ny info instead. compiled just fine. but when I ran the server, it never started up. just went through this cmd prompt loop. forceclosed itself, and did it continuously. at first I thought it was just the shops.cfg, but world-objects.cfg made it loop as well. this all started with the want to make a custom donors shop, then downgraded to a regular shop in the donor zone, to just wanting to know what’s happening. I want to also add a bank and skill area to my donorzone, but if I can’t even find out how to correctly edit the files, I’m stuck with a useless command that takes me to tutorial island. I would appreciate some help, I am fairly new to java, but am learning fairly quickly.</p>
<p>other info:<br>
I am able toedit server-spawn.cfg fine, I have the npc where I want, just need to know how to connect a shop to him. I looked in src&gt;server&gt;models&gt;PLAYER:client.java and couldn’t even find wanneshop or anything like that. editing shophandler.java left me with a bunch of errors and most of it seemed to be connected to the skillcape shop. id offer pics but I’m on my phone atm. ill post a link to the source I’m using.<br>
change google to runel0cus<br>
<a href="http://www.google.com/forums/showthread.php?58699-Eclipse-Rsps-317-562-Dicing-Frosts-Gamble-zone" rel="nofollow noopener">www.google.com/forums/showthread.php?58699-Eclipse-Rsps-317-562-Dicing-Frosts-Gamble-zone</a><br>
this is the source and client I’ve been editing. credits to eclipse for source and coding apparently.<br>
I am not positive on linking, but if I need to change it I will. or delete.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/server-issues-adding-shops-eclipse-317-source/433231/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/server-issues-adding-shops-eclipse-317-source/433231/1</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 17 Feb 2012 05:31:07 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-433231-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/server-issues-adding-shops-eclipse-317-source/433231.rss">Server issues// adding shops - eclipse 317 source</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
