<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>A level Maths with BTEC ICT?</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/a-level-maths-with-btec-ict/150676</link>
    <description>I went to a college open evening the other day to have a look at a few courses. I&#39;m going to take a BTEC in ICT which is a two year course which counts for two A levels. Because of that, it takes up 2/4 of my A level choices. Speaking to the IT teacher yesterday, he said that doing Maths along with the BTEC would be a great advantage, and it would look much better for Uni&#39;s with Maths under me. However, I FUCKING HATE MATHS. I&#39;m not great at it (I&#39;m expecting a C or a B for GCSE), but my mum and dad are pretty much forcing me to take it without them knowing. 

For those of you in Uni or college now, studying IT, did you take Maths A level? How hard was it? Should I really take it for more Uni opportunities to arise? 

I&#39;m planning on taking the following courses:
BTEC National course for IT Practitioners
English Literature
Maths/Business Studies/History

English and Maths just sounds so boring. I like English, but hate Maths, but I don&#39;t see any other courses I could possibly take.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 11 Oct 2007 02:03:15 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>General Discussion</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/a-level-maths-with-btec-ict/150676.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>A level Maths with BTEC ICT?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Mr.Chris Mr.Chris]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/mr.chris">@Mr.Chris</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Thanks davidude. Goodluck also. It looks like I’m going to have to take maths as a A level, no matter how much I hate it. Keep me updated. Thanks x</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/a-level-maths-with-btec-ict/150676/7">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/a-level-maths-with-btec-ict/150676/7</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 11 Oct 2007 02:03:15 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-150676-7</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/a-level-maths-with-btec-ict/150676.rss">A level Maths with BTEC ICT?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>A level Maths with BTEC ICT?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@davidude36 Brolapse]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/davidude36">@davidude36</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Well i don’t know what ICT course i am going to choose (mainly because i haven’t looked into it much).</p>
<p>But I am definitely taking maths as well, mainly because i’m good at it, but if you are really interested in ICT as a job then you should definitely take maths. It’s like if you wanted to be a journalist and you take a journalism course at A level then its definitely worth while to take an English course also.</p>
<p>My advice probably wont help you as I’m only stating the obvious but i thought I’d post to a fellow year 11! (Good luck with gcse’s btw)</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/a-level-maths-with-btec-ict/150676/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/a-level-maths-with-btec-ict/150676/6</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 11 Oct 2007 00:32:56 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-150676-6</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/a-level-maths-with-btec-ict/150676.rss">A level Maths with BTEC ICT?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>A level Maths with BTEC ICT?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Mr.Chris Mr.Chris]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/mr.chris">@Mr.Chris</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Thanks for that UCAS site. Looks like most Uni’s have an absolute must on A level mathematics to get in to the Computer Science course. Most of the Uni’s I looked at accepted the BTEC cert. Damn, I hate maths…I do plan to go to Uni and I wouldn’t think I’d drop out of college.</p>
<p>Thanks a lot for your help there, Mopman.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/a-level-maths-with-btec-ict/150676/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/a-level-maths-with-btec-ict/150676/5</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 10 Oct 2007 20:16:06 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-150676-5</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/a-level-maths-with-btec-ict/150676.rss">A level Maths with BTEC ICT?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>A level Maths with BTEC ICT?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Mopman Mopman]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/mopman">@Mopman</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Ahh, the certificate has less units than the diploma I believe? So you would be doing A level alongside it.</p>
<p>Yeah, since the whole points system came in, BTecs are pretty much equal how they should be when apply to unis. The only trouble is if you drop out early and want to get a job (which is what I did) - employers haven’t really switched over to the new ideas for IT yet. If you’re a bricklayer or plumber, a BTec/NVQ is awesome, they consider it valuable and relevant, but for some reason IT employers still like A Levels.</p>
<p>Was just a warning in case you think you might not get to uni. If you’re not a lazy shit like me and actually stick it out though, BTec would be fine. As for if you should do maths or not, hop on UCAS website and check out the courses you’d be interested in, see if they have “A maths related subject at a level” in their entry requirements - I seem to remember most did <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/confused.png?v=6" title=":confused:" class="emoji" alt=":confused:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/a-level-maths-with-btec-ict/150676/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/a-level-maths-with-btec-ict/150676/4</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 10 Oct 2007 20:04:23 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-150676-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/a-level-maths-with-btec-ict/150676.rss">A level Maths with BTEC ICT?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>A level Maths with BTEC ICT?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Mr.Chris Mr.Chris]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/mr.chris">@Mr.Chris</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I was hoping for a reply from you. It’s a BTEC National Certificate for IT Practitioners. It’s a two year long course which takes up half of my timetable. It used to be regarded as lower than an A level, but in the recent years it has been made up to be the equivalent as two A levels (if you complete the course (you can’t drop out after one year)). Most employers and Uni’s (Apart from Oxford, Cambridge ect) regard it as the same, and welcome people with BTECs. Brighton and Manchester certainly (from what I have heard).</p>
<p>Taking four A levels is a bit of a bitch for me. I prefer coursework 100 times more than sitting a 2 hour exam at the end of the year. With BTEC you are entirely assessed on coursework alone, no exams. I’m not great at exams, but I’m good with coursework. The reason being with coursework teachers can send it back to you, telling you how to improve. So really, I should be getting As on most pieces of coursework I do. I can’t say I’m great at school, because I’m not, and fucking about in the last year and a half is something I’ve grown to regret.</p>
<p>The only subject of the 3 courses I’m going to be bored with will be Maths. I like English, but it would be something I’m prepared to change for a better subject.</p>
<p>One last thing is that the college I want to go to is mainly for Media and Arts so a very large majority of the courses are things like Drama, Art, Photography ect, non of which I’m at all interested in.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/a-level-maths-with-btec-ict/150676/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/a-level-maths-with-btec-ict/150676/3</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 10 Oct 2007 19:00:58 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-150676-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/a-level-maths-with-btec-ict/150676.rss">A level Maths with BTEC ICT?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>A level Maths with BTEC ICT?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Mopman Mopman]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/mopman">@Mopman</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Are you doing the BTec National Diploma for IT? I took a year of that once, and didn’t do any A levels at the same time. In fact, I’ve never heard of anyone taking A Levels at the same time, my timetable was pretty full with just the BTec, it is a full time course after all…</p>
<p>If I was in your position, I would be taking four A Levels. I’m NOT saying this is right for you (and I’m unemployed, so don’t take my fuckin’ advice anyway) but from my experience the BTec/NVQ qualifications hold next to no weight in the IT sector, unless you plan on doing Tech Support, and even then it’s debatable.</p>
<p>If you want to go to uni and do Comp Sci or another programming-related degree, take the maths A level, for sure. It’s a requirement for the best colleges, and highly recommended for the slightly less revered ones. Do it. (It’s really not that bad, I quite enjoyed the AS year at least).</p>
<p>If it seems like you’re gonna be bored shitless, take maths, IT or computing, and then 1 or two fun a levels (just pick them at random from what looks cool, they’re only to make up points). If you get good grades like this, you’re pretty much guaranteed a decent degree course.</p>
<p>You’re making me want to go back to school.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/a-level-maths-with-btec-ict/150676/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/a-level-maths-with-btec-ict/150676/2</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 10 Oct 2007 18:29:50 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-150676-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/a-level-maths-with-btec-ict/150676.rss">A level Maths with BTEC ICT?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>A level Maths with BTEC ICT?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Mr.Chris Mr.Chris]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/mr.chris">@Mr.Chris</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I went to a college open evening the other day to have a look at a few courses. I’m going to take a BTEC in ICT which is a two year course which counts for two A levels. Because of that, it takes up 2/4 of my A level choices. Speaking to the IT teacher yesterday, he said that doing Maths along with the BTEC would be a great advantage, and it would look much better for Uni’s with Maths under me. However, I FUCKING HATE MATHS. I’m not great at it (I’m expecting a C or a B for GCSE), but my mum and dad are pretty much forcing me to take it without them knowing.</p>
<p>For those of you in Uni or college now, studying IT, did you take Maths A level? How hard was it? Should I really take it for more Uni opportunities to arise?</p>
<p>I’m planning on taking the following courses:<br>
BTEC National course for IT Practitioners<br>
English Literature<br>
Maths/Business Studies/History</p>
<p>English and Maths just sounds so boring. I like English, but hate Maths, but I don’t see any other courses I could possibly take.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/a-level-maths-with-btec-ict/150676/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/a-level-maths-with-btec-ict/150676/1</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 10 Oct 2007 18:11:42 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-150676-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/a-level-maths-with-btec-ict/150676.rss">A level Maths with BTEC ICT?</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
