<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Trancer3&#39;s FL Studio Tutorials</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/trancer3s-fl-studio-tutorials/162393</link>
    <description>OK, so I do not know where to post this, but, as you make music with fl studio, I suppose this is the right place. True? So lets begin.

THESE GUIDES HAS BEEN POSTED ON ANOTHER FORUM, YES, BUT I HAVE WRITTEN THEM ALL (Except that my friend did translate one of my Swedish tutorials to English.)


-------------------------------------

[b]How You Can Make Songs In FL-Studio (Textbased) *[LONG]:[/b]

[i]I&#39;ve got a request to make this tutorial, so I&#39;ll do my best.[/i]

Ok, as long as I can&#39;t get hypercam or anything else to capture my sound, I wont be able to make a video.

Anyway here comes a textbased guide on how you can make songs in FL Studio:

1. I search through my fl browser for a nice kick and some other drums.
2. I either search in Vanguard, or in the fl browser for a sweet bass and some synths to use.
3. I make a bassline, mostly in the C-scale using the piano roll. The bass is marking every offbeat 1/4s. Usually I make them a length of 8 or 4 tacts, but it doesn&#39;t have to be that long. In this tutorial I am gonna use 8 tacts so it is way easier to follow it if you do the same.
4. I make a melody in same scale as the bassline using the pianoroll. One great way to know I&#39;ve got a ground in same scale as the bassline is to make it mark the same notes every 1/4 (not offbeat). Then I put other notes to make it a melody as long as the bassline.
5. I have not got drums to use, a melody and a bassline, so lets use the drums. I select the buttom at the top of step sequencer called Repeat Step Sequencer.  This will repeat the drums, and not stop after 1 tact.
6. I put the kick on every 4 step, the snare on step 5 and 13, the open hat on every 4 step offbeat and the closed hat on every 2 step/every step, or, closed hat on step 1 2 3 5 6 7 9 10 11 13 14 and 15, so I&#39;d recommend you to do something like that too.
7. Now I want to start making a song of this as I do actually have pretty much of what I need. I start with opening playlist. The pattern you are viewing right now is having a orange colour, so look for that one.
8. Before you do something in the playlist, rightclick on the pattern you have everything in. If you already have made anything in playlist, click on one pattern instance/clip and use Ctrl+A to mark all of them, then delete to delete them. When you have rightclicked, select split by channel, as this will make it split by the instruments.
9. Make a fill on an empty pattern (including drums and if you want a discrete fx effect). Now build up your song as you wish and delete all drums that your fill includes and put the fill on ever 8 bar.
10. Look up a crash, and, if you think it is really hard, you can make it some softer by finding a reversed cymbal. I&#39;d recommed you to drag it into the clip field (the field below the pattern instances) from your browser as that way you can see when they ends. If the crash still is too hard you can use an envelope by clicking on the little arrow on the clip so a menu comes. Go to Automate and select Volume. From there, take down the start a bit so it get a little lower volume. You can automate all sound clip that way so remember that. Put the crash in the beginning of bar 9 and in the beginning of the song, and the reverse in front of the crash, so it ends and then the crash start.


I am not going to take Fx and other effects in this part as I don&#39;t have time for that. Anyway I might be able to take that one in another part, but only if it is neccessary and if people really NEED tutorials about that.



[b]How to make an automation clip *[EASY]:[/b]

You have seen all those knobs where you could change to volume? Well if you want to change one of those while in the song, right click on them and press Create Automation Clip. Then there is a automation clip in your playlist. You could just click on them to make it a different volume, and when you want to delete the &#39;points&#39;, just simply right click and press delete (ON THE POINT). You can change almost everything using those, though, you might have some problems to do that on a Plug-In. I beleive it is possible to use this on ANY plug-in that comes together with FL, but I have acually myself not figured out how to make it work in for example Vanguard. You could do this on the master volume and panning and pitch too.

[b]How to insert an effect *[Halfeasy]:[/b]

[i]Credits: DJ Futz1one for translating.[/i]

1. Adding effect/plugin. 

If the instruments u want to add the effects too doesn&#39;t show in template, do like this: 

1. Mark the instrument. 
2. Open the mixer (U can see it in the same bar as where the piano roll icon is). 
3. Choose a free channel. In the original the first free channel in the Trancetemplate is named Insert 9. Left-click the one u want to use, and click on &quot;Link selected channels -&gt; To this track&quot;. If u have more instruments, do the same or mark all and do the same. 
4. It says &quot;In&quot; and there also is a little rectangle where u can choose between different line-in ports. (These are usually used when u are going to record a vocal or record something else. Under that rectangle there are numbers like 1, 2, 3, etc. Widthened, u can open it in an (Fx slot # options). Click it then select &quot;Select -&gt; Plugin that u want to use&quot;. If u are sure u have installed a new plugin and it doesn&#39;t show, click on &quot;Select -&gt; More...&quot; instead. Then a menu will popup with all the plugins that FL could find. If u still can&#39;t see it there, Click the refresh button. Then Fl will search ur plugins folder, if u are lucky, u can see the plugin u installed. Select the plugin u have found and check the little checkbox. U will now find the plugin in the add channel (Or effect) menu. 

If the instrument u want a plug-in on is showed in Mixer when u first opened the template, u won&#39;t have to try to link it to a track. Just click the track it belongs to and add plugins like i wrote before. 

2. How to use plug-ins/effects: 

This is actually quite easy if u just know how to do it. we will use Fruity Flanger, just to begin easy. There is many finished setups for flanger, so i advice u to use some of them instead. 

1. Click the arrows &lt;- -&gt; until u find one that sounds good to you. U can play the instrument u want to add it to while u look trough the different effect templates. 

When/If u find one u are satisfied with, minimize it. If u don&#39;t get satisfied with any of them, Experiment(Tweak) The buttons a bit. Be aware that some instruments makes big differense in volum some places. It can ruin the feeling of the song. 

We can go on by adding some reverb and delay. I personally like (The ones that is default in FL) Delay Bank, so open it. 

Look trough the 19 different delay presets until u find one that u get satisfied with. With the instruments i use, &quot;Classic 3 Steps&quot; should work just fine, but allways remember, all effects sounds different various from all the instruments. 

U should try adding a compressor on the instrument u know is loud or to low. Fruity Compressor is quite easy and good, but if u want something that is a little bit more advanced, then u should try out the Fruity Multiband Compressor.

-----------------------

More coming soon.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 03 Dec 2007 20:09:34 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>General Discussion</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/trancer3s-fl-studio-tutorials/162393.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Trancer3&#39;s FL Studio Tutorials</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Trancer3 Trancer3]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/trancer3">@Trancer3</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>OK, so I do not know where to post this, but, as you make music with fl studio, I suppose this is the right place. True? So lets begin.</p>
<p>THESE GUIDES HAS BEEN POSTED ON ANOTHER FORUM, YES, BUT I HAVE WRITTEN THEM ALL (Except that my friend did translate one of my Swedish tutorials to English.)</p>
<hr>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">How You Can Make Songs In FL-Studio (Textbased) *[LONG]:</span></p>
<p><span class="bbcode-i">I’ve got a request to make this tutorial, so I’ll do my best.</span></p>
<p>Ok, as long as I can’t get hypercam or anything else to capture my sound, I wont be able to make a video.</p>
<p>Anyway here comes a textbased guide on how you can make songs in FL Studio:</p>
<ol>
<li>I search through my fl browser for a nice kick and some other drums.</li>
<li>I either search in Vanguard, or in the fl browser for a sweet bass and some synths to use.</li>
<li>I make a bassline, mostly in the C-scale using the piano roll. The bass is marking every offbeat 1/4s. Usually I make them a length of 8 or 4 tacts, but it doesn’t have to be that long. In this tutorial I am gonna use 8 tacts so it is way easier to follow it if you do the same.</li>
<li>I make a melody in same scale as the bassline using the pianoroll. One great way to know I’ve got a ground in same scale as the bassline is to make it mark the same notes every 1/4 (not offbeat). Then I put other notes to make it a melody as long as the bassline.</li>
<li>I have not got drums to use, a melody and a bassline, so lets use the drums. I select the buttom at the top of step sequencer called Repeat Step Sequencer.  This will repeat the drums, and not stop after 1 tact.</li>
<li>I put the kick on every 4 step, the snare on step 5 and 13, the open hat on every 4 step offbeat and the closed hat on every 2 step/every step, or, closed hat on step 1 2 3 5 6 7 9 10 11 13 14 and 15, so I’d recommend you to do something like that too.</li>
<li>Now I want to start making a song of this as I do actually have pretty much of what I need. I start with opening playlist. The pattern you are viewing right now is having a orange colour, so look for that one.</li>
<li>Before you do something in the playlist, rightclick on the pattern you have everything in. If you already have made anything in playlist, click on one pattern instance/clip and use Ctrl+A to mark all of them, then delete to delete them. When you have rightclicked, select split by channel, as this will make it split by the instruments.</li>
<li>Make a fill on an empty pattern (including drums and if you want a discrete fx effect). Now build up your song as you wish and delete all drums that your fill includes and put the fill on ever 8 bar.</li>
<li>Look up a crash, and, if you think it is really hard, you can make it some softer by finding a reversed cymbal. I’d recommed you to drag it into the clip field (the field below the pattern instances) from your browser as that way you can see when they ends. If the crash still is too hard you can use an envelope by clicking on the little arrow on the clip so a menu comes. Go to Automate and select Volume. From there, take down the start a bit so it get a little lower volume. You can automate all sound clip that way so remember that. Put the crash in the beginning of bar 9 and in the beginning of the song, and the reverse in front of the crash, so it ends and then the crash start.</li>
</ol>
<p>I am not going to take Fx and other effects in this part as I don’t have time for that. Anyway I might be able to take that one in another part, but only if it is neccessary and if people really NEED tutorials about that.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">How to make an automation clip *[EASY]:</span></p>
<p>You have seen all those knobs where you could change to volume? Well if you want to change one of those while in the song, right click on them and press Create Automation Clip. Then there is a automation clip in your playlist. You could just click on them to make it a different volume, and when you want to delete the ‘points’, just simply right click and press delete (ON THE POINT). You can change almost everything using those, though, you might have some problems to do that on a Plug-In. I beleive it is possible to use this on ANY plug-in that comes together with FL, but I have acually myself not figured out how to make it work in for example Vanguard. You could do this on the master volume and panning and pitch too.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">How to insert an effect *[Halfeasy]:</span></p>
<p><span class="bbcode-i">Credits: DJ Futz1one for translating.</span></p>
<ol>
<li>Adding effect/plugin.</li>
</ol>
<p>If the instruments u want to add the effects too doesn’t show in template, do like this:</p>
<ol>
<li>Mark the instrument.</li>
<li>Open the mixer (U can see it in the same bar as where the piano roll icon is).</li>
<li>Choose a free channel. In the original the first free channel in the Trancetemplate is named Insert 9. Left-click the one u want to use, and click on “Link selected channels -&gt; To this track”. If u have more instruments, do the same or mark all and do the same.</li>
<li>It says “In” and there also is a little rectangle where u can choose between different line-in ports. (These are usually used when u are going to record a vocal or record something else. Under that rectangle there are numbers like 1, 2, 3, etc. Widthened, u can open it in an (Fx slot # options). Click it then select “Select -&gt; Plugin that u want to use”. If u are sure u have installed a new plugin and it doesn’t show, click on “Select -&gt; More…” instead. Then a menu will popup with all the plugins that FL could find. If u still can’t see it there, Click the refresh button. Then Fl will search ur plugins folder, if u are lucky, u can see the plugin u installed. Select the plugin u have found and check the little checkbox. U will now find the plugin in the add channel (Or effect) menu.</li>
</ol>
<p>If the instrument u want a plug-in on is showed in Mixer when u first opened the template, u won’t have to try to link it to a track. Just click the track it belongs to and add plugins like i wrote before.</p>
<ol start="2">
<li>How to use plug-ins/effects:</li>
</ol>
<p>This is actually quite easy if u just know how to do it. we will use Fruity Flanger, just to begin easy. There is many finished setups for flanger, so i advice u to use some of them instead.</p>
<ol>
<li>Click the arrows &lt;- -&gt; until u find one that sounds good to you. U can play the instrument u want to add it to while u look trough the different effect templates.</li>
</ol>
<p>When/If u find one u are satisfied with, minimize it. If u don’t get satisfied with any of them, Experiment(Tweak) The buttons a bit. Be aware that some instruments makes big differense in volum some places. It can ruin the feeling of the song.</p>
<p>We can go on by adding some reverb and delay. I personally like (The ones that is default in FL) Delay Bank, so open it.</p>
<p>Look trough the 19 different delay presets until u find one that u get satisfied with. With the instruments i use, “Classic 3 Steps” should work just fine, but allways remember, all effects sounds different various from all the instruments.</p>
<p>U should try adding a compressor on the instrument u know is loud or to low. Fruity Compressor is quite easy and good, but if u want something that is a little bit more advanced, then u should try out the Fruity Multiband Compressor.</p>
<hr>
<p>More coming soon.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/trancer3s-fl-studio-tutorials/162393/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/trancer3s-fl-studio-tutorials/162393/1</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 03 Dec 2007 20:09:34 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-162393-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/trancer3s-fl-studio-tutorials/162393.rss">Trancer3&#39;s FL Studio Tutorials</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
