<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Client doesn&#39;t work on my computer 0.o Helpz? :)</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/client-doesnt-work-on-my-computer-0-o-helpz/360051</link>
    <description>Alright, so I&#39;ve got classpath set to my java folder, obviously, in the environment variables. But, whenever I try to run my client it says &quot;java is not a yada yada yada&quot;, you know, what it says when you don&#39;t have the variable set.

I&#39;ve had my friends test out the client for me, it works just fine on their computers, and it works just fine on the housing server. My brother tried, it didn&#39;t work on his either. My friends were running XP, me and my brother are sadly making the mistake of running Windows 7. Do you think that could be the problem, or is there more variables I have to set up on my system?

Edit: Cancel this, I misread and missed a variable :p Lock plz! :)</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 13 Sep 2010 08:39:28 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/client-doesnt-work-on-my-computer-0-o-helpz/360051.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Client doesn&#39;t work on my computer 0.o Helpz? :)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@deadheart deadheart]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/deadheart">@deadheart</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Alright, so I’ve got classpath set to my java folder, obviously, in the environment variables. But, whenever I try to run my client it says “java is not a yada yada yada”, you know, what it says when you don’t have the variable set.</p>
<p>I’ve had my friends test out the client for me, it works just fine on their computers, and it works just fine on the housing server. My brother tried, it didn’t work on his either. My friends were running XP, me and my brother are sadly making the mistake of running Windows 7. Do you think that could be the problem, or is there more variables I have to set up on my system?</p>
<p>Edit: Cancel this, I misread and missed a variable <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=5" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"> Lock plz! <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=5" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/client-doesnt-work-on-my-computer-0-o-helpz/360051/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/client-doesnt-work-on-my-computer-0-o-helpz/360051/1</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 13 Sep 2010 08:39:28 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-360051-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/client-doesnt-work-on-my-computer-0-o-helpz/360051.rss">Client doesn&#39;t work on my computer 0.o Helpz? :)</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
