<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>New RSPS Help PLEASE!</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-rsps-help-please/544410</link>
    <description>Hello, I am currently trying to create a server of my very own, like so many others, I too have ideas of my own, and would love to see a server go my way, and I also would like to implement my player&#39;s ideas as well. Currently, I have damn-near no experience, but I would LOVE to start. I pretty much need all the help I can get. I have looked through almost 50 different sources and clients. I figured it would be easy to code a 314 or 317? i forget, just for some practice, but I can&#39;t find a source/client that runs smoothly under that. I would like to make a 562 purely for it&#39;s graphics and availability for coding. If anyone can help me out with a GREAT Source and client under a 562 graphics, I would HIGHLY appreciate it. (one that has a download link that works, and will also run :D thanks!). Furthermore, If someone can help me pretty much get it to run on my computer (where I will toy around with it until I learn how to code java - and watch videos on how to add things/take things away I don&#39;t want in my server), and possibly later on get it uploaded online so I can start getting players. I would appreciate this beyond appreciate... Thank you for your time and for your help!</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 29 Jun 2014 05:39:27 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-rsps-help-please/544410.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>New RSPS Help PLEASE!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@lol_space1 lol space]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/lol_space1">@lol_space1</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote" data-post="3" data-topic="544410">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/solias2500/40/5_e05bb34c421432ee4d40de30c10af3e5.png" class="avatar"> solias2500:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>OMG, you’re a life saver. I’m gonna literally try every single one of them .-. ILY haha</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Okay. Don’t listen to the guy above. He’s suggesting these sources because he’s clearly an underdeveloped coder. DeathlyPVPz is full of interfaces easy to rip that you could use. But the server itself is just bad. Full of memleaks, deadlocks and other shit that I wouldn’t want someone newish to this to deal with. My suggestion, if you want a clean gameframe and shit to start with to get to your goals, start with Asteria 2.0. It is a somewhat good starting base, and has some of what you are looking for in it. Again. TyrettaScape and DeathlyPVPz are the same source lmao with a swapped home. I wouldn’t want you trying to learn to code off bases like that…</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-rsps-help-please/544410/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-rsps-help-please/544410/4</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 29 Jun 2014 05:39:27 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-544410-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-rsps-help-please/544410.rss">New RSPS Help PLEASE!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>New RSPS Help PLEASE!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@solias2500 solias2500]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/solias2500">@solias2500</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>OMG, you’re a life saver. I’m gonna literally try every single one of them .-. ILY haha</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-rsps-help-please/544410/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-rsps-help-please/544410/3</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 29 Jun 2014 04:49:45 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-544410-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-rsps-help-please/544410.rss">New RSPS Help PLEASE!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>New RSPS Help PLEASE!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@geowayne geowayne]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/geowayne">@geowayne</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Hello! I too was in your space, and so far I was working on a server as well.</p>
<p>here is a list of tutorial to aid you on your way.</p>
<p><a href="https://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php?topic=488877.0#post_PORTF" class="onebox" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">https://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php?topic=488877.0#post_PORTF</a></p>
<p>try tyreatascape and deathlypvpz.</p>
<p>great easy 317 source and very eassssyyy.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-rsps-help-please/544410/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-rsps-help-please/544410/2</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 29 Jun 2014 02:22:55 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-544410-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-rsps-help-please/544410.rss">New RSPS Help PLEASE!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>New RSPS Help PLEASE!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@solias2500 solias2500]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/solias2500">@solias2500</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Hello, I am currently trying to create a server of my very own, like so many others, I too have ideas of my own, and would love to see a server go my way, and I also would like to implement my player’s ideas as well. Currently, I have damn-near no experience, but I would LOVE to start. I pretty much need all the help I can get. I have looked through almost 50 different sources and clients. I figured it would be easy to code a 314 or 317? i forget, just for some practice, but I can’t find a source/client that runs smoothly under that. I would like to make a 562 purely for it’s graphics and availability for coding. If anyone can help me out with a GREAT Source and client under a 562 graphics, I would HIGHLY appreciate it. (one that has a download link that works, and will also run <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/smiley.png?v=5" title=":smiley:" class="emoji" alt=":smiley:"> thanks!). Furthermore, If someone can help me pretty much get it to run on my computer (where I will toy around with it until I learn how to code java - and watch videos on how to add things/take things away I don’t want in my server), and possibly later on get it uploaded online so I can start getting players. I would appreciate this beyond appreciate… Thank you for your time and for your help!</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-rsps-help-please/544410/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-rsps-help-please/544410/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 28 Jun 2014 22:08:59 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-544410-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-rsps-help-please/544410.rss">New RSPS Help PLEASE!</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
