<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Stuck with Hamachi.. Someone reply please [//]</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/stuck-with-hamachi-someone-reply-please/36371</link>
    <description>Ok, basically downloaded moparscape and got hybridscape and couldnt change it. Then i downloaded himachi and i get all the network rubbish. So does anyone know the pass and name of merlinscape and after ive got that do i start up moparscape and does merlinscape auto come on or do i need the port and server aswell? I really do need an in depth guide but dont make it too complicated please... Im sorta new to this sort of thing... Also if you dont know the merlinscape server could 1 of you give me the server to yours and pass and stuff? PLEASE REPLY!</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 17 Dec 2006 20:37:52 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/stuck-with-hamachi-someone-reply-please/36371.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Stuck with Hamachi.. Someone reply please [//]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@MoparScape_0wnz MoparScape 0wnz!]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/moparscape_0wnz">@MoparScape_0wnz</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Ok, basically downloaded moparscape and got hybridscape and couldnt change it. Then i downloaded himachi and i get all the network rubbish. So does anyone know the pass and name of merlinscape and after ive got that do i start up moparscape and does merlinscape auto come on or do i need the port and server aswell? I really do need an in depth guide but dont make it too complicated please… Im sorta new to this sort of thing… Also if you dont know the merlinscape server could 1 of you give me the server to yours and pass and stuff? PLEASE REPLY!</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/stuck-with-hamachi-someone-reply-please/36371/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/stuck-with-hamachi-someone-reply-please/36371/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 17 Dec 2006 20:37:52 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-36371-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/stuck-with-hamachi-someone-reply-please/36371.rss">Stuck with Hamachi.. Someone reply please [//]</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
