<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>NEED HELP ASAP! Compiler is not picking up updates I make!</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/need-help-asap-compiler-is-not-picking-up-updates-i-make/373686</link>
    <description>Okay, well. I was making some updates on my allstar server, and was compiling frequently to see if I made any errors. I made a couple making a rules list, and fixed it. (I accidently put a few rules on the same line) Then, it still says i have the same errors. Thought I would just remove the lines, and retype them. So I removed them, and compiled again, still said I have these errors. So in short: My compiler isn&#39;t picking up any updates. It just quit randomly on me at a random time. Replacing it doesn&#39;t help. The same thing still happens.

Help would be greatly appreciated. Thank you.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 17 Dec 2010 22:14:23 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Game Development</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/need-help-asap-compiler-is-not-picking-up-updates-i-make/373686.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>NEED HELP ASAP! Compiler is not picking up updates I make!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@xxxlolzxxx xxxlolzxxx]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/xxxlolzxxx">@xxxlolzxxx</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Okay, well. I was making some updates on my allstar server, and was compiling frequently to see if I made any errors. I made a couple making a rules list, and fixed it. (I accidently put a few rules on the same line) Then, it still says i have the same errors. Thought I would just remove the lines, and retype them. So I removed them, and compiled again, still said I have these errors. So in short: My compiler isn’t picking up any updates. It just quit randomly on me at a random time. Replacing it doesn’t help. The same thing still happens.</p>
<p>Help would be greatly appreciated. Thank you.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/need-help-asap-compiler-is-not-picking-up-updates-i-make/373686/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/need-help-asap-compiler-is-not-picking-up-updates-i-make/373686/1</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 17 Dec 2010 22:14:23 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-373686-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/need-help-asap-compiler-is-not-picking-up-updates-i-make/373686.rss">NEED HELP ASAP! Compiler is not picking up updates I make!</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
