<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Jeep Jacking</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/jeep-jacking/408278</link>
    <description>Hello people, MBB is back from Spain. 


This was one hell of a vacation, so let me start at the beginning, Spain is 1800 km from where I live wich equals to 18 hours driving. At about 1200 km already droven on 5 in the morning, we hear a sound in our new Jeep Patriot, a sort of exploding sound, so we go to the sideway. Another car stops in front of our Jeep, and a hysteric woman exits the vechicle and start yelling like fuck and she spins her arm a couple of time indicating something is wrong with the tires. 


Then another even more hysteric man exits the vechicle and runs towards our car, he opens all the doors, (they automatically unlock when the driver exits the car wich he did), and starts yelling in spanish he&#39;s really scared and hes saying por favor por favor this that exploding car please run please run por favor all in spanish but we got the point, so we exit the car to see what was going on, I was kinda still asleep. Then my mom looked under the car to see if something was wrong with the tires and she saw some white sneakers, she yelled that whore is stealing our car! Both the woman and the man runned to their car and drove away fast, basicly that man was distracting us, noone payed attention to the woman while she was crunching next to the drivers seat to steal the car. We thought we defeated the Spanish fucks but then I noticed that the woman was able to steal my laptop case wich included my laptop with the source code of my 95% finished game that I&#39;ve been working on for about 6 months now, the laptop, my wallet, my necklace, the charger of the laptop, the power cable of my hard drive and my HTC charger. My wallet had 56 cents in it.


Luckily my dad always removes the key when exiting the car, luckily, the laptop was as secured as possible, with a boot password, a BIOS password and a hard drive password followed up with a windows password.


When you push the on button on the laptop it asks for a password, if you try to enter setup, it asks for a password, and when you try to boot the hard drive it asks for a password. The only way to crack all those is to flash the BIOS but I don&#39;t think some stupid spanish dogs will be able to do that, also, in France, in our hotel, the charger exploded the night before the theft, but you could not tell it was exploded, it looked fine from the outside, the battery was empty, so when they try to start the laptop it won&#39;t start at all. Ha-ha. Also, my laptop is a bit fucked up as in, you have to boot the laptop 3 times before it is able to load because the processor needs to heat up. Again, ha-ha.


So yeah, they threw a big stone to our trunk wich made the noise wich left some marks on the new car. Awesome.


Also, 1 week later in that fucked up country where it&#39;s to warm and full of angry bugs and stupid people that only speak spanish, when after parking in the city to buy some bread and returning back to the car, there was a big fucking hole in our car, appareantly, the spanish people find it normal to smash all the cars with hammers, because then maybe 3 people out of those 100 will let their car be fixed. The local spanish police told us that, and yes cars without any holes in Spain in the city where we were on holiday, (no tourists), are rare.


Good thing my dad gave me 700 euros (989.45 U.S. dollars) to buy a new laptop.


So here&#39;s a question, what do you guys think about HP laptops, Asus laptops, Samsung laptops, Sony laptops and Toshiba laptops. My ex-laptop was Acer and it was the biggest mistake of my life.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 05 Aug 2011 02:29:55 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>General Discussion</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/jeep-jacking/408278.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Jeep Jacking</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@drubrkletern drubrkletern]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/drubrkletern">@drubrkletern</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote quote-modified" data-post="11" data-topic="408278">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/acrodox/40/5_e05bb34c421432ee4d40de30c10af3e5.png" class="avatar"> Acrodox:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>unleash… THE DRUB ARMY</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p><div class="lazyYT" data-youtube-id="8v_1iEa8wQ0" data-youtube-title="" data-width="480" data-height="270" data-parameters="feature=oembed&amp;wmode=opaque"></div><br>
<div class="lazyYT" data-youtube-id="xJVoq9-awFc" data-youtube-title="" data-width="480" data-height="270" data-parameters="feature=oembed&amp;wmode=opaque"></div></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/jeep-jacking/408278/12">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/jeep-jacking/408278/12</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 05 Aug 2011 02:29:55 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-408278-12</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/jeep-jacking/408278.rss">Jeep Jacking</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Jeep Jacking</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Acrodox Acrodox]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/acrodox">@Acrodox</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>unleash… THE DRUB ARMY</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/jeep-jacking/408278/11">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/jeep-jacking/408278/11</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 05 Aug 2011 02:20:42 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-408278-11</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/jeep-jacking/408278.rss">Jeep Jacking</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Jeep Jacking</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@drubrkletern drubrkletern]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/drubrkletern">@drubrkletern</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote" data-post="9" data-topic="408278">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/acrodox/40/5_e05bb34c421432ee4d40de30c10af3e5.png" class="avatar"> Acrodox:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Lets make a moparscape army and raid those bastards /flex.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>++ lol</p>
<p>This is why when i becum a big strawng troll, im going to carry a sidearm @ ALL times.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/jeep-jacking/408278/10">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/jeep-jacking/408278/10</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 05 Aug 2011 02:00:56 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-408278-10</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/jeep-jacking/408278.rss">Jeep Jacking</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Jeep Jacking</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Acrodox Acrodox]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/acrodox">@Acrodox</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Lets make a moparscape army and raid those bastards /flex.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/jeep-jacking/408278/9">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/jeep-jacking/408278/9</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 05 Aug 2011 01:57:48 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-408278-9</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/jeep-jacking/408278.rss">Jeep Jacking</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Jeep Jacking</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Muroth Muroth]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/muroth">@Muroth</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>My opinion is, if it has a lot of fans and doesn’t really overheat, and has decent specifications, then I like it.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/jeep-jacking/408278/8">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/jeep-jacking/408278/8</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 05 Aug 2011 01:47:09 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-408278-8</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/jeep-jacking/408278.rss">Jeep Jacking</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Jeep Jacking</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@the_elve_age the elve age]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/the_elve_age">@the_elve_age</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Hp laptops.</p>
<p>Also, its funny how desperate people are for money, how did that lady manage to steal your laptop without being seen…?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/jeep-jacking/408278/7">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/jeep-jacking/408278/7</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 05 Aug 2011 01:46:32 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-408278-7</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/jeep-jacking/408278.rss">Jeep Jacking</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Jeep Jacking</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@CoonHunter CoonHunter]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/coonhunter">@CoonHunter</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Really brands of laptops make <span class="bbcode-b">NO</span> difference at all. You will need to do research on specific laptops. Every brand has its duds and studs (bad words lol) for laptops. I personally used to grudge against how shitty Asus was about laptops, when infact, it was a partial dud of theirs. My uncle had an old Asus G3 laptop, that after playing Americas Army on for a while, would be near temp to cook an egg. I have bought a Asus G73jw from them and have had no real issues with cooling unless I have it ontop of something that will limit its air-flow majorly. Just look into reviews of a few laptops and such, don’t specify over brands.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/jeep-jacking/408278/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/jeep-jacking/408278/6</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 05 Aug 2011 01:03:41 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-408278-6</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/jeep-jacking/408278.rss">Jeep Jacking</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Jeep Jacking</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@B2300_T4nk B2300 T4nk]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/b2300_t4nk">@B2300_T4nk</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Congratulations.</p>
<p><span class="mention">@OT</span>: HP.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/jeep-jacking/408278/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/jeep-jacking/408278/5</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 05 Aug 2011 01:01:20 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-408278-5</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/jeep-jacking/408278.rss">Jeep Jacking</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Jeep Jacking</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Fridder Fridder]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/fridder">@Fridder</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>My sister has a Toshiba laptop, it’s an absolute piece of shit. It overheats if you keep it on your lap the wrong way. You have to give it the whole left side of your leg and somehow put your left leg somewhere else and let the laptop have air. If you want it on the table, you have to keep it on the corner of the left side of the table. This is one of the many laptops by Toshiba, but imo get an HP. My screen’s frame came off but it’s better having a laptop with a broken frame than a laptop that overheats every 3 minutes.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/jeep-jacking/408278/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/jeep-jacking/408278/4</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 05 Aug 2011 00:58:11 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-408278-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/jeep-jacking/408278.rss">Jeep Jacking</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Jeep Jacking</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Vexillum Vexillum]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/vexillum">@Vexillum</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Hp or Toshiba, I have an Hp and my cousin has a Toshiba and they both seem to work great. Toshiba seems to run better on games like RS and WoW.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/jeep-jacking/408278/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/jeep-jacking/408278/3</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 04 Aug 2011 23:18:18 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-408278-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/jeep-jacking/408278.rss">Jeep Jacking</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Jeep Jacking</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Mack_n_cheese Mack n cheese]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/mack_n_cheese">@Mack_n_cheese</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>spanish fucks ahaha, sorry to hear about your stuff <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=5" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"></p>
<p>idk much bout computers so…</p>
<p>idk to your question</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/jeep-jacking/408278/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/jeep-jacking/408278/2</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 04 Aug 2011 23:05:10 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-408278-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/jeep-jacking/408278.rss">Jeep Jacking</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Jeep Jacking</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@MistaBigBoss MistaBigBoss]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/mistabigboss">@MistaBigBoss</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Hello people, MBB is back from Spain.</p>
<p>This was one hell of a vacation, so let me start at the beginning, Spain is 1800 km from where I live wich equals to 18 hours driving. At about 1200 km already droven on 5 in the morning, we hear a sound in our new Jeep Patriot, a sort of exploding sound, so we go to the sideway. Another car stops in front of our Jeep, and a hysteric woman exits the vechicle and start yelling like fuck and she spins her arm a couple of time indicating something is wrong with the tires.</p>
<p>Then another even more hysteric man exits the vechicle and runs towards our car, he opens all the doors, (they automatically unlock when the driver exits the car wich he did), and starts yelling in spanish he’s really scared and hes saying por favor por favor this that exploding car please run please run por favor all in spanish but we got the point, so we exit the car to see what was going on, I was kinda still asleep. Then my mom looked under the car to see if something was wrong with the tires and she saw some white sneakers, she yelled that whore is stealing our car! Both the woman and the man runned to their car and drove away fast, basicly that man was distracting us, noone payed attention to the woman while she was crunching next to the drivers seat to steal the car. We thought we defeated the Spanish fucks but then I noticed that the woman was able to steal my laptop case wich included my laptop with the source code of my 95% finished game that I’ve been working on for about 6 months now, the laptop, my wallet, my necklace, the charger of the laptop, the power cable of my hard drive and my HTC charger. My wallet had 56 cents in it.</p>
<p>Luckily my dad always removes the key when exiting the car, luckily, the laptop was as secured as possible, with a boot password, a BIOS password and a hard drive password followed up with a windows password.</p>
<p>When you push the on button on the laptop it asks for a password, if you try to enter setup, it asks for a password, and when you try to boot the hard drive it asks for a password. The only way to crack all those is to flash the BIOS but I don’t think some stupid spanish dogs will be able to do that, also, in France, in our hotel, the charger exploded the night before the theft, but you could not tell it was exploded, it looked fine from the outside, the battery was empty, so when they try to start the laptop it won’t start at all. Ha-ha. Also, my laptop is a bit fucked up as in, you have to boot the laptop 3 times before it is able to load because the processor needs to heat up. Again, ha-ha.</p>
<p>So yeah, they threw a big stone to our trunk wich made the noise wich left some marks on the new car. Awesome.</p>
<p>Also, 1 week later in that fucked up country where it’s to warm and full of angry bugs and stupid people that only speak spanish, when after parking in the city to buy some bread and returning back to the car, there was a big fucking hole in our car, appareantly, the spanish people find it normal to smash all the cars with hammers, because then maybe 3 people out of those 100 will let their car be fixed. The local spanish police told us that, and yes cars without any holes in Spain in the city where we were on holiday, (no tourists), are rare.</p>
<p>Good thing my dad gave me 700 euros (989.45 U.S. dollars) to buy a new laptop.</p>
<p>So here’s a question, what do you guys think about HP laptops, Asus laptops, Samsung laptops, Sony laptops and Toshiba laptops. My ex-laptop was Acer and it was the biggest mistake of my life.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/jeep-jacking/408278/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/jeep-jacking/408278/1</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 04 Aug 2011 22:41:56 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-408278-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/jeep-jacking/408278.rss">Jeep Jacking</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
