<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Hyperion Password Help</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/hyperion-password-help/425401</link>
    <description>Okay, so I&#39;ve come across an unusual situation.

[URL=http://imageshack.us/photo/my-images/41/94469436.png/][IMG]http://img41.imageshack.us/img41/8462/94469436.png[/img][/URL]

Now I don&#39;t want to start inviting players to come play the server and have this happen because at the moment I can only resolve it by deleting the character file.

The file is in .dat format so if I edit the file (open it with notepad it&#39;s no longer compatible with the server). I&#39;ve been trying pieces of code to change the password for me upon log in but nothing has worked (kind of like the same way I would set player rights upon log in).

I also have no idea what is flagging this, and obviously I can&#39;t log in to ::change pass, and there&#39;s no website connected to the server.

Any ideas/thoughts appreciated.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 15 Dec 2011 18:28:59 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/hyperion-password-help/425401.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Hyperion Password Help</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@The_Outsider The Outsider]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/the_outsider">@The_Outsider</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Okay, so I’ve come across an unusual situation.</p>
<p><a href="http://imageshack.us/photo/my-images/41/94469436.png/" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener"><img src="http://img41.imageshack.us/img41/8462/94469436.png" alt width="" height=""></a></p>
<p>Now I don’t want to start inviting players to come play the server and have this happen because at the moment I can only resolve it by deleting the character file.</p>
<p>The file is in .dat format so if I edit the file (open it with notepad it’s no longer compatible with the server). I’ve been trying pieces of code to change the password for me upon log in but nothing has worked (kind of like the same way I would set player rights upon log in).</p>
<p>I also have no idea what is flagging this, and obviously I can’t log in to ::change pass, and there’s no website connected to the server.</p>
<p>Any ideas/thoughts appreciated.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/hyperion-password-help/425401/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/hyperion-password-help/425401/1</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 15 Dec 2011 18:28:59 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-425401-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/hyperion-password-help/425401.rss">Hyperion Password Help</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
