<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>[660] Online mapdata dumping [help us collect mapdata]</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/660-online-mapdata-dumping-help-us-collect-mapdata/408376</link>
    <description>Hey today I worked pretty much all day lol to make this happen. Pretty much it&#39;s like any dumper here but all the mapdata gets saved on this website.

http://www.rushgamer.com/mapdata

(Hopefully you guys won&#39;t ruin this by submitting false mapdata.. although i&#39;ll have a fix for this in the future.. where i&#39;ll check do some kind of cache check.)

I&#39;ll keep updating the online version of mapdata to make it downloadable in compressed format of txt files.. and maybe even a binary format.

Download Link:
[url=http://www.mediafire.com/?kkf707lkn09123g]660 db mapdata dumper.zip[/url]

If anyone has any doubts if this is keylogged or anything in that matter.. I dont know what to say but you have to trust me, it does send data to rushgamer.com.. but that data doesn&#39;t contain your username or password, only mapdata keys+regionIndex

Credits go to 03data for his good deobfuscator without it, I wouldn&#39;t know where to put mapdata method, and Graham too I used his loader in this.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 05 Aug 2011 13:52:25 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/660-online-mapdata-dumping-help-us-collect-mapdata/408376.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>[660] Online mapdata dumping [help us collect mapdata]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@sspoke sspoke]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/sspoke">@sspoke</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Hey today I worked pretty much all day lol to make this happen. Pretty much it’s like any dumper here but all the mapdata gets saved on this website.</p>
<p><a href="http://www.rushgamer.com/mapdata" class="onebox" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">http://www.rushgamer.com/mapdata</a></p>
<p>(Hopefully you guys won’t ruin this by submitting false mapdata… although i’ll have a fix for this in the future… where i’ll check do some kind of cache check.)</p>
<p>I’ll keep updating the online version of mapdata to make it downloadable in compressed format of txt files… and maybe even a binary format.</p>
<p>Download Link:<br>
<a href="http://www.mediafire.com/?kkf707lkn09123g" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">660 db mapdata dumper.zip</a></p>
<p>If anyone has any doubts if this is keylogged or anything in that matter… I dont know what to say but you have to trust me, it does send data to <a href="http://rushgamer.com" rel="nofollow noopener">rushgamer.com</a>… but that data doesn’t contain your username or password, only mapdata keys+regionIndex</p>
<p>Credits go to 03data for his good deobfuscator without it, I wouldn’t know where to put mapdata method, and Graham too I used his loader in this.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/660-online-mapdata-dumping-help-us-collect-mapdata/408376/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/660-online-mapdata-dumping-help-us-collect-mapdata/408376/1</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 05 Aug 2011 13:52:25 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-408376-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/660-online-mapdata-dumping-help-us-collect-mapdata/408376.rss">[660] Online mapdata dumping [help us collect mapdata]</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
