<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>[READ] Moparcraft Information Thread [/READ]</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/read-moparcraft-information-thread-read/434110</link>
    <description>[center][size=18pt]Moparcraft[/size][/center]

This thread will be used to outline important information, that you must read before considering to report anybody, or do anything relating to that. 

[hr]

[b][u]Player communication[/u][/b]

Please ensure you speak to the person you&#39;re reporting before posting the topic, you have to remember, that we&#39;re all human and we all make mistakes. Please speak to each other in a mature manner and try to resolve it without staff intervention.

We are not a first resort, we&#39;re a last resort.

[hr]

[b][u]Cheaters[/u][/b]

Cheating has always been against the rules on Moparcraft, whether it be fly hacking or the abuse of a bug - it is cheating and we have never accepted it. We&#39;re now putting our foot down even further on those who wish to cheat on Moparcraft.

From xraying, to bug abuse, to speed hacking, to whatever else there may be in the weird and wonderful world of client modifications, we&#39;ll be keeping a closer eye on those who wish to abuse said modifications.

[b]From now on (05/05/2012) all players found cheating will recieve a significantly longer ban than previously given[/b]. We have explored various enforcement techniques and they will be put into actions.

[hr]

[b][u]How to report somebody[/u][/b]

We use a rollback tool called core inspect, to use it do:

/co inspect

You can then evaluate who has done what to your blocks, [b]when reporting somebody it is vital that you provide evidence in the form of screenshots showing the core protect data. Also not everyone knows where you live so please also post the coordinates of the evidence.[/b]</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Feb 2012 02:57:52 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Minecraft</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/read-moparcraft-information-thread-read/434110.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>[READ] Moparcraft Information Thread [/READ]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Tom Tom]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/tom">@Tom</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[center][size=18pt]Moparcraft[/size][/center]</p>
<p>This thread will be used to outline important information, that you must read before considering to report anybody, or do anything relating to that.</p>
<p>[hr]</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b"><span class="bbcode-u">Player communication</span></span></p>
<p>Please ensure you speak to the person you’re reporting before posting the topic, you have to remember, that we’re all human and we all make mistakes. Please speak to each other in a mature manner and try to resolve it without staff intervention.</p>
<p>We are not a first resort, we’re a last resort.</p>
<p>[hr]</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b"><span class="bbcode-u">Cheaters</span></span></p>
<p>Cheating has always been against the rules on Moparcraft, whether it be fly hacking or the abuse of a bug - it is cheating and we have never accepted it. We’re now putting our foot down even further on those who wish to cheat on Moparcraft.</p>
<p>From xraying, to bug abuse, to speed hacking, to whatever else there may be in the weird and wonderful world of client modifications, we’ll be keeping a closer eye on those who wish to abuse said modifications.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">From now on (05/05/2012) all players found cheating will recieve a significantly longer ban than previously given</span>. We have explored various enforcement techniques and they will be put into actions.</p>
<p>[hr]</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b"><span class="bbcode-u">How to report somebody</span></span></p>
<p>We use a rollback tool called core inspect, to use it do:</p>
<p>/co inspect</p>
<p>You can then evaluate who has done what to your blocks, <span class="bbcode-b">when reporting somebody it is vital that you provide evidence in the form of screenshots showing the core protect data. Also not everyone knows where you live so please also post the coordinates of the evidence.</span></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/read-moparcraft-information-thread-read/434110/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/read-moparcraft-information-thread-read/434110/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 25 Feb 2012 02:57:52 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-434110-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/read-moparcraft-information-thread-read/434110.rss">[READ] Moparcraft Information Thread [/READ]</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
