<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Project Insanity sound</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/project-insanity-sound/468007</link>
    <description>I&#39;m trying to make a F2P Remake using Project Insanity. So far it&#39;s going pretty damn amazing if I was to be modest, however it quickly sprang to mind that I&#39;d need sound. I&#39;m aware that some of it is client sided and some is server so I wasn&#39;t sure what section to post in. However, does anyone know how to add sounds? In terms of when you level up or what have you as well as area sounds so if you&#39;re in certain coordinates it changes track? Even if you can only provide some or part of the requested information it&#39;s better than nothing and it&#39;d be appreciated. Please bare in mind I&#39;m not great so bare with me. Thanks a lot:)</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 13 Nov 2012 17:27:17 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Game Development</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/project-insanity-sound/468007.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Project Insanity sound</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@The_Unholy The Unholy]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/the_unholy">@The_Unholy</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I’m trying to make a F2P Remake using Project Insanity. So far it’s going pretty damn amazing if I was to be modest, however it quickly sprang to mind that I’d need sound. I’m aware that some of it is client sided and some is server so I wasn’t sure what section to post in. However, does anyone know how to add sounds? In terms of when you level up or what have you as well as area sounds so if you’re in certain coordinates it changes track? Even if you can only provide some or part of the requested information it’s better than nothing and it’d be appreciated. Please bare in mind I’m not great so bare with me. Thanks a lot:)</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/project-insanity-sound/468007/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/project-insanity-sound/468007/1</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 13 Nov 2012 17:27:17 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-468007-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/project-insanity-sound/468007.rss">Project Insanity sound</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
