<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Server used to work, got virus and fixed, now doesn&#39;t work</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/server-used-to-work-got-virus-and-fixed-now-doesnt-work/340596</link>
    <description>Hey, I&#39;m having some issues running a server available to other people. I used to be able to run servers from my computer perfectly fine (my old server had around 20-25 people on at all times), but now it just isn&#39;t working. I got some type of rogue malware on my computer around April (april 12, to be exact), and running a server with me and my friend was working fine that day, as well as the weekend. That night, I left my computer running and when I came back a fake antivirus was installed that called itself &quot;digital protection&quot;. This virus disabled task manager, added links to my computer, and randomly rebooted my computer telling me that I had a critical system virus or something. I ran my norton 2009 from a bootable disc and partially removed the malware (if that&#39;s even possible. What I mean is it deleted one of the threats), but it didn&#39;t fully resolve the threat. Booting windows in safe mode wasn&#39;t working, and I haven&#39;t checked if it has since I fixed. I ended up going using a CD-R to transfer an application known as killbox (works like task manager, basically), and stopped the viruses processes, according to a trusted virus help website (and my dad with a professional career in computers). I then went into the registry and fixed the keys that were added, and deleted them, and ran malwarebytes (trusted free antimalware) and deleted a total of 19 threats. Unfortunately, my norton is picking up attacks from external servers aimed at my svchost, which I downloaded peerblock and manually blocked out the attacking IPs. 

Anyways, all servers are running fine on my computer, and things are going well (virus seems to be removed, I&#39;ve scanned my computer with multiple different programs; malwarebytes, norton, windows defender). But I&#39;m unable to host the server from my computer, and I&#39;m not sure what&#39;s wrong. If anybody knows anything about this type of stuff, can you help me out? Any help is greatly appreciated, I want to be able to host a server again soon.

Thanks for your time,
Legendz (Mod Whip)
Proud owner of Legendz PK</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 19 May 2010 00:25:23 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/server-used-to-work-got-virus-and-fixed-now-doesnt-work/340596.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Server used to work, got virus and fixed, now doesn&#39;t work</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Mod_Whip Mod Whip]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/mod_whip">@Mod_Whip</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote no-group quote-modified" data-post="2" data-topic="340596">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 Mighty Penguin:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Wow! This is the exact same thing that happened to me. I’m seeking out the answer. But yea, good luck.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>yeah it might be linked to the virus… If I ping my computer from my other computer I do recieve a response… need to try out and see if I can get a friend to do it.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/server-used-to-work-got-virus-and-fixed-now-doesnt-work/340596/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/server-used-to-work-got-virus-and-fixed-now-doesnt-work/340596/3</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 19 May 2010 00:25:23 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-340596-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/server-used-to-work-got-virus-and-fixed-now-doesnt-work/340596.rss">Server used to work, got virus and fixed, now doesn&#39;t work</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Server used to work, got virus and fixed, now doesn&#39;t work</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Mighty_Penguin Mighty Penguin]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/mighty_penguin">@Mighty_Penguin</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Wow! This is the exact same thing that happened to me. I’m seeking out the answer. But yea, good luck.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/server-used-to-work-got-virus-and-fixed-now-doesnt-work/340596/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/server-used-to-work-got-virus-and-fixed-now-doesnt-work/340596/2</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 18 May 2010 23:46:13 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-340596-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/server-used-to-work-got-virus-and-fixed-now-doesnt-work/340596.rss">Server used to work, got virus and fixed, now doesn&#39;t work</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Server used to work, got virus and fixed, now doesn&#39;t work</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Mod_Whip Mod Whip]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/mod_whip">@Mod_Whip</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Hey, I’m having some issues running a server available to other people. I used to be able to run servers from my computer perfectly fine (my old server had around 20-25 people on at all times), but now it just isn’t working. I got some type of rogue malware on my computer around April (april 12, to be exact), and running a server with me and my friend was working fine that day, as well as the weekend. That night, I left my computer running and when I came back a fake antivirus was installed that called itself “digital protection”. This virus disabled task manager, added links to my computer, and randomly rebooted my computer telling me that I had a critical system virus or something. I ran my norton 2009 from a bootable disc and partially removed the malware (if that’s even possible. What I mean is it deleted one of the threats), but it didn’t fully resolve the threat. Booting windows in safe mode wasn’t working, and I haven’t checked if it has since I fixed. I ended up going using a CD-R to transfer an application known as killbox (works like task manager, basically), and stopped the viruses processes, according to a trusted virus help website (and my dad with a professional career in computers). I then went into the registry and fixed the keys that were added, and deleted them, and ran malwarebytes (trusted free antimalware) and deleted a total of 19 threats. Unfortunately, my norton is picking up attacks from external servers aimed at my svchost, which I downloaded peerblock and manually blocked out the attacking IPs.</p>
<p>Anyways, all servers are running fine on my computer, and things are going well (virus seems to be removed, I’ve scanned my computer with multiple different programs; malwarebytes, norton, windows defender). But I’m unable to host the server from my computer, and I’m not sure what’s wrong. If anybody knows anything about this type of stuff, can you help me out? Any help is greatly appreciated, I want to be able to host a server again soon.</p>
<p>Thanks for your time,<br>
Legendz (Mod Whip)<br>
Proud owner of Legendz PK</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/server-used-to-work-got-virus-and-fixed-now-doesnt-work/340596/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/server-used-to-work-got-virus-and-fixed-now-doesnt-work/340596/1</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 18 May 2010 22:53:53 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-340596-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/server-used-to-work-got-virus-and-fixed-now-doesnt-work/340596.rss">Server used to work, got virus and fixed, now doesn&#39;t work</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
