<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>RE1 Remake Livestream</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/re1-remake-livestream/547208</link>
    <description>Going to set-up a live stream of me running through this game, haven&#39;t played it in awhile and seeing as how they are going to release an enhanced version of this for next-gen consoles may as well dust the cobwebs off.

If you didn&#39;t know this game was originally release on the Playstation 1, so imagine the graphics, though that one is a classic and is one of my personal favorites, this game which was the ONLY Resident Evil overhauled from the old genre, it was released on GameCube with better Graphics and more content packed into the Mansion without messing with how the original story unfolded.

This is one of the best Resident Evil games ever made IMO so if you like the games even somewhat feel free to stop by and watch this epic survival-horror.

Link: http://www.twitch.tv/ep1cfps</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 11 Oct 2014 07:18:47 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Games</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/re1-remake-livestream/547208.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>RE1 Remake Livestream</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@MicroZoft MicroZoft]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/microzoft">@MicroZoft</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Going to set-up a live stream of me running through this game, haven’t played it in awhile and seeing as how they are going to release an enhanced version of this for next-gen consoles may as well dust the cobwebs off.</p>
<p>If you didn’t know this game was originally release on the Playstation 1, so imagine the graphics, though that one is a classic and is one of my personal favorites, this game which was the ONLY Resident Evil overhauled from the old genre, it was released on GameCube with better Graphics and more content packed into the Mansion without messing with how the original story unfolded.</p>
<p>This is one of the best Resident Evil games ever made IMO so if you like the games even somewhat feel free to stop by and watch this epic survival-horror.</p>
<p>Link: <a href="http://www.twitch.tv/ep1cfps" rel="nofollow noopener">http://www.twitch.tv/ep1cfps</a></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/re1-remake-livestream/547208/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/re1-remake-livestream/547208/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 11 Oct 2014 07:18:47 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-547208-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/re1-remake-livestream/547208.rss">RE1 Remake Livestream</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
