<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Behind the scenes November</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/behind-the-scenes-november/420224</link>
    <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;While recovering from RuneFest and some epic Halloween parties, it’s nice to know there&#39;ll be some chunky updates to help me recover. Updates to take my mind off all the sweets and pumpkin pie I didn’t eat. Honest! 

[b]Thanksgiving 2011[/b]

We&#39;re not done partying quite yet, although the turkeys of RuneScape have a different idea on how to celebrate Thanksgiving this year. Captain Turkerton and his turkey brethren are planning a protest against their species being put on the Thanksgiving menu for another year! If their demands aren’t met, a turkey invasion seems imminent, and they&#39;re prepared to gobble up the land. Can you find a peaceful solution? Can you stand the thought of Thanksgiving dinner without turkey? 

Free players and members completing the turkey event will be able to unlock the new Thanksgiving crest for their herald capes, which will also change the turkey emote if played while worn. Members will also be able to unlock a brand new turkey pet! 

[b]Re-working the Interface[/b]

We are continually re-working areas of RuneScape that we feel could do with a lick of paint. These improvements aren’t just about NPC models, environments and gameplay, though. They also relate to the main game screen itself, which we call the &quot;top level interface&quot;. 

The top level rework involves an overhaul of the interfaces that are used by players all the time. We are improving the style and functionality, and are introducing a new vibrant colour scheme. These changes include: 


[ul][li]Brand-new info boxes, making examine messages and left click actions appear over the item your clicking on rather than hidden as a text message. No more checking the top left corner for NPC names - they&#39;ll appear next to your mouse cursor if this option is enabled.[/li]
[li]New “stone buttons” (the ones you use to open your inventory, quest journal etc) with new icons (don’t worry; they’re based on the old ones).[/li]
[li]A rework of the borders of the minimap, including a new “metallic” look.[/li]
[li]New “trims” to the side panel interfaces themselves (like the inventory).[/li][/ul]


[b]New Website[/b]

We’re undergoing a complete overhaul of the RuneScape website design. The new design is a big departure from the current look and feel. We aim to capture the grand sense of adventure and exploration that RuneScape offers and bring that right out into the foundations of the site, while keeping all of the great features and information that you use on a day-to-day basis. 

[b]New Slayer Dungeon[/b]

If, like myself, you’re a fan of the Slayer skill, you’ll be excited when you read the title of this update! As soon as you enter this new dungeon, you will find yourself immersed in some amazing, jaw-dropping scenery, but don’t look down, as this dungeon has a real sense of ‘depth’ to it. 

Towards the end of the month, we’ll be launching the Polypore Dungeon. A ramokee has snuck into RuneScape and used her skinweaving powers to create a variety of horrific new monsters, many of which can only be killed by high-level slayers, and are best tackled with magic. Those who can defeat the ganodermic beasts (level 95 Slayer) may emerge with a unique kind of battlestaff and the materials to make incredibly protective mage armour. Elsewhere in the dungeon, there’ll be mage armour for lower-level fighters, and a very suspicious mushroom for PKers to eat. 

The ramokee herself was originally destined from birth to serve her tribe as a healer, but she has rejected that destiny and abandoned her tribe. Now she sits enthroned in the depths of the cave, revelling in the freedom to use her skinweaving powers to indulge her own whims and curiosity. Along with the skinweaver, the dungeon is home to a strange little man with a sad story. He sells bizarre garments that form the basis of the mage armour. 

[b]One Piercing Note[/b]

If you’ve seen the bottom of our newest Lores and Histories story, you’ll already know the title of November’s quest: One Piercing Note. Legend has it that, during the God Wars, there lived a holy woman named Elspeth whose voice was so perfect that no demon could bear to hear it. In the present age, a group of Saradominist holy women found Elspeth’s remains on a remote desert plateau and set up an abbey in her memory. Within the abbey’s sand-blasted walls the Sisters of Saint Elspeth devote their lives to prayer and sacred music. 

Now there has been a murder in the abbey, and Abbess Benita is praying for an adventurer to investigate. To complicate matters, a wandering troubadour has set up camp outside the abbey, despite the order’s rules forbidding secular music. It’s up to you to uncover the abbey’s secrets and find the killer. 

As befitting a quest involving a troubadour and a holy choir, sound and music play a prominent role in One Piercing Note. The music is woven into the story, and includes recordings of real musicians and singers. In addition, in a first for RuneScape, all NPC dialogue will be voice-acted. So, turn your speakers on and enjoy our latest all-singing, all-dancing quest!

[hr]

[b]Requirements for One Piercing Note:[/b]


[ul][li]None (besides being members-only)[/li]
[li]Higher-level players who own god books can return after the quest for a new activity requiring level 60 in Prayer and Crafting.[/li][/ul]


[hr]

[b]Wilderness Graphical Updates[/b]

Last, but not least, we’re planning on reworking large areas of the Wilderness graphics. These include: 


[ul][li]Many landmark locations including: the King Black Dragon’s lair, teleport obelisks, the Mage Arena and the Agility training area.[/li]
[li]New lava environments.[/li]
[li]A higher frame rate; reducing PK issues, not adding to them![/li][/ul]


Visit our [url=http://www.runescape.com/kbase/guid/media]media page[/url] for some sneak preview screenshots! 

Have fun! 

Mod Mark 
RS Lead Designer&lt;/blockquote&gt;
[url=http://www.runescape.com/img/news/Screenshots/BTS/1111/site_ss.jpg]New website[/url]
[url=http://img525.imageshack.us/img525/4219/capturefy.png]Entrance to the new dungeon[/url]</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 01 Nov 2011 21:44:58 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/behind-the-scenes-november/420224.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Behind the scenes November</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@vManlyMan vManlyMan]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/vmanlyman">@vManlyMan</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Slayer dungeon sounds cool.  I’m really not anticipating the change of the wilderness.  Probably just going to fuck up everything for pkers.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/behind-the-scenes-november/420224/21">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/behind-the-scenes-november/420224/21</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 01 Nov 2011 21:44:58 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-420224-21</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/behind-the-scenes-november/420224.rss">Behind the scenes November</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Behind the scenes November</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Kidpaparoach Kidpaparoach]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/kidpaparoach">@Kidpaparoach</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>New sites oooogly.<br>
The in-game maps look well good, I play in min specs (although 50ps on high;) ) just because it still kind of looks like the old rs in a sense.<br>
Rs’s maps have always been good but i don’t like all this hdd shit, I like rs for being unique… Like I don’t like full-screen games like wow etc…</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/behind-the-scenes-november/420224/20">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/behind-the-scenes-november/420224/20</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 01 Nov 2011 21:18:40 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-420224-20</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/behind-the-scenes-november/420224.rss">Behind the scenes November</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Behind the scenes November</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@the_elve_age the elve age]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/the_elve_age">@the_elve_age</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“Native^, post:7, topic:420224”]Looking 1337! Really like the new graphical updates. I only don’t hope all the PIs are now going to load 670…[/quote]You do know that its a client loading higher revisions. Not a “source” as Project Insanity is a source…</p>
<p>But in all honesty, I don’t like how Runescape has changed. I can’t let go of those great times 4-5 years ago. The website I think looks hideous, but in retrospect they are just trying to be like every other game with flashy websites. Which isn’t what Runescape was originally about (to me at least). They are now a business of truly making money instead of satisfying players, and caring about the community (which got them 100-150k legit players). Ugh.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/behind-the-scenes-november/420224/19">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/behind-the-scenes-november/420224/19</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 01 Nov 2011 20:40:59 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-420224-19</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/behind-the-scenes-november/420224.rss">Behind the scenes November</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Behind the scenes November</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Fridder Fridder]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/fridder">@Fridder</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>New lava looks awesome. The new website looks a lot better compared to what they’re doing now. They’re finally doing a thanksgiving event, I think the last event was in 2009. I remember last year there was nothing, either that or I just didn’t give enough shits (the phrase ‘shits’ is being used as a currency here) to log in. Everything looks good so far. Graphics are improving, the website is improving etc,… how does this affect older computers? They need to go out and buy new ones because this shit is going to be too slow for their computers. I’m talking about computers that are from 2005 with under 1GB of RAM.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/behind-the-scenes-november/420224/18">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/behind-the-scenes-november/420224/18</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 01 Nov 2011 20:34:20 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-420224-18</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/behind-the-scenes-november/420224.rss">Behind the scenes November</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Behind the scenes November</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Frell Frell]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/frell">@Frell</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Open the link and then click in the address bar and hit enter</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/behind-the-scenes-november/420224/17">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/behind-the-scenes-november/420224/17</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 01 Nov 2011 20:26:41 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-420224-17</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/behind-the-scenes-november/420224.rss">Behind the scenes November</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Behind the scenes November</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@davidi2 Davidi2]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/davidi2">@davidi2</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Genuinely interested in the website/gui updates</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/behind-the-scenes-november/420224/16">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/behind-the-scenes-november/420224/16</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 01 Nov 2011 20:05:26 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-420224-16</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/behind-the-scenes-november/420224.rss">Behind the scenes November</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Behind the scenes November</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Wet_Dreamss Wet Dreamss]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/wet_dreamss">@Wet_Dreamss</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote" data-post="14" data-topic="420224">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/rip4d/40/5_e05bb34c421432ee4d40de30c10af3e5.png" class="avatar"> rip4d:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Its not out yet, its in the BTS.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I know its not out lmao, im saying i click his link and it says invalid link or whatever</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/behind-the-scenes-november/420224/15">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/behind-the-scenes-november/420224/15</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 01 Nov 2011 20:05:09 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-420224-15</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/behind-the-scenes-november/420224.rss">Behind the scenes November</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Behind the scenes November</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@rip4d rip4d]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/rip4d">@rip4d</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Its not out yet, its in the BTS.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/behind-the-scenes-november/420224/14">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/behind-the-scenes-november/420224/14</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 01 Nov 2011 20:03:56 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-420224-14</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/behind-the-scenes-november/420224.rss">Behind the scenes November</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Behind the scenes November</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Wet_Dreamss Wet Dreamss]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/wet_dreamss">@Wet_Dreamss</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>can’t see new website even refreshed D:</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/behind-the-scenes-november/420224/13">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/behind-the-scenes-november/420224/13</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 01 Nov 2011 20:03:38 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-420224-13</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/behind-the-scenes-november/420224.rss">Behind the scenes November</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Behind the scenes November</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Frell Frell]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/frell">@Frell</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>The new website looks beautiful. I’m so glad they’re ditching all of that sabrey shit that makes rs look like a flash game. I loved the old rs’s stone textures on interfaces etc. everything is too shiny now, I hope they flatten the hp bars.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/behind-the-scenes-november/420224/12">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/behind-the-scenes-november/420224/12</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 01 Nov 2011 20:01:52 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-420224-12</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/behind-the-scenes-november/420224.rss">Behind the scenes November</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Behind the scenes November</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@rip4d rip4d]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/rip4d">@rip4d</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“Phaze One, post:10, topic:420224”]New slayer dungeon :):):)[/quote]Yup, its supposed to be a lot more interactive; a runefest video said that they can charge you, meaning no more safe spotting.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/behind-the-scenes-november/420224/11">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/behind-the-scenes-november/420224/11</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 01 Nov 2011 19:54:14 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-420224-11</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/behind-the-scenes-november/420224.rss">Behind the scenes November</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Behind the scenes November</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Phaze_One Fuscate]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/phaze_one">@Phaze_One</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>New slayer dungeon :):)<img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=5" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/behind-the-scenes-november/420224/10">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/behind-the-scenes-november/420224/10</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 01 Nov 2011 19:49:08 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-420224-10</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/behind-the-scenes-november/420224.rss">Behind the scenes November</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Behind the scenes November</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Wet_Dreamss Wet Dreamss]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/wet_dreamss">@Wet_Dreamss</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“rip4d, post:8, topic:420224”]Relating to the Dominion Tower, I need <span class="bbcode-b">ONE. FUCKING. QUEST</span> before I can do it;</p>
<p>Vampyre Slayer. Ya know, the F2P one.[/quote]<br>
It takes 5 mins <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/wink.png?v=5" title=":wink:" class="emoji" alt=":wink:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/behind-the-scenes-november/420224/9">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/behind-the-scenes-november/420224/9</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 01 Nov 2011 19:42:01 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-420224-9</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/behind-the-scenes-november/420224.rss">Behind the scenes November</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Behind the scenes November</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@rip4d rip4d]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/rip4d">@rip4d</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Relating to the Dominion Tower, I need <span class="bbcode-b">ONE. FUCKING. QUEST</span> before I can do it;</p>
<p>Vampyre Slayer. Ya know, the F2P one.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/behind-the-scenes-november/420224/8">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/behind-the-scenes-november/420224/8</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 01 Nov 2011 19:22:06 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-420224-8</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/behind-the-scenes-november/420224.rss">Behind the scenes November</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Behind the scenes November</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Native1 Native^]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/native1">@Native1</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Looking 1337! Really like the new graphical updates. I only don’t hope all the PIs are now going to load 670…</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/behind-the-scenes-november/420224/7">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/behind-the-scenes-november/420224/7</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 01 Nov 2011 16:47:49 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-420224-7</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/behind-the-scenes-november/420224.rss">Behind the scenes November</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Behind the scenes November</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@_Rich Rich]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/_rich">@_Rich</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote" data-post="5" data-topic="420224">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/buut15/40/5_e05bb34c421432ee4d40de30c10af3e5.png" class="avatar"> buut15:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Also does <a href="http://www.runescape.com/img/main/kbase/downloads_and_wallpapers/media/screenshots/Runescape_32.jpg" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">this</a> photo look like Al Kharid?</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I believe that’s an area for the new quest.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/behind-the-scenes-november/420224/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/behind-the-scenes-november/420224/6</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 01 Nov 2011 16:46:14 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-420224-6</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/behind-the-scenes-november/420224.rss">Behind the scenes November</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Behind the scenes November</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@buut15 buut15]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/buut15">@buut15</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>November seems very promising. I really love the new <a href="http://www.runescape.com/img/main/kbase/downloads_and_wallpapers/media/screenshots/Runescape_30.jpg" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">lava</a> and website.</p>
<p>Also does <a href="http://www.runescape.com/img/main/kbase/downloads_and_wallpapers/media/screenshots/Runescape_32.jpg" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">this</a> photo look like Al Kharid?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/behind-the-scenes-november/420224/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/behind-the-scenes-november/420224/5</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 01 Nov 2011 16:43:49 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-420224-5</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/behind-the-scenes-november/420224.rss">Behind the scenes November</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Behind the scenes November</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@tinyscape TinyScape]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/tinyscape">@tinyscape</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>The website is amazing.</p>
<blockquote>[b]Re-working the Interface[/b]
<p>We are continually re-working areas of RuneScape that we feel could do with a lick of paint. These improvements aren’t just about NPC models, environments and gameplay, though. They also relate to the main game screen itself, which we call the “top level interface”.</p>
<p>The top level rework involves an overhaul of the interfaces that are used by players all the time. We are improving the style and functionality, and are introducing a new vibrant colour scheme. These changes include:</p>
<p>[ul][li]Brand-new info boxes, making examine messages and left click actions app[ear over the item your clicking on rather than hidden as a text message. No more checking the top left corner for NPC names - they’ll appear next to your mouse cursor if this option is enabled.[/li]<br>
[li]New “stone buttons” (the ones you use to open your inventory, quest journal etc) with new icons (don’t worry; they’re based on the old ones).[/li]<br>
[li]A rework of the borders of the minimap, including a new “metallic” look.[/li]<br>
[li]New “trims” to the side panel interfaces themselves (like the inventory).[/li][/ul]</p>
</blockquote> win?<br>
<a href="http://www.runescape.com/img/news/Screenshots/BTS/1111/site_ss.jpg" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">New website</a>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/behind-the-scenes-november/420224/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/behind-the-scenes-november/420224/4</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 01 Nov 2011 16:43:41 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-420224-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/behind-the-scenes-november/420224.rss">Behind the scenes November</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Behind the scenes November</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@_Rich Rich]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/_rich">@_Rich</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote quote-modified" data-post="2" data-topic="420224">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/ashley001/40/5_e05bb34c421432ee4d40de30c10af3e5.png" class="avatar"> ashley001:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>The “New website” link is not functional.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>You have to click it then refresh the page. I’m too lazy to upload it.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/behind-the-scenes-november/420224/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/behind-the-scenes-november/420224/3</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 01 Nov 2011 16:43:29 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-420224-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/behind-the-scenes-november/420224.rss">Behind the scenes November</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Behind the scenes November</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@ashley001 ashley001]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/ashley001">@ashley001</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>The “New website” link is not functional.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/behind-the-scenes-november/420224/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/behind-the-scenes-november/420224/2</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 01 Nov 2011 16:42:38 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-420224-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/behind-the-scenes-november/420224.rss">Behind the scenes November</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Behind the scenes November</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@_Rich Rich]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/_rich">@_Rich</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <blockquote>While recovering from RuneFest and some epic Halloween parties, it’s nice to know there'll be some chunky updates to help me recover. Updates to take my mind off all the sweets and pumpkin pie I didn’t eat. Honest! 
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Thanksgiving 2011</span></p>
<p>We’re not done partying quite yet, although the turkeys of RuneScape have a different idea on how to celebrate Thanksgiving this year. Captain Turkerton and his turkey brethren are planning a protest against their species being put on the Thanksgiving menu for another year! If their demands aren’t met, a turkey invasion seems imminent, and they’re prepared to gobble up the land. Can you find a peaceful solution? Can you stand the thought of Thanksgiving dinner without turkey?</p>
<p>Free players and members completing the turkey event will be able to unlock the new Thanksgiving crest for their herald capes, which will also change the turkey emote if played while worn. Members will also be able to unlock a brand new turkey pet!</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Re-working the Interface</span></p>
<p>We are continually re-working areas of RuneScape that we feel could do with a lick of paint. These improvements aren’t just about NPC models, environments and gameplay, though. They also relate to the main game screen itself, which we call the “top level interface”.</p>
<p>The top level rework involves an overhaul of the interfaces that are used by players all the time. We are improving the style and functionality, and are introducing a new vibrant colour scheme. These changes include:</p>
<p>[ul][li]Brand-new info boxes, making examine messages and left click actions appear over the item your clicking on rather than hidden as a text message. No more checking the top left corner for NPC names - they’ll appear next to your mouse cursor if this option is enabled.[/li]<br>
[li]New “stone buttons” (the ones you use to open your inventory, quest journal etc) with new icons (don’t worry; they’re based on the old ones).[/li]<br>
[li]A rework of the borders of the minimap, including a new “metallic” look.[/li]<br>
[li]New “trims” to the side panel interfaces themselves (like the inventory).[/li][/ul]</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">New Website</span></p>
<p>We’re undergoing a complete overhaul of the RuneScape website design. The new design is a big departure from the current look and feel. We aim to capture the grand sense of adventure and exploration that RuneScape offers and bring that right out into the foundations of the site, while keeping all of the great features and information that you use on a day-to-day basis.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">New Slayer Dungeon</span></p>
<p>If, like myself, you’re a fan of the Slayer skill, you’ll be excited when you read the title of this update! As soon as you enter this new dungeon, you will find yourself immersed in some amazing, jaw-dropping scenery, but don’t look down, as this dungeon has a real sense of ‘depth’ to it.</p>
<p>Towards the end of the month, we’ll be launching the Polypore Dungeon. A ramokee has snuck into RuneScape and used her skinweaving powers to create a variety of horrific new monsters, many of which can only be killed by high-level slayers, and are best tackled with magic. Those who can defeat the ganodermic beasts (level 95 Slayer) may emerge with a unique kind of battlestaff and the materials to make incredibly protective mage armour. Elsewhere in the dungeon, there’ll be mage armour for lower-level fighters, and a very suspicious mushroom for PKers to eat.</p>
<p>The ramokee herself was originally destined from birth to serve her tribe as a healer, but she has rejected that destiny and abandoned her tribe. Now she sits enthroned in the depths of the cave, revelling in the freedom to use her skinweaving powers to indulge her own whims and curiosity. Along with the skinweaver, the dungeon is home to a strange little man with a sad story. He sells bizarre garments that form the basis of the mage armour.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">One Piercing Note</span></p>
<p>If you’ve seen the bottom of our newest Lores and Histories story, you’ll already know the title of November’s quest: One Piercing Note. Legend has it that, during the God Wars, there lived a holy woman named Elspeth whose voice was so perfect that no demon could bear to hear it. In the present age, a group of Saradominist holy women found Elspeth’s remains on a remote desert plateau and set up an abbey in her memory. Within the abbey’s sand-blasted walls the Sisters of Saint Elspeth devote their lives to prayer and sacred music.</p>
<p>Now there has been a murder in the abbey, and Abbess Benita is praying for an adventurer to investigate. To complicate matters, a wandering troubadour has set up camp outside the abbey, despite the order’s rules forbidding secular music. It’s up to you to uncover the abbey’s secrets and find the killer.</p>
<p>As befitting a quest involving a troubadour and a holy choir, sound and music play a prominent role in One Piercing Note. The music is woven into the story, and includes recordings of real musicians and singers. In addition, in a first for RuneScape, all NPC dialogue will be voice-acted. So, turn your speakers on and enjoy our latest all-singing, all-dancing quest!</p>
<p>[hr]</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Requirements for One Piercing Note:</span></p>
<p>[ul][li]None (besides being members-only)[/li]<br>
[li]Higher-level players who own god books can return after the quest for a new activity requiring level 60 in Prayer and Crafting.[/li][/ul]</p>
<p>[hr]</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Wilderness Graphical Updates</span></p>
<p>Last, but not least, we’re planning on reworking large areas of the Wilderness graphics. These include:</p>
<p>[ul][li]Many landmark locations including: the King Black Dragon’s lair, teleport obelisks, the Mage Arena and the Agility training area.[/li]<br>
[li]New lava environments.[/li]<br>
[li]A higher frame rate; reducing PK issues, not adding to them![/li][/ul]</p>
<p>Visit our <a href="http://www.runescape.com/kbase/guid/media" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">media page</a> for some sneak preview screenshots!</p>
<p>Have fun!</p>
<p>Mod Mark<br>
RS Lead Designer</p>
</blockquote><br>
<a href="http://www.runescape.com/img/news/Screenshots/BTS/1111/site_ss.jpg" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">New website</a><br>
<a href="http://img525.imageshack.us/img525/4219/capturefy.png" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">Entrance to the new dungeon</a>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/behind-the-scenes-november/420224/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/behind-the-scenes-november/420224/1</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 01 Nov 2011 16:29:39 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-420224-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/behind-the-scenes-november/420224.rss">Behind the scenes November</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
