<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>SCAR Tutorial.exe (drigers tut)</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/scar-tutorial-exe-drigers-tut/6028</link>
    <description>This Tutorial was made by driger and i consider it to be one of the best ones out there.
i havent found his tutorial here yet so i decided to post it..

ALL credits go to driger.

________________________________________________________________________________


My Tutorial Project is Finished! I have taken out a couple of the less-needed things to get this out earlier, and I finished the code for it faster than I could have ever imagined.

For those of you who don&#39;t know, I&#39;ve been working on this since February, though up until late April, I had zero time to work on it because of school. I started working on it and came back to SRL. Now, it&#39;s 12:00am here, and I&#39;m tired, but I had to get this out here!

The tutorials include the following topics:

    * Introduction
    * Procedure List
    * Variables
    * Constants
    * Basics
    * Procedures
    * Functions
    * If..Then
    * Includes
    * Cases
    * Loops
    * Bitmaps
    * DTMs
    * Auto Color Detection
    * Working with Text
    * Arrays
    * Forms
    * Fixing Errors


I hope that everyone learns at least something from this. Take a look at the basics section, and go to the third page, for example. I&#39;m sure quite a few people will learn something new there, but I&#39;m also 100% sure there are others who will not.

PLEASE report every little error to me either in this thread or through a PM so I can make version 2 all the better Wink If it&#39;s a little fix, I can do it quickly and release that within probably 10 minutes.

I&#39;ve made the whole thing into a setup.exe type file which compresses everything similar to how a .rar or .zip would, but I used this type of setup because you don&#39;t need any additional programs to use a .exe file. Every file that comes with this will install itself where you want it to be installed, and includes an option to include it in the start menu. I encourage you to check the place where the program is installed. I&#39;ve left you all with .rtf versions of every tutorial which you can open in wordpad. I&#39;ve also left example scripts on all of the topics so that you have something to compare your scripts to that you make by following this collection of tutorials.

Also, it has been brought to my attention that some people may not notice the arrows at the bottom of the tutorial window. It&#39;s not on the first page (the intro page), but is on every other page. The arrows lead you to other tutorials in the category Wink

Oh, yes, before I forget, StarBlaster100 did close to 95% of what&#39;s in the include section Wink He wanted to help, but I didn&#39;t really see his skills as what I wanted. I seriously spent about an hour editting what he wrote, and then I added a few things. Sorry it didn&#39;t work out StarBlaster :\

download here :[url=http://www.driger1592.com/SCAR%20Tutorial%20Setup.exe]http://www.driger1592.com/SCAR%20Tutorial%20Setup.exe[/url]

Enjoy my fellow scripters Very Happy</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 25 Jul 2006 01:38:58 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/scar-tutorial-exe-drigers-tut/6028.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>SCAR Tutorial.exe (drigers tut)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Janilabo Janilabo]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/janilabo">@Janilabo</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Exactly dark… And as it’s a good tutorial… Definitely should be moved to there <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/confused.png?v=9" title=":confused:" class="emoji" alt=":confused:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/scar-tutorial-exe-drigers-tut/6028/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/scar-tutorial-exe-drigers-tut/6028/4</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 25 Jul 2006 01:38:58 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-6028-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/scar-tutorial-exe-drigers-tut/6028.rss">SCAR Tutorial.exe (drigers tut)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>SCAR Tutorial.exe (drigers tut)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@dark_sniper dark_sniper]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/dark_sniper">@dark_sniper</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>wonder why they didnt move it to scar tutorial :\ where most people look</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/scar-tutorial-exe-drigers-tut/6028/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/scar-tutorial-exe-drigers-tut/6028/3</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 25 Jul 2006 01:35:39 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-6028-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/scar-tutorial-exe-drigers-tut/6028.rss">SCAR Tutorial.exe (drigers tut)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>SCAR Tutorial.exe (drigers tut)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@mikkomainer Secet]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/mikkomainer">@mikkomainer</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p><a href="http://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php/topic,3700.0.html" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">http://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php/topic,3700.0.html</a></p>
<p>It’s already here and stickied <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=9" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
<p>And yes, it’s very good guide. I suggest all those who are starting scripting to download it!</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/scar-tutorial-exe-drigers-tut/6028/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/scar-tutorial-exe-drigers-tut/6028/2</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 24 Jul 2006 21:26:16 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-6028-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/scar-tutorial-exe-drigers-tut/6028.rss">SCAR Tutorial.exe (drigers tut)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>SCAR Tutorial.exe (drigers tut)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@dark_sniper dark_sniper]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/dark_sniper">@dark_sniper</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>This Tutorial was made by driger and i consider it to be one of the best ones out there.<br>
i havent found his tutorial here yet so i decided to post it…</p>
<p>ALL credits go to driger.</p>
<hr>
<p>My Tutorial Project is Finished! I have taken out a couple of the less-needed things to get this out earlier, and I finished the code for it faster than I could have ever imagined.</p>
<p>For those of you who don’t know, I’ve been working on this since February, though up until late April, I had zero time to work on it because of school. I started working on it and came back to SRL. Now, it’s 12:00am here, and I’m tired, but I had to get this out here!</p>
<p>The tutorials include the following topics:</p>
<pre><code>* Introduction
* Procedure List
* Variables
* Constants
* Basics
* Procedures
* Functions
* If..Then
* Includes
* Cases
* Loops
* Bitmaps
* DTMs
* Auto Color Detection
* Working with Text
* Arrays
* Forms
* Fixing Errors
</code></pre>
<p>I hope that everyone learns at least something from this. Take a look at the basics section, and go to the third page, for example. I’m sure quite a few people will learn something new there, but I’m also 100% sure there are others who will not.</p>
<p>PLEASE report every little error to me either in this thread or through a PM so I can make version 2 all the better Wink If it’s a little fix, I can do it quickly and release that within probably 10 minutes.</p>
<p>I’ve made the whole thing into a setup.exe type file which compresses everything similar to how a .rar or .zip would, but I used this type of setup because you don’t need any additional programs to use a .exe file. Every file that comes with this will install itself where you want it to be installed, and includes an option to include it in the start menu. I encourage you to check the place where the program is installed. I’ve left you all with .rtf versions of every tutorial which you can open in wordpad. I’ve also left example scripts on all of the topics so that you have something to compare your scripts to that you make by following this collection of tutorials.</p>
<p>Also, it has been brought to my attention that some people may not notice the arrows at the bottom of the tutorial window. It’s not on the first page (the intro page), but is on every other page. The arrows lead you to other tutorials in the category Wink</p>
<p>Oh, yes, before I forget, StarBlaster100 did close to 95% of what’s in the include section Wink He wanted to help, but I didn’t really see his skills as what I wanted. I seriously spent about an hour editting what he wrote, and then I added a few things. Sorry it didn’t work out StarBlaster :\</p>
<p>download here :<a href="http://www.driger1592.com/SCAR%20Tutorial%20Setup.exe" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">http://www.driger1592.com/SCAR%20Tutorial%20Setup.exe</a></p>
<p>Enjoy my fellow scripters Very Happy</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/scar-tutorial-exe-drigers-tut/6028/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/scar-tutorial-exe-drigers-tut/6028/1</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 24 Jul 2006 19:56:05 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-6028-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/scar-tutorial-exe-drigers-tut/6028.rss">SCAR Tutorial.exe (drigers tut)</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
