<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Quest makin troubles</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/quest-makin-troubles/175253</link>
    <description>hey, im trying to create a quest. i&#39;ve got pretty much all of it down. the last thing i need is i need it to where if a player clicks &quot;talk to&quot; on the npc i want them to, they start the quest, or in other words the quest = 1. AND how do i get an npc i just spawned to drop a certain item?</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 22 Jan 2008 16:15:53 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/quest-makin-troubles/175253.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Quest makin troubles</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@akanaz akanaz]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/akanaz">@akanaz</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>To make a npc drop a certain item (this is for devolution, maybe other servers too) go into your server files and double-click config, then go into npcdrops. Once in there you will see a list of npc drops set out like this:</p>
<p>npcdrop = 2745	6570	1	1	//jad (Fire cape)100%</p>
<p>That’s Jad dropping a fire cape its’ pretty straight-foward.</p>
<p>npcdrop =   :    The opening phrase to make an npc drop an item.</p>
<p>2745:  The npcid of the particular monster you wish to create or alter drops of.</p>
<p>6570:  The item id you want the npc to drop eg. firecape.</p>
<p>1: The amount of items dropped, put in note form if you want more than 1 item to be dropped by the monster. Note: Note is usually 1 item id above the original item.</p>
<p>1: The percent (%) you want the npc to drop that item. eg. Jad will have a 1 in 100 chance of dropping fire cape.</p>
<p>//jad (Fire cape)100%: Just a reminder for you to keep track of what is what. “//” means the compiler will not read this therefore causing no errors no matter what text is placed afterwards.</p>
<p>If you want more than 1 drop just press enter and the end of the previous item drop and start again, or even easier copy the previous one and just edit the different text to suit the item you want that npc to drop.</p>
<p>If create your own do not use spaces for the gaps, press Tab once and then type the next lot of text.</p>
<p>Hope i helped.</p>
<p>Thanx  <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=6" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/quest-makin-troubles/175253/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/quest-makin-troubles/175253/2</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jan 2008 16:15:53 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-175253-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/quest-makin-troubles/175253.rss">Quest makin troubles</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Quest makin troubles</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@omg_ffs_ownd omg ffs ownd]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/omg_ffs_ownd">@omg_ffs_ownd</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>hey, im trying to create a quest. i’ve got pretty much all of it down. the last thing i need is i need it to where if a player clicks “talk to” on the npc i want them to, they start the quest, or in other words the quest = 1. AND how do i get an npc i just spawned to drop a certain item?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/quest-makin-troubles/175253/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/quest-makin-troubles/175253/1</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jan 2008 13:21:19 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-175253-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/quest-makin-troubles/175253.rss">Quest makin troubles</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
