<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Creation - Bringing old times back</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/creation-bringing-old-times-back/552654</link>
    <description>Creation is a server of fun. I will be making this project to learn coding as well. I think I have learnt a bit from it by dialogues and stuff like that. The project will consist of training your combat and skills. There will be rewardable quests that npc&#39;s will host and myself will host. The quests will be made so that you have to get certain items by crafting them. Once you start the quests your rank will be changed and you won&#39;t be able to go into shops until you have completed the quest. You will also be able to pay to get out of the quest for a understandable amount of GP. This is only the beginning. This might change but as of now it is staying like this. There will be lots more other things like bossing and stuff like that. I&#39;m just trying to enhance gaming of RSPS and trying to make it more fun.

RELEASE DATE: Undecided as of now.

UPDATES (30/07/2015, only just started working on it today):
Changed home to draynor(Good small home for a beginner server).
Added a starter dialogue to welcome you. (Using Lumbridge guide as npc).

Upcoming Updates (TO-DO-LIST):
Redo the shops(Remove the items and re add the certain items).
Add a training area with multiple monsters. (Dungeons will still be available to do slayer. I&#39;m also still thinking of an area. Suggest an area for me).
Adding iron man since it was removed with the source and client I have now.
Removing bug/glitches (Will do a alpha stage/bug testing week for this as well).
MORE UPDATES WILL COME ONCE I FINISHED THESE.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 27 Jul 2015 13:16:46 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/creation-bringing-old-times-back/552654.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Creation - Bringing old times back</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Just_Creative Just Creative]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/just_creative">@Just_Creative</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Creation is a server of fun. I will be making this project to learn coding as well. I think I have learnt a bit from it by dialogues and stuff like that. The project will consist of training your combat and skills. There will be rewardable quests that npc’s will host and myself will host. The quests will be made so that you have to get certain items by crafting them. Once you start the quests your rank will be changed and you won’t be able to go into shops until you have completed the quest. You will also be able to pay to get out of the quest for a understandable amount of GP. This is only the beginning. This might change but as of now it is staying like this. There will be lots more other things like bossing and stuff like that. I’m just trying to enhance gaming of RSPS and trying to make it more fun.</p>
<p>RELEASE DATE: Undecided as of now.</p>
<p>UPDATES (30/07/2015, only just started working on it today):<br>
Changed home to draynor(Good small home for a beginner server).<br>
Added a starter dialogue to welcome you. (Using Lumbridge guide as npc).</p>
<p>Upcoming Updates (TO-DO-LIST):<br>
Redo the shops(Remove the items and re add the certain items).<br>
Add a training area with multiple monsters. (Dungeons will still be available to do slayer. I’m also still thinking of an area. Suggest an area for me).<br>
Adding iron man since it was removed with the source and client I have now.<br>
Removing bug/glitches (Will do a alpha stage/bug testing week for this as well).<br>
MORE UPDATES WILL COME ONCE I FINISHED THESE.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/creation-bringing-old-times-back/552654/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/creation-bringing-old-times-back/552654/1</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 27 Jul 2015 13:16:46 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-552654-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/creation-bringing-old-times-back/552654.rss">Creation - Bringing old times back</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
