<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Compiling error</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/compiling-error/541697</link>
    <description>Hey guys, thanks for reading this far. As you can tell from the title, im having trouble compiling and coding in general. Trying to learn the ropes but and I&#39;ve been able to remove snow textures and all that, some stuff I thought I would have trouble on but never would I think that this would be hard.. Basically I opened my client and soruce. Searched the server name and opened all of the files that had the server name in it with notepad p++. I did CTRL F and found and replaced every instance with &quot;NovaScape&quot; and now it is giving me these compiling errors, client sided. Please help, would be much appreciated.

[img]http://i61.tinypic.com/fypufb.png[/img]

Here are the following files where the error is occurring.

[url=http://pastebin.com/hjPmQa9Z]http://pastebin.com/hjPmQa9Z[/url] - Cache Downloader Errors 1 and 4, on lines 7 and 162.

[url=http://pastebin.com/dgnfcqSU]http://pastebin.com/dgnfcqSU[/url] - Client.Java Errors 2 and 3, Errors on lines 250 and 1169. - *NOTE* I ONLY PUT UP TO LINE LIKE 1175, BECAUSE THE WHOLE FILE WAS TO BIG TO COPY AND PASTE. IF YOU NEED MORE LET ME KNOW!*


Thanks to everyone who read through and is willing to help.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 30 Mar 2014 13:04:42 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Uncategorized</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/compiling-error/541697.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Compiling error</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@threat_is_me threat is me]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/threat_is_me">@threat_is_me</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Hey guys, thanks for reading this far. As you can tell from the title, im having trouble compiling and coding in general. Trying to learn the ropes but and I’ve been able to remove snow textures and all that, some stuff I thought I would have trouble on but never would I think that this would be hard… Basically I opened my client and soruce. Searched the server name and opened all of the files that had the server name in it with notepad p++. I did CTRL F and found and replaced every instance with “NovaScape” and now it is giving me these compiling errors, client sided. Please help, would be much appreciated.</p>
<p><img src="http://i61.tinypic.com/fypufb.png" alt width="" height=""></p>
<p>Here are the following files where the error is occurring.</p>
<p><a href="http://pastebin.com/hjPmQa9Z" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">http://pastebin.com/hjPmQa9Z</a> - Cache Downloader Errors 1 and 4, on lines 7 and 162.</p>
<p><a href="http://pastebin.com/dgnfcqSU" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">http://pastebin.com/dgnfcqSU</a> - Client.Java Errors 2 and 3, Errors on lines 250 and 1169. - <em>NOTE</em> I ONLY PUT UP TO LINE LIKE 1175, BECAUSE THE WHOLE FILE WAS TO BIG TO COPY AND PASTE. IF YOU NEED MORE LET ME KNOW!*</p>
<p>Thanks to everyone who read through and is willing to help.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/compiling-error/541697/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/compiling-error/541697/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 30 Mar 2014 13:04:42 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-541697-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/compiling-error/541697.rss">Compiling error</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
