<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Mad libs</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/mad-libs/269499</link>
    <description>Only four minutes left, and the score was tied 89292882373738 to 89292882373738. “Get in there, Maniown!” cried Coach yz85racer. “I&#39;m counting on you to help us win the game.”

I grabbed my lucky used condom and Humped onto the field. What luck. I got the io9&#39;s dildo right away and raced past three opponents. The crowd was banging eachother. I kicked the io9&#39;s dildo right at the goal. “HOLY JESUS THAT FEELS NICE! YES YES YES!!!,” I missed! The crowd became silent. I spotted Katy perry and Brad pit in the stands looking very disappointed.

The other team had the io9&#39;s dildo with only two minutes left — that is until I intercepted it! I Fucked toward the goal and smashed the io9&#39;s dildo right into the net. “Goooooal!” screamed the announcer.

The crowd was licking wildly. “Hooray for Maniown! Maniown! Maniown! Maniown!”

Then my alarm clock woke me up for school



[url=http://www.eduplace.com/tales/]http://www.eduplace.com/tales/[/url]


Everybody make one! make this shit epic.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 28 Mar 2009 18:30:27 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>General Discussion</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/mad-libs/269499.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Mad libs</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@sanga282 sanga282]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/sanga282">@sanga282</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Radio Announcer: Thank you for tuning in today. We are here in Watford to celebrate National Poetry Month. In just a moment, the nation’s poet laureate, Sanga, will read a poem about a(n) tree. And here is Sanga.</p>
<p>Sanga: Thank you, everyone. This is a very green poem I wrote about a(n) tree.</p>
<p>An Ode to a(n) tree</p>
<p>The tree is as big as a(n) stork.<br>
It reminds me of small stork’s fucking.<br>
O, the tree. O, the tree!<br>
What do raunchy people think when they see you for the first time?<br>
Perhaps they know there are happy days ahead.<br>
O, the tree. O, the tree!<br>
For some, you are erotic, but for others, you are sexy.<br>
If we are dieing, we pause when we think of you.<br>
May you always runing.<br>
O, the tree. O, the tree!<br>
The end.</p>
<p>Radio Announcer: On behalf of the poets, thank you for killing.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/mad-libs/269499/15">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/mad-libs/269499/15</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 28 Mar 2009 18:30:27 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-269499-15</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/mad-libs/269499.rss">Mad libs</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Mad libs</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@ilyaostr9 io9]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/ilyaostr9">@ilyaostr9</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>u fags need to l2notcapitalizeio9</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/mad-libs/269499/14">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/mad-libs/269499/14</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 28 Mar 2009 02:01:11 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-269499-14</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/mad-libs/269499.rss">Mad libs</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Mad libs</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Tulitikku Tulitikku]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/tulitikku">@Tulitikku</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>This year our class is doing a special science project. We have a(n) nigger that we are taking care of. It is very retarded and it has black eyes. It lives in a(n) cage in the back of our classroom. We feed it shit and Io9 every day, but I think it really wants to eat my dick. Everyone likes our nigger.</p>
<p>One day, the nigger got out of its cage and started faggoting all around the room. It made a loud nigger sound. I think it was trying to say, “i have human rights too!”</p>
<p>This site is fucking epic!</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/mad-libs/269499/13">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/mad-libs/269499/13</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Mar 2009 23:12:57 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-269499-13</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/mad-libs/269499.rss">Mad libs</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Mad libs</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Fat_Cookies Fat Cookies]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/fat_cookies">@Fat_Cookies</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>An Ode</p>
<p>Radio Announcer: Thank you for tuning in today. We are here in Detriot to celebrate National Poetry Month. In just a moment, the nation’s poet laureate, Jme, will read a poem about a sniff. And here is Jme.</p>
<p>Jme: Thank you, everyone. This is a very quietly poem I wrote about a sniff.</p>
<p>An Ode to a sniff</p>
<p>The sniff is as big as a shove.<br>
It reminds me of small walks bumming.<br>
O, the sniff. O, the sniff!<br>
What do slowly people think when they see you for the first time?<br>
Perhaps they know there are happy days ahead.<br>
O, the sniff. O, the sniff!<br>
For some, you are hastily, but for others, you are madly.<br>
If we are snortling, we pause when we think of you.<br>
May you always ate.<br>
O, the sniff. O, the sniff!<br>
The end.</p>
<p>Radio Announcer: On behalf of the poets, thank you for wanking.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/mad-libs/269499/12">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/mad-libs/269499/12</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Mar 2009 16:56:58 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-269499-12</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/mad-libs/269499.rss">Mad libs</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Mad libs</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@cocoa cocoa]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/cocoa">@cocoa</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>The Play’s the Thing</p>
<p>Travis: Did you try out for the boob in the school play?</p>
<p>cocoa: I wanted to be waldo, but I didn’t get the part. I don’t know why. I wore cocky boobs on my butt cheeks and happy birds on my legs. Then I had my arms and sang “Second Chance.” When I finished, Mrs. Walsh drank on the stage and told me I didn’t get the part.</p>
<p>Travis: You must have felt sad.</p>
<p>cocoa: Not really. Mrs. Walsh told me I could smoke the curtain. That’ll be a blast!</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/mad-libs/269499/11">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/mad-libs/269499/11</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 Mar 2009 23:18:07 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-269499-11</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/mad-libs/269499.rss">Mad libs</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Mad libs</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@T41 t4]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/t41">@T41</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <blockquote>Special News Report
<p>Good evening, I’m Billy Gates, and this is a special report from NASA. Strange things are occurring during this important mission to the Moon. As most of the world knows, the astronauts on this mission are studying whether or not it is possible to get fucked on the Moon.</p>
<p>Today, two of the astronauts, david and george, were outside the space shuttle performing tests. The astronauts reported that an alien spacecraft with fucking lights landed next to the space shuttle. More than 90 aliens left the spacecraft and queefed over to the astronauts.</p>
<p>Astronaut david said, “The aliens are about 13 feet tall, and they have darkie skin. We think they are sandy, but we are not sure.”</p>
<p>The astronauts have been trying to talk to the aliens. “Communication has been difficult,” astronaut george told officials at NASA. “The aliens make sounds like niggers when they are talking.”</p>
<p>The aliens stayed on the Moon for about an hour before they got back into their spacecraft and flew away. Before they left, they gave the astronauts one whore. NASA officials think this is a token of friendship and hope we see our alien friends again.</p>
<p>I’m Billy Gates, and this has been a special report. Thank you.</p>
</blockquote><br>
Lol!
<blockquote>[b]Astronaut david said, “The aliens are about 13 feet tall, and they have darkie skin. We think they are sandy, but we are not sure.”
<p>The astronauts have been trying to talk to the aliens. “Communication has been difficult,” astronaut george told officials at NASA. “The aliens make sounds like niggers when they are talking.”<br>
[/b]</p>
</blockquote>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/mad-libs/269499/10">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/mad-libs/269499/10</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 Mar 2009 20:35:06 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-269499-10</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/mad-libs/269499.rss">Mad libs</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Mad libs</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@goatee goatee]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/goatee">@goatee</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Lmao this is great</p>
<p>The Play’s the Thing</p>
<p>Octopussy: Did you try out for the Duck anus in the school play?</p>
<p>Goatee: I wanted to be Vaginal Spinal the Carpenter, but I didn’t get the part. I don’t know why. I wore delicate cows on my fingers and juicy balls on my buttcheeks. Then I fucked my noodles and sang “Rape me baby one more time.” When I finished, Mr Fukuwitarake cummed on the stage and told me I didn’t get the part.</p>
<p>Octopussy: You must have felt sad.</p>
<p>Goatee: Not really. Mr Fukuwitarake told me I could lick the curtain. That’ll be a blast!</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/mad-libs/269499/9">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/mad-libs/269499/9</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 Mar 2009 20:00:49 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-269499-9</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/mad-libs/269499.rss">Mad libs</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Mad libs</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@maniown maniown]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/maniown">@maniown</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Things That Drive Me Bonkers</p>
<p>I just hate it when…</p>
<p>Mom serves clit sandwich for dinner.</p>
<p>My pet sex panther chews my sex toy.</p>
<p>A crazy old asian gets mad at the class for being hot and wet.</p>
<p>My friend io9 decides to start anal fucking with somebody else.</p>
<p>I get pre ejaculated for something I didn’t do.</p>
<p>Dad makes me wear Lederhosen to school.</p>
<p>My favorite TV show “That 70’s show” gets canceled because the station has to broadcast a news conference.</p>
<p>People doing the reverse cowboy into my bedroom without knocking</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/mad-libs/269499/8">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/mad-libs/269499/8</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 Mar 2009 19:47:36 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-269499-8</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/mad-libs/269499.rss">Mad libs</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Mad libs</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@ilyaostr9 io9]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/ilyaostr9">@ilyaostr9</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Dear Diary</p>
<p>Dear Diary,</p>
<p>Today was the most nigger-rigged day at school! Shaquamaneesha didn’t speak to me all day. I forgot my homework for math class. My new friend Tapramaneek isn’t talking to me anymore. And to top it all off, I forgot my lunch, so I had to borrow money to buy lunch. I hate borrowing money, I hate forgetting my homework, and I hate it when my friends don’t talk to me! Niggers! I hope tomorrow is a better day!</p>
<p>Dear Diary,</p>
<p>Everything was much better today. Shaquamaneesha wasn’t mad at me; she was just upset because her parents would not let her go to a party. She was black toward everyone. My math teacher said she’d only take one point off my homework because this was the only time I’d ever forgotten anything. She said everyone makes niggerly mistakes sometimes. My new friend Tapramaneek is talking to me. He was just busy helping out a sick friend. He had to gather all of his friend’s homework. My friend who loaned me the money for lunch yesterday said I didn’t have to pay him back, because I had loaned him money for lunch a while ago. I hope every day is a good as today!</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/mad-libs/269499/7">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/mad-libs/269499/7</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 Mar 2009 19:37:04 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-269499-7</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/mad-libs/269499.rss">Mad libs</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Mad libs</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@maniown maniown]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/maniown">@maniown</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“io9, post:5, topic:269499”]The Hanukkah Party</p>
<p>Last week my whole family went to a Hanukkah party at my Uncle Rabbi’s house in Jerusalem. The first thing we did when we got there was open presents. Uncle Rabbi always gives us Jewish presents. This year he gave me a(n) circumcision and my little sister, Rachel, a(n) penis.</p>
<p>“L’chaim!, Uncle Rabbi,” I said, “How did you know I wanted a(n) circumcision?”</p>
<p>Then Rachel, my cousins, and I played a dreidel game. My cousin Shlomo put an empty bowl in the center of the table, and gave us each our own pile of candy for the game. Rachel went first, spun a shin, and had to put a piece of her candy in the bowl. I could tell she wanted to hail Hitler, but she knew she had to behave. The bowl continued to fill with candy, with most of us spinning shin. Then I spun a gimel. I got the whole bowl of candy!</p>
<p>On the way home, I whispered to Rachel that I would share my candy with her, but she had fallen fast asleep.[/quote]</p>
<p>LOL thats a epic story.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/mad-libs/269499/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/mad-libs/269499/6</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 Mar 2009 19:31:10 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-269499-6</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/mad-libs/269499.rss">Mad libs</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Mad libs</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@ilyaostr9 io9]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/ilyaostr9">@ilyaostr9</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>The Hanukkah Party</p>
<p>Last week my whole family went to a Hanukkah party at my Uncle Rabbi’s house in Jerusalem. The first thing we did when we got there was open presents. Uncle Rabbi always gives us Jewish presents. This year he gave me a(n) circumcision and my little sister, Rachel, a(n) penis.</p>
<p>“L’chaim!, Uncle Rabbi,” I said, “How did you know I wanted a(n) circumcision?”</p>
<p>Then Rachel, my cousins, and I played a dreidel game. My cousin Shlomo put an empty bowl in the center of the table, and gave us each our own pile of candy for the game. Rachel went first, spun a shin, and had to put a piece of her candy in the bowl. I could tell she wanted to hail Hitler, but she knew she had to behave. The bowl continued to fill with candy, with most of us spinning shin. Then I spun a gimel. I got the whole bowl of candy!</p>
<p>On the way home, I whispered to Rachel that I would share my candy with her, but she had fallen fast asleep.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/mad-libs/269499/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/mad-libs/269499/5</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 Mar 2009 03:36:21 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-269499-5</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/mad-libs/269499.rss">Mad libs</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Mad libs</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@chrisn2323 chrisn2323]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/chrisn2323">@chrisn2323</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Radio Announcer: Thank you for tuning in today. We are here in hell to celebrate National Poetry Month. In just a moment, the nation’s poet laureate, your mom, will read a poem about a(n) faggot. And here is your mom.</p>
<p>your mom: Thank you, everyone. This is a very gay poem I wrote about a(n) faggot.</p>
<p>An Ode to a(n) faggot</p>
<p>The faggot is as big as a(n) cock.<br>
It reminds me of small vaginas masturbating.<br>
O, the faggot. O, the faggot!<br>
What do horny people think when they see you for the first time?<br>
Perhaps they know there are happy days ahead.<br>
O, the faggot. O, the faggot!<br>
For some, you are silly, but for others, you are angry.<br>
If we are fellating, we pause when we think of you.<br>
May you always shit.<br>
O, the faggot. O, the faggot!<br>
The end.</p>
<p>Radio Announcer: On behalf of the poets, thank you for buttfucking.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/mad-libs/269499/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/mad-libs/269499/4</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 Mar 2009 02:48:35 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-269499-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/mad-libs/269499.rss">Mad libs</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Mad libs</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@maniown maniown]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/maniown">@maniown</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>lmfao nice.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/mad-libs/269499/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/mad-libs/269499/3</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 Mar 2009 02:27:35 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-269499-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/mad-libs/269499.rss">Mad libs</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Mad libs</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@lawl lawl]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/lawl">@lawl</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>All a Dream</p>
<p>I fell asleep yesterday listening to an old album that my mom had. I really enjoyed it, though I had a weird dream. It was kind of like one of the old songs.</p>
<p>I’ve been workin’ in vagina,<br>
All the gay day.<br>
I’ve been workin’ in vagina,<br>
Just to pass the time away.<br>
Don’t you hear the whistle raping?<br>
Rise up so early in the morn.<br>
Don’t you hear jesus shouting<br>
“penis, rape your horn? ”</p>
<p>penis, won’t you rape,<br>
penis, won’t you rape,<br>
penis, won’t you rape your horn?<br>
penis, won’t you rape,<br>
penis, won’t you rape,<br>
penis, won’t you rape your horn?</p>
<p>Someone’s in the bathroom with penis.<br>
Someone’s in the bathroom, I know.<br>
Someone’s in the bathroom with penis<br>
Strumming on the old guitar.</p>
<p>It was the weirdest dream I’ve had in a long time!</p>
<p>[hr]<br>
edit: heres another, i think the last line is pretty epic reference to goatse</p>
<p>The Sky Is Falling!</p>
<p>Each spring, the sky turns white. Giant drops of semen fall from the sky. All this semen helps the grass and the vaginas to grow, but it can make things really gentle too.</p>
<p>Some places get so much semen, that rivers rape into the streets. Driving can be tricky when this happens, so some people put special women on their cars.</p>
<p>And when the semen is falling, don’t forget your man. Otherwise, your feet might get fat if you kill in puddles!</p>
<p>After all the semen has fallen, the skies begin to urinate. If you are lucky, you might see a huge anus stretched across the sky.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/mad-libs/269499/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/mad-libs/269499/2</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 Mar 2009 02:08:09 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-269499-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/mad-libs/269499.rss">Mad libs</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Mad libs</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@maniown maniown]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/maniown">@maniown</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Only four minutes left, and the score was tied 89292882373738 to 89292882373738. “Get in there, Maniown!” cried Coach yz85racer. “I’m counting on you to help us win the game.”</p>
<p>I grabbed my lucky used condom and Humped onto the field. What luck. I got the io9’s dildo right away and raced past three opponents. The crowd was banging eachother. I kicked the io9’s dildo right at the goal. “HOLY JESUS THAT FEELS NICE! YES YES YES!!!,” I missed! The crowd became silent. I spotted Katy perry and Brad pit in the stands looking very disappointed.</p>
<p>The other team had the io9’s dildo with only two minutes left — that is until I intercepted it! I Fucked toward the goal and smashed the io9’s dildo right into the net. “Goooooal!” screamed the announcer.</p>
<p>The crowd was licking wildly. “Hooray for Maniown! Maniown! Maniown! Maniown!”</p>
<p>Then my alarm clock woke me up for school</p>
<p><a href="http://www.eduplace.com/tales/" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">http://www.eduplace.com/tales/</a></p>
<p>Everybody make one! make this shit epic.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/mad-libs/269499/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/mad-libs/269499/1</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 Mar 2009 01:54:43 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-269499-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/mad-libs/269499.rss">Mad libs</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
