<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Help with new file</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/help-with-new-file/62663</link>
    <description>Ok, i added a whole swimming area, and its kinda long so i wanted to add it to an external file, i added all the stuff and got a million errors, like it cant find symbal so i added swimming. b4 the spots in the client were it refered to a void in the swimming file. um now im at this, cannot find symbal absX, um... i tried just making it client.absX and client.absY in the swimmin file but it said sumthin about then being non static or sumthin, i figured i wud just make add static to the void or watever they are defined in, but i cant find it, i have no idea were absX or absY come from... i cant find a void or boolean or int or nething... so ne clues how i can use absx in an external file?</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 01 Mar 2007 13:57:56 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/help-with-new-file/62663.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Help with new file</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Nirvana.Marijuana Nirvana.Marijuana]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/nirvana.marijuana">@Nirvana.Marijuana</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>do u keep a copy of your source before you update i should try that saves fixing a million errors or starting again</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/help-with-new-file/62663/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/help-with-new-file/62663/2</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 01 Mar 2007 13:57:56 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-62663-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/help-with-new-file/62663.rss">Help with new file</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Help with new file</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@dracar dracar]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/dracar">@dracar</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Ok, i added a whole swimming area, and its kinda long so i wanted to add it to an external file, i added all the stuff and got a million errors, like it cant find symbal so i added swimming. b4 the spots in the client were it refered to a void in the swimming file. um now im at this, cannot find symbal absX, um… i tried just making it client.absX and client.absY in the swimmin file but it said sumthin about then being non static or sumthin, i figured i wud just make add static to the void or watever they are defined in, but i cant find it, i have no idea were absX or absY come from… i cant find a void or boolean or int or nething… so ne clues how i can use absx in an external file?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/help-with-new-file/62663/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/help-with-new-file/62663/1</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 01 Mar 2007 07:58:10 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-62663-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/help-with-new-file/62663.rss">Help with new file</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
