<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Could not find or</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/could-not-find-or/478428</link>
    <description>Could not find or load main class then a URL follows after it.

I know this probably sounds pathetic, but I&#39;m trying to learn this stuff and the only way to is to give it a go, trouble shoot continuously and obtain knowledge from others. 

So i&#39;ve installed everything required, so no &#39;ant&#39; errors or &#39;javac&#39; errors... Set all my env&#39;s under the computer system. Basically what is happening is when I compile my client side or my server side, the RSCD / java file itself deletes...

Then I compile it does nothing, doesnt even change the XML file, I tried this with the server side as well, does the same thing.. gives me the &quot; Could Not find or load main class &quot; error and also deletes the RSCD / Java file.. Basically the error  is happening at run, but without the compiler working correctly, I would imagine why... 

I&#39;ve troubleshooted everything I possibly could, i&#39;ve turned all the links in Google PURPLE lol and I just am stumped... I know you guy&#39;s hate noobies like myself but help a noob out, give me that bronze long haha</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 14 Jan 2013 16:26:41 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/could-not-find-or/478428.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Could not find or</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@its2013 its2013]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/its2013">@its2013</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I dont recall saying im not a noobie, infact i said i was in the end, but anyhow I’m assuming this would be under a envt right? probably PATH?</p>
<p>EDIT: Nvm… stupid thought where does this go<br>
EDIT AGAIN: the -XM looks familiar like i’d run as in eclipse and set it in the config? But im not very good with eclipse yet neither…</p>
<p>Tried another source, EASYRSC this time and now i’m getting Java.exe not found so im assuming if I use that snipplet you gave me this should work. Help me out with that snipplet? <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=5" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"> pleaseeeeee</p>
<hr>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">OK now what is happening since ive played with it a bit more is this:</span></p>
<p>ERROR: The process “java.exe” with PID 4588 could not be terminated.<br>
Reason: Access is denied.<br>
Buildfile: C:\Users****\Desktop\EasyRSC\Server\build.xml</p>
<p>compile:<br>
[delete] Deleting: C:\Users****\Desktop\EasyRSC\Server\rscd.jar<br>
[mkdir] Created dir: C:\Users****\Desktop\EasyRSC\Server\build<br>
[javac] C:\Users****\Desktop\EasyRSC\Server\build.xml:13: warning: ‘include<br>
antruntime’ was not set, defaulting to build.sysclasspath=last; set to false for<br>
repeatable builds<br>
[javac] Compiling 167 source files to C:\Users****\Desktop\EasyRSC\Server\b<br>
uild</p>
<p>THAT ERROR IS FOR THE COMPILE SIDE OF SERVER, although i dont think the server will run at all because of this…</p>
<p>I havnt messed with the client side at all yet im more concerned about the server atm.</p>
<hr>
<p>last edit, fixed problem, close thread if want…</p>
<p>So I back tracked myself, everything was good then i went over envt’ runtimes, and well there was a small tiny mistake lol… that caused all of this trouble so I took care of that, then I tried to run again and got a taskill error, i simply removed that and run it again, POOF the server started up, now im working on getting it online and hopefully into a browser within the next week <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=5" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
<p>OH Yeah and RSCEasy was missing a lot of Def’s that I had to add as well… such an easy client NOT, got to add missing stuff, and deal with crap errors… but other servers are even more complicated atm for me <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/frowning.png?v=5" title=":frowning:" class="emoji" alt=":frowning:"></p>
<p>Im a genius haha, a newbie one too i guess… trouble shoot, trouble shoot, and never give up because eventually it will give in!</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/could-not-find-or/478428/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/could-not-find-or/478428/3</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 14 Jan 2013 16:26:41 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-478428-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/could-not-find-or/478428.rss">Could not find or</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Could not find or</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Team_Rocket Team_Rocket]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/team_rocket">@Team_Rocket</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>EDIT: You say you aren’t a newbie, so I guess I don’t need to hold your hand. Try this:</p>
<p>Origin:</p>
<blockquote>"Program Files\java\jdk1.7.0\bin\java.exe" -Xmx1024M src/Server</blockquote>
<p>After:</p>
<blockquote>"Program Files\java\jdk1.7.0\bin\java.exe" -Xmx1024M -cp .; src/Server</blockquote>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/could-not-find-or/478428/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/could-not-find-or/478428/2</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 14 Jan 2013 16:22:53 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-478428-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/could-not-find-or/478428.rss">Could not find or</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Could not find or</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@its2013 its2013]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/its2013">@its2013</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Could not find or load main class then a URL follows after it.</p>
<p>I know this probably sounds pathetic, but I’m trying to learn this stuff and the only way to is to give it a go, trouble shoot continuously and obtain knowledge from others.</p>
<p>So i’ve installed everything required, so no ‘ant’ errors or ‘javac’ errors… Set all my env’s under the computer system. Basically what is happening is when I compile my client side or my server side, the RSCD / java file itself deletes…</p>
<p>Then I compile it does nothing, doesnt even change the XML file, I tried this with the server side as well, does the same thing… gives me the " Could Not find or load main class " error and also deletes the RSCD / Java file… Basically the error  is happening at run, but without the compiler working correctly, I would imagine why…</p>
<p>I’ve troubleshooted everything I possibly could, i’ve turned all the links in Google PURPLE lol and I just am stumped… I know you guy’s hate noobies like myself but help a noob out, give me that bronze long haha</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/could-not-find-or/478428/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/could-not-find-or/478428/1</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 14 Jan 2013 16:16:53 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-478428-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/could-not-find-or/478428.rss">Could not find or</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
