<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Webclient problem on erasedpkz client Pi/DSPK</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/webclient-problem-on-erasedpkz-client-pi-dspk/415017</link>
    <description>Ok so I&#39;ve been Attempting to make the erased-pkz source into a webclient although from looking at the coding in the signlink.java client.java and cachedownloader.java everything seems to be fine. But! When I jarred it since I always test out te jar file before using the web browser (yes after jarring the Client makingthe certificate and signing the client) the jar file doesn&#39;t open up which is te jarred client an I check my task manager and java.exe nor javaw from my perspective it must be something with the client.java thus when I tried the webclient on my browser I get on error but the java console does not tell me the error so from my perspective this is quite rather odd Im an experienced webclient developer but this is the first source that&#39;s been bugging me haha well if I got an error and the console told me what&#39;s wrong I&#39;d be able to fix it but it doesn&#39;t so can any of you guys share you&#39;re experiences if you&#39;ve had any related to the situation I&#39;m in. It would be very appreciated thus if I manage to make this source webclient ready I&#39;m planning on releasing it to the public hopefully I&#39;ll manage to do that.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 18 Sep 2011 02:30:31 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Game Development</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/webclient-problem-on-erasedpkz-client-pi-dspk/415017.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Webclient problem on erasedpkz client Pi/DSPK</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Dextrell Dextrell]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/dextrell">@Dextrell</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Ok so I’ve been Attempting to make the erased-pkz source into a webclient although from looking at the coding in the signlink.java client.java and cachedownloader.java everything seems to be fine. But! When I jarred it since I always test out te jar file before using the web browser (yes after jarring the Client makingthe certificate and signing the client) the jar file doesn’t open up which is te jarred client an I check my task manager and java.exe nor javaw from my perspective it must be something with the client.java thus when I tried the webclient on my browser I get on error but the java console does not tell me the error so from my perspective this is quite rather odd Im an experienced webclient developer but this is the first source that’s been bugging me haha well if I got an error and the console told me what’s wrong I’d be able to fix it but it doesn’t so can any of you guys share you’re experiences if you’ve had any related to the situation I’m in. It would be very appreciated thus if I manage to make this source webclient ready I’m planning on releasing it to the public hopefully I’ll manage to do that.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/webclient-problem-on-erasedpkz-client-pi-dspk/415017/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/webclient-problem-on-erasedpkz-client-pi-dspk/415017/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 18 Sep 2011 02:30:31 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-415017-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/webclient-problem-on-erasedpkz-client-pi-dspk/415017.rss">Webclient problem on erasedpkz client Pi/DSPK</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
