<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Enternal lands must see it like wow and runescape</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/enternal-lands-must-see-it-like-wow-and-runescape/8991</link>
    <description>w00t i have finaly found a game like WOW and RUNESCAPE it rocks this world so far enyway

[size=20pt]http://www.eternal-lands.com/[/size]

Heres some info on the playable races

Humans: feel the need to create a shelter by cutting down trees, and anything else that stands in their way, and to constantly create, build, and improve things. They hunt animals for food, as well as eating the vegetation of the land. The humans take whatever they could and use it to their advantage. Although they also show compassion, kindness, and generousity when the times are right. They have many abilities and create big cities and towns.

Elves: revere life, and are very careful not to waste things. They hunt animals in low moderation, always giving thanks to their god when they kill, and before they eat. They build their homes in the forests, in a style all their own. The Elves are very friendly to the most of the other races, but have a deep hatred for everything they consider to be evil (such as the goblins, orcs, ogres, etc.), and don&#39;t fully trust the dwarves or the Orchan(whom they consider barbaric). The Elves are very knowledgable, and harbor a great repository of historical books in libraries which they open to all, for they live lives of up to five times that of a human.

Dwarves: stay to themselves the majority of the time. They don&#39;t travel too much, prefering the warmth and comfort of their own home to the outside world. Dwarves are excellent craftsmen. They buid the most sturdy and elaborate structures, the most accurately carved statues, and exquisite jewelry. They carve wood, chip stone, and shape metal until it is almost perfect. Because of this they generally have their homes in or around caves, building mines that they share together.

Gnomes: are another small dwarfish race, but unlike dwarves they are outgoing social travelers. They are also pretty good craftsmen, and tailors of clothing. Another skill of their&#39;s is map making, although you can never trust a Gnome&#39;s map to be 100% accurate all the time. And not to forget their unsatiable curiosity for trying to find a new invention for one of life&#39;s many difficulties. They are probably the most helpful, generous, and unbiased of all the races.

Draegoni: are what look to be a cross between a human and a dragon, yet much more human than dragon like. Legend says that they are children of the mythical dragon god, Iringold. They are highly magical beings that dwell in the colder regions on the extreme ends of the world. It is said that their inherent magical abilities come from the dragon blood that is mixed in their veins, and in their few scales that sparkle on their bodies.

Orchans: were named so because they look like a cross between a human, and an orc. Whether or not they were bred that way is a commonly disputed topic, no one knows for sure. There are legends and myths going in each direction. They are a people that believe in judging someone on their strength, heroism, and bravery. They hold many contests of strength, and also elect their leaders by the competitions. Many of them are fights to the death, which the other races see them as being barbaric. They are also very honorable however, always keeping their word when they took an oath, even if it means their life is at stake.
____________________________

Here is the Info i just copyed this

You&#39;re at the official homepage of Eternal Lands! Eternal Lands is a FREE MMORPG (massively multiplayer online role playing game) currently under development. The game is now in Beta stage, but that doesn&#39;t mean it&#39;s incomplete. It&#39;s currently fully playable and we are constantly working on adding more things to do, more items to make, monsters to fight, and also improving the current systems. If you want to help us in any way, take a look in our forums and there you can post your ideas/suggestions, or perhaps even get involved with programming or mapmaking which we can always use help with!

[br][size=1]Posted at: August 11, 2006, 11:09:06 AM[/size][hr][QUOTE]Fighting:
Fighting is broken down into attack and defense skills. To start raising these skills, you must fight with animals like rabbits, beavers, rats, deer and such, and later monsters like goblins and skeletons. Another option is going onto special PK (player killing) maps and fighting other players. Beginners should start with some of the weaker creatures in this game such as rabbits, rats, and beavers. Keep the meat and bones and fur they drop, you will need these for other skills you will learn later on.

All you need to do to start fighting is to place your cursor on the animal you are trying to kill. Your cursor should turn into a little sword icon. Then you just click on it! You have to be fast, those rabbits can hop away! When you get a little better and advance to stronger animals, (and learn to make some money), you can buy armour to protect you, and weapons to help you.

While fighting you get injured or sometimes killed. To regain health, make sure that your food level (the yellow bar) is positive. To do this you must eat. You can eat bread, fruits and veggies, and cooked meat. You can buy your food at the taverns, find it in bags on the ground on Isla Prima, or harvest the veggies yourself. You can eat it by clicking on the pointing finger icon at the bottom of your screen and then click on the food. To heal even faster, you can buy or make healing potions and drink them. Another option is to cast healing spells on yourself (see Magic skill).

When you first start the game and die, you respawn near the campfire on Isla Prima. When your levels are a little higher, you are sent to the underworld. To leave the underworld, go north until you see large steps with candles on each side leading to a red glowing portal. Walk up close and click on it, that&#39;s the exit. You will lose some of your items when you die. This is normal, it happens to everyone! They will be dropped in a little tan bag in the spot where you died. Most people do not get their items back, this is legal and normal. Anything in a bag on the ground is fair game for others, no matter why it was dropped.



Harvesting:
Harvesting is the skill in which you gather the resources you will use in the game. These include flowers, fruits and vegetables, quartz, ore, gemstones, sulfur, etc. The best way to start this skill is to find a flower and click on it. When you click on your bag icon (your inventory), a window will open up and you will see the flowers adding up in your bag! You can either save these flowers and bring them to storage (you will need them for ingredients later) or sell them at a flowershop.

You will get experience for only the first 120 items you harvest each ingame hour. (To see what time it is ingame, click on the clock on the right of your screen.) A red message tells you when you have reached this limit. You can, of course, continue harvesting so you can get more of this item, but you won&#39;t get any harvesting experience for these.

While harvesting different kinds of flowers, you might notice that you get different amounts of experience for each kind. Items that are hard to get, or require more research, give more experience than easy to get items. After getting a few harvesting levels with flowers, a beginner should move to vegetables (there is a lovely veggie patch just a little bit away from the beam on Isla Prima). It will take longer than the flowers did, but it is worth it. You get more experience (and therefore level up faster!) per vegetable, you can use the vegetables for food to keep your yellow food bar over 0, and you can sell them to taverns for money.

There are also some harvesting events that can occur from time to time. Some affect you negatively, and some positively. For example, you can get stung by a bee (and lose some health), the Queen of Nature can bless you with extra harvesting experience, or you can possibly find a bag with gold coins in it! Each time you get one of these events, your harvesting will stop. You must reclick the item to continue. Simply clicking on the item will stop and/or start the harvesting process. You can also end harvesting by simply getting up and walking away.



Manufacturing:
Manufacturing is the skill where you will learn to make your clothes, armour, and weapons. To first start this skill, you will need to be patient and begin with some warm fur clothing. Not as exciting as making armour and swords, but you need to earn some levels first before you can attempt such weighty items! Check your ingame encyclopedia (the ? icon) for all of the items you can make, and the ingredients you need to do so.

To start making items, you need a needle, thread, and furs. While hunting rabbits, keep the furs and sell only the meat. Then go to a General Store, Lakeside has one for example, and buy some thread and one needle. Lakeside is the village at the docks on Whitestone map. To go there from Isla Prima, go south to the docks and click on the flag on the ship. Press TAB key to see a map. General Stores are the green dots on it. Make sure you have food in your inventory. You can&#39;t manufacture when you are hungry (yellow bar below 0) so keep your food level positive.

The first thing to make is warm fur gloves. You need 3 brown rabbit furs and 2 thread. Make sure that you have the needle in your inventory too. Open the manufacturing window by clicking on the &quot;hammer and anvil&quot; icon on the bottom. Then click 3 times on the rabbit furs, 2 times on the thread. You should see 3 furs and 2 threads drop into the lower boxes next to the &quot;mix&quot; button. Now click the &quot;Mix&quot; button and wait. And, hopefully, you have made your first pair of fur gloves.

**Note**: You will sometimes fail to make an item. This is normal. Just try again.

Now make as many fur gloves as you can get rabbit furs for until your manufacture level is up to 4 or 5. You can sell the gloves to any General Store to make some money.

Now it&#39;s time to make yourself a fur hat. Go on the Whitestone map and try to kill a white rabbit. Tirnwood Vale (click Tab to see where that is) is a good place to find white rabbits. You will also need to get 3 beaver furs, you can find beavers on Isla Prima. Then all you need to do is buy 3 threads and you have the ingredients for &quot;teh one hat&quot;. To make the hat, be sure that you have the needle in your inventory, then open the manufacturing window (hammer and anvil icon) and click 3 times on the beaver furs, 3 times on the thread and 1 time on the white rabbit fur. Then click the &quot;Mix&quot; button, wait, and pray that you have now made a fur hat.

When you can make fur hats easily, try to get some wolf and fox furs for a fur cloak. Ask players who are training (fighting) on foxes or wolves if they can sell you a few furs. Of course you can try to kill some wolves and foxes yourself, but they are much harder to kill than rabbits or rats, so instead of committing suicide, better ask other players for furs. You need 3 wolf furs, 2 fox furs, and 5 thread to make a fur cloak. Don&#39;t forget you need your needle and food in your inventory as well. Follow the same procedure as above to start to make the cloak. And now your set of fur clothes is complete; gloves, hat, and cloak. Now you can wear them. Congratulations!

The next useful things to make are leather gloves. You need 4 leather and 4 thread. Leather can be bought at General Stores. Have your needle in your inventory and eat some food, open the manufacture window, click 4 times on leather, 4 times on thread and then the &quot;Mix&quot; button. Expect to fail and you could even lose the ingredients. After a few tries, you should now have a leather glove, which is very useful. Leather gloves are needed to harvest sulfur and pick cactus, and you can even use it as a weapon!



Alchemy:
Alchemy is the art of making essences and metal bars. You will use essences to cast your magic spells and for ingredients in some items you can make, and metal bars for manufacturing your armour and weapons and for crafting your magic rings and medallions. Check your ingame encyclopedia ( the ? icon at the bottom of your screen) for a list of all of the essences and bars you can make, and their ingredients. So let&#39;s make fire essences to start out with, they are easy to make and you can save them to use later or you can sell them to magic shops or players to make money. Fire essences are used for metal smelting, to make metalbars, and other metal stuff. Everybody needs fire essences for something.

You are going to need three ingredients to make fire essences. You need red snapdragons, red roses, and sulfur (sometimes spelled sulphur). Both flowers can be found on the Valley of the Dwarves map, on the eastern side of the river (they might be hidden a bit, you will have to search for them). To get to the Valley of the Dwarves map from Isla Prima, head south to the docks again. Click on the boat flag and that will take you to the Lakeside docks. Get off the boat, and go to the second boat there. That will have a picture of a deer on the flag, click on that. You now will have come to the Corren, Desert Pines docks. Get off of the boat, and find the boat that has the flag with the bear on it. That is the boat that will take you to the Valley of the Dwarves map.

Now you need sulfur. Don&#39;t forget your leather gloves! This can be found in Crystal Caverns, which is on the Desert Pines map (remember the ship with the deer flag on it?) The cave, or caverns, is located in the mountain range located in the middle of the map. To find the sulfur inside the cave, you can either ask other players in there to guide you to the sulfur, or you can find a help site that has a map of the cave and find where the yellow dots are (thats the sulfur). Now that you found the sulfur, you need to &quot;equip&quot; your leather gloves. This means you open your inventory window, and drag your glove over to one of the 8 little boxes on the right side of that window over where it says &quot;quantity&quot;. Now just click on the sulfur and watch it fill up your bag. You can deposit your sulfur at the Desert Pines storage (brown dot on your map).

Now that you have stored your flowers and sulfur, get some food in your inventory. Make sure you eat it and have your yellow food bar over 0. You cannot make items with a food level less than 0. Now withdraw an equal number of sulfur, red roses, and snapdragons. Open your Mix window (anvil and hammer icon). Click on 1 rose, 1 snapdragon, and 1 sulfur. One of each should drop into the lower boxes next to the &quot;mix&quot; button. Then click &quot;mix&quot;. It&#39;s possible to fail, if that happens, you just try again. It is a good idea to make a lot of these essences, players like to buy them in bulk, you will use a lot of them yourself, and you can sell them to magic shops for money. It is also a fast and easy way to get your alchemy level up.

Pay attention when you make your fire essences. You might see one go into a different box in your inventory. If that happens, click on the eye icon then click on the essence that went into the different spot. It should say it&#39;s an enriched fire essence. If that happens, you are very lucky and can sell it to other players for a LOT of money.



Magic:
Magic is the art of casting spells. You can use magic for a variety of things, including healing yourself and others, teleporting, and fighting. To use and train magic, you need sigils and essences and mana (blue bar at the bottom of your screen). You can buy sigils in the two magic shops on the White Stone map. Once you have bought a sigil, it shows up in your magic window (click on the magic wand icon), NOT in your inventory. This item will last forever, so even though sigils are expensive, you only need to buy each one once. You cannot give or trade or sell sigils to other players. Essences are a single use item, and can either be bought from the magic shops, bought from other players, or made yourself with your alchemy skill.

To start with magic, go to the magic shop in Grahm&#39;s Village and purchase the &quot;health&quot; sigil. Then find the magic shop in White Stone City and buy the &quot;increase&quot; sigil. You should buy some &quot;health essences&quot; there too. Now you are ready to cast &quot;heal&quot; spells on yourself. This is very useful when you lose health by fighting or harvesting events.

To cast a spell: Click on the magic wand icon. You should see the two sigils you just bought. First click on the &#39;increase&quot; sigil, and then click on the &quot;health&quot; sigil. You should see them drop down into the boxes next to the &quot;cast&quot; button. Make sure you have the health essences you just bought in your inventory. Now click the &quot;cast&quot; button. If you don&#39;t fail, you should have recovered 5 material points (the green bar over your characters head shows the same thing as the red bar at the bottom of your screen). However, it will have taken away 5 mana points (your blue bar). You can cast spells until you run out of enough mana. To bring your mana back up to full, you need to keep a positive food level (yellow bar over 0) to regenerate it, just like your health. You can also make potions or buy them from Mira the potionseller to raise your mana back up.



Potioning:
Potions is obviously the art of making potions. There are potions to do a variety of things, such as healing, mana regeneration, temporarily raising some stats or attributes, even one for food!

To make all potions, you need empty vials. The easiest way to get vials is to buy mana potions from Mira the potion seller in White Stone City. She charges 5 gold coins per mana potion, so buy some and drink them to get your vials. (Good time to start training magic too). You can also have Harvy in Desert Pines make you vials, but you need to mine quartz first, or buy it from him (very expensive and time consuming), so most people choose to drink the potions.

Let&#39;s start with making healing potions. When you drink these, you regain 5 material points (health), so these are good to use when fighting animals. For healing potions, you need vials, sunflowers, and wine, and of course some veggies (for your food level). Grahms village is the perfect place to go. There is a veggie patch there for your veggies, some sunflower plants at the house by the veggie patch, and a tavern to buy the wine at. When you have these 3 things in your inventory, click on your manufacturing icon (hammer and anvil) and open your manufacturing window. Click once on a vial, then on the wine, then on the sunflower. You should have one of each of those 3 things drop down into the boxes next to the &quot;mix&quot; button. Make sure your food level is over 0, then click the &quot;mix&quot; button and poof! You have a healing potion! If you get a fail message instead, don&#39;t worry, just try again!



Summoning:
Summoning is the art of bringing creatures back to life for a short amount of time. They will follow you wherever you go, and gradually lose health, until they die. We will practise with a rabbit, but with training and practise and research, you will be able to summon the fiercest creatures in EL! You can summon for fun, or a common practise is to summon in pk(player kill) maps for attacking your enemies.

First you need a dead rabbit. Just go kill one. You need 1 rabbit fur, 1 bone, and 1 raw meat. Next you need a life essence, you can buy one at either magic shop on the White Stone map. This skill also uses mana, so make sure your blue bar is full. And as always, make sure your food level is over 0. Now you need to find a quiet place, away from any storages or people. Never summon at beam or wraith, or at any storages or large gatherings of people.

Open your manufacture window (hammer and anvil icon) and click once on the brown rabbit fur, once on the meat, once on the bone, and once on the life essence. You should see 1 of each item drop down into the boxes next to the &quot;mix&quot; icon. Now click &quot;mix&quot; and you should see a rabbit hopping along next to you! If you are in a guild, it will have your guild tag as well. Now walk away, he will follow you!



Crafting:
Crafting is a more advanced skill, only started after a fair level of expertise has been acquired in other skills. You rely heavily on alchemy and research and harvesting skill to work on crafting, and you will find you need a lot of gold coins as well. Crafting is the art of making magical jewelry such as the fighting medallions and rings, and the teleporting rings. It is time consuming and expensive, and requires a lot of research.

To start crafting, you need a lot of knowledge. Meaning you must read books first before you can start. Go to Tarsengaard and enter the magic school. Beware of the armoured goblin roaming that map! You can enter Tarsengaard from either White Stone or from the Valley of the Dwarves maps. Find Itilli in the registry room, that&#39;s on the left side of the entrance hall. Buy from her the &quot;Generic Rings&quot; and &quot;Gold Rings&quot; books and start reading them. We will start with making simple gold rings.

While reading, make sure your artificial nexus is at level 1 (you can do that at the Wraith). Now you need some gold bars. You can make them (alchemy) or buy them from other players. You will also need some fire essences. Again, you can make them (alchemy) or buy them from other players or from the magic shops. And lastly, you will need a ring mold. There is a specialty magic shop in Portland, where you can buy all your crafting tools and equipment and some of the teleport rings. (Just a note, you cannot buy sigils and essences at the Portland magic shop). This is the yellow dot on the Portland map.

When you are done reading both books, have the gold bars, fire essences, and ring mold in your inventory, you are ready to start. Don&#39;t forget your food!

Now open the manufacture window by clicking on the hammer and anvil icon. Click 2 times on the gold bar, click 3 times on the fire essences and you should see 2 gold bars and 3 fire essences drop down into the boxes next to the &quot;mix&quot; button. Click &quot;mix&quot; and hopefully you will make your first gold ring. If you fail, simply try again. This is a hard skill, and you will fail a lot and lose ingredients as well. To continue on and make silver rings, you need to go back to Itilli and buy the &quot;Silver Rings&quot; book and read it. And so forth. The gold and silver rings you make now are part of the base ingredients needed to make the magic rings we use ingame, such as the teleport rings, disengage rings, and damage rings.[QUOTE]
[br][size=1]Posted at: August 11, 2006, 11:16:41 AM[/size][hr]That should do it</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 09 Oct 2006 06:00:45 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Games</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/enternal-lands-must-see-it-like-wow-and-runescape/8991.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Enternal lands must see it like wow and runescape</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@coolcool coolcool]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/coolcool">@coolcool</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>any one know the id for monye on eternal lands for artmoney</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/enternal-lands-must-see-it-like-wow-and-runescape/8991/9">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/enternal-lands-must-see-it-like-wow-and-runescape/8991/9</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 09 Oct 2006 06:00:45 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-8991-9</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/enternal-lands-must-see-it-like-wow-and-runescape/8991.rss">Enternal lands must see it like wow and runescape</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Enternal lands must see it like wow and runescape</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Mopman Mopman]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/mopman">@Mopman</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote no-group quote-modified" data-post="1" data-topic="9107">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/anon95490785/40/5_6259e4fa9dfe0dec282fb0955bb1974c.png" class="avatar"><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/9107/1">On another topic</a>
</div>
<blockquote>
<p>The game is terrible and was created by a couple of kids from gamedev so I wouldn’t get attached to it.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Kids?<br>
If you mean the original developer (since you said a couple of kids, but there is way more than two developers on the team, so I’m assuming you mean the original developer), his WIFE created the art. Also, he writes properly enough on his blog.</p>
<p>Not a kid.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/enternal-lands-must-see-it-like-wow-and-runescape/8991/8">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/enternal-lands-must-see-it-like-wow-and-runescape/8991/8</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 26 Sep 2006 17:09:30 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-8991-8</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/enternal-lands-must-see-it-like-wow-and-runescape/8991.rss">Enternal lands must see it like wow and runescape</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Enternal lands must see it like wow and runescape</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@solemn_wishes solemn wishes]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/solemn_wishes">@solemn_wishes</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>its not a bad game, though it does require alot more powerfull graphic cards, fast net and a pretty fast pc. You can play world of warcraft with less lagg then eternal lands and the fps on it sucks.</p>
<p>The content is nice, combat maybe a lil slow but its a nice free open source game…you can also make your own maps for it and if they are good they add them to the game.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/enternal-lands-must-see-it-like-wow-and-runescape/8991/7">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/enternal-lands-must-see-it-like-wow-and-runescape/8991/7</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 26 Sep 2006 14:48:29 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-8991-7</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/enternal-lands-must-see-it-like-wow-and-runescape/8991.rss">Enternal lands must see it like wow and runescape</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Enternal lands must see it like wow and runescape</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Urgonnadie Urgonnadie]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/urgonnadie">@Urgonnadie</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>i kno this may sound nooby but wat is the website for WOW i thought it was <a href="http://www.WOW.com" rel="nofollow noopener">www.WOW.com</a> but it just goes to a internet browser</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/enternal-lands-must-see-it-like-wow-and-runescape/8991/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/enternal-lands-must-see-it-like-wow-and-runescape/8991/6</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 20 Sep 2006 23:23:39 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-8991-6</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/enternal-lands-must-see-it-like-wow-and-runescape/8991.rss">Enternal lands must see it like wow and runescape</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Enternal lands must see it like wow and runescape</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@kenashi kenashi]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/kenashi">@kenashi</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>open source makes it way better <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/smiley.png?v=9" title=":smiley:" class="emoji" alt=":smiley:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/enternal-lands-must-see-it-like-wow-and-runescape/8991/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/enternal-lands-must-see-it-like-wow-and-runescape/8991/5</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 20 Aug 2006 02:50:22 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-8991-5</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/enternal-lands-must-see-it-like-wow-and-runescape/8991.rss">Enternal lands must see it like wow and runescape</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Enternal lands must see it like wow and runescape</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@moparisthebest Moparisthebest]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/moparisthebest">@moparisthebest</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>open source client &lt;3</p>
<p>bot time? <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=9" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/enternal-lands-must-see-it-like-wow-and-runescape/8991/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/enternal-lands-must-see-it-like-wow-and-runescape/8991/4</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 15 Aug 2006 19:49:17 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-8991-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/enternal-lands-must-see-it-like-wow-and-runescape/8991.rss">Enternal lands must see it like wow and runescape</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Enternal lands must see it like wow and runescape</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@king_jerome king jerome]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/king_jerome">@king_jerome</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p><em>goes to check it out</em></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/enternal-lands-must-see-it-like-wow-and-runescape/8991/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/enternal-lands-must-see-it-like-wow-and-runescape/8991/3</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 15 Aug 2006 12:03:38 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-8991-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/enternal-lands-must-see-it-like-wow-and-runescape/8991.rss">Enternal lands must see it like wow and runescape</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Enternal lands must see it like wow and runescape</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@MoO MoO]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/moo">@MoO</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I hated this game… too… umm  <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/expressionless.png?v=9" title=":expressionless:" class="emoji" alt=":expressionless:">  annoying to load up lol</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/enternal-lands-must-see-it-like-wow-and-runescape/8991/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/enternal-lands-must-see-it-like-wow-and-runescape/8991/2</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 11 Aug 2006 16:00:29 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-8991-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/enternal-lands-must-see-it-like-wow-and-runescape/8991.rss">Enternal lands must see it like wow and runescape</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Enternal lands must see it like wow and runescape</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@xerlot xerlot]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/xerlot">@xerlot</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>w00t i have finaly found a game like WOW and RUNESCAPE it rocks this world so far enyway</p>
<p>[size=20pt]<a href="http://www.eternal-lands.com/%5B/size%5D" rel="nofollow noopener">http://www.eternal-lands.com/[/size]</a></p>
<p>Heres some info on the playable races</p>
<p>Humans: feel the need to create a shelter by cutting down trees, and anything else that stands in their way, and to constantly create, build, and improve things. They hunt animals for food, as well as eating the vegetation of the land. The humans take whatever they could and use it to their advantage. Although they also show compassion, kindness, and generousity when the times are right. They have many abilities and create big cities and towns.</p>
<p>Elves: revere life, and are very careful not to waste things. They hunt animals in low moderation, always giving thanks to their god when they kill, and before they eat. They build their homes in the forests, in a style all their own. The Elves are very friendly to the most of the other races, but have a deep hatred for everything they consider to be evil (such as the goblins, orcs, ogres, etc.), and don’t fully trust the dwarves or the Orchan(whom they consider barbaric). The Elves are very knowledgable, and harbor a great repository of historical books in libraries which they open to all, for they live lives of up to five times that of a human.</p>
<p>Dwarves: stay to themselves the majority of the time. They don’t travel too much, prefering the warmth and comfort of their own home to the outside world. Dwarves are excellent craftsmen. They buid the most sturdy and elaborate structures, the most accurately carved statues, and exquisite jewelry. They carve wood, chip stone, and shape metal until it is almost perfect. Because of this they generally have their homes in or around caves, building mines that they share together.</p>
<p>Gnomes: are another small dwarfish race, but unlike dwarves they are outgoing social travelers. They are also pretty good craftsmen, and tailors of clothing. Another skill of their’s is map making, although you can never trust a Gnome’s map to be 100% accurate all the time. And not to forget their unsatiable curiosity for trying to find a new invention for one of life’s many difficulties. They are probably the most helpful, generous, and unbiased of all the races.</p>
<p>Draegoni: are what look to be a cross between a human and a dragon, yet much more human than dragon like. Legend says that they are children of the mythical dragon god, Iringold. They are highly magical beings that dwell in the colder regions on the extreme ends of the world. It is said that their inherent magical abilities come from the dragon blood that is mixed in their veins, and in their few scales that sparkle on their bodies.</p>
<p>Orchans: were named so because they look like a cross between a human, and an orc. Whether or not they were bred that way is a commonly disputed topic, no one knows for sure. There are legends and myths going in each direction. They are a people that believe in judging someone on their strength, heroism, and bravery. They hold many contests of strength, and also elect their leaders by the competitions. Many of them are fights to the death, which the other races see them as being barbaric. They are also very honorable however, always keeping their word when they took an oath, even if it means their life is at stake.</p>
<hr>
<p>Here is the Info i just copyed this</p>
<p>You’re at the official homepage of Eternal Lands! Eternal Lands is a FREE MMORPG (massively multiplayer online role playing game) currently under development. The game is now in Beta stage, but that doesn’t mean it’s incomplete. It’s currently fully playable and we are constantly working on adding more things to do, more items to make, monsters to fight, and also improving the current systems. If you want to help us in any way, take a look in our forums and there you can post your ideas/suggestions, or perhaps even get involved with programming or mapmaking which we can always use help with!</p>
<p>[br][size=1]Posted at: August 11, 2006, 11:09:06 AM[/size][hr][QUOTE]Fighting:<br>
Fighting is broken down into attack and defense skills. To start raising these skills, you must fight with animals like rabbits, beavers, rats, deer and such, and later monsters like goblins and skeletons. Another option is going onto special PK (player killing) maps and fighting other players. Beginners should start with some of the weaker creatures in this game such as rabbits, rats, and beavers. Keep the meat and bones and fur they drop, you will need these for other skills you will learn later on.</p>
<p>All you need to do to start fighting is to place your cursor on the animal you are trying to kill. Your cursor should turn into a little sword icon. Then you just click on it! You have to be fast, those rabbits can hop away! When you get a little better and advance to stronger animals, (and learn to make some money), you can buy armour to protect you, and weapons to help you.</p>
<p>While fighting you get injured or sometimes killed. To regain health, make sure that your food level (the yellow bar) is positive. To do this you must eat. You can eat bread, fruits and veggies, and cooked meat. You can buy your food at the taverns, find it in bags on the ground on Isla Prima, or harvest the veggies yourself. You can eat it by clicking on the pointing finger icon at the bottom of your screen and then click on the food. To heal even faster, you can buy or make healing potions and drink them. Another option is to cast healing spells on yourself (see Magic skill).</p>
<p>When you first start the game and die, you respawn near the campfire on Isla Prima. When your levels are a little higher, you are sent to the underworld. To leave the underworld, go north until you see large steps with candles on each side leading to a red glowing portal. Walk up close and click on it, that’s the exit. You will lose some of your items when you die. This is normal, it happens to everyone! They will be dropped in a little tan bag in the spot where you died. Most people do not get their items back, this is legal and normal. Anything in a bag on the ground is fair game for others, no matter why it was dropped.</p>
<p>Harvesting:<br>
Harvesting is the skill in which you gather the resources you will use in the game. These include flowers, fruits and vegetables, quartz, ore, gemstones, sulfur, etc. The best way to start this skill is to find a flower and click on it. When you click on your bag icon (your inventory), a window will open up and you will see the flowers adding up in your bag! You can either save these flowers and bring them to storage (you will need them for ingredients later) or sell them at a flowershop.</p>
<p>You will get experience for only the first 120 items you harvest each ingame hour. (To see what time it is ingame, click on the clock on the right of your screen.) A red message tells you when you have reached this limit. You can, of course, continue harvesting so you can get more of this item, but you won’t get any harvesting experience for these.</p>
<p>While harvesting different kinds of flowers, you might notice that you get different amounts of experience for each kind. Items that are hard to get, or require more research, give more experience than easy to get items. After getting a few harvesting levels with flowers, a beginner should move to vegetables (there is a lovely veggie patch just a little bit away from the beam on Isla Prima). It will take longer than the flowers did, but it is worth it. You get more experience (and therefore level up faster!) per vegetable, you can use the vegetables for food to keep your yellow food bar over 0, and you can sell them to taverns for money.</p>
<p>There are also some harvesting events that can occur from time to time. Some affect you negatively, and some positively. For example, you can get stung by a bee (and lose some health), the Queen of Nature can bless you with extra harvesting experience, or you can possibly find a bag with gold coins in it! Each time you get one of these events, your harvesting will stop. You must reclick the item to continue. Simply clicking on the item will stop and/or start the harvesting process. You can also end harvesting by simply getting up and walking away.</p>
<p>Manufacturing:<br>
Manufacturing is the skill where you will learn to make your clothes, armour, and weapons. To first start this skill, you will need to be patient and begin with some warm fur clothing. Not as exciting as making armour and swords, but you need to earn some levels first before you can attempt such weighty items! Check your ingame encyclopedia (the ? icon) for all of the items you can make, and the ingredients you need to do so.</p>
<p>To start making items, you need a needle, thread, and furs. While hunting rabbits, keep the furs and sell only the meat. Then go to a General Store, Lakeside has one for example, and buy some thread and one needle. Lakeside is the village at the docks on Whitestone map. To go there from Isla Prima, go south to the docks and click on the flag on the ship. Press TAB key to see a map. General Stores are the green dots on it. Make sure you have food in your inventory. You can’t manufacture when you are hungry (yellow bar below 0) so keep your food level positive.</p>
<p>The first thing to make is warm fur gloves. You need 3 brown rabbit furs and 2 thread. Make sure that you have the needle in your inventory too. Open the manufacturing window by clicking on the “hammer and anvil” icon on the bottom. Then click 3 times on the rabbit furs, 2 times on the thread. You should see 3 furs and 2 threads drop into the lower boxes next to the “mix” button. Now click the “Mix” button and wait. And, hopefully, you have made your first pair of fur gloves.</p>
<p><strong>Note</strong>: You will sometimes fail to make an item. This is normal. Just try again.</p>
<p>Now make as many fur gloves as you can get rabbit furs for until your manufacture level is up to 4 or 5. You can sell the gloves to any General Store to make some money.</p>
<p>Now it’s time to make yourself a fur hat. Go on the Whitestone map and try to kill a white rabbit. Tirnwood Vale (click Tab to see where that is) is a good place to find white rabbits. You will also need to get 3 beaver furs, you can find beavers on Isla Prima. Then all you need to do is buy 3 threads and you have the ingredients for “teh one hat”. To make the hat, be sure that you have the needle in your inventory, then open the manufacturing window (hammer and anvil icon) and click 3 times on the beaver furs, 3 times on the thread and 1 time on the white rabbit fur. Then click the “Mix” button, wait, and pray that you have now made a fur hat.</p>
<p>When you can make fur hats easily, try to get some wolf and fox furs for a fur cloak. Ask players who are training (fighting) on foxes or wolves if they can sell you a few furs. Of course you can try to kill some wolves and foxes yourself, but they are much harder to kill than rabbits or rats, so instead of committing suicide, better ask other players for furs. You need 3 wolf furs, 2 fox furs, and 5 thread to make a fur cloak. Don’t forget you need your needle and food in your inventory as well. Follow the same procedure as above to start to make the cloak. And now your set of fur clothes is complete; gloves, hat, and cloak. Now you can wear them. Congratulations!</p>
<p>The next useful things to make are leather gloves. You need 4 leather and 4 thread. Leather can be bought at General Stores. Have your needle in your inventory and eat some food, open the manufacture window, click 4 times on leather, 4 times on thread and then the “Mix” button. Expect to fail and you could even lose the ingredients. After a few tries, you should now have a leather glove, which is very useful. Leather gloves are needed to harvest sulfur and pick cactus, and you can even use it as a weapon!</p>
<p>Alchemy:<br>
Alchemy is the art of making essences and metal bars. You will use essences to cast your magic spells and for ingredients in some items you can make, and metal bars for manufacturing your armour and weapons and for crafting your magic rings and medallions. Check your ingame encyclopedia ( the ? icon at the bottom of your screen) for a list of all of the essences and bars you can make, and their ingredients. So let’s make fire essences to start out with, they are easy to make and you can save them to use later or you can sell them to magic shops or players to make money. Fire essences are used for metal smelting, to make metalbars, and other metal stuff. Everybody needs fire essences for something.</p>
<p>You are going to need three ingredients to make fire essences. You need red snapdragons, red roses, and sulfur (sometimes spelled sulphur). Both flowers can be found on the Valley of the Dwarves map, on the eastern side of the river (they might be hidden a bit, you will have to search for them). To get to the Valley of the Dwarves map from Isla Prima, head south to the docks again. Click on the boat flag and that will take you to the Lakeside docks. Get off the boat, and go to the second boat there. That will have a picture of a deer on the flag, click on that. You now will have come to the Corren, Desert Pines docks. Get off of the boat, and find the boat that has the flag with the bear on it. That is the boat that will take you to the Valley of the Dwarves map.</p>
<p>Now you need sulfur. Don’t forget your leather gloves! This can be found in Crystal Caverns, which is on the Desert Pines map (remember the ship with the deer flag on it?) The cave, or caverns, is located in the mountain range located in the middle of the map. To find the sulfur inside the cave, you can either ask other players in there to guide you to the sulfur, or you can find a help site that has a map of the cave and find where the yellow dots are (thats the sulfur). Now that you found the sulfur, you need to “equip” your leather gloves. This means you open your inventory window, and drag your glove over to one of the 8 little boxes on the right side of that window over where it says “quantity”. Now just click on the sulfur and watch it fill up your bag. You can deposit your sulfur at the Desert Pines storage (brown dot on your map).</p>
<p>Now that you have stored your flowers and sulfur, get some food in your inventory. Make sure you eat it and have your yellow food bar over 0. You cannot make items with a food level less than 0. Now withdraw an equal number of sulfur, red roses, and snapdragons. Open your Mix window (anvil and hammer icon). Click on 1 rose, 1 snapdragon, and 1 sulfur. One of each should drop into the lower boxes next to the “mix” button. Then click “mix”. It’s possible to fail, if that happens, you just try again. It is a good idea to make a lot of these essences, players like to buy them in bulk, you will use a lot of them yourself, and you can sell them to magic shops for money. It is also a fast and easy way to get your alchemy level up.</p>
<p>Pay attention when you make your fire essences. You might see one go into a different box in your inventory. If that happens, click on the eye icon then click on the essence that went into the different spot. It should say it’s an enriched fire essence. If that happens, you are very lucky and can sell it to other players for a LOT of money.</p>
<p>Magic:<br>
Magic is the art of casting spells. You can use magic for a variety of things, including healing yourself and others, teleporting, and fighting. To use and train magic, you need sigils and essences and mana (blue bar at the bottom of your screen). You can buy sigils in the two magic shops on the White Stone map. Once you have bought a sigil, it shows up in your magic window (click on the magic wand icon), NOT in your inventory. This item will last forever, so even though sigils are expensive, you only need to buy each one once. You cannot give or trade or sell sigils to other players. Essences are a single use item, and can either be bought from the magic shops, bought from other players, or made yourself with your alchemy skill.</p>
<p>To start with magic, go to the magic shop in Grahm’s Village and purchase the “health” sigil. Then find the magic shop in White Stone City and buy the “increase” sigil. You should buy some “health essences” there too. Now you are ready to cast “heal” spells on yourself. This is very useful when you lose health by fighting or harvesting events.</p>
<p>To cast a spell: Click on the magic wand icon. You should see the two sigils you just bought. First click on the 'increase" sigil, and then click on the “health” sigil. You should see them drop down into the boxes next to the “cast” button. Make sure you have the health essences you just bought in your inventory. Now click the “cast” button. If you don’t fail, you should have recovered 5 material points (the green bar over your characters head shows the same thing as the red bar at the bottom of your screen). However, it will have taken away 5 mana points (your blue bar). You can cast spells until you run out of enough mana. To bring your mana back up to full, you need to keep a positive food level (yellow bar over 0) to regenerate it, just like your health. You can also make potions or buy them from Mira the potionseller to raise your mana back up.</p>
<p>Potioning:<br>
Potions is obviously the art of making potions. There are potions to do a variety of things, such as healing, mana regeneration, temporarily raising some stats or attributes, even one for food!</p>
<p>To make all potions, you need empty vials. The easiest way to get vials is to buy mana potions from Mira the potion seller in White Stone City. She charges 5 gold coins per mana potion, so buy some and drink them to get your vials. (Good time to start training magic too). You can also have Harvy in Desert Pines make you vials, but you need to mine quartz first, or buy it from him (very expensive and time consuming), so most people choose to drink the potions.</p>
<p>Let’s start with making healing potions. When you drink these, you regain 5 material points (health), so these are good to use when fighting animals. For healing potions, you need vials, sunflowers, and wine, and of course some veggies (for your food level). Grahms village is the perfect place to go. There is a veggie patch there for your veggies, some sunflower plants at the house by the veggie patch, and a tavern to buy the wine at. When you have these 3 things in your inventory, click on your manufacturing icon (hammer and anvil) and open your manufacturing window. Click once on a vial, then on the wine, then on the sunflower. You should have one of each of those 3 things drop down into the boxes next to the “mix” button. Make sure your food level is over 0, then click the “mix” button and poof! You have a healing potion! If you get a fail message instead, don’t worry, just try again!</p>
<p>Summoning:<br>
Summoning is the art of bringing creatures back to life for a short amount of time. They will follow you wherever you go, and gradually lose health, until they die. We will practise with a rabbit, but with training and practise and research, you will be able to summon the fiercest creatures in EL! You can summon for fun, or a common practise is to summon in pk(player kill) maps for attacking your enemies.</p>
<p>First you need a dead rabbit. Just go kill one. You need 1 rabbit fur, 1 bone, and 1 raw meat. Next you need a life essence, you can buy one at either magic shop on the White Stone map. This skill also uses mana, so make sure your blue bar is full. And as always, make sure your food level is over 0. Now you need to find a quiet place, away from any storages or people. Never summon at beam or wraith, or at any storages or large gatherings of people.</p>
<p>Open your manufacture window (hammer and anvil icon) and click once on the brown rabbit fur, once on the meat, once on the bone, and once on the life essence. You should see 1 of each item drop down into the boxes next to the “mix” icon. Now click “mix” and you should see a rabbit hopping along next to you! If you are in a guild, it will have your guild tag as well. Now walk away, he will follow you!</p>
<p>Crafting:<br>
Crafting is a more advanced skill, only started after a fair level of expertise has been acquired in other skills. You rely heavily on alchemy and research and harvesting skill to work on crafting, and you will find you need a lot of gold coins as well. Crafting is the art of making magical jewelry such as the fighting medallions and rings, and the teleporting rings. It is time consuming and expensive, and requires a lot of research.</p>
<p>To start crafting, you need a lot of knowledge. Meaning you must read books first before you can start. Go to Tarsengaard and enter the magic school. Beware of the armoured goblin roaming that map! You can enter Tarsengaard from either White Stone or from the Valley of the Dwarves maps. Find Itilli in the registry room, that’s on the left side of the entrance hall. Buy from her the “Generic Rings” and “Gold Rings” books and start reading them. We will start with making simple gold rings.</p>
<p>While reading, make sure your artificial nexus is at level 1 (you can do that at the Wraith). Now you need some gold bars. You can make them (alchemy) or buy them from other players. You will also need some fire essences. Again, you can make them (alchemy) or buy them from other players or from the magic shops. And lastly, you will need a ring mold. There is a specialty magic shop in Portland, where you can buy all your crafting tools and equipment and some of the teleport rings. (Just a note, you cannot buy sigils and essences at the Portland magic shop). This is the yellow dot on the Portland map.</p>
<p>When you are done reading both books, have the gold bars, fire essences, and ring mold in your inventory, you are ready to start. Don’t forget your food!</p>
<p>Now open the manufacture window by clicking on the hammer and anvil icon. Click 2 times on the gold bar, click 3 times on the fire essences and you should see 2 gold bars and 3 fire essences drop down into the boxes next to the “mix” button. Click “mix” and hopefully you will make your first gold ring. If you fail, simply try again. This is a hard skill, and you will fail a lot and lose ingredients as well. To continue on and make silver rings, you need to go back to Itilli and buy the “Silver Rings” book and read it. And so forth. The gold and silver rings you make now are part of the base ingredients needed to make the magic rings we use ingame, such as the teleport rings, disengage rings, and damage rings.[QUOTE]<br>
[br][size=1]Posted at: August 11, 2006, 11:16:41 AM[/size][hr]That should do it</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/enternal-lands-must-see-it-like-wow-and-runescape/8991/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/enternal-lands-must-see-it-like-wow-and-runescape/8991/1</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 11 Aug 2006 15:17:37 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-8991-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/enternal-lands-must-see-it-like-wow-and-runescape/8991.rss">Enternal lands must see it like wow and runescape</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
