<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>A bunch of problems, errors</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/a-bunch-of-problems-errors/235265</link>
    <description>Hey guys. I&#39;ve been hiding in the shadows a bit just looking for topics that have to do with this. Reading readme&#39;s, reading server stuff, ect but haven&#39;t found what I&#39;m looking for and asking a question on. First of all I have Vista. I don&#39;t know if that interferes with anything... Now I downloaded the latest version of MoparScape yesterday. Got that played a bit on it but it rly isn&#39;t that fun without servers. So I downloaded a couple player made servers to test them out.

So I have them all downloaded now. I opened up one folder and clicked &#39;runserver&#39; because as of now I believe that is what you are supposed to do. I got the console and in it said that the server was online like its supposed to be. I open up MoparScape click &#39;enter&#39; type in a username and password. I clicked login and logged in. SOOO, this is where things get dumb (this is just one of my errors). I login and my character doesn&#39;t show up. I&#39;m invisible. I walk around and trade with a vendor. Some of their shops open others cause the server to disconnect so I reopen everything again. I click on my equipment and the server disconnects me again. Here is the message I get (this happened for various servers not just FigmentScape):

- FigmentScape -
 ..  Online!
Connection accepted from 127.0.0.1: 49503.
Client type: low memory version
UserId: 62467803
thor is signing onto server.
LOADED: 3
[client-1-thor]: Loading finished.
Game saved for player thor
ClientHandler: Client thor disconnected.

This happens all the time! I can&#39;t do anything at all. Can someone please help me with this problem? ;)

The other problem I&#39;m having is with Butter&#39;s Dream actually. I start up the client and click &#39;enter&#39; fill in my username and password and then click login. It says connecting to server for a moment then goes back to the menu that says simply &#39;enter&#39;. it doesn&#39;t matter how many times I try logging in it always does this. Could someone please help me?  ;)</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 06 Oct 2008 17:24:17 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/a-bunch-of-problems-errors/235265.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>A bunch of problems, errors</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Jordiescape Jordiescape]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/jordiescape">@Jordiescape</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>You’ll need to use this webclient;<br>
<a href="http://www.client.silabsoft.org" class="onebox" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">www.client.silabsoft.org</a><br>
That’s what most shitty player made servers consist of.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/a-bunch-of-problems-errors/235265/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/a-bunch-of-problems-errors/235265/3</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 06 Oct 2008 17:24:17 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-235265-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/a-bunch-of-problems-errors/235265.rss">A bunch of problems, errors</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>A bunch of problems, errors</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@sanjay1994 sanjay1994]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/sanjay1994">@sanjay1994</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>i need the cache</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/a-bunch-of-problems-errors/235265/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/a-bunch-of-problems-errors/235265/2</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 06 Oct 2008 17:06:10 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-235265-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/a-bunch-of-problems-errors/235265.rss">A bunch of problems, errors</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>A bunch of problems, errors</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Marcus_Rethan Marcus Rethan]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/marcus_rethan">@Marcus_Rethan</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Hey guys. I’ve been hiding in the shadows a bit just looking for topics that have to do with this. Reading readme’s, reading server stuff, ect but haven’t found what I’m looking for and asking a question on. First of all I have Vista. I don’t know if that interferes with anything… Now I downloaded the latest version of MoparScape yesterday. Got that played a bit on it but it rly isn’t that fun without servers. So I downloaded a couple player made servers to test them out.</p>
<p>So I have them all downloaded now. I opened up one folder and clicked ‘runserver’ because as of now I believe that is what you are supposed to do. I got the console and in it said that the server was online like its supposed to be. I open up MoparScape click ‘enter’ type in a username and password. I clicked login and logged in. SOOO, this is where things get dumb (this is just one of my errors). I login and my character doesn’t show up. I’m invisible. I walk around and trade with a vendor. Some of their shops open others cause the server to disconnect so I reopen everything again. I click on my equipment and the server disconnects me again. Here is the message I get (this happened for various servers not just FigmentScape):</p>
<ul>
<li>FigmentScape -<br>
…  Online!<br>
Connection accepted from 127.0.0.1: 49503.<br>
Client type: low memory version<br>
UserId: 62467803<br>
thor is signing onto server.<br>
LOADED: 3<br>
[client-1-thor]: Loading finished.<br>
Game saved for player thor<br>
ClientHandler: Client thor disconnected.</li>
</ul>
<p>This happens all the time! I can’t do anything at all. Can someone please help me with this problem? <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/wink.png?v=6" title=":wink:" class="emoji" alt=":wink:"></p>
<p>The other problem I’m having is with Butter’s Dream actually. I start up the client and click ‘enter’ fill in my username and password and then click login. It says connecting to server for a moment then goes back to the menu that says simply ‘enter’. it doesn’t matter how many times I try logging in it always does this. Could someone please help me?  <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/wink.png?v=6" title=":wink:" class="emoji" alt=":wink:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/a-bunch-of-problems-errors/235265/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/a-bunch-of-problems-errors/235265/1</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 06 Oct 2008 14:48:31 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-235265-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/a-bunch-of-problems-errors/235265.rss">A bunch of problems, errors</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
