<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>How do I Run DropEditor.java? (Eclipse/.bat)</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-do-i-run-dropeditor-java-eclipse-bat/447643</link>
    <description>I&#39;ve heard I need Eclipse, but I have no idea how to use it and it only seems to open the file, not run it. I have a .bat I&#39;m using to run it but it apparently can&#39;t find it (or more likely can&#39;t load it).

run.bat
[CODE]@echo off
title rundropeditor
&quot;C:/Program Files/Java/jre7/bin/java.exe&quot; -Xmx815m -cp bin;lib/*; com.rs.tools.DropEditor true true false
pause [/CODE]
I&#39;ve been changing it around trying to figure out why it can&#39;t find/load it, no luck. I&#39;ve put it right next to the file (and removed &#39;com.rs.tools.&#39;) and it didn&#39;t work.

Error
[CODE]Error: Could not find or load main class com.rs.tools.DropEditor
Press any key to continue . . .[/CODE]

I don&#39;t get it, how do I run it lol? I&#39;ve directly opened the file with Eclipse and Java, but it doesn&#39;t do anything (except Eclipse let&#39;s me edit the file...). I&#39;ve opened it with Eclipse and pressed the run button, but nothing happens. I&#39;ve downloaded multiple sources to make sure it wasn&#39;t a broken file or something, but it&#39;s the same thing. I must be doing something wrong, but I don&#39;t know what.

Even little hints help, so please tell. I would like to get back to funner things, this is being rather annoying and I won&#39;t move on until it&#39;s fixed. I put a lot of work into this and was going to save drops for last, but I wanted to remove them and noticed I couldn&#39;t.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 19 Dec 2012 01:33:48 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-do-i-run-dropeditor-java-eclipse-bat/447643.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>How do I Run DropEditor.java? (Eclipse/.bat)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@joeyulanch joeyulanch]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/joeyulanch">@joeyulanch</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>change capital D in DropEditor to dropEditor <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=5" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"> hope it helps you. thats what mine was anyways.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-do-i-run-dropeditor-java-eclipse-bat/447643/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-do-i-run-dropeditor-java-eclipse-bat/447643/2</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 19 Dec 2012 01:33:48 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-447643-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-do-i-run-dropeditor-java-eclipse-bat/447643.rss">How do I Run DropEditor.java? (Eclipse/.bat)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>How do I Run DropEditor.java? (Eclipse/.bat)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@USKO USKO]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/usko">@USKO</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I’ve heard I need Eclipse, but I have no idea how to use it and it only seems to open the file, not run it. I have a .bat I’m using to run it but it apparently can’t find it (or more likely can’t load it).</p>
<p>run.bat</p>
<p><code>@echo off
title rundropeditor
"C:/Program Files/Java/jre7/bin/java.exe" -Xmx815m -cp bin;lib/*; com.rs.tools.DropEditor true true false
pause </code><br>
I’ve been changing it around trying to figure out why it can’t find/load it, no luck. I’ve put it right next to the file (and removed ‘com.rs.tools.’) and it didn’t work.</p>
<p>Error</p>
<p><code>Error: Could not find or load main class com.rs.tools.DropEditor
Press any key to continue . . .</code></p>
<p>I don’t get it, how do I run it lol? I’ve directly opened the file with Eclipse and Java, but it doesn’t do anything (except Eclipse let’s me edit the file…). I’ve opened it with Eclipse and pressed the run button, but nothing happens. I’ve downloaded multiple sources to make sure it wasn’t a broken file or something, but it’s the same thing. I must be doing something wrong, but I don’t know what.</p>
<p>Even little hints help, so please tell. I would like to get back to funner things, this is being rather annoying and I won’t move on until it’s fixed. I put a lot of work into this and was going to save drops for last, but I wanted to remove them and noticed I couldn’t.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-do-i-run-dropeditor-java-eclipse-bat/447643/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-do-i-run-dropeditor-java-eclipse-bat/447643/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 01 Jul 2012 03:26:19 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-447643-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-do-i-run-dropeditor-java-eclipse-bat/447643.rss">How do I Run DropEditor.java? (Eclipse/.bat)</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
