<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Hyperion #612</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/hyperion-612/363044</link>
    <description>So, after seeing the lack of effort put into #612 servers, I have taken the liberty of creating the first, SUPERIOR, #612 Server. The base, was released by whom ever made RevengeScape, so credits to the owner. Anyways, the server folder map, has been rearranged and cleaned up by yours truly. This will problay be released, since I don&#39;t have the time to host it, I just like to download these and review the code. I felt that if you are going to be downloading a source, you should problay have some basic backround on coding the source. So, if and when I release the server, (I problay will..), there will be a guide on how you can easily code this server. Current features are just some things I decided to throw together, which I will edit problay this weekend..

Feature(s):
-GrandExchange
I realize, some faggot on Google, decided to release a guide on how to edit this, so me adding this into the server &#39;perfected&#39;, was just a waste of time. Basically, there are no bugs, except the little hourglass which states that the item you are buying and/or selling, the price is outdated or out of range, I couldn&#39;t figure out what JaGex was trying to do by this.. Anyways, it comes equipped with FULL item searching, with all current RuneScape item PRICES, up-to-date. Also, you can sell in bulk. YOU CANNOT, buy from your self, and you also cannot buy from the same IP Address; (stops from transferring items). You can also, right click the box in which you item is selling, or buying, and click &#39;abort offer&#39; and you will get your item or money back, depending on the action you are trying to attempt. When you abort an offer, if the item is in bulk (+1), than the items will be in NOTE form, rather than filling your inventory. 

-Player Vs. Player
This is something I will problay perfect later on, but as of now it is VERY, basic. Like real RuneScape, you can activate the combat prayers, I belive they are called? You can aswell do that in this server. Food, Specials when I got bored, ETC, have all been added. So other than the face that PVP is everywhere, I would call it perfect. Combat is problay as good as it&#39;s going to get, I want you guys to have something too work with..

-Skills
Woodcutting:
So far, all axes work on every tree through out RuneScape. I&#39;m aiming to make every skill &#39;Flawless, so I&#39;m problay going to add the random event, &#39;spirit tree&#39;, as well as the bird nest randomly being added into your inventory. So as of now, every axe + Inferno Adze, works 100%, just need to finish up some last bits of code and it should be all set.

Thieving:
I just started this, but PickPocketing is perfect. Times in between thieving, and you can fail; meaning, that the man will turn to you, punch you and stun you, and the forcechat will say, &quot;Hey, What do you think you&#39;re doing?!&quot;. Sometimes, they will go into combat with you, depending on your combat level.

RuneCrafting
All altars work, as well as using the talisman to direct you towards the altar. You do need, either a Tiara or an Talisman to enter the Altar area, and you do need Rune essence to make the Rune you are trying to make.

Combat:
/*To be written..

All other skills:
/*To be written..

Other:
Private Chat:
I have everything down, to where you can change the color of your private chat text, as in advance option selections. For some reason I&#39;m still trying to get to the bottom of, I cannot get the other player to RECEIVE any of the messages, but it does tell me that the message is sending.

Media:
Player Banking: http://s661.photobucket.com/albums/uu331/deathlyags/?action=view&amp;current=Banking.mp4&amp;newest=1
Player GrandEXchange: 

Additional Media:
[IMG]http://i661.photobucket.com/albums/uu331/deathlyags/Capture_135.jpg[/img]

[IMG]http://i661.photobucket.com/albums/uu331/deathlyags/Capture_134.jpg[/img]

[IMG]http://i661.photobucket.com/albums/uu331/deathlyags/Capture_133.jpg[/img]

[IMG]http://i661.photobucket.com/albums/uu331/deathlyags/Capture_132.jpg[/img]

[IMG]http://i661.photobucket.com/albums/uu331/deathlyags/Capture_131.jpg[/img]

[IMG]http://i661.photobucket.com/albums/uu331/deathlyags/614-WeaponReq.jpg[/img]</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 07 Oct 2010 17:29:36 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/hyperion-612/363044.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Hyperion #612</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Phaze_One Fuscate]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/phaze_one">@Phaze_One</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote no-group" data-post="3" data-topic="363044">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/d.ducky911/40/5_513041d5f7104045db30895d3b90af16.png" class="avatar"> D.Ducky911:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>You can name the server what ever you want, I chose Hyperion. Your pathetic, Revengescape is a 612/613/614? God, I hate Moparscape kids.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Moparscape kids? Shut the fuck up. Go back to wherever you came from.</p>
<p>‘Hyperion’ is a multi-revision framework base server which was developed by Graham. As you plainly stated, this is ‘RevengeScape’ (whatever that is). I would recommend that you do not call your project Hyperion as that is misleading.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/hyperion-612/363044/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/hyperion-612/363044/5</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 07 Oct 2010 17:29:36 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-363044-5</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/hyperion-612/363044.rss">Hyperion #612</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Hyperion #612</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@D_D_3 D D 3]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/d_d_3">@D_D_3</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote no-group" data-post="3" data-topic="363044">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/d.ducky911/40/5_513041d5f7104045db30895d3b90af16.png" class="avatar"> D.Ducky911:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>You can name the server what ever you want, I chose Hyperion. Your pathetic, Revengescape is a 612/613/614? God, I hate Moparscape kids.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Lol your a fucking moron your going to name the server Hyperion when Hyperion is a base name? That’s like calling my server Project Czar 612, and the server is a 613/614.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/hyperion-612/363044/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/hyperion-612/363044/4</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 06 Oct 2010 00:41:49 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-363044-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/hyperion-612/363044.rss">Hyperion #612</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Hyperion #612</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@D.Ducky911 D.Ducky911]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/d.ducky911">@D.Ducky911</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>You can name the server what ever you want, I chose Hyperion. Your pathetic, Revengescape is a 612/613/614? God, I hate Moparscape kids.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/hyperion-612/363044/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/hyperion-612/363044/3</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 06 Oct 2010 00:32:01 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-363044-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/hyperion-612/363044.rss">Hyperion #612</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Hyperion #612</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Pure_Slay Pure Slay]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/pure_slay">@Pure_Slay</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Reasons why this is going to fail:</p>
<ol>
<li>You don’t realize that the source is 613/614</li>
<li>You don’t realize that everything you have stated has already been released</li>
<li>Its not Hyperion idiot…rofl</li>
</ol>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/hyperion-612/363044/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/hyperion-612/363044/2</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 06 Oct 2010 00:14:09 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-363044-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/hyperion-612/363044.rss">Hyperion #612</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Hyperion #612</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@D.Ducky911 D.Ducky911]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/d.ducky911">@D.Ducky911</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>So, after seeing the lack of effort put into <span class="hashtag">#612</span> servers, I have taken the liberty of creating the first, SUPERIOR, <span class="hashtag">#612</span> Server. The base, was released by whom ever made RevengeScape, so credits to the owner. Anyways, the server folder map, has been rearranged and cleaned up by yours truly. This will problay be released, since I don’t have the time to host it, I just like to download these and review the code. I felt that if you are going to be downloading a source, you should problay have some basic backround on coding the source. So, if and when I release the server, (I problay will…), there will be a guide on how you can easily code this server. Current features are just some things I decided to throw together, which I will edit problay this weekend…</p>
<p>Feature(s):<br>
-GrandExchange<br>
I realize, some faggot on Google, decided to release a guide on how to edit this, so me adding this into the server ‘perfected’, was just a waste of time. Basically, there are no bugs, except the little hourglass which states that the item you are buying and/or selling, the price is outdated or out of range, I couldn’t figure out what JaGex was trying to do by this… Anyways, it comes equipped with FULL item searching, with all current RuneScape item PRICES, up-to-date. Also, you can sell in bulk. YOU CANNOT, buy from your self, and you also cannot buy from the same IP Address; (stops from transferring items). You can also, right click the box in which you item is selling, or buying, and click ‘abort offer’ and you will get your item or money back, depending on the action you are trying to attempt. When you abort an offer, if the item is in bulk (+1), than the items will be in NOTE form, rather than filling your inventory.</p>
<p>-Player Vs. Player<br>
This is something I will problay perfect later on, but as of now it is VERY, basic. Like real RuneScape, you can activate the combat prayers, I belive they are called? You can aswell do that in this server. Food, Specials when I got bored, ETC, have all been added. So other than the face that PVP is everywhere, I would call it perfect. Combat is problay as good as it’s going to get, I want you guys to have something too work with…</p>
<p>-Skills<br>
Woodcutting:<br>
So far, all axes work on every tree through out RuneScape. I’m aiming to make every skill 'Flawless, so I’m problay going to add the random event, ‘spirit tree’, as well as the bird nest randomly being added into your inventory. So as of now, every axe + Inferno Adze, works 100%, just need to finish up some last bits of code and it should be all set.</p>
<p>Thieving:<br>
I just started this, but PickPocketing is perfect. Times in between thieving, and you can fail; meaning, that the man will turn to you, punch you and stun you, and the forcechat will say, “Hey, What do you think you’re doing?!”. Sometimes, they will go into combat with you, depending on your combat level.</p>
<p>RuneCrafting<br>
All altars work, as well as using the talisman to direct you towards the altar. You do need, either a Tiara or an Talisman to enter the Altar area, and you do need Rune essence to make the Rune you are trying to make.</p>
<p>Combat:<br>
/*To be written…</p>
<p>All other skills:<br>
/*To be written…</p>
<p>Other:<br>
Private Chat:<br>
I have everything down, to where you can change the color of your private chat text, as in advance option selections. For some reason I’m still trying to get to the bottom of, I cannot get the other player to RECEIVE any of the messages, but it does tell me that the message is sending.</p>
<p>Media:<br>
Player Banking: <a href="http://s661.photobucket.com/albums/uu331/deathlyags/?action=view&amp;current=Banking.mp4&amp;newest=1" rel="nofollow noopener">http://s661.photobucket.com/albums/uu331/deathlyags/?action=view&amp;current=Banking.mp4&amp;newest=1</a><br>
Player GrandEXchange:</p>
<p>Additional Media:<br>
<img src="http://i661.photobucket.com/albums/uu331/deathlyags/Capture_135.jpg" alt width="" height=""></p>
<p><img src="http://i661.photobucket.com/albums/uu331/deathlyags/Capture_134.jpg" alt width="" height=""></p>
<p><img src="http://i661.photobucket.com/albums/uu331/deathlyags/Capture_133.jpg" alt width="" height=""></p>
<p><img src="http://i661.photobucket.com/albums/uu331/deathlyags/Capture_132.jpg" alt width="" height=""></p>
<p><img src="http://i661.photobucket.com/albums/uu331/deathlyags/Capture_131.jpg" alt width="" height=""></p>
<p><img src="http://i661.photobucket.com/albums/uu331/deathlyags/614-WeaponReq.jpg" alt width="" height=""></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/hyperion-612/363044/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/hyperion-612/363044/1</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 06 Oct 2010 00:06:05 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-363044-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/hyperion-612/363044.rss">Hyperion #612</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
