<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Please help! need help putting server online</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/please-help-need-help-putting-server-online/369498</link>
    <description>Hey guys.. I need some help with putting my server online. I did every single frigen thing in the book and for some reason its not going up. I use this site called cpsv.. I have the no-ip DUC and I have my server name checked. I have the server running its in green letters saying your server is online! and all that what the hell am i doing wrong I even port fowarded so i have no idea. I put the utorrent to 43594 and im using a 43594 client and it doesnt let me in. like when i type the ip in it says error connecting to server but then when i type no server in it lets me in. if anyone has Team viewer or whatever Plz comment and fix this cuz my server is beast im makig co owner and admins to ppl that help</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 20 Nov 2010 14:50:26 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/please-help-need-help-putting-server-online/369498.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Please help! need help putting server online</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@usman555 usman555]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/usman555">@usman555</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Make sure your client connects to your server. When you set no server ip, it’s basically 127.0.0.1 (localhost) localhost is how the owner logs in. The players login from your server’s ip. If your players can’t get in, you portforwarded wrong.</p>
<p>However, I don’t know your client’s name. So I can’t help you change IP.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/please-help-need-help-putting-server-online/369498/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/please-help-need-help-putting-server-online/369498/2</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 20 Nov 2010 14:50:26 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-369498-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/please-help-need-help-putting-server-online/369498.rss">Please help! need help putting server online</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Please help! need help putting server online</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@runyluny runyluny]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/runyluny">@runyluny</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Hey guys… I need some help with putting my server online. I did every single frigen thing in the book and for some reason its not going up. I use this site called cpsv… I have the no-ip DUC and I have my server name checked. I have the server running its in green letters saying your server is online! and all that what the hell am i doing wrong I even port fowarded so i have no idea. I put the utorrent to 43594 and im using a 43594 client and it doesnt let me in. like when i type the ip in it says error connecting to server but then when i type no server in it lets me in. if anyone has Team viewer or whatever Plz comment and fix this cuz my server is beast im makig co owner and admins to ppl that help</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/please-help-need-help-putting-server-online/369498/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/please-help-need-help-putting-server-online/369498/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 20 Nov 2010 13:57:44 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-369498-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/please-help-need-help-putting-server-online/369498.rss">Please help! need help putting server online</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
