<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Left 4 Tread (Name is subject to be chagned :D)</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/left-4-tread-name-is-subject-to-be-chagned-d/309917</link>
    <description>I&#39;m starting a project called &quot;Left 4 Tread&quot;. This project, if you haven&#39;t already guessed, is a Undead based game. You spawn in an area where portals take you to different areas which you fight mostly undead and disease/poison based npcs. I have most of the coordinates and once i finish those off i&#39;m starting to code.
Im looking for 1 or 2 people who have BASIC+ KNOWLEDGE OF JAVA. I am going to be working on this every moment i have time for and i expect the feeling to be mutual. If you need me to post pictures, you can cry in the corner. I suppose every great recruitment thread needs an application form right? I know this is pretty broad, don&#39;t attack me for it. if you ask, I&#39;ll answer. This is for a community called Tread Marks, that I own. 

experience :
Age ( i wont discriminate ):
How active are you? :
Do you have steam? :
Why do you want to join? (Ever good thread needs this question right?) :

Ask and you may receive.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 21 Oct 2009 21:30:31 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/left-4-tread-name-is-subject-to-be-chagned-d/309917.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Left 4 Tread (Name is subject to be chagned :D)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Uberkist Uberkist]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/uberkist">@Uberkist</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I’m starting a project called “Left 4 Tread”. This project, if you haven’t already guessed, is a Undead based game. You spawn in an area where portals take you to different areas which you fight mostly undead and disease/poison based npcs. I have most of the coordinates and once i finish those off i’m starting to code.<br>
Im looking for 1 or 2 people who have BASIC+ KNOWLEDGE OF JAVA. I am going to be working on this every moment i have time for and i expect the feeling to be mutual. If you need me to post pictures, you can cry in the corner. I suppose every great recruitment thread needs an application form right? I know this is pretty broad, don’t attack me for it. if you ask, I’ll answer. This is for a community called Tread Marks, that I own.</p>
<p>experience :<br>
Age ( i wont discriminate ):<br>
How active are you? :<br>
Do you have steam? :<br>
Why do you want to join? (Ever good thread needs this question right?) :</p>
<p>Ask and you may receive.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/left-4-tread-name-is-subject-to-be-chagned-d/309917/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/left-4-tread-name-is-subject-to-be-chagned-d/309917/1</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 21 Oct 2009 21:30:31 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-309917-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/left-4-tread-name-is-subject-to-be-chagned-d/309917.rss">Left 4 Tread (Name is subject to be chagned :D)</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
