<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Paying For Webclient - All Info Here</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/paying-for-webclient-all-info-here/362374</link>
    <description>You don&#39;t need to read this story if you don&#39;t want to, I recommend it but if you want, skip down to the bottom for a summary.

I am in need of a webclient. I&#39;m not really a noob, I&#39;m just really lazy. I tried configuring my client to download the cache and run from it for about 3 hours now, and I&#39;m not wasting any more of my time on it. I really need one.

I&#39;m the owner of ForeverPkers which was a pretty big (100+ players) game, and I&#39;m starting from scratch using a Project Insanity source. The client has Chaotic weapons and all that jazz, so I can&#39;t just use the default Project Insanity webclient.

The download for my client is on my website,
[url=http://www.ForeverPkers.com/download.zip]http://www.ForeverPkers.com/download.zip[/url]
I&#39;d tell you the IP and port, but I don&#39;t want you to go and make a new webclient from an existing one, I want it made from my client.

I&#39;d like the cache to be in C:/ForeverPkers_cache.


I&#39;ll pay you with PayPal, and I&#39;m offering 10$ for the work.

My MSN is [email]ForeverPkers@live.com[/email].

Check my website ForeverPkers.com and here&#39;s a pic of my old success, to show you can trust me sending you money &gt;.&gt; There are a lot of scammers here.

[IMG]http://www.Foreverpkers.com/foreverpkers.png[/img]


Summary:

Client: [url=http://www.foreverpkers.com/download.zip]http://www.foreverpkers.com/download.zip[/url]
Java Files for Client: [url=http://www.foreverpkers.com/files.zip]http://www.foreverpkers.com/files.zip[/url]
Where I want the cache: C:/ForeverPkers_cache
Port and IP are in my client, I want it made from that.
My MSN for contact: [email]ForeverPkers@live.com[/email]
Payment: 10$ PayPal, please refer to above
Files I am requesting: client.jar (after you jar the webclient, so I can test it), cache.zip (With MY cache in it), Client Files in a folder and open source.
I&#39;d also appreciate if you would first CONNECT to my game and make sure everything looks good with your .jar, so it&#39;s not all null items like my attempt.

Thank you, thank you, thank you for whoever can do this for me.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 01 Oct 2010 01:19:30 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Game Development</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/paying-for-webclient-all-info-here/362374.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Paying For Webclient - All Info Here</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@fpkers fpkers]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/fpkers">@fpkers</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>You don’t need to read this story if you don’t want to, I recommend it but if you want, skip down to the bottom for a summary.</p>
<p>I am in need of a webclient. I’m not really a noob, I’m just really lazy. I tried configuring my client to download the cache and run from it for about 3 hours now, and I’m not wasting any more of my time on it. I really need one.</p>
<p>I’m the owner of ForeverPkers which was a pretty big (100+ players) game, and I’m starting from scratch using a Project Insanity source. The client has Chaotic weapons and all that jazz, so I can’t just use the default Project Insanity webclient.</p>
<p>The download for my client is on my website,<br>
<a href="http://www.ForeverPkers.com/download.zip" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">http://www.ForeverPkers.com/download.zip</a><br>
I’d tell you the IP and port, but I don’t want you to go and make a new webclient from an existing one, I want it made from my client.</p>
<p>I’d like the cache to be in C:/ForeverPkers_cache.</p>
<p>I’ll pay you with PayPal, and I’m offering 10$ for the work.</p>
<p>My MSN is <a href="mailto:ForeverPkers@live.com" data-bbcode="true">ForeverPkers@live.com</a>.</p>
<p>Check my website <a href="http://ForeverPkers.com" rel="nofollow noopener">ForeverPkers.com</a> and here’s a pic of my old success, to show you can trust me sending you money &gt;.&gt; There are a lot of scammers here.</p>
<p><img src="http://www.Foreverpkers.com/foreverpkers.png" alt width="" height=""></p>
<p>Summary:</p>
<p>Client: <a href="http://www.foreverpkers.com/download.zip" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">http://www.foreverpkers.com/download.zip</a><br>
Java Files for Client: <a href="http://www.foreverpkers.com/files.zip" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">http://www.foreverpkers.com/files.zip</a><br>
Where I want the cache: C:/ForeverPkers_cache<br>
Port and IP are in my client, I want it made from that.<br>
My MSN for contact: <a href="mailto:ForeverPkers@live.com" data-bbcode="true">ForeverPkers@live.com</a><br>
Payment: 10$ PayPal, please refer to above<br>
Files I am requesting: client.jar (after you jar the webclient, so I can test it), cache.zip (With MY cache in it), Client Files in a folder and open source.<br>
I’d also appreciate if you would first CONNECT to my game and make sure everything looks good with your .jar, so it’s not all null items like my attempt.</p>
<p>Thank you, thank you, thank you for whoever can do this for me.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/paying-for-webclient-all-info-here/362374/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/paying-for-webclient-all-info-here/362374/1</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Oct 2010 01:19:30 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-362374-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/paying-for-webclient-all-info-here/362374.rss">Paying For Webclient - All Info Here</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
