<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>On the Doll (2007)</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/on-the-doll-2007/297320</link>
    <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;On the Doll (2008) is a very dark and intense dramatic feature film directed and written by acclaimed music video director Thomas Mignone, who has directed award-winning videos for artists such as Mudvayne[1], Slipknot[2], System Of A Down, Megadeth, Danzig, Sepultura[3], Otep, American Head Charge, Cradle Of Filth, Toadies, and others. The film&#39;s title comes from the phrase &quot;Show me on the doll where you were touched&quot;, often asked of young children who have been the victims of sexual abuse. &quot;On The Doll&quot; had a limited theatrical release in the United States, as well as a continuously growing popularity upon its DVD and online release due to several unexpected and highly graphic scenes.&lt;/blockquote&gt;

Oh my god. Best movie I&#39;ve seen in such a long time. It basically has a few story plots for several groups of people, and there is a slight connection to each of these groups. As it keeps switching between the plots you see how they are all connected the more you watch. This movie really makes you think, and leaves you with food for thought. 

On the doll is [b]fucked[/b] up. It&#39;s too hard to explain the plot. But it involves a lot of people working in the sex industry, and people who were abused as children. I strongly suggest this movie to anyone who likes &quot;different&quot; or &quot;dark&quot; movies. It truly is interesting.

Find a torrent on thepiratebay. It doesn&#39;t seem to popular though and the best torrent i could find only had 7 seeds but it downloaded quickly. 


Spoiler: If you want to watch 2 underaged girls chop off their teachers balls, this movie is for you.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 24 Aug 2009 21:16:47 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>General Discussion</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/on-the-doll-2007/297320.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>On the Doll (2007)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@goatee goatee]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/goatee">@goatee</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Pirate Bay is blocked for me now :’(.</p>
<p>Sounds interesting though, like the fact that it’s by a music video director.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/on-the-doll-2007/297320/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/on-the-doll-2007/297320/2</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 24 Aug 2009 21:16:47 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-297320-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/on-the-doll-2007/297320.rss">On the Doll (2007)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>On the Doll (2007)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@jme jme]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/jme">@jme</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <blockquote>On the Doll (2008) is a very dark and intense dramatic feature film directed and written by acclaimed music video director Thomas Mignone, who has directed award-winning videos for artists such as Mudvayne[1], Slipknot[2], System Of A Down, Megadeth, Danzig, Sepultura[3], Otep, American Head Charge, Cradle Of Filth, Toadies, and others. The film's title comes from the phrase "Show me on the doll where you were touched", often asked of young children who have been the victims of sexual abuse. "On The Doll" had a limited theatrical release in the United States, as well as a continuously growing popularity upon its DVD and online release due to several unexpected and highly graphic scenes.</blockquote>
<p>Oh my god. Best movie I’ve seen in such a long time. It basically has a few story plots for several groups of people, and there is a slight connection to each of these groups. As it keeps switching between the plots you see how they are all connected the more you watch. This movie really makes you think, and leaves you with food for thought.</p>
<p>On the doll is <span class="bbcode-b">fucked</span> up. It’s too hard to explain the plot. But it involves a lot of people working in the sex industry, and people who were abused as children. I strongly suggest this movie to anyone who likes “different” or “dark” movies. It truly is interesting.</p>
<p>Find a torrent on thepiratebay. It doesn’t seem to popular though and the best torrent i could find only had 7 seeds but it downloaded quickly.</p>
<p>Spoiler: If you want to watch 2 underaged girls chop off their teachers balls, this movie is for you.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/on-the-doll-2007/297320/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/on-the-doll-2007/297320/1</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 24 Aug 2009 03:28:41 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-297320-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/on-the-doll-2007/297320.rss">On the Doll (2007)</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
