<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Help making chicken outfit equip to the right place</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/help-making-chicken-outfit-equip-to-the-right-place/141659</link>
    <description>I am working on my next release of my source and right now I am working on making the new items from Silabs client being able to work. I updated my Item.Java file and I noticed or thought that the chicken outfit wasn&#39;t in the item.java file. I added the feet and re-compiled the server then logged in (As you do) but I wasn&#39;t able to equip the chicken feet instead it did nothing.

I don&#39;t know whats gone wrong I am using ChaosScape (My Server Source) which is packed a little different to other servers. But I can&#39;t equip it and I am wondering if someone could help me out because I&#39;ve never needed to add new items to a server before.

Any help or ideas will be much appreciated.

-Cheers guys!</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 09 Sep 2007 14:49:07 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/help-making-chicken-outfit-equip-to-the-right-place/141659.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Help making chicken outfit equip to the right place</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@EwfsPrince EwfsPrince]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/ewfsprince">@EwfsPrince</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I am working on my next release of my source and right now I am working on making the new items from Silabs client being able to work. I updated my Item.Java file and I noticed or thought that the chicken outfit wasn’t in the item.java file. I added the feet and re-compiled the server then logged in (As you do) but I wasn’t able to equip the chicken feet instead it did nothing.</p>
<p>I don’t know whats gone wrong I am using ChaosScape (My Server Source) which is packed a little different to other servers. But I can’t equip it and I am wondering if someone could help me out because I’ve never needed to add new items to a server before.</p>
<p>Any help or ideas will be much appreciated.</p>
<p>-Cheers guys!</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/help-making-chicken-outfit-equip-to-the-right-place/141659/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/help-making-chicken-outfit-equip-to-the-right-place/141659/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 09 Sep 2007 14:49:07 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-141659-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/help-making-chicken-outfit-equip-to-the-right-place/141659.rss">Help making chicken outfit equip to the right place</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
