<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Moparscape client... I need help!</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/moparscape-client-i-need-help/219209</link>
    <description>Hi there. My name&#39;s Kristine and I&#39;ve been pking on runescape for over 5 years. And since they took away the wilderness as we knew it I have quit rs. Now, I know there are many many servers out there made for pking, but I use a macintosh computer and can&#39;t get Silabsoft to work anymore. I&quot;ve come back to good oldd mopar to see if anyone can help me. Does anyone know of a way to upload scrips to the mopar client on mac? Does anyone know a good private server that has it&#39;s own webclient or a client that works on mac? and finally. Does anyone know how to get silabsoft to work on macs again? I know many many mac users are having difficulty. Sorry if i had many typos english is my second language.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 11 Jul 2008 09:50:16 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/moparscape-client-i-need-help/219209.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Moparscape client... I need help!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@xoxkrstnxox xoxkrstnxox]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/xoxkrstnxox">@xoxkrstnxox</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Hi there. My name’s Kristine and I’ve been pking on runescape for over 5 years. And since they took away the wilderness as we knew it I have quit rs. Now, I know there are many many servers out there made for pking, but I use a macintosh computer and can’t get Silabsoft to work anymore. I"ve come back to good oldd mopar to see if anyone can help me. Does anyone know of a way to upload scrips to the mopar client on mac? Does anyone know a good private server that has it’s own webclient or a client that works on mac? and finally. Does anyone know how to get silabsoft to work on macs again? I know many many mac users are having difficulty. Sorry if i had many typos english is my second language.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/moparscape-client-i-need-help/219209/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/moparscape-client-i-need-help/219209/1</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 11 Jul 2008 09:50:16 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-219209-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/moparscape-client-i-need-help/219209.rss">Moparscape client... I need help!</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
