<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>[FIXED] Client/Server Broke?!</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/fixed-client-server-broke/382203</link>
    <description>
[b]LOL  :eek: sorry...an item corrupted my character or something.  :o 

It&#39;s all good now...thanks for no one helping me...but whatever this was up for like almost an hour at night, didn&#39;t expect an answer. Thanks for reading this I guess?[/b]  ;D :)


[s][b]Short story:[/b]
When I log in, it freezes. I tried everything I know to fix this. I redownloaded the client, but it still doesn&#39;t work. I redownloaded the cache, but it still doesn&#39;t work.

[b]Full story:[/b]
Please help. I&#39;m not sure what&#39;s wrong. I was just standing around on my PI server (it&#39;s not online or anything) looking for cool fish on a list on notepad. I added a few items using commands and their image appeared blank. I was wondering WTF was wrong at that point, but I was like whatever. Then, every other item I added thereon (like 5 items) had a blank icon, no drop model, and no wear model. So, I closed and reopened the client. The items were back to normal and everything. A little later (like 3 minutes) I added another item. Guess what...the icon was blank and everything. So, I did the same thing. I closed and reopened the client, but this time, it froze when I logged in. I then saw the error in the Client.bat. So, I thought it was just my cache. I had a backup of the cache when I first downloaded the client (downloaded like a week or so ago). So, I replaced the cache, but it still showed the error and it still froze on log in. So, I thought it was my client (that&#39;s my problem, client is freezing), so I replaced the client folder (I also had a backup of the client), but it still does the same thing every single time. I tried restarting my computer and everything. What do I do?? 

By the way, those green things are legs, and are always there when I first log in. The change clothes interface appears for a second when I first log in (not sure why). Now, my problem makes it last forever (frozen).

Also, I made a new character, and it logged me on, but it was SUPER LAGGY at first. I then relogged back in and it was fine, except that in the cmd it still says &quot;Error: T1 - 123,0 - 36,36&quot;. At least it doesn&#39;t freeze. I&#39;m starting to think an item broke me!

[img]http://img28.imageshack.us/img28/6717/wtfhelp.png[/img]
[code]
Operating System: Windows 7 6.1
ShadyScape - Client.
Revision: 317
Error: 11 - 123.0 - 36,36
Exception in thread &quot;Thread-6&quot; java.lang.ArrayIndexOutofBoundsExeption: 11797
                 at ItemDef.forID(ItemDef.java:196)
                 at ItemDef.getSprite(ItemDef.java:594)
                 at client.drawInterface(client.java:8307)
                 at client.drawTabArea(client.java:2174)
                 at client.drawGameScreen(client.java:8122)
                 at client.processDrawing{client.java:8885}
                 at RSApplet.run(RSApplet.java:94)
                 at client.run(client.java:5008)
                 at java.lang.Thread.run(Uknown Source)
[/code]

 :| :confused: :|
[/s]</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 12 Feb 2011 06:12:26 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Game Development</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/fixed-client-server-broke/382203.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>[FIXED] Client/Server Broke?!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@adamknightz adamknightz]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/adamknightz">@adamknightz</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[b]LOL  :eek: sorry…an item corrupted my character or something.  :o</p>
<p>It’s all good now…thanks for no one helping me…but whatever this was up for like almost an hour at night, didn’t expect an answer. Thanks for reading this I guess?[/b]  ;D <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=5" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
<p>[s]<span class="bbcode-b">Short story:</span><br>
When I log in, it freezes. I tried everything I know to fix this. I redownloaded the client, but it still doesn’t work. I redownloaded the cache, but it still doesn’t work.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Full story:</span><br>
Please help. I’m not sure what’s wrong. I was just standing around on my PI server (it’s not online or anything) looking for cool fish on a list on notepad. I added a few items using commands and their image appeared blank. I was wondering WTF was wrong at that point, but I was like whatever. Then, every other item I added thereon (like 5 items) had a blank icon, no drop model, and no wear model. So, I closed and reopened the client. The items were back to normal and everything. A little later (like 3 minutes) I added another item. Guess what…the icon was blank and everything. So, I did the same thing. I closed and reopened the client, but this time, it froze when I logged in. I then saw the error in the Client.bat. So, I thought it was just my cache. I had a backup of the cache when I first downloaded the client (downloaded like a week or so ago). So, I replaced the cache, but it still showed the error and it still froze on log in. So, I thought it was my client (that’s my problem, client is freezing), so I replaced the client folder (I also had a backup of the client), but it still does the same thing every single time. I tried restarting my computer and everything. What do I do??</p>
<p>By the way, those green things are legs, and are always there when I first log in. The change clothes interface appears for a second when I first log in (not sure why). Now, my problem makes it last forever (frozen).</p>
<p>Also, I made a new character, and it logged me on, but it was SUPER LAGGY at first. I then relogged back in and it was fine, except that in the cmd it still says “Error: T1 - 123,0 - 36,36”. At least it doesn’t freeze. I’m starting to think an item broke me!</p>
<p><img src="http://img28.imageshack.us/img28/6717/wtfhelp.png" alt width="" height=""></p>
<pre><code class="lang-auto">Operating System: Windows 7 6.1
ShadyScape - Client.
Revision: 317
Error: 11 - 123.0 - 36,36
Exception in thread "Thread-6" java.lang.ArrayIndexOutofBoundsExeption: 11797
                 at ItemDef.forID(ItemDef.java:196)
                 at ItemDef.getSprite(ItemDef.java:594)
                 at client.drawInterface(client.java:8307)
                 at client.drawTabArea(client.java:2174)
                 at client.drawGameScreen(client.java:8122)
                 at client.processDrawing{client.java:8885}
                 at RSApplet.run(RSApplet.java:94)
                 at client.run(client.java:5008)
                 at java.lang.Thread.run(Uknown Source)</code></pre>
<p><img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/expressionless.png?v=5" title=":expressionless:" class="emoji" alt=":expressionless:"> <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/confused.png?v=5" title=":confused:" class="emoji" alt=":confused:"> <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/expressionless.png?v=5" title=":expressionless:" class="emoji" alt=":expressionless:"><br>
[/s]</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/fixed-client-server-broke/382203/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/fixed-client-server-broke/382203/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 12 Feb 2011 06:12:26 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-382203-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/fixed-client-server-broke/382203.rss">[FIXED] Client/Server Broke?!</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
