<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>667 Matrix Base RockCrab Wont Respawn!</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/667-matrix-base-rockcrab-wont-respawn/450275</link>
    <description>Hey everyone!

Well all i hear on 667 tutorials is the word &quot;leech&quot;! However, I am not going to publish this I am just using it so i can learn how to code 667s and maybe make my own one day.

Anyway, iv added loads of things like the Armadyl Boss, Zamarok Boss. Iv fixed the trade glitch and the duel arena mess! 

But when I tried to move on to the next part, which was adding rock crabs to train on. When I spanwed them and attacked them, they didn&#39;t respawn. I spawned them through NPC Spawning but is it something to do with Combat Definitions?? I dont know im new to 667. Iv tried everything to try and get it to work I just can&#39;t see the light at the end of the tunnel. I tried everything and have gotten loads of errors. Iv even tied to make it a custom npc which didn&#39;t work out. Please help!

Anyway, I really need help with this.

Thanks,

Jack</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 19 Jul 2012 11:17:49 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/667-matrix-base-rockcrab-wont-respawn/450275.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>667 Matrix Base RockCrab Wont Respawn!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@jackabe jackabe]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/jackabe">@jackabe</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Hey everyone!</p>
<p>Well all i hear on 667 tutorials is the word “leech”! However, I am not going to publish this I am just using it so i can learn how to code 667s and maybe make my own one day.</p>
<p>Anyway, iv added loads of things like the Armadyl Boss, Zamarok Boss. Iv fixed the trade glitch and the duel arena mess!</p>
<p>But when I tried to move on to the next part, which was adding rock crabs to train on. When I spanwed them and attacked them, they didn’t respawn. I spawned them through NPC Spawning but is it something to do with Combat Definitions?? I dont know im new to 667. Iv tried everything to try and get it to work I just can’t see the light at the end of the tunnel. I tried everything and have gotten loads of errors. Iv even tied to make it a custom npc which didn’t work out. Please help!</p>
<p>Anyway, I really need help with this.</p>
<p>Thanks,</p>
<p>Jack</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/667-matrix-base-rockcrab-wont-respawn/450275/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/667-matrix-base-rockcrab-wont-respawn/450275/1</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jul 2012 11:17:49 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-450275-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/667-matrix-base-rockcrab-wont-respawn/450275.rss">667 Matrix Base RockCrab Wont Respawn!</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
