<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Welcome to the RSC section....I mean...Moparcraft!</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/welcome-to-the-rsc-section-i-mean-moparcraft/447707</link>
    <description>I think the title is pretty self-explanatory, for those of you who aren&#39;t aware, the RSC section is a drama entailed mess where any member of staff who does their job gets given a hard time, and told to fuck off by an angry mob. I think we&#39;re heading down the same route, right now we have a plethora of arguments popping up which somehow involve me without having anything to do with them.

Generally, issues such as: Such a person removed my post, censorship, somebody banned me for no reason, the staff aren&#39;t doing there job, the playerbase are idiots, the server is laggy.

I&#39;m sick to death of seeing the same thing, over and over again, on every single topic or on a new one. I want to outline a better forum moderation plan because right now it&#39;s just a case of &#39;do your job on the forums, get a topic posted about you&#39; I tell you now, this shit wouldn&#39;t be tolerated on _any_ other Mopar community by _anybody_ and I don&#39;t intend for this community to turn into a glorified RSC section, either. I want to continue to promote growth as a community as well. 

Radical or not. What do you think the general moderation of the forum should be like?

I&#39;d also like to introduce a new sub-rank that has been added, Moparcraft forum moderator, generally, it&#39;s the same badge except you have forum abilities, you can remove posts, modify posts, remove topics, move topics and so on. 

If you&#39;d like to moderate the forum then please post here stating so, obviously we don&#39;t really need everyone to moderate the forum as some of you are best suited ingame, and due to timezone constrictions. Generally we just want to balance it out timezone wise.

Generally, we want to smooth the community, and make the environment where people can get a long. This has been dealt with ingame, but not on the forums.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 02 Jul 2012 23:00:08 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Games</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/welcome-to-the-rsc-section-i-mean-moparcraft/447707.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Welcome to the RSC section....I mean...Moparcraft!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@si_force Si Force]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/si_force">@si_force</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I would apply for moderating here, but I already can, so yeah.</p>
<p><span class="mention">@topic</span> If a topic regarding a specific member is made, and the intentions of the poster is to give out (for lack of a better term), then I believe the topic should be locked and the issue to be taken to the PM system/IRC. There’s no real reason why anybody should get the community involved since it just stirs the forums up, buddys help buddys and subsequently a flame war may ensue. That’s what I do on Moparscape anyway, i’m never quick enough to the scene here.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/welcome-to-the-rsc-section-i-mean-moparcraft/447707/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/welcome-to-the-rsc-section-i-mean-moparcraft/447707/4</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 02 Jul 2012 23:00:08 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-447707-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/welcome-to-the-rsc-section-i-mean-moparcraft/447707.rss">Welcome to the RSC section....I mean...Moparcraft!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Welcome to the RSC section....I mean...Moparcraft!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Tom Tom]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/tom">@Tom</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Thanks for volunteering, you now have forum abilities <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=5" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/welcome-to-the-rsc-section-i-mean-moparcraft/447707/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/welcome-to-the-rsc-section-i-mean-moparcraft/447707/3</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 02 Jul 2012 19:20:07 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-447707-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/welcome-to-the-rsc-section-i-mean-moparcraft/447707.rss">Welcome to the RSC section....I mean...Moparcraft!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Welcome to the RSC section....I mean...Moparcraft!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Phaze_One Fuscate]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/phaze_one">@Phaze_One</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I would be happy to do so, the current wave of rubbish flowing from a number of the players (Agl specifically) needs more than a couple of people to moderate. In terms of timezones i’m around 8 hours ahead of the UK and about 12 hours infront of the US, so if need be I can set a balance around that time.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/welcome-to-the-rsc-section-i-mean-moparcraft/447707/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/welcome-to-the-rsc-section-i-mean-moparcraft/447707/2</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 02 Jul 2012 08:54:11 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-447707-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/welcome-to-the-rsc-section-i-mean-moparcraft/447707.rss">Welcome to the RSC section....I mean...Moparcraft!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Welcome to the RSC section....I mean...Moparcraft!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Tom Tom]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/tom">@Tom</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I think the title is pretty self-explanatory, for those of you who aren’t aware, the RSC section is a drama entailed mess where any member of staff who does their job gets given a hard time, and told to fuck off by an angry mob. I think we’re heading down the same route, right now we have a plethora of arguments popping up which somehow involve me without having anything to do with them.</p>
<p>Generally, issues such as: Such a person removed my post, censorship, somebody banned me for no reason, the staff aren’t doing there job, the playerbase are idiots, the server is laggy.</p>
<p>I’m sick to death of seeing the same thing, over and over again, on every single topic or on a new one. I want to outline a better forum moderation plan because right now it’s just a case of ‘do your job on the forums, get a topic posted about you’ I tell you now, this shit wouldn’t be tolerated on <em>any</em> other Mopar community by <em>anybody</em> and I don’t intend for this community to turn into a glorified RSC section, either. I want to continue to promote growth as a community as well.</p>
<p>Radical or not. What do you think the general moderation of the forum should be like?</p>
<p>I’d also like to introduce a new sub-rank that has been added, Moparcraft forum moderator, generally, it’s the same badge except you have forum abilities, you can remove posts, modify posts, remove topics, move topics and so on.</p>
<p>If you’d like to moderate the forum then please post here stating so, obviously we don’t really need everyone to moderate the forum as some of you are best suited ingame, and due to timezone constrictions. Generally we just want to balance it out timezone wise.</p>
<p>Generally, we want to smooth the community, and make the environment where people can get a long. This has been dealt with ingame, but not on the forums.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/welcome-to-the-rsc-section-i-mean-moparcraft/447707/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/welcome-to-the-rsc-section-i-mean-moparcraft/447707/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 01 Jul 2012 18:05:50 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-447707-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/welcome-to-the-rsc-section-i-mean-moparcraft/447707.rss">Welcome to the RSC section....I mean...Moparcraft!</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
