<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>** BloodFire-RS **</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/bloodfire-rs/309849</link>
    <description>[center][size=15pt]Hello Mopar![/size][/center]

[center]I&#39;m Crusix, from Bloodfire-wow. We have decided, to also make a Runescape private server. Bloodfire is an extremely huge private server company, with over 250 staff so far. We are now looking for the coders for a Runescape private server. I will be the leader for the RS server, and I&#39;m looking for staff.[/center]

[center]Current Staff Positions:
[b] Head Developer 
Three Java Coders
Head Web Designer
Three Web Designers
Assistant Manager
Five Moderators
Ten Beta Testers
[/b][/center]

[center]To apply for staff, here are the requirements for each different position:
[b]Java Coder[/b]; Need at least one year experience, high dedication, and a minimum age of 16.
[b]Head Developer[/b]; Need at least three years in experience, have previous work sites ready to show. Need to heavily know Java and other languages can help you get this position. Need to be at least 18 years of age.
[b]Web Designer[/b]; Need to understand at least two of the following, PHP, CSS, HTML, XHTML. Need to be atleast 15 years of age, have following projects ready to show. 
[b]Head Web Designer[/b]; Need to understand PHP, CSS, MySQL, HTML, XHTML. Need to be atleast 18 years of age, and understand all the above and flash design.
[b]Assistant Manager[/b]: This job will pretty much be my assistant, which you will make sure everything is going well and keeping stuff organized. Requirements for this job are; Need to be extremely organized. Able to keep up with the community, which will consist of thousands of people. Need to be very mature and a minimum age of 15.[/center]

[center]If your one of the best developers around here, why should you apply? Well, you should apply because first of all, this isn&#39;t a joke. You will be payed, each month. How much will you be payed? It just depends how much is done. We&#39;re not looking for people that just want some cash, I want people who are dedicated to coding Runescape servers, and have a lot of experience with them. Why start with so many staff? If you knew how much work is being done with the World of Warcraft server, you would know. We are under constant development there, and it needs to be the same way for the Runescape server. We need about 25-40 staff to start for this project, and need them now. So if you are looking to be apart of the next generations biggest private server community, here is your chance. [/center] 

[center]To Apply: Please copy and email the following code.
&lt;blockquote&gt;Real Name:
Real Age:
Position I&#39;m Applying For:
Experience in this previously:
Why should I be picked:
Email:
Where I found this:&lt;/blockquote&gt;
ALL Emails, please send either via private message here, or emails. To E-Mail Crusix, it&#39;s Crusix@live.com
Hurry while positions are available! [/center]</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 22 Oct 2009 10:05:53 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/bloodfire-rs/309849.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>** BloodFire-RS **</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@SickScape SickScape]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/sickscape">@SickScape</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>NICE and good luck, im new to rspservers and i dont understand anything yet <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=5" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/bloodfire-rs/309849/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/bloodfire-rs/309849/5</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 22 Oct 2009 10:05:53 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-309849-5</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/bloodfire-rs/309849.rss">** BloodFire-RS **</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>** BloodFire-RS **</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Crusix Crusix]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/crusix">@Crusix</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“xxlukexx, post:3, topic:309849”]not many people are 18 and are still coding servers, neither are 16 as im sure they HAVE lifes.</p>
<p>anyway, gl.[/quote]<br>
Thanks for comment, I actually got 20 applications so far. And sorry if your community is filled with 12 year olds trying to make a server. I respect this community, but you flamers are just immature.<br>
<a class="mention" href="/u/mitko5">@Mitko5</a>, Yes I am aware that there is a development board. Are you aware how long it takes to be approved?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/bloodfire-rs/309849/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/bloodfire-rs/309849/4</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 21 Oct 2009 22:36:16 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-309849-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/bloodfire-rs/309849.rss">** BloodFire-RS **</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>** BloodFire-RS **</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@xxlukexx xxlukexx]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/xxlukexx">@xxlukexx</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>not many people are 18 and are still coding servers, neither are 16 as im sure they HAVE lifes.</p>
<p>anyway, gl.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/bloodfire-rs/309849/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/bloodfire-rs/309849/3</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 21 Oct 2009 17:05:14 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-309849-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/bloodfire-rs/309849.rss">** BloodFire-RS **</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>** BloodFire-RS **</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Mitko5 Mitko5]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/mitko5">@Mitko5</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>You do know there’s a <span class="bbcode-b">Development Teams</span> board…</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/bloodfire-rs/309849/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/bloodfire-rs/309849/2</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 21 Oct 2009 16:46:46 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-309849-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/bloodfire-rs/309849.rss">** BloodFire-RS **</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>** BloodFire-RS **</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Crusix Crusix]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/crusix">@Crusix</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[center][size=15pt]Hello Mopar![/size][/center]</p>
<p>[center]I’m Crusix, from Bloodfire-wow. We have decided, to also make a Runescape private server. Bloodfire is an extremely huge private server company, with over 250 staff so far. We are now looking for the coders for a Runescape private server. I will be the leader for the RS server, and I’m looking for staff.[/center]</p>
<p>[center]Current Staff Positions:<br>
<span class="bbcode-b"> Head Developer<br>
Three Java Coders<br>
Head Web Designer<br>
Three Web Designers<br>
Assistant Manager<br>
Five Moderators<br>
Ten Beta Testers<br>
</span>[/center]</p>
<p>[center]To apply for staff, here are the requirements for each different position:<br>
<span class="bbcode-b">Java Coder</span>; Need at least one year experience, high dedication, and a minimum age of 16.<br>
<span class="bbcode-b">Head Developer</span>; Need at least three years in experience, have previous work sites ready to show. Need to heavily know Java and other languages can help you get this position. Need to be at least 18 years of age.<br>
<span class="bbcode-b">Web Designer</span>; Need to understand at least two of the following, PHP, CSS, HTML, XHTML. Need to be atleast 15 years of age, have following projects ready to show.<br>
<span class="bbcode-b">Head Web Designer</span>; Need to understand PHP, CSS, MySQL, HTML, XHTML. Need to be atleast 18 years of age, and understand all the above and flash design.<br>
<span class="bbcode-b">Assistant Manager</span>: This job will pretty much be my assistant, which you will make sure everything is going well and keeping stuff organized. Requirements for this job are; Need to be extremely organized. Able to keep up with the community, which will consist of thousands of people. Need to be very mature and a minimum age of 15.[/center]</p>
<p>[center]If your one of the best developers around here, why should you apply? Well, you should apply because first of all, this isn’t a joke. You will be payed, each month. How much will you be payed? It just depends how much is done. We’re not looking for people that just want some cash, I want people who are dedicated to coding Runescape servers, and have a lot of experience with them. Why start with so many staff? If you knew how much work is being done with the World of Warcraft server, you would know. We are under constant development there, and it needs to be the same way for the Runescape server. We need about 25-40 staff to start for this project, and need them now. So if you are looking to be apart of the next generations biggest private server community, here is your chance. [/center]</p>
<p>[center]To Apply: Please copy and email the following code.</p>
<blockquote>Real Name:
Real Age:
Position I'm Applying For:
Experience in this previously:
Why should I be picked:
Email:
Where I found this:</blockquote>
ALL Emails, please send either via private message here, or emails. To E-Mail Crusix, it's Crusix@live.com
Hurry while positions are available! [/center]
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/bloodfire-rs/309849/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/bloodfire-rs/309849/1</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 21 Oct 2009 14:40:29 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-309849-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/bloodfire-rs/309849.rss">** BloodFire-RS **</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
