<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Help with my server, shop attacking players [delta]</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/help-with-my-server-shop-attacking-players-delta/394023</link>
    <description>OK, ive seen shops attacking players an followign them around and moving and it is rly anoyying me when that happened cause it ruins the point of my shops being organized n all together and i dont like them being in wrong spot. at first i thought players were using magic to hit shops and shops attack them (that is a glitch that was on rly rly old servers, some people might know bout that old glitch) but anyways.. thats the glitch i thought they was doing to i threatened to ban somebody who was being attacked by a shop, but he said all he did was trade it. ive not seen it ofter but i have seen shops attacking players a few times and i just want to know if anybody could help me fix. ide be extremely thankful(:</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 06 May 2011 23:51:36 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/help-with-my-server-shop-attacking-players-delta/394023.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Help with my server, shop attacking players [delta]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@krunt krunt]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/krunt">@krunt</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>OK, ive seen shops attacking players an followign them around and moving and it is rly anoyying me when that happened cause it ruins the point of my shops being organized n all together and i dont like them being in wrong spot. at first i thought players were using magic to hit shops and shops attack them (that is a glitch that was on rly rly old servers, some people might know bout that old glitch) but anyways… thats the glitch i thought they was doing to i threatened to ban somebody who was being attacked by a shop, but he said all he did was trade it. ive not seen it ofter but i have seen shops attacking players a few times and i just want to know if anybody could help me fix. ide be extremely thankful(:</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/help-with-my-server-shop-attacking-players-delta/394023/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/help-with-my-server-shop-attacking-players-delta/394023/1</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 06 May 2011 23:51:36 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-394023-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/help-with-my-server-shop-attacking-players-delta/394023.rss">Help with my server, shop attacking players [delta]</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
