<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>The Catcher in the Rye</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-catcher-in-the-rye/283070</link>
    <description>If anyone has read this book, please comment on this thread. ;)

This is an essay I&#39;ve written for my 10th grade English class on, of course, The Catcher in the Rye.

Please leave any comments and suggestions; thanks! (It would be awesome if you actually took time to read the essay as a whole.)





The Catcher in the Rye
	
	One of the most taught novels in America, The Catcher in the Rye, written by J. D. Salinger, can be categorized into various classifications. The majority of this novel seems to consist of a philosophical point of view, expressed by Holden. Although most of the novel can be classified as philosophical, there are also other classifications that can be applied to it, such as satire. This novel satirizes and ridicules the society that every individual currently lives in, and points out the flaws of our system. This novel also portrays youth and innocence, and how Holden sees the concept of both. Even though he is young, Holden also depicts the concept of isolation and how his views on isolation change throughout the novel. These various themes, when put together, create this interesting, yet “crude” novel, as judged by some critics.
	The central character of this novel, Holden, illustrates a philosophical view on life. He is a young teenager who has minimal knowledge, and is only in high school. As he progresses throughout the story, he soon realizes what he desires to be; the catcher in the rye. He realizes that life has no purpose, so he sets out to find his. “And I&#39;m standing on the edge of some crazy cliff. What I have to do, I have to catch everybody if they start to go over the cliff—I mean if they&#39;re running and they don&#39;t look where they&#39;re going I have to come out from somewhere and catch them. That&#39;s all I&#39;d do all day. I&#39;d just be the catcher in the rye and all.” (173) Holden tells this to Phoebe when she wants to know what Holden wishes to do with his life. He has decided that this is what he wants to do with his life; to be “the catcher in the rye.” Although he has found what he wants to pursue, this is only an image; a fantasy. He sees all children as pure and innocent, while adults are corrupt and ignorant. Holden sees his own idea as very unreal, but he cannot come up with anything more logical to do with his life. This fantasy of his symbolizes his youth and determination to protect the innocence of other children, but it also symbolizes his lack of ability to relate and connect to the real world outside of him and the concept of how satirical the novel is.
	Along with his philosophical views, Holden is also able to depict the satirical aspects of our everyday society. A tremendous amount of satire coming from this novel lies in Holden’s deceitfulness. “Old Ernie, I said. He’s one of the most popular boys at Pencey. Did you know that?” (56) Holden has a tendency to lie. This is also true for our society; lying is inevitable, and is a major flaw in our society. Although, in this particular statement, Holden lies only to indulge Mrs. Morrow. He takes careful action in what he says to others, in order to please others’ feelings. This is a great trait, but is also a flaw in society. Lying in order to please others shows that humans cannot accept the truth and need to be lied to in order to be comforted. Another theory of Holden’s statement may be the need for entertainment and comedy as a young and innocent boy.
	Holden is a young and innocent boy, and his attitude towards other young individuals are different of those towards adults. “She thanked me and all when I had tightened it for her. She was a very nice, polite little kid. God, I love it when a kid&#39;s nice and polite when you tighten their skate for them or something. Most kids are. They really are. I asked her if she&#39;d care to have a hot chocolate or something with me, but she said no, thank you.” (119) Holden seems to collaborate and communicate better with children than adults. This shows that he respects children more, and that he admires youth and innocence. Tightening an adult’s skate would be out of the question for Holden, because adults, in his interpretation, are corrupt, and do not deserve the same treatment as innocent children. “So he buttoned them right up where he was standing talking to me – he didn&#39;t even bother to go behind a post or anything. He killed me.” (202) This statement that Holden makes shows that the little boy is not a phony; he is not embarrassed to zip up his pants right in front of him, and Holden admires that. Holden is also young, and only in high school, but he already perceives the theory of isolation.
	The Catcher in the Rye can also be classified as a novel that portrays the concept of isolation. “The reason I was standing way up on Thompsen Hill, instead of down at the game, was because I’d just got back from New York with the fencing team. Very big deal. We’d gone in to New York that morning for this fencing meet with McBurney School. Only, we didn’t have the meet. I left all the foils and equipment and stuff on the goddam subway.” (3) This statement shows how easily Holden tends to isolate himself from everyone else. He is watching the other people play and the crowd cheer rather than trying to connect and interact with them. “He was making out like he was walking a very straight line, the way kids do, and the whole time he kept singing and humming. -- It made me feel better. It made me feel not so depressed anymore.” In these few sentences, Holden resists his isolation in a different and unique method. By watching the little boy sing and hum, Holden immediately cheers up a bit. This shows that even a small child has the power to cheer up an individual who chosen to be isolated from the rest of society.
	The Catcher in the Rye, by J. D. Salinger, is a very complex novel that can be classified into various themes, with the most prominent one being philosophy, where Holden tries to find a meaning in his life. This novel can also be classified as a satirical view of life, because of all the flaws depicted within the novel and merely by Holden’s actions. Other possible classifications include the concept of youth and innocence, which Holden has, but also admires. All of these elements combine to form a complex, but undoubtedly, interesting novel.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 10 Jun 2009 10:39:53 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>General Discussion</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-catcher-in-the-rye/283070.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>The Catcher in the Rye</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@jc22493 Jc22493]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/jc22493">@jc22493</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“zuppers, post:2, topic:283070”]I’ve read the book and thought it was pretty good. I enjoy the time period the most tho. Salinger also wrote a few other pieces like A Perfect Day for Bananafish, The Laughingman and those were put into a book called “Nine Stories”.</p>
<p>tbh I’m not sure why I liked this book so much <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/confused.png?v=5" title=":confused:" class="emoji" alt=":confused:"></p>
<p>But good job on the essay looks great to me, also the part on the subway where he was lying to “Mrs. Morrow” was pretty funny, but sad at the same time. Personally I thought she was being dimwitted. I mean she really couldn’t have believed everything he said like that so easily.</p>
<p>Just a question because this part of the book was completely unanswered, like the ending. Is the old school teacher he stays half the night with towards the end a pedophile? I mean Holden might have just freaked out. But his old school teacher might have just been admiring his youth.  <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/expressionless.png?v=5" title=":expressionless:" class="emoji" alt=":expressionless:"></p>
<p>And I also like all the parts where he uses his gray hair to make people think hes older lol <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=5" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"></p>
<p>I agree about the isolation, personally I think he isolated himself on accident, just because he over analyzes everything. But I guess that could just be me, the whole book was based off his “point of view” after all. And I can’t shake the feeling he was lying about having gray hair…[/quote]<br>
Thanks for the reply. I, myself, also enjoyed the book. The part where Mr. Antolini was petting Holden’s head makes it seems as if he’s a pedophile, but this idea is controversial and can be argued both ways, due to the fact that the novel itself does not supply sufficient information for us to determine the truth. Many readers and critics see it as just another element to the book that shows Holden’s insecurities, while others agree that Mr. Antolini is homosexual. I, to be honest, am not sure about this matter.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-catcher-in-the-rye/283070/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-catcher-in-the-rye/283070/3</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jun 2009 10:39:53 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-283070-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-catcher-in-the-rye/283070.rss">The Catcher in the Rye</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The Catcher in the Rye</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@zuppers zuppers]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/zuppers">@zuppers</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I’ve read the book and thought it was pretty good. I enjoy the time period the most tho. Salinger also wrote a few other pieces like A Perfect Day for Bananafish, The Laughingman and those were put into a book called “Nine Stories”.</p>
<p>tbh I’m not sure why I liked this book so much <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/confused.png?v=5" title=":confused:" class="emoji" alt=":confused:"></p>
<p>But good job on the essay looks great to me, also the part on the subway where he was lying to “Mrs. Morrow” was pretty funny, but sad at the same time. Personally I thought she was being dimwitted. I mean she really couldn’t have believed everything he said like that so easily.</p>
<p>Just a question because this part of the book was completely unanswered, like the ending. Is the old school teacher he stays half the night with towards the end a pedophile? I mean Holden might have just freaked out. But his old school teacher might have just been admiring his youth.  <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/expressionless.png?v=5" title=":expressionless:" class="emoji" alt=":expressionless:"></p>
<p>And I also like all the parts where he uses his gray hair to make people think hes older lol <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=5" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"></p>
<p>I agree about the isolation, personally I think he isolated himself on accident, just because he over analyzes everything. But I guess that could just be me, the whole book was based off his “point of view” after all. And I can’t shake the feeling he was lying about having gray hair…</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-catcher-in-the-rye/283070/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-catcher-in-the-rye/283070/2</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jun 2009 04:07:46 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-283070-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-catcher-in-the-rye/283070.rss">The Catcher in the Rye</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The Catcher in the Rye</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@jc22493 Jc22493]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/jc22493">@jc22493</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>If anyone has read this book, please comment on this thread. <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/wink.png?v=5" title=":wink:" class="emoji" alt=":wink:"></p>
<p>This is an essay I’ve written for my 10th grade English class on, of course, The Catcher in the Rye.</p>
<p>Please leave any comments and suggestions; thanks! (It would be awesome if you actually took time to read the essay as a whole.)</p>
<p>The Catcher in the Rye</p>
<pre><code>One of the most taught novels in America, The Catcher in the Rye, written by J. D. Salinger, can be categorized into various classifications. The majority of this novel seems to consist of a philosophical point of view, expressed by Holden. Although most of the novel can be classified as philosophical, there are also other classifications that can be applied to it, such as satire. This novel satirizes and ridicules the society that every individual currently lives in, and points out the flaws of our system. This novel also portrays youth and innocence, and how Holden sees the concept of both. Even though he is young, Holden also depicts the concept of isolation and how his views on isolation change throughout the novel. These various themes, when put together, create this interesting, yet “crude” novel, as judged by some critics.
The central character of this novel, Holden, illustrates a philosophical view on life. He is a young teenager who has minimal knowledge, and is only in high school. As he progresses throughout the story, he soon realizes what he desires to be; the catcher in the rye. He realizes that life has no purpose, so he sets out to find his. “And I'm standing on the edge of some crazy cliff. What I have to do, I have to catch everybody if they start to go over the cliff—I mean if they're running and they don't look where they're going I have to come out from somewhere and catch them. That's all I'd do all day. I'd just be the catcher in the rye and all.” (173) Holden tells this to Phoebe when she wants to know what Holden wishes to do with his life. He has decided that this is what he wants to do with his life; to be “the catcher in the rye.” Although he has found what he wants to pursue, this is only an image; a fantasy. He sees all children as pure and innocent, while adults are corrupt and ignorant. Holden sees his own idea as very unreal, but he cannot come up with anything more logical to do with his life. This fantasy of his symbolizes his youth and determination to protect the innocence of other children, but it also symbolizes his lack of ability to relate and connect to the real world outside of him and the concept of how satirical the novel is.
Along with his philosophical views, Holden is also able to depict the satirical aspects of our everyday society. A tremendous amount of satire coming from this novel lies in Holden’s deceitfulness. “Old Ernie, I said. He’s one of the most popular boys at Pencey. Did you know that?” (56) Holden has a tendency to lie. This is also true for our society; lying is inevitable, and is a major flaw in our society. Although, in this particular statement, Holden lies only to indulge Mrs. Morrow. He takes careful action in what he says to others, in order to please others’ feelings. This is a great trait, but is also a flaw in society. Lying in order to please others shows that humans cannot accept the truth and need to be lied to in order to be comforted. Another theory of Holden’s statement may be the need for entertainment and comedy as a young and innocent boy.
Holden is a young and innocent boy, and his attitude towards other young individuals are different of those towards adults. “She thanked me and all when I had tightened it for her. She was a very nice, polite little kid. God, I love it when a kid's nice and polite when you tighten their skate for them or something. Most kids are. They really are. I asked her if she'd care to have a hot chocolate or something with me, but she said no, thank you.” (119) Holden seems to collaborate and communicate better with children than adults. This shows that he respects children more, and that he admires youth and innocence. Tightening an adult’s skate would be out of the question for Holden, because adults, in his interpretation, are corrupt, and do not deserve the same treatment as innocent children. “So he buttoned them right up where he was standing talking to me – he didn't even bother to go behind a post or anything. He killed me.” (202) This statement that Holden makes shows that the little boy is not a phony; he is not embarrassed to zip up his pants right in front of him, and Holden admires that. Holden is also young, and only in high school, but he already perceives the theory of isolation.
The Catcher in the Rye can also be classified as a novel that portrays the concept of isolation. “The reason I was standing way up on Thompsen Hill, instead of down at the game, was because I’d just got back from New York with the fencing team. Very big deal. We’d gone in to New York that morning for this fencing meet with McBurney School. Only, we didn’t have the meet. I left all the foils and equipment and stuff on the goddam subway.” (3) This statement shows how easily Holden tends to isolate himself from everyone else. He is watching the other people play and the crowd cheer rather than trying to connect and interact with them. “He was making out like he was walking a very straight line, the way kids do, and the whole time he kept singing and humming. -- It made me feel better. It made me feel not so depressed anymore.” In these few sentences, Holden resists his isolation in a different and unique method. By watching the little boy sing and hum, Holden immediately cheers up a bit. This shows that even a small child has the power to cheer up an individual who chosen to be isolated from the rest of society.
The Catcher in the Rye, by J. D. Salinger, is a very complex novel that can be classified into various themes, with the most prominent one being philosophy, where Holden tries to find a meaning in his life. This novel can also be classified as a satirical view of life, because of all the flaws depicted within the novel and merely by Holden’s actions. Other possible classifications include the concept of youth and innocence, which Holden has, but also admires. All of these elements combine to form a complex, but undoubtedly, interesting novel.</code></pre>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-catcher-in-the-rye/283070/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-catcher-in-the-rye/283070/1</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jun 2009 02:20:38 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-283070-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-catcher-in-the-rye/283070.rss">The Catcher in the Rye</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
