<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>This one is interesting</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/this-one-is-interesting/381807</link>
    <description>http://detnews.com/article/20110208/METRO01/102080398</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 11 Feb 2011 19:01:54 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>General Discussion</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/this-one-is-interesting/381807.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>This one is interesting</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@R.I.P_RSC R.I.P RSC]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/r.i.p_rsc">@R.I.P_RSC</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Cases like these are on the edge of what is right and what isn’t. If I were the guy, I wouldn’t do it. Let’s just put the question about if it’s legal or not aside for a moment. The law says it’s illegal, and the law is what people are judged by.</p>
<p>Imagine the court case. Especially in the US, where the jury has the final word, a victim can act like a victim and convince the jury, even if the victim isn’t really a victim. What the girl can do here, is to say that she didn’t agree to have sex with the guy, and then there’s no way the jury will let the guy go. The girl can demand a huge amount of money for damages, and she’ll have fun for the rest of her life.</p>
<p>It’s hard to find out if the girl gave consent. Is a 13 year old even able to decide for him/herself? You’d expect that she wouldn’t date a guy that old, but she did. Did she know that he was that old, or did he lie to her? A case like this comes with a lot of questions, and I know that people like to judge, but let’s leave that to the judges. A case like this shouldn’t be done by a jury in the first place. Only a judge can be rational enough to see what’s really there.</p>
<p><a class="mention" href="/u/lothy">@Lothy</a>: That ‘rule’ only applies to normal couples. When one has a lot of power or wealth, it’s common to have a partner that could be your grandchild.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/this-one-is-interesting/381807/28">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/this-one-is-interesting/381807/28</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 11 Feb 2011 19:01:54 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-381807-28</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/this-one-is-interesting/381807.rss">This one is interesting</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>This one is interesting</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@lothy Lothy]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/lothy">@lothy</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>There’s a whole bunch of information on wikipedia regarding age of consent and such in America.<br>
Across America, the minimum is 16 and the maximum seems to be 18. It’s quite random, and I don’t know why it isn’t uniform.</p>
<p>According to wikipedia, the age of consent is actually 16 in Ohio.</p>
<blockquote>Ohio
<p>The age of consent in Ohio is 16 as specified by Section 2907.04 of Ohio legislation. However there exists a close in age exception where an offender can be charged only if 18 years of age or older. However in that case, it is possible for both minors to be charged as “unruly” if brought to court {§ 2151.022}.</p>
<pre><code>2907.04 Unlawful sexual conduct with minor.

    (A) No person who is eighteen years of age or older shall engage in sexual conduct with another, who is not the spouse of the offender, when the offender knows the other person is thirteen years of age or older but less than sixteen years of age, or the offender is reckless in that regard. {§ 2907.04}.&lt;/blockquote&gt;
</code></pre>
<p>Ohio has a close in age exception, so a 17 year old could sleep with a 15 year old and use that defence.<br>
However, if the youngest party was 16 and gave consent, she could sleep with whoever.</p>
<p>I trust the wikipedia information as they seem to be excerpts straight from the constitutions of each state.</p>
<p>Anyway, some examples of close-in-age laws I found:</p>
<blockquote>Colorado
<p>The age of consent in Colorado is 17, however there exists in the legislation close in age exceptions, which allow those aged 15 and 16 to engage in acts with those less than ten years older and those less than 15 to engage in acts with those less than four years older. However a 17-year-old can not legally consent to person that is in position of trust.</p>
<p>18-3-402(1) Any actor who knowingly inflicts sexual intrusion or sexual penetration on a victim commits sexual assault if: (d) At the time of the commission of the act, the victim is less than fifteen years of age and the actor is at least four years older than the victim and is not the spouse of the victim; or (e) At the time of the commission of the act, the victim is at least fifteen years of age but less than seventeen years of age and the actor is at least ten years older than the victim and is not the spouse of the victim;</p>
<p>Delaware</p>
<p>The age of consent in Delaware is 18, but it is legal for teenagers aged 16 and 17 to engage in sexual intercourse as long as the older partner is younger than 30.</p>
<p>Florida</p>
<p>The age of consent in Florida is 18, but close in age exemptions exist. By law, the exception permits a person 23 years of age or younger to engage in legal sexual activity with a minor aged 16 or 17.</p>
</blockquote>
<p>In short, it’s not ‘hard’ to legislate exceptions. It certainly gets very wordy though, and reading the legislation of a few states actually did my head in. <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=5" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"></p>
<p>Also, I’m in the same boat as Mopman. I couldn’t imagine having any sort of relationship with a 16 year old, for a few reasons.<br>
Firstly, they aren’t all that bright. I’d have all the power in the relationship, and that irks me (as, in my eyes, there should be equality).<br>
Secondly, 16 year olds can be pretty stupid and irritating at the best of times. Wouldn’t want to be near one on a bad day.</p>
<p>Anyway, all of the above is just my two cents.</p>
<p>EDIT: Also, just to clarify, I noticed the use of the word ‘date’ above. Anybody can date. The act of dating in and of itself is inherently innocent; it doesn’t imply intimacy… although you could argue that it doesn’t preclude it, either.<br>
With that said, if a 20 year old really wanted to <span class="bbcode-b">just</span> date a 15 year old, he wouldn’t be breaking any laws. It only becomes illegal when sex comes into the equation, so it’s a very important distinction to make.</p>
</blockquote>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/this-one-is-interesting/381807/27">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/this-one-is-interesting/381807/27</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 11 Feb 2011 13:28:07 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-381807-27</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/this-one-is-interesting/381807.rss">This one is interesting</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>This one is interesting</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Mopman Mopman]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/mopman">@Mopman</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>IIRC, statutory rape here applies to under 13’s, and is basically the pedo law - there’s no getting out of it, basically no possible defense that can be mounted. The actual age of consent for girls is 16, I believe there’s no formal age for guys? Though there is child abuse cases with older women and young guys, so I dunno how that works.</p>
<p>Essentially, the age of consent is considered to be 16.</p>
<p><a class="mention" href="/u/mopar">@Mopar</a>: what happens if two underage people have sex in the states, generally?</p>
<p>EDIT: As for “what about almost 16” I know a guy and girl who were 23 and 15 respectively when they got together… its like 4-5 years later now and they’re very happy.</p>
<p>I realise this is not the case always, and probably shouldn’t change law, but just pointing out that not everyones motives are to take advantage or whatever, gut reaction to things is sometimes OH GOD THATS SO WRONG and then it turns out that it really isnt</p>
<p>We did tell him he should have waited, though : &gt; Her dad was a friggin cop too</p>
<p>EDIT2: actually, upon reflection he was 21 not 23. still feels odd to me though, i cant imagine being with a 16 year old.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/this-one-is-interesting/381807/26">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/this-one-is-interesting/381807/26</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 11 Feb 2011 12:21:39 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-381807-26</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/this-one-is-interesting/381807.rss">This one is interesting</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>This one is interesting</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@moparisthebest Moparisthebest]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/moparisthebest">@moparisthebest</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote no-group quote-modified" data-post="22" data-topic="381807">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/user_avatar/forum.moparisthebest.com/lothy/40/51_1.png" class="avatar"> Lothy:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>I don’t see anything wrong with say an 18/19 year old and a 16 year old</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>It’s hard to make a law for that though.  What if they just turned 18, can they still date a 16 year old?  What about almost 16?  Maybe 15?  Pretty soon you are down to dating 13 year olds.</p>
<p>The law here is that someone 18 or over cannot have sex with anyone not yet 18 years old.  Even if it is ‘consensual’, it is statutory rape because someone not of age can not consent.  As I said before though, no one can think that it is good for a 13 year old to have sex with a 56 year old.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/this-one-is-interesting/381807/25">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/this-one-is-interesting/381807/25</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 11 Feb 2011 10:54:20 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-381807-25</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/this-one-is-interesting/381807.rss">This one is interesting</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>This one is interesting</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@lothy Lothy]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/lothy">@lothy</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote no-group" data-post="23" data-topic="381807">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/user_avatar/forum.moparisthebest.com/mopman/40/33_1.png" class="avatar"> Mopman:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>does that mean people younger than 7 can only date older people</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Doesn’t apply for all real n. <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=5" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"><br>
15 &lt; n &lt; x I suppose.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/this-one-is-interesting/381807/24">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/this-one-is-interesting/381807/24</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 11 Feb 2011 08:44:30 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-381807-24</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/this-one-is-interesting/381807.rss">This one is interesting</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>This one is interesting</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Mopman Mopman]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/mopman">@Mopman</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>does that mean people younger than 7 can only date older people</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/this-one-is-interesting/381807/23">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/this-one-is-interesting/381807/23</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 11 Feb 2011 08:40:16 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-381807-23</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/this-one-is-interesting/381807.rss">This one is interesting</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>This one is interesting</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@lothy Lothy]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/lothy">@lothy</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I don’t see anything wrong with say an 18/19 year old and a 16 year old. There’s actually a mathematical rule for ‘age appropriate’ relationships. You shouldn’t seek a relationship with anyone younger than half your age plus 7.<br>
So if you were 22, then you would date someone no younger than 11 + 7, or 18 years of age.</p>
<p>If it’s within the law then there’s nothing wrong with them having sex either.<br>
I know it’s a hard thing for some people to swallow, but parents don’t ‘own’ their daughter’s right to take part in sex. In many places around the world, age of consent is 16. It’s none of the father’s business if his 16 year old daughter has sex with someone.<br>
This does mean that, in those places, a dinosaur could theoretically have sex with a 16 year old girl and, as long as she consents to it, he’s in the clear.<br>
The good news is that most 16 year old girls wouldn’t.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/this-one-is-interesting/381807/22">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/this-one-is-interesting/381807/22</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 11 Feb 2011 08:29:11 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-381807-22</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/this-one-is-interesting/381807.rss">This one is interesting</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>This one is interesting</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Pwnd Pwnd]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/pwnd">@Pwnd</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“Moparisthebest, post:9, topic:381807”][quote author=n10si t link=topic=477617.msg3494824#msg3494824 date=1297222535]</p>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p>That’s ridiculous, hopefully that guy goes to prison for a long, long time.  And hopefully everyone in there knows what he was convicted for and treats him accordingly.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>he’d like it<br>
[/quote]</p>
<p>If they beat him half to death all the time? I doubt it.[/quote]Half to death with their wieners.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/this-one-is-interesting/381807/21">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/this-one-is-interesting/381807/21</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 09 Feb 2011 15:42:09 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-381807-21</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/this-one-is-interesting/381807.rss">This one is interesting</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>This one is interesting</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Unlimited1 .Unlimited]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/unlimited1">@Unlimited1</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“Moparisthebest, post:13, topic:381807”][quote author=the bank link=topic=477617.msg3494851#msg3494851 date=1297225055]<br>
Its sick of him…but from the sounds of the article it doesn’t sound like she was raped.  Still horribly disgusting though.<br>
[/quote]</p>
<p>Anyone over 18 having sex with anyone under 18 is raping them, it’s statutory rape, but rape nonetheless.  No one can think this is good for the girl.[/quote]<br>
Except for the states where it is 16.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/this-one-is-interesting/381807/20">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/this-one-is-interesting/381807/20</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 09 Feb 2011 15:16:28 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-381807-20</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/this-one-is-interesting/381807.rss">This one is interesting</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>This one is interesting</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@davidude36 Brolapse]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/davidude36">@davidude36</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote no-group" data-post="17" data-topic="381807">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 Miss Silabsoft:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>brooks was here.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>so was red</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/this-one-is-interesting/381807/19">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/this-one-is-interesting/381807/19</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 09 Feb 2011 15:05:25 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-381807-19</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/this-one-is-interesting/381807.rss">This one is interesting</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>This one is interesting</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Speljohan Speljohan]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/speljohan">@Speljohan</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“Moparisthebest, post:13, topic:381807”][quote author=the bank link=topic=477617.msg3494851#msg3494851 date=1297225055]<br>
Its sick of him…but from the sounds of the article it doesn’t sound like she was raped.  Still horribly disgusting though.<br>
[/quote]</p>
<p>Anyone over 18 having sex with anyone under 18 is raping them, it’s statutory rape, but rape nonetheless.  No one can think this is good for the girl.[/quote]You have a truly fucked up world-view.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/this-one-is-interesting/381807/18">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/this-one-is-interesting/381807/18</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 09 Feb 2011 15:02:41 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-381807-18</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/this-one-is-interesting/381807.rss">This one is interesting</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>This one is interesting</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@silabsoft RuneAgent]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/silabsoft">@silabsoft</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>brooks was here.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/this-one-is-interesting/381807/17">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/this-one-is-interesting/381807/17</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 09 Feb 2011 14:58:30 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-381807-17</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/this-one-is-interesting/381807.rss">This one is interesting</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>This one is interesting</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@lothy Lothy]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/lothy">@lothy</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote no-group quote-modified" data-post="14" data-topic="381807">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 Miss Silabsoft:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>the real question is what the fuck is wrong with the girl? 53 isn’t exactly sexy.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>You said it. Presuming it was ‘consensual’ in the sense that she said ‘yeah, let’s fuck and stuff’ (obviously she can’t actually consent to sex by law), what was running through her mind?<br>
Few screws loose.</p>
<p>I agree with Mopar’s sentiment though. It reminded me of The Shawshank Redemption, and a bit of me hopes that either<br>
a) He experiences what Andy Dufresne experienced at the hands of ‘The Sisters’ or<br>
b) He experiences what the ringleader of ‘The Sisters’ experiences at the hands of one of the guards.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/this-one-is-interesting/381807/16">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/this-one-is-interesting/381807/16</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 09 Feb 2011 13:23:41 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-381807-16</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/this-one-is-interesting/381807.rss">This one is interesting</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>This one is interesting</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Speljohan Speljohan]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/speljohan">@Speljohan</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote no-group quote-modified" data-post="14" data-topic="381807">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 Miss Silabsoft:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>the real question is what the fuck is wrong with the girl? 53 isn’t exactly sexy.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/this-one-is-interesting/381807/15">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/this-one-is-interesting/381807/15</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 09 Feb 2011 12:32:05 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-381807-15</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/this-one-is-interesting/381807.rss">This one is interesting</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>This one is interesting</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@silabsoft RuneAgent]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/silabsoft">@silabsoft</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>the real question is what the fuck is wrong with the girl? 53 isn’t exactly sexy.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/this-one-is-interesting/381807/14">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/this-one-is-interesting/381807/14</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 09 Feb 2011 10:52:46 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-381807-14</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/this-one-is-interesting/381807.rss">This one is interesting</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>This one is interesting</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@moparisthebest Moparisthebest]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/moparisthebest">@moparisthebest</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote no-group quote-modified" data-post="10" data-topic="381807">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 the bank:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Its sick of him…but from the sounds of the article it doesn’t sound like she was raped.  Still horribly disgusting though.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Anyone over 18 having sex with anyone under 18 is raping them, it’s statutory rape, but rape nonetheless.  No one can think this is good for the girl.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/this-one-is-interesting/381807/13">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/this-one-is-interesting/381807/13</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 09 Feb 2011 10:04:19 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-381807-13</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/this-one-is-interesting/381807.rss">This one is interesting</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>This one is interesting</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@IlikeArrays IlikeArrays]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/ilikearrays">@IlikeArrays</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote no-group quote-modified" data-post="11" data-topic="381807">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/krackkid/40/5_1887921562df0dabfae55079ddabeb03.png" class="avatar"> krackkid:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>I don’t see the big deal, I mean the preist in the lumby castle wed them. So it’s real duh.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>&lt;3</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/this-one-is-interesting/381807/12">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/this-one-is-interesting/381807/12</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 09 Feb 2011 09:17:47 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-381807-12</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/this-one-is-interesting/381807.rss">This one is interesting</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>This one is interesting</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@krackkid Krackkid]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/krackkid">@krackkid</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I don’t see the big deal, I mean the preist in the lumby castle wed them. So it’s real duh.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/this-one-is-interesting/381807/11">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/this-one-is-interesting/381807/11</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 09 Feb 2011 06:26:55 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-381807-11</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/this-one-is-interesting/381807.rss">This one is interesting</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>This one is interesting</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@the_bank the bank]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/the_bank">@the_bank</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Its sick of him…but from the sounds of the article it doesn’t sound like she was raped.  Still horribly disgusting though.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/this-one-is-interesting/381807/10">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/this-one-is-interesting/381807/10</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 09 Feb 2011 04:17:35 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-381807-10</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/this-one-is-interesting/381807.rss">This one is interesting</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>This one is interesting</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@moparisthebest Moparisthebest]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/moparisthebest">@moparisthebest</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“n10si t, post:8, topic:381807”][quote author=Moparisthebest link=topic=477617.msg3494822#msg3494822 date=1297222451]<br>
That’s ridiculous, hopefully that guy goes to prison for a long, long time.  And hopefully everyone in there knows what he was convicted for and treats him accordingly.<br>
[/quote]</p>
<p>he’d like it[/quote]</p>
<p>If they beat him half to death all the time? I doubt it.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/this-one-is-interesting/381807/9">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/this-one-is-interesting/381807/9</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 09 Feb 2011 04:07:27 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-381807-9</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/this-one-is-interesting/381807.rss">This one is interesting</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>This one is interesting</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@n10si_t n10si t]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/n10si_t">@n10si_t</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote no-group" data-post="7" data-topic="381807">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/user_avatar/forum.moparisthebest.com/moparisthebest/40/30_1.png" class="avatar"> Moparisthebest:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>That’s ridiculous, hopefully that guy goes to prison for a long, long time.  And hopefully everyone in there knows what he was convicted for and treats him accordingly.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>he’d like it</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/this-one-is-interesting/381807/8">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/this-one-is-interesting/381807/8</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 09 Feb 2011 03:35:35 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-381807-8</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/this-one-is-interesting/381807.rss">This one is interesting</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>This one is interesting</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@moparisthebest Moparisthebest]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/moparisthebest">@moparisthebest</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>That’s ridiculous, hopefully that guy goes to prison for a long, long time.  And hopefully everyone in there knows what he was convicted for and treats him accordingly.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/this-one-is-interesting/381807/7">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/this-one-is-interesting/381807/7</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 09 Feb 2011 03:34:11 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-381807-7</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/this-one-is-interesting/381807.rss">This one is interesting</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>This one is interesting</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@cooper cooper]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/cooper">@cooper</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>haha hey i live near there<br>
““This is probably a case in a lot of households where the parents are working to support their families and the kids have a lot of alone time, and it’s amazing what they can do when they’re alone and they have access to the internet,” said Corporal Ray Johnson with the Internet Crimes Unit.”</p>
<blockquote>RuneScape has rules in place for RuneScape players’ safety. In the RuneScape rules, it states specifically that “For our players' privacy and safety, you must not ask for personal details such as full name, email address, instant messenger handles, telephone number or your home/school address or age. You also must not post anyone's personal contact details (including your own) on our in-game chat or forums.”
RuneScape players who follow these rules should be safe. John Phillips clearly violated the rules and got away this far as the girl’s mother worked multiple jobs and couldn’t keep a close eye on things. RuneScape is a safe game provided general internet caution is excercised.</blockquote>
also of interest
http://www.detnews.com/article/20110208/METRO/102080401/1409/METRO
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/this-one-is-interesting/381807/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/this-one-is-interesting/381807/6</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 09 Feb 2011 03:10:59 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-381807-6</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/this-one-is-interesting/381807.rss">This one is interesting</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>This one is interesting</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@NewbieNewty Newty]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/newbienewty">@NewbieNewty</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“Niall, post:4, topic:381807”][quote author=Newty link=topic=477617.msg3494737#msg3494737 date=1297216724]<br>
I wonder what game. [/quote]</p>
<p>[quote]Wayne County Sheriff Benny Napoleon said Phillips met the girl while playing RuneScape online and that they chatted online through the game in 2010.</p>
<p>Napoleon said Phillips and the girl wed in the role-playing game, which allows players to assume identities and interact with other players, some of whom live in other countries.</p>
<p>“They got married in the game,” sheriff’s corporal Ray Johnson said.[/quote][/quote]</p>
<p>hurr durr apparently I missed that <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/frowning.png?v=5" title=":frowning:" class="emoji" alt=":frowning:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/this-one-is-interesting/381807/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/this-one-is-interesting/381807/5</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 09 Feb 2011 02:47:03 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-381807-5</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/this-one-is-interesting/381807.rss">This one is interesting</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>This one is interesting</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@The_Un-Named The Un-Named]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/the_un-named">@The_Un-Named</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote no-group" data-post="2" data-topic="381807">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 Newty:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>I wonder what game.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<blockquote>Wayne County Sheriff Benny Napoleon said Phillips met the girl while playing RuneScape online and that they chatted online through the game in 2010. 
<p>Napoleon said Phillips and the girl wed in the role-playing game, which allows players to assume identities and interact with other players, some of whom live in other countries.</p>
<p>“They got married in the game,” sheriff’s corporal Ray Johnson said.</p>
</blockquote>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/this-one-is-interesting/381807/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/this-one-is-interesting/381807/4</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 09 Feb 2011 02:08:56 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-381807-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/this-one-is-interesting/381807.rss">This one is interesting</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
