<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>718 matrix - sql loading/saving</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/718-matrix-sql-loading-saving/528690</link>
    <description>Hi everyone,

[size=36pt]PLEASE STOP IGNORING THIS POST. [/size]

WHAT I NEED HELP WITH:
I&#39;d really appreciate it if someone could just give me the code for SQL player loading/saving methods or at least the login synchronization methods with vBulletin forums. We have everything setup on the website and I would like to save A HUGE hassle of programming it all myself... I can do it, but if someone could help me out by just pointing me to a tutorial or even the code itself that would be lovely. It would save us a lot of time and I could focus my attention to more important things like a full on Adventurer&#39;s Log on our website. 

Thanks in advance!


EDIT/UPDATE: I refactored the 747 matrix-based source we have and implemented an entirely new SQL player loading/saving system. I will not be releasing the work we have put into this project. 40 views on this thread and no responses? I&#39;d like to thank the community for the wonderful help and support it has to offer...</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 22 Aug 2013 23:36:36 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/718-matrix-sql-loading-saving/528690.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>718 matrix - sql loading/saving</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@No_Life2 No  Life]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/no_life2">@No_Life2</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Hi everyone,</p>
<p>[size=36pt]PLEASE STOP IGNORING THIS POST. [/size]</p>
<p>WHAT I NEED HELP WITH:<br>
I’d really appreciate it if someone could just give me the code for SQL player loading/saving methods or at least the login synchronization methods with vBulletin forums. We have everything setup on the website and I would like to save A HUGE hassle of programming it all myself… I can do it, but if someone could help me out by just pointing me to a tutorial or even the code itself that would be lovely. It would save us a lot of time and I could focus my attention to more important things like a full on Adventurer’s Log on our website.</p>
<p>Thanks in advance!</p>
<p>EDIT/UPDATE: I refactored the 747 matrix-based source we have and implemented an entirely new SQL player loading/saving system. I will not be releasing the work we have put into this project. 40 views on this thread and no responses? I’d like to thank the community for the wonderful help and support it has to offer…</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/718-matrix-sql-loading-saving/528690/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/718-matrix-sql-loading-saving/528690/1</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 22 Aug 2013 23:36:36 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-528690-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/718-matrix-sql-loading-saving/528690.rss">718 matrix - sql loading/saving</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
