<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>[317] Ivy [317]</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/317-ivy-317/378194</link>
    <description>Um hey, I kinda need help with Ivy, you know with woodcutting like real runescape, So i took a lot of time searching and couldn&#39;t find anything, So i need you to help me out. Please?
Anyhow, i thought about it at first, so i need the object. Umm, there isnt one already in 317s, so i thought about how id have to make a custom object for it. Yet, i couldn&#39;t find someone who had one. Besides that, after i had it added, i could just place it somewhere on my server, then all id have to do is add it into the woodcutting methods with the other trees, and just make it do the sM and it doesnt even give an item, that simple.So, if you could possibly spoon feed, and give me a model and/or the INTS and where exactly to put the ints? i totally forgot. Thanks in advance.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 13 Jan 2011 18:18:33 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/317-ivy-317/378194.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>[317] Ivy [317]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Evocation Evocation]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/evocation">@Evocation</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Um hey, I kinda need help with Ivy, you know with woodcutting like real runescape, So i took a lot of time searching and couldn’t find anything, So i need you to help me out. Please?<br>
Anyhow, i thought about it at first, so i need the object. Umm, there isnt one already in 317s, so i thought about how id have to make a custom object for it. Yet, i couldn’t find someone who had one. Besides that, after i had it added, i could just place it somewhere on my server, then all id have to do is add it into the woodcutting methods with the other trees, and just make it do the sM and it doesnt even give an item, that simple.So, if you could possibly spoon feed, and give me a model and/or the INTS and where exactly to put the ints? i totally forgot. Thanks in advance.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/317-ivy-317/378194/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/317-ivy-317/378194/1</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 13 Jan 2011 18:18:33 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-378194-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/317-ivy-317/378194.rss">[317] Ivy [317]</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
