<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Rune-Sanctum Pray to our Sanctum</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rune-sanctum-pray-to-our-sanctum/549313</link>
    <description>[center]Welcome and thank you for viewing my thread we hope you are willing to stay with our server and continue to support us if you do!

New just Released server [url=http://www.Rune-Sanctum.com]Rune-Sanctum | #1 Growings RSPS[/url]


Core re-work for great server stability
Friendly and active community
Duo Slayer
Dwarf multi cannon
In game PvP highscores
Perfect item switches for amazing hybridding
Flawless combat system
Client settings - Including 100% fullscreen &amp; resizeable
A unique Donator zone with many Donator benefits
All skills fully working and being worked on every day
Daily server and website updates
A hard working owner who listens to his players
Pk Points for killing players and Voting Points both with amazing reward shops
Many bosses to defeat all dropping well rewarding items!
Clean and efficient client, small cache size and low memory usage
Many mini-games including fully working duel arena with staking
The server is hosted on a powerful VPS which is ran 24/7 for 100% uptime
Great combat rates so you may enjoy the server for as long as possible without losing interest fast!
Max cape for players who accomplish all 99&#39;s
Highscores and auto donations
And many, many more features join today to see them for your self!
Multi world management system!

[URL=http://rune-sanctum.com][img]http://i.imgur.com/ZXVyzVj.png[/img][/URL]

Why should you choose to play Rune-Sanctum over other servers?

A very good question.. But a very simple answer which is, Rune-Sanctum cares about it&#39;s players, it cares about it&#39;s economy, it cares about how the server is ran and what the players suggest and what they want. We do everything we possible can to ensure that the players of Rune-Sanctum/Rune-Honor enjoy playing the game and get the most friendly, fun and enjoyable game play they can!

The server does frequent and daily updates almost every day, you can view all/most of the updates that happen on Rune-Sanctum on the update-log on the forums. Rune-Sanctum focuses on every players enjoyment, we have every aspect of game-play that we know players enjoy PvM, PvP, skilling, you name it we have it! We are not like other servers which are ignorant to there players and just ignores there opinions and even ignores there players when they talk to them.. I have played over 50 servers over the past 4 years and have watched very carefully how the best servers are ran and also how the bad servers are ran, I have learnt there mistakes and adapted to how the best servers are ran which is why Rune-Sanctum/Rune-Honor is the place for you.

Both of our servers are ran by Highly trained staff teams who do their best to make your enjoyment and your stay on the server we try our best to add daily game content to also make the server more competitive as well as weekly events where my staff team will fluoridate so we can all have decent fun!

We put time into FUN and ENJOYMENT!

- An incredibly well balanced economy, with prices that aren&#39;t too easy to reach, yet they aren&#39;t too hard either.

- Every single skill from Old School Runescape (excluding construction and hunter) can be fully trained, with multiple ways to go about raising your levels.

- A FLAWLESS combat system, giving you the PERFECT old school PKing/PvMing experience.

- Extremely smooth chatting system, with zero delays.

- Fully functioning clan chat system, with working ranks, as well as an extremely charismatic ::help clan chat in game

- A fully working webclient (the link is at the top) for players who don&#39;t enjoy a desktop/downloadable client.

- A fully working desktop/downloadable client (the link is at the top) for players who don&#39;t enjoy a webclient.

- Fully working, extremely well made Highscores, that allow you to compete with the hundreds of other players on Rune-Sanctum for dominance.

- Daily community/staff held events, which help players get together and bond to become more than just a private server, but a family.

Extremely hard working staff team, that puts your needs above their own. Respectful, helpful, and most importantly, fun to be around!


[url=https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=q73kwVuw2uw]https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=q73kwVuw2uw[/url]
[url=https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Q7pYfeaqa8o]https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Q7pYfeaqa8o[/url]
[url=https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=oKi-34eS_OE]https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=oKi-34eS_OE[/url]
[URL=http://minus.com/i/bhhNZzYBIfDsu][IMG]http://i.minus.com/jbhhNZzYBIfDsu.png[/img][/URL]
[URL=http://minus.com/i/vrCgnYiihSVx][IMG]http://i.minus.com/jvrCgnYiihSVx.png[/img][/URL]
[URL=http://minus.com/i/KtouLj4HQ2mX][IMG]http://i.minus.com/jKtouLj4HQ2mX.png[/img][/URL][/center]</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2015 12:33:24 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rune-sanctum-pray-to-our-sanctum/549313.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Rune-Sanctum Pray to our Sanctum</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@runehonor runehonor]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/runehonor">@runehonor</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[center]Welcome and thank you for viewing my thread we hope you are willing to stay with our server and continue to support us if you do!</p>
<p>New just Released server <a href="http://www.Rune-Sanctum.com" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">Rune-Sanctum | #1 Growings RSPS</a></p>
<p>Core re-work for great server stability<br>
Friendly and active community<br>
Duo Slayer<br>
Dwarf multi cannon<br>
In game PvP highscores<br>
Perfect item switches for amazing hybridding<br>
Flawless combat system<br>
Client settings - Including 100% fullscreen &amp; resizeable<br>
A unique Donator zone with many Donator benefits<br>
All skills fully working and being worked on every day<br>
Daily server and website updates<br>
A hard working owner who listens to his players<br>
Pk Points for killing players and Voting Points both with amazing reward shops<br>
Many bosses to defeat all dropping well rewarding items!<br>
Clean and efficient client, small cache size and low memory usage<br>
Many mini-games including fully working duel arena with staking<br>
The server is hosted on a powerful VPS which is ran 24/7 for 100% uptime<br>
Great combat rates so you may enjoy the server for as long as possible without losing interest fast!<br>
Max cape for players who accomplish all 99’s<br>
Highscores and auto donations<br>
And many, many more features join today to see them for your self!<br>
Multi world management system!</p>
<p>[URL=http://rune-sanctum.com]<img src="http://i.imgur.com/ZXVyzVj.png" alt width="" height="">[/URL]</p>
<p>Why should you choose to play Rune-Sanctum over other servers?</p>
<p>A very good question… But a very simple answer which is, Rune-Sanctum cares about it’s players, it cares about it’s economy, it cares about how the server is ran and what the players suggest and what they want. We do everything we possible can to ensure that the players of Rune-Sanctum/Rune-Honor enjoy playing the game and get the most friendly, fun and enjoyable game play they can!</p>
<p>The server does frequent and daily updates almost every day, you can view all/most of the updates that happen on Rune-Sanctum on the update-log on the forums. Rune-Sanctum focuses on every players enjoyment, we have every aspect of game-play that we know players enjoy PvM, PvP, skilling, you name it we have it! We are not like other servers which are ignorant to there players and just ignores there opinions and even ignores there players when they talk to them… I have played over 50 servers over the past 4 years and have watched very carefully how the best servers are ran and also how the bad servers are ran, I have learnt there mistakes and adapted to how the best servers are ran which is why Rune-Sanctum/Rune-Honor is the place for you.</p>
<p>Both of our servers are ran by Highly trained staff teams who do their best to make your enjoyment and your stay on the server we try our best to add daily game content to also make the server more competitive as well as weekly events where my staff team will fluoridate so we can all have decent fun!</p>
<p>We put time into FUN and ENJOYMENT!</p>
<ul>
<li>
<p>An incredibly well balanced economy, with prices that aren’t too easy to reach, yet they aren’t too hard either.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Every single skill from Old School Runescape (excluding construction and hunter) can be fully trained, with multiple ways to go about raising your levels.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>A FLAWLESS combat system, giving you the PERFECT old school PKing/PvMing experience.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Extremely smooth chatting system, with zero delays.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Fully functioning clan chat system, with working ranks, as well as an extremely charismatic ::help clan chat in game</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>A fully working webclient (the link is at the top) for players who don’t enjoy a desktop/downloadable client.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>A fully working desktop/downloadable client (the link is at the top) for players who don’t enjoy a webclient.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Fully working, extremely well made Highscores, that allow you to compete with the hundreds of other players on Rune-Sanctum for dominance.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Daily community/staff held events, which help players get together and bond to become more than just a private server, but a family.</p>
</li>
</ul>
<p>Extremely hard working staff team, that puts your needs above their own. Respectful, helpful, and most importantly, fun to be around!</p>
<p><a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=q73kwVuw2uw" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=q73kwVuw2uw</a><br>
<a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Q7pYfeaqa8o" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Q7pYfeaqa8o</a><br>
<a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=oKi-34eS_OE" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=oKi-34eS_OE</a><br>
[URL=http://minus.com/i/bhhNZzYBIfDsu]<img src="http://i.minus.com/jbhhNZzYBIfDsu.png" alt width="" height="">[/URL]<br>
[URL=http://minus.com/i/vrCgnYiihSVx]<img src="http://i.minus.com/jvrCgnYiihSVx.png" alt width="" height="">[/URL]<br>
[URL=http://minus.com/i/KtouLj4HQ2mX]<img src="http://i.minus.com/jKtouLj4HQ2mX.png" alt width="" height="">[/URL][/center]</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rune-sanctum-pray-to-our-sanctum/549313/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rune-sanctum-pray-to-our-sanctum/549313/1</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2015 12:33:24 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-549313-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rune-sanctum-pray-to-our-sanctum/549313.rss">Rune-Sanctum Pray to our Sanctum</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
