<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Help with server admin</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/help-with-server-admin/164104</link>
    <description>OK, so iv just started playing on my private server again after about 7 months and cant remember a thing about java coding because i haven&#39;t used it in so long.  :|
iv found a problem with my server, when i change my admin permissions, my file saves and i still have it while I&#39;m logged in (gold crown as well) and when i log out, for some reason my admin permission disappears and im left with no crown, and it keeps happening, but it never used to happen when i last used the server, everything was perfect, so i need some code to give the permission always when the account name logs in. can anybody help? thanks.  ;)

(P.S. i have tried saving while logged off, compiling and all that sort of stuff, iv tried everything in the book, if anybody has any suggestions that i might have missed i would be thankful  :))</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 12 Dec 2007 00:17:56 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/help-with-server-admin/164104.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Help with server admin</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@pu123_5k1ll3 pu123 5k1ll3]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/pu123_5k1ll3">@pu123_5k1ll3</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>well f you coded your server correctly changing all of the playerName.equalsIgnoreCase in your username there is no need since those mean that the character has permission to do that so realy just replace all of the playerName.equalsIgnoreCase(“name”) to the username you use for owner like playerName.equalsIgnoreCase(“webbsta”) and note it may be different but not by that much it should still have the equalsignorecase with the spot to put your name</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/help-with-server-admin/164104/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/help-with-server-admin/164104/2</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 12 Dec 2007 00:17:56 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-164104-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/help-with-server-admin/164104.rss">Help with server admin</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Help with server admin</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@webbsta webbsta]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/webbsta">@webbsta</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>OK, so iv just started playing on my private server again after about 7 months and cant remember a thing about java coding because i haven’t used it in so long.  <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/expressionless.png?v=6" title=":expressionless:" class="emoji" alt=":expressionless:"><br>
iv found a problem with my server, when i change my admin permissions, my file saves and i still have it while I’m logged in (gold crown as well) and when i log out, for some reason my admin permission disappears and im left with no crown, and it keeps happening, but it never used to happen when i last used the server, everything was perfect, so i need some code to give the permission always when the account name logs in. can anybody help? thanks.  <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/wink.png?v=6" title=":wink:" class="emoji" alt=":wink:"></p>
<p>(P.S. i have tried saving while logged off, compiling and all that sort of stuff, iv tried everything in the book, if anybody has any suggestions that i might have missed i would be thankful  :))</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/help-with-server-admin/164104/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/help-with-server-admin/164104/1</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 11 Dec 2007 23:39:21 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-164104-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/help-with-server-admin/164104.rss">Help with server admin</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
