<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>~~~ help making a client please ~~~</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/help-making-a-client-please/137299</link>
    <description>I am trying to make a client for my server PicoScape.
Problem is, I can&#39;t seem to get anything to work. I figured out how to use jar files. So using the standard 317 deod or whatever it is, I can compile it. But nothing happens when it is launched. I tryed googling all this, but nothing seems to help. I am able to compile other peoples clients, the work but don&#39;t connect to my server, nor theres. 

I don&#39;t want to use someone else&#39;s client, or change someone elses work around. I want to make my own. But I need help, can anyone please help? Any kind of guide/tutorial anywhere? I already read everthing on this forum. So, anything external for help? Please anyone?</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 27 Aug 2007 00:52:04 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/help-making-a-client-please/137299.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>~~~ help making a client please ~~~</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@gman035t gman035t]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/gman035t">@gman035t</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I am trying to make a client for my server PicoScape.<br>
Problem is, I can’t seem to get anything to work. I figured out how to use jar files. So using the standard 317 deod or whatever it is, I can compile it. But nothing happens when it is launched. I tryed googling all this, but nothing seems to help. I am able to compile other peoples clients, the work but don’t connect to my server, nor theres.</p>
<p>I don’t want to use someone else’s client, or change someone elses work around. I want to make my own. But I need help, can anyone please help? Any kind of guide/tutorial anywhere? I already read everthing on this forum. So, anything external for help? Please anyone?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/help-making-a-client-please/137299/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/help-making-a-client-please/137299/1</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 27 Aug 2007 00:52:04 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-137299-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/help-making-a-client-please/137299.rss">~~~ help making a client please ~~~</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
