<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>I cant find the file which has the prayer xp init</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/i-cant-find-the-file-which-has-the-prayer-xp-init/358918</link>
    <description>hi there i cant seem to find the prayer xp anywhere .  i thought it was prayer.def but that dont not have it in there</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 11 Sep 2010 10:29:22 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/i-cant-find-the-file-which-has-the-prayer-xp-init/358918.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>I cant find the file which has the prayer xp init</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@KO9 KO9]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/ko9">@KO9</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>And the inevitable flame ensues…</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/i-cant-find-the-file-which-has-the-prayer-xp-init/358918/37">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/i-cant-find-the-file-which-has-the-prayer-xp-init/358918/37</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 11 Sep 2010 10:29:22 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-358918-37</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/i-cant-find-the-file-which-has-the-prayer-xp-init/358918.rss">I cant find the file which has the prayer xp init</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>I cant find the file which has the prayer xp init</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@CodeForFame CodeForFame]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/codeforfame">@CodeForFame</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“Asylum, post:35, topic:358918”][quote author=CodeForFame link=topic=455416.msg3338951#msg3338951 date=1284191914]</p>
<p>[quote author=Asylum link=topic=455416.msg3338690#msg3338690 date=1284170185]</p>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p>I don’t care what anyone thinks of me, seeing it doesn’t matter, and I am happy with who I am.  As for your attempts at insulting my intelligence, I merely laugh.  As for your degrade in respect towards me, I can only speculate as to the reason, but I think that you started to try and argue with me, and that you’re butthurt from losing.[/quote]</p>
<p>What exactly am I losing? What? Not a single thing. You’re acting as if you’re in some heated argument to where someone can win or lose. CodeForFame, how old are you?<br>
If you’re happy being an <span class="bbcode-u">arrogant</span>, stubborn human being then that is all on you. You will soon find out, you’ll get no where in life this way.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p>As for you not knowing what arrogance is, it is clear, since you said this, " Also what was the point of saying I don’t know what arrogant means, and then acknowledging that you were being arrogant."  I did not acknowledge being arrogant (seeing I wasn’t) I was simply explaining what had transpired, then stated there is a difference between being arrogant, and correct.[/quote]</p>
<p>You’re being arrogant, because you think you’re correct. You get pride out of <span class="bbcode-u">thinking</span> you’re correct, and then play it out by putting down ideas.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p>Additionally, there is something wrong with flexibility, especially when you’re trying to make constants flexible…  Furthermore, I don’t think you understand that the base xp establishes a relationship, between all the actions, and a relative difficulty for each action.  You get more xp, the harder/more advanced the task is.  Altering this ratio can easily cause an imbalance, which would negate all the work that went into balancing it…</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>That’s a very poor excuse to me. Just reading it made me nod my head. It seems as if it took some time for you just to come up with such an excuse.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>You’re losing because every single point you make is being countered.  An argument doesn’t need to be heated to win or lose, there is always a winner and a loser.  As for age, I don’t see how it’s relevant, in any way.  And again, you still haven’t figure out what arrogance is.  I will admit, I am stubborn, but I don’t see how requiring proof/facts/logic is a bad thing…  As for not getting anywhere in life, you make me laugh, I am successful because of my stubbornness.</p>
<p>Thinking your correct isn’t arrogance, but attempting to display superiority, or self-importance is, and I have done neither of those.  And I didn’t put down any ideas until the person presenting those ideas gave up on them, which I can only assume is because they saw flaws.</p>
<p>A poor excuse?  Lol, as I said, I don’t think you understand it.  The basic principle is that you’re trying to add flexibility to constants, which is stupid.  If you can’t understand that, I truly feel sorry for you.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>You’re an idiot dude. Countered how? Lmfao. I can’t help but laugh at you dude; You’re pathetic. I’m almost at a loss of words here. There’s not enough words in the English dictionary to explain how moronic you’re being right now; It’s hilarious.</p>
<p>Also that’s where you’re wrong; The reason why he quit was because you wouldn’t shut up thinking you’re ‘right’ all of the time (putting down his ideas). It’s pointless to keep arguing with people like you (take this for example; Re-read your responses and <span class="bbcode-u">hopefully</span> you will understand; Though I’m not going to count on it).</p>
<p><a href="http://google.com" rel="nofollow noopener">http://google.com</a> define: arrogant - Having excessive pride in oneself</p>
<p>Adding the EXP to their own class and modifying it via SQL will cause an imbalance? Seriously that doesn’t even sound like it fits. Get someone else here to corroborate this.<br>
Also it doesn’t matter, in ANY way, if you think it’s ‘stupid’. Period.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I am loving how your argument is boiling down to, “ur a idiot n i cant cum up wif a argument so i call u stoopid”</p>
<p>I didn’t put down his ideas, I simple asked a question, he answered, I offered a better solution, and asked why his was better, and he gave up.  Most people will gladly tell you why their idea is better, when they think it is indeed better.  But for some reason he didn’t, and when this happens, it generally means they don’t think their idea is better.  As for people arguing with me, ya, it pretty much is a lost cause, unless you’re right, in which case I will admit it, and respect you for it.  But, you aren’t right, so this will continue until you accept defeat, or you’ve had enough.  I am perfectly fine with this, seeing I enjoy arguing with people, and watching them try to win an argument when they’re wrong is rather funny.</p>
<p>The definition by Oxford (official dictionary of the English language) - having or revealing an exaggerated sense of one’s own importance or abilities.  Which goes along with exactly what I said…  The one you provided is from wiktionary, which is rather unreliable, seeing anyone can modify it.</p>
<p>If you had the ability to think, you’d see, very clearly, that skills would be unbalanced if you modified exp for a single action, instead of just multiplying the base xp by a certain value (giving you the xp rate).  Do you even realize that Jagex takes almost everything into account when it comes to skills?  They count the number of steps to a bank, from an anvil, and furnace, etc.  And if you mindlessly go and change the base xp given for an action, you’ve wasted the time, and effort they went through to balance skills.  Furthermore, I don’t think you understand the concept of a constant; they never change, therefore making them flexible is idiotic.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>That isn’t at all what my argument is boiling down to; How you came up with that is beyond me. Then again it’s typical for any of you Moparscape kids to randomly think of a random sentence and attempt to use it against someone when it makes no sense at all.</p>
<p>You can try and make what you said out to be something that you didn’t do. I can make what you say out to what you actually <span class="bbcode-u">did</span> do. Point of the matter is, you did do it, no matter how many times you deny it. Simple as that.<br>
I’m also perfectly fine with arguing to the bitter end. You obviously don’t know exactly who I am. We can drag this on to grammar for all I care; You will give up before I do and that’s a fact.</p>
<p>I just checked 3 sources, 3 of which supported “Overbearing pride”. Yes, someone modified 3 dictionaries and added a new definition for arrogance. Yep that must be the case. We have a bunch of outlaws running around changing definitions!</p>
<p>You don’t understand the concept of which he tried explaining to you. I honestly don’t feel like it either, but think of it like this;</p>
<p>-New game just starting, the owner isn’t sure about the EXP rate so he is constantly making changes to fit his needs. It’s easy update-able.</p>
<p>That is just 1 example. I can think of at least 3 why it would be a cool idea. Just because you find it idiotic (and I’m really sick of saying this) doesn’t mean it’s a bad idea; So really… Just shut it.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>The last few posts (besides this one) have been mainly about calling me an idiot, moron, etc…</p>
<p>Questioning someones idea is not putting it down…  And I don’t care who you are tbh…</p>
<p>It doesn’t matter which sources you checked, the Oxford dictionary is the official dictionary of the English language, you can’t argue the definition.</p>
<p>As for changing the XP rate, that’s fine and dandy, but you don’t need to change the XP of each action, for each skill…  And I’d like to hear all these reasons as to why it’d be cool…</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Read back, you may understand why. It still doesn’t matter; When I call you an idiot or moron, it’s because you completely made a fool out of yourself (which you did). It is not at all what my argument is coming down to (hence my last post), but damn if I’m not going to point out your stupidity.</p>
<p>Your first post was questioning. The rest was putting it down. You’ve still have been putting it down, even with me. Let me quote you; “they never change, therefore making them flexible is idiotic.”. If you STILL don’t see how that is an attempt to put it down.<br>
This is just like the last argument we were in. When you said I had intentions of making ‘Kryptix’ to look like a fool when I posted the piece of code. Where I’m from, that’s not insulting, yet you wouldn’t shut up about how it was insulting. SAME RULES APPLY HERE TOO BUDDY. Acting like your ideas are much better, passing it off just as an (and I quote) “idiotic” idea while being sarcastic about it is putting someone down, my friend.</p>
<p>Sarcasm isn’t arguing, it’s mocking according to your oxford dictionary. Regardless if some book doesn’t say what it means, I know what <span class="bbcode-b"><span class="bbcode-u">I</span></span> meant, and I’m pretty confident that you do too.</p>
<p>Actually my friend, you do. Each ore you smelt, each bar you smith has it’s own EXP. Prayers, agility, herblaw, need I go on? As you said yourself (you may have anyways), if they’re not correct it could be imbalanced. Why not make it easier on yourself with just a ‘point and click’ instead of ‘point, click, edit, save, compile’ for each skill?</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I haven’t made a fool of myself, it’s actually quite the opposite…</p>
<p>I didn’t “put-down” the idea until the 18th post of this thread, and he had given up well before then.  Your initial argument was that he quit because I “put-down” his idea, anything I said that is a “put-down” after that is completely irrelevant.  As for pointing out you trying to be a dick, and me not leaving it alone, I made 2 posts talking about it, which is not by any normal standards “not leaving it alone.”</p>
<p>If you’re trying to say when I called his idea amazing was sarcasm, you’re wrong, but I can see how it can be misinterpreted.  In that post, I was being completely serious, because I do like hearing other peoples ideas.  I generally don’t care how dumb their idea is, as long as they have a good reason for doing so.</p>
<p>Ya, I understand exactly how much work it is to change the xp of each individual task, for each skill, and it’s good that it’s a lot because they’re constants; they should not be changed.  If you change them they will be imbalanced, because they are currently balanced by Jagex.  Additionally, it would not be ‘point and click’ it would be, ‘access the SQL server, access the correct database, access the SQL table, find the value, edit the value, execute the query, and restart the server’ vs what it currently is (‘find the file, decompress, find the value, edit it, save, compress, restart the server’), and both take about the same time.  And, if you decided to make an interface for editing the SQL verson (ie making it connect to the correct database/table to reduce steps the user takes), you could just as easily make on for the compressed XML version.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>It’s hard to admit that you’re wrong; I know. You just can’t swallow your <span class="bbcode-u"><span class="bbcode-b">pride</span></span>. I admit I have trouble doing it also; But I actually do it when it is due. I’ll give you some time though, I understand that it may take others a little bit more time. Don’t worry, you will get there.</p>
<p>Ok lets recap. He offered the idea, you asked a question, he gave an honest answer, and then you missed the point entirely (which he pointed out), and then you posted.<br>
Now, you argue that it wasn’t sarcasm, CLEARLY it is, but you argue that it isn’t, because you were SO interested in ideas (which you disprove here because throughout this whole topic you’ve been trying to shut out the idea rather than looking at the Pros). If it wasn’t sarcasm, you would drop this part of the argument a long time ago. So, I’m not buying it; It is too clear that it’s sarcasm for me to think otherwise. Even when I try not to think of it as sarcasm, the wording doesn’t fit at all. SO, the 9’th post, right before he stopped, is when this started.<br>
Also I’m going to point out, that after he left (the very next post), you still continued, as one would try to bait the person back. THAT is clear.</p>
<p>What exactly do you mean “they shouldn’t be changed”? Adding an EXP multiplier is changing them. Your argument isn’t holding up in my eyes. Also in my example we’re not talking about changing them mid-game after it has been up for a couple weeks, we’re talking about making it easier for the person when first opening (which you don’t seem to understand).<br>
Now your argument is going to be “Jagex doesn’t change them, so neither should you”? What?</p>
<p>When talking to The_AFKer over MSN about this when it first started, the main idea was just having options on your site ((I can provide proof of this) Ex: making it easier for the person). This was another one of those “cool ideas” i had in mind, so I’ll say it now. So with this in mind, you wouldn’t have to ‘open SQL, find the table’ blah blah, no you would just jump on the site and modify it instantly.</p>
<p>On a side note: In EasyRSC, can’t you modify the EXP on the GUI? I never even bothered with that source, but I can vaguely remember a picture of it someone sent me.[/quote]</p>
<p>You’re wrong, it’s not hard for me to admit I’m wrong.  I can’t help but laugh at how you think you’re proving things, when all you’re doing is using logical fallacies.</p>
<p>You obviously don’t know me, or my style of sarcasm.  It’s generally subtle… (btw I love how often you use logical fallacies)  Furthermore, I have looked at the pros, and cons, but the pros you have provided are not pros at all, and are completely worthless.</p>
<p>Adding a multiplier is not changing the data (read ratio), it’s simply shifting the amount given.  Changing the XP multiplier is perfectly fine, seeing you’re not changing the data/ratio (which I have already said multiple times), additionally, changing the multiplier is easier than changing the data for each action, because you literally change the multiplier, and can scale the amount of xp given.  My argument has never been, “Jagex doesn’t change them, so neither should you.” my argument is that Jagex spent a considerable amount of time calculating the relative difficulty for each action, and assigning them values relative to the others, and they have balanced skills, so that a single action isn’t more advantageous than another for the current state of the skill.</p>
<p>Ok, so you’re doing exactly what I said, making an interface to do this easily…  You can do the exact same thing with the current system (not that it should be done(with either method), but it can be).</p>
<p>Response to side note:  No clue, but it would be modifying the xp multiplier, not the actual data itself.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/i-cant-find-the-file-which-has-the-prayer-xp-init/358918/36">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/i-cant-find-the-file-which-has-the-prayer-xp-init/358918/36</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 11 Sep 2010 10:24:46 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-358918-36</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/i-cant-find-the-file-which-has-the-prayer-xp-init/358918.rss">I cant find the file which has the prayer xp init</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>I cant find the file which has the prayer xp init</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Asylum Asylum]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/asylum">@Asylum</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“CodeForFame, post:34, topic:358918”][quote author=Asylum link=topic=455416.msg3338690#msg3338690 date=1284170185]</p>
<p>[quote author=CodeForFame link=topic=455416.msg3338401#msg3338401 date=1284154729]</p>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p>I don’t care what anyone thinks of me, seeing it doesn’t matter, and I am happy with who I am.  As for your attempts at insulting my intelligence, I merely laugh.  As for your degrade in respect towards me, I can only speculate as to the reason, but I think that you started to try and argue with me, and that you’re butthurt from losing.[/quote]</p>
<p>What exactly am I losing? What? Not a single thing. You’re acting as if you’re in some heated argument to where someone can win or lose. CodeForFame, how old are you?<br>
If you’re happy being an <span class="bbcode-u">arrogant</span>, stubborn human being then that is all on you. You will soon find out, you’ll get no where in life this way.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p>As for you not knowing what arrogance is, it is clear, since you said this, " Also what was the point of saying I don’t know what arrogant means, and then acknowledging that you were being arrogant."  I did not acknowledge being arrogant (seeing I wasn’t) I was simply explaining what had transpired, then stated there is a difference between being arrogant, and correct.[/quote]</p>
<p>You’re being arrogant, because you think you’re correct. You get pride out of <span class="bbcode-u">thinking</span> you’re correct, and then play it out by putting down ideas.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p>Additionally, there is something wrong with flexibility, especially when you’re trying to make constants flexible…  Furthermore, I don’t think you understand that the base xp establishes a relationship, between all the actions, and a relative difficulty for each action.  You get more xp, the harder/more advanced the task is.  Altering this ratio can easily cause an imbalance, which would negate all the work that went into balancing it…</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>That’s a very poor excuse to me. Just reading it made me nod my head. It seems as if it took some time for you just to come up with such an excuse.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>You’re losing because every single point you make is being countered.  An argument doesn’t need to be heated to win or lose, there is always a winner and a loser.  As for age, I don’t see how it’s relevant, in any way.  And again, you still haven’t figure out what arrogance is.  I will admit, I am stubborn, but I don’t see how requiring proof/facts/logic is a bad thing…  As for not getting anywhere in life, you make me laugh, I am successful because of my stubbornness.</p>
<p>Thinking your correct isn’t arrogance, but attempting to display superiority, or self-importance is, and I have done neither of those.  And I didn’t put down any ideas until the person presenting those ideas gave up on them, which I can only assume is because they saw flaws.</p>
<p>A poor excuse?  Lol, as I said, I don’t think you understand it.  The basic principle is that you’re trying to add flexibility to constants, which is stupid.  If you can’t understand that, I truly feel sorry for you.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>You’re an idiot dude. Countered how? Lmfao. I can’t help but laugh at you dude; You’re pathetic. I’m almost at a loss of words here. There’s not enough words in the English dictionary to explain how moronic you’re being right now; It’s hilarious.</p>
<p>Also that’s where you’re wrong; The reason why he quit was because you wouldn’t shut up thinking you’re ‘right’ all of the time (putting down his ideas). It’s pointless to keep arguing with people like you (take this for example; Re-read your responses and <span class="bbcode-u">hopefully</span> you will understand; Though I’m not going to count on it).</p>
<p><a href="http://google.com" rel="nofollow noopener">http://google.com</a> define: arrogant - Having excessive pride in oneself</p>
<p>Adding the EXP to their own class and modifying it via SQL will cause an imbalance? Seriously that doesn’t even sound like it fits. Get someone else here to corroborate this.<br>
Also it doesn’t matter, in ANY way, if you think it’s ‘stupid’. Period.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I am loving how your argument is boiling down to, “ur a idiot n i cant cum up wif a argument so i call u stoopid”</p>
<p>I didn’t put down his ideas, I simple asked a question, he answered, I offered a better solution, and asked why his was better, and he gave up.  Most people will gladly tell you why their idea is better, when they think it is indeed better.  But for some reason he didn’t, and when this happens, it generally means they don’t think their idea is better.  As for people arguing with me, ya, it pretty much is a lost cause, unless you’re right, in which case I will admit it, and respect you for it.  But, you aren’t right, so this will continue until you accept defeat, or you’ve had enough.  I am perfectly fine with this, seeing I enjoy arguing with people, and watching them try to win an argument when they’re wrong is rather funny.</p>
<p>The definition by Oxford (official dictionary of the English language) - having or revealing an exaggerated sense of one’s own importance or abilities.  Which goes along with exactly what I said…  The one you provided is from wiktionary, which is rather unreliable, seeing anyone can modify it.</p>
<p>If you had the ability to think, you’d see, very clearly, that skills would be unbalanced if you modified exp for a single action, instead of just multiplying the base xp by a certain value (giving you the xp rate).  Do you even realize that Jagex takes almost everything into account when it comes to skills?  They count the number of steps to a bank, from an anvil, and furnace, etc.  And if you mindlessly go and change the base xp given for an action, you’ve wasted the time, and effort they went through to balance skills.  Furthermore, I don’t think you understand the concept of a constant; they never change, therefore making them flexible is idiotic.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>That isn’t at all what my argument is boiling down to; How you came up with that is beyond me. Then again it’s typical for any of you Moparscape kids to randomly think of a random sentence and attempt to use it against someone when it makes no sense at all.</p>
<p>You can try and make what you said out to be something that you didn’t do. I can make what you say out to what you actually <span class="bbcode-u">did</span> do. Point of the matter is, you did do it, no matter how many times you deny it. Simple as that.<br>
I’m also perfectly fine with arguing to the bitter end. You obviously don’t know exactly who I am. We can drag this on to grammar for all I care; You will give up before I do and that’s a fact.</p>
<p>I just checked 3 sources, 3 of which supported “Overbearing pride”. Yes, someone modified 3 dictionaries and added a new definition for arrogance. Yep that must be the case. We have a bunch of outlaws running around changing definitions!</p>
<p>You don’t understand the concept of which he tried explaining to you. I honestly don’t feel like it either, but think of it like this;</p>
<p>-New game just starting, the owner isn’t sure about the EXP rate so he is constantly making changes to fit his needs. It’s easy update-able.</p>
<p>That is just 1 example. I can think of at least 3 why it would be a cool idea. Just because you find it idiotic (and I’m really sick of saying this) doesn’t mean it’s a bad idea; So really… Just shut it.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>The last few posts (besides this one) have been mainly about calling me an idiot, moron, etc…</p>
<p>Questioning someones idea is not putting it down…  And I don’t care who you are tbh…</p>
<p>It doesn’t matter which sources you checked, the Oxford dictionary is the official dictionary of the English language, you can’t argue the definition.</p>
<p>As for changing the XP rate, that’s fine and dandy, but you don’t need to change the XP of each action, for each skill…  And I’d like to hear all these reasons as to why it’d be cool…</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Read back, you may understand why. It still doesn’t matter; When I call you an idiot or moron, it’s because you completely made a fool out of yourself (which you did). It is not at all what my argument is coming down to (hence my last post), but damn if I’m not going to point out your stupidity.</p>
<p>Your first post was questioning. The rest was putting it down. You’ve still have been putting it down, even with me. Let me quote you; “they never change, therefore making them flexible is idiotic.”. If you STILL don’t see how that is an attempt to put it down.<br>
This is just like the last argument we were in. When you said I had intentions of making ‘Kryptix’ to look like a fool when I posted the piece of code. Where I’m from, that’s not insulting, yet you wouldn’t shut up about how it was insulting. SAME RULES APPLY HERE TOO BUDDY. Acting like your ideas are much better, passing it off just as an (and I quote) “idiotic” idea while being sarcastic about it is putting someone down, my friend.</p>
<p>Sarcasm isn’t arguing, it’s mocking according to your oxford dictionary. Regardless if some book doesn’t say what it means, I know what <span class="bbcode-b"><span class="bbcode-u">I</span></span> meant, and I’m pretty confident that you do too.</p>
<p>Actually my friend, you do. Each ore you smelt, each bar you smith has it’s own EXP. Prayers, agility, herblaw, need I go on? As you said yourself (you may have anyways), if they’re not correct it could be imbalanced. Why not make it easier on yourself with just a ‘point and click’ instead of ‘point, click, edit, save, compile’ for each skill?</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I haven’t made a fool of myself, it’s actually quite the opposite…</p>
<p>I didn’t “put-down” the idea until the 18th post of this thread, and he had given up well before then.  Your initial argument was that he quit because I “put-down” his idea, anything I said that is a “put-down” after that is completely irrelevant.  As for pointing out you trying to be a dick, and me not leaving it alone, I made 2 posts talking about it, which is not by any normal standards “not leaving it alone.”</p>
<p>If you’re trying to say when I called his idea amazing was sarcasm, you’re wrong, but I can see how it can be misinterpreted.  In that post, I was being completely serious, because I do like hearing other peoples ideas.  I generally don’t care how dumb their idea is, as long as they have a good reason for doing so.</p>
<p>Ya, I understand exactly how much work it is to change the xp of each individual task, for each skill, and it’s good that it’s a lot because they’re constants; they should not be changed.  If you change them they will be imbalanced, because they are currently balanced by Jagex.  Additionally, it would not be ‘point and click’ it would be, ‘access the SQL server, access the correct database, access the SQL table, find the value, edit the value, execute the query, and restart the server’ vs what it currently is (‘find the file, decompress, find the value, edit it, save, compress, restart the server’), and both take about the same time.  And, if you decided to make an interface for editing the SQL verson (ie making it connect to the correct database/table to reduce steps the user takes), you could just as easily make on for the compressed XML version.[/quote]</p>
<p>It’s hard to admit that you’re wrong; I know. You just can’t swallow your <span class="bbcode-u"><span class="bbcode-b">pride</span></span>. I admit I have trouble doing it also; But I actually do it when it is due. I’ll give you some time though, I understand that it may take others a little bit more time. Don’t worry, you will get there.</p>
<p>Ok lets recap. He offered the idea, you asked a question, he gave an honest answer, and then you missed the point entirely (which he pointed out), and then you posted.<br>
Now, you argue that it wasn’t sarcasm, CLEARLY it is, but you argue that it isn’t, because you were SO interested in ideas (which you disprove here because throughout this whole topic you’ve been trying to shut out the idea rather than looking at the Pros). If it wasn’t sarcasm, you would drop this part of the argument a long time ago. So, I’m not buying it; It is too clear that it’s sarcasm for me to think otherwise. Even when I try not to think of it as sarcasm, the wording doesn’t fit at all. SO, the 9’th post, right before he stopped, is when this started.<br>
Also I’m going to point out, that after he left (the very next post), you still continued, as one would try to bait the person back. THAT is clear.</p>
<p>What exactly do you mean “they shouldn’t be changed”? Adding an EXP multiplier is changing them. Your argument isn’t holding up in my eyes. Also in my example we’re not talking about changing them mid-game after it has been up for a couple weeks, we’re talking about making it easier for the person when first opening (which you don’t seem to understand).<br>
Now your argument is going to be “Jagex doesn’t change them, so neither should you”? What?</p>
<p>When talking to The_AFKer over MSN about this when it first started, the main idea was just having options on your site ((I can provide proof of this) Ex: making it easier for the person). This was another one of those “cool ideas” i had in mind, so I’ll say it now. So with this in mind, you wouldn’t have to ‘open SQL, find the table’ blah blah, no you would just jump on the site and modify it instantly.</p>
<p>On a side note: In EasyRSC, can’t you modify the EXP on the GUI? I never even bothered with that source, but I can vaguely remember a picture of it someone sent me.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/i-cant-find-the-file-which-has-the-prayer-xp-init/358918/35">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/i-cant-find-the-file-which-has-the-prayer-xp-init/358918/35</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 11 Sep 2010 08:53:25 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-358918-35</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/i-cant-find-the-file-which-has-the-prayer-xp-init/358918.rss">I cant find the file which has the prayer xp init</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>I cant find the file which has the prayer xp init</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@CodeForFame CodeForFame]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/codeforfame">@CodeForFame</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“Asylum, post:31, topic:358918”][quote author=CodeForFame link=topic=455416.msg3338401#msg3338401 date=1284154729]</p>
<p>[quote author=Asylum link=topic=455416.msg3338373#msg3338373 date=1284152576]</p>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p>I don’t care what anyone thinks of me, seeing it doesn’t matter, and I am happy with who I am.  As for your attempts at insulting my intelligence, I merely laugh.  As for your degrade in respect towards me, I can only speculate as to the reason, but I think that you started to try and argue with me, and that you’re butthurt from losing.[/quote]</p>
<p>What exactly am I losing? What? Not a single thing. You’re acting as if you’re in some heated argument to where someone can win or lose. CodeForFame, how old are you?<br>
If you’re happy being an <span class="bbcode-u">arrogant</span>, stubborn human being then that is all on you. You will soon find out, you’ll get no where in life this way.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p>As for you not knowing what arrogance is, it is clear, since you said this, " Also what was the point of saying I don’t know what arrogant means, and then acknowledging that you were being arrogant."  I did not acknowledge being arrogant (seeing I wasn’t) I was simply explaining what had transpired, then stated there is a difference between being arrogant, and correct.[/quote]</p>
<p>You’re being arrogant, because you think you’re correct. You get pride out of <span class="bbcode-u">thinking</span> you’re correct, and then play it out by putting down ideas.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p>Additionally, there is something wrong with flexibility, especially when you’re trying to make constants flexible…  Furthermore, I don’t think you understand that the base xp establishes a relationship, between all the actions, and a relative difficulty for each action.  You get more xp, the harder/more advanced the task is.  Altering this ratio can easily cause an imbalance, which would negate all the work that went into balancing it…</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>That’s a very poor excuse to me. Just reading it made me nod my head. It seems as if it took some time for you just to come up with such an excuse.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>You’re losing because every single point you make is being countered.  An argument doesn’t need to be heated to win or lose, there is always a winner and a loser.  As for age, I don’t see how it’s relevant, in any way.  And again, you still haven’t figure out what arrogance is.  I will admit, I am stubborn, but I don’t see how requiring proof/facts/logic is a bad thing…  As for not getting anywhere in life, you make me laugh, I am successful because of my stubbornness.</p>
<p>Thinking your correct isn’t arrogance, but attempting to display superiority, or self-importance is, and I have done neither of those.  And I didn’t put down any ideas until the person presenting those ideas gave up on them, which I can only assume is because they saw flaws.</p>
<p>A poor excuse?  Lol, as I said, I don’t think you understand it.  The basic principle is that you’re trying to add flexibility to constants, which is stupid.  If you can’t understand that, I truly feel sorry for you.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>You’re an idiot dude. Countered how? Lmfao. I can’t help but laugh at you dude; You’re pathetic. I’m almost at a loss of words here. There’s not enough words in the English dictionary to explain how moronic you’re being right now; It’s hilarious.</p>
<p>Also that’s where you’re wrong; The reason why he quit was because you wouldn’t shut up thinking you’re ‘right’ all of the time (putting down his ideas). It’s pointless to keep arguing with people like you (take this for example; Re-read your responses and <span class="bbcode-u">hopefully</span> you will understand; Though I’m not going to count on it).</p>
<p><a href="http://google.com" rel="nofollow noopener">http://google.com</a> define: arrogant - Having excessive pride in oneself</p>
<p>Adding the EXP to their own class and modifying it via SQL will cause an imbalance? Seriously that doesn’t even sound like it fits. Get someone else here to corroborate this.<br>
Also it doesn’t matter, in ANY way, if you think it’s ‘stupid’. Period.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I am loving how your argument is boiling down to, “ur a idiot n i cant cum up wif a argument so i call u stoopid”</p>
<p>I didn’t put down his ideas, I simple asked a question, he answered, I offered a better solution, and asked why his was better, and he gave up.  Most people will gladly tell you why their idea is better, when they think it is indeed better.  But for some reason he didn’t, and when this happens, it generally means they don’t think their idea is better.  As for people arguing with me, ya, it pretty much is a lost cause, unless you’re right, in which case I will admit it, and respect you for it.  But, you aren’t right, so this will continue until you accept defeat, or you’ve had enough.  I am perfectly fine with this, seeing I enjoy arguing with people, and watching them try to win an argument when they’re wrong is rather funny.</p>
<p>The definition by Oxford (official dictionary of the English language) - having or revealing an exaggerated sense of one’s own importance or abilities.  Which goes along with exactly what I said…  The one you provided is from wiktionary, which is rather unreliable, seeing anyone can modify it.</p>
<p>If you had the ability to think, you’d see, very clearly, that skills would be unbalanced if you modified exp for a single action, instead of just multiplying the base xp by a certain value (giving you the xp rate).  Do you even realize that Jagex takes almost everything into account when it comes to skills?  They count the number of steps to a bank, from an anvil, and furnace, etc.  And if you mindlessly go and change the base xp given for an action, you’ve wasted the time, and effort they went through to balance skills.  Furthermore, I don’t think you understand the concept of a constant; they never change, therefore making them flexible is idiotic.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>That isn’t at all what my argument is boiling down to; How you came up with that is beyond me. Then again it’s typical for any of you Moparscape kids to randomly think of a random sentence and attempt to use it against someone when it makes no sense at all.</p>
<p>You can try and make what you said out to be something that you didn’t do. I can make what you say out to what you actually <span class="bbcode-u">did</span> do. Point of the matter is, you did do it, no matter how many times you deny it. Simple as that.<br>
I’m also perfectly fine with arguing to the bitter end. You obviously don’t know exactly who I am. We can drag this on to grammar for all I care; You will give up before I do and that’s a fact.</p>
<p>I just checked 3 sources, 3 of which supported “Overbearing pride”. Yes, someone modified 3 dictionaries and added a new definition for arrogance. Yep that must be the case. We have a bunch of outlaws running around changing definitions!</p>
<p>You don’t understand the concept of which he tried explaining to you. I honestly don’t feel like it either, but think of it like this;</p>
<p>-New game just starting, the owner isn’t sure about the EXP rate so he is constantly making changes to fit his needs. It’s easy update-able.</p>
<p>That is just 1 example. I can think of at least 3 why it would be a cool idea. Just because you find it idiotic (and I’m really sick of saying this) doesn’t mean it’s a bad idea; So really… Just shut it.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>The last few posts (besides this one) have been mainly about calling me an idiot, moron, etc…</p>
<p>Questioning someones idea is not putting it down…  And I don’t care who you are tbh…</p>
<p>It doesn’t matter which sources you checked, the Oxford dictionary is the official dictionary of the English language, you can’t argue the definition.</p>
<p>As for changing the XP rate, that’s fine and dandy, but you don’t need to change the XP of each action, for each skill…  And I’d like to hear all these reasons as to why it’d be cool…</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Read back, you may understand why. It still doesn’t matter; When I call you an idiot or moron, it’s because you completely made a fool out of yourself (which you did). It is not at all what my argument is coming down to (hence my last post), but damn if I’m not going to point out your stupidity.</p>
<p>Your first post was questioning. The rest was putting it down. You’ve still have been putting it down, even with me. Let me quote you; “they never change, therefore making them flexible is idiotic.”. If you STILL don’t see how that is an attempt to put it down.<br>
This is just like the last argument we were in. When you said I had intentions of making ‘Kryptix’ to look like a fool when I posted the piece of code. Where I’m from, that’s not insulting, yet you wouldn’t shut up about how it was insulting. SAME RULES APPLY HERE TOO BUDDY. Acting like your ideas are much better, passing it off just as an (and I quote) “idiotic” idea while being sarcastic about it is putting someone down, my friend.</p>
<p>Sarcasm isn’t arguing, it’s mocking according to your oxford dictionary. Regardless if some book doesn’t say what it means, I know what <span class="bbcode-b"><span class="bbcode-u">I</span></span> meant, and I’m pretty confident that you do too.</p>
<p>Actually my friend, you do. Each ore you smelt, each bar you smith has it’s own EXP. Prayers, agility, herblaw, need I go on? As you said yourself (you may have anyways), if they’re not correct it could be imbalanced. Why not make it easier on yourself with just a ‘point and click’ instead of ‘point, click, edit, save, compile’ for each skill?[/quote]</p>
<p>I haven’t made a fool of myself, it’s actually quite the opposite…</p>
<p>I didn’t “put-down” the idea until the 18th post of this thread, and he had given up well before then.  Your initial argument was that he quit because I “put-down” his idea, anything I said that is a “put-down” after that is completely irrelevant.  As for pointing out you trying to be a dick, and me not leaving it alone, I made 2 posts talking about it, which is not by any normal standards “not leaving it alone.”</p>
<p>If you’re trying to say when I called his idea amazing was sarcasm, you’re wrong, but I can see how it can be misinterpreted.  In that post, I was being completely serious, because I do like hearing other peoples ideas.  I generally don’t care how dumb their idea is, as long as they have a good reason for doing so.</p>
<p>Ya, I understand exactly how much work it is to change the xp of each individual task, for each skill, and it’s good that it’s a lot because they’re constants; they should not be changed.  If you change them they will be imbalanced, because they are currently balanced by Jagex.  Additionally, it would not be ‘point and click’ it would be, ‘access the SQL server, access the correct database, access the SQL table, find the value, edit the value, execute the query, and restart the server’ vs what it currently is (‘find the file, decompress, find the value, edit it, save, compress, restart the server’), and both take about the same time.  And, if you decided to make an interface for editing the SQL verson (ie making it connect to the correct database/table to reduce steps the user takes), you could just as easily make on for the compressed XML version.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/i-cant-find-the-file-which-has-the-prayer-xp-init/358918/34">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/i-cant-find-the-file-which-has-the-prayer-xp-init/358918/34</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 11 Sep 2010 07:58:34 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-358918-34</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/i-cant-find-the-file-which-has-the-prayer-xp-init/358918.rss">I cant find the file which has the prayer xp init</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>I cant find the file which has the prayer xp init</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Pompano21 Pompano21]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/pompano21">@Pompano21</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Pointless arguement tbh. Each to there own…</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/i-cant-find-the-file-which-has-the-prayer-xp-init/358918/33">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/i-cant-find-the-file-which-has-the-prayer-xp-init/358918/33</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 11 Sep 2010 03:25:37 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-358918-33</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/i-cant-find-the-file-which-has-the-prayer-xp-init/358918.rss">I cant find the file which has the prayer xp init</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>I cant find the file which has the prayer xp init</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Asylum Asylum]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/asylum">@Asylum</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote no-group quote-modified" data-post="2" data-topic="359490">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/kryptix/40/5_513041d5f7104045db30895d3b90af16.png" class="avatar">
</div>
<blockquote>
<p>[quote author=Asylum link=topic=455416.msg3338690#msg3338690 date=1284170185]Why not make it easier on yourself with just a ‘point and click’ instead of ‘point, click, edit, save, compile’ for each skill?</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>If we’re talking about RSCD it would actually be point, click, uncompress, point, click, edit, save, compress… I genuinely think I could edit the actual source code and compile quicker than pissing about extracting a file, editing and re-compressing, etc. It would be really close anyway which is my point.[/quote]</p>
<p>Right. Compress.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/i-cant-find-the-file-which-has-the-prayer-xp-init/358918/32">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/i-cant-find-the-file-which-has-the-prayer-xp-init/358918/32</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 11 Sep 2010 02:12:43 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-358918-32</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/i-cant-find-the-file-which-has-the-prayer-xp-init/358918.rss">I cant find the file which has the prayer xp init</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>I cant find the file which has the prayer xp init</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Asylum Asylum]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/asylum">@Asylum</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“CodeForFame, post:28, topic:358918”][quote author=Asylum link=topic=455416.msg3338373#msg3338373 date=1284152576]</p>
<p>[quote author=CodeForFame link=topic=455416.msg3338250#msg3338250 date=1284146209]</p>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p>I don’t care what anyone thinks of me, seeing it doesn’t matter, and I am happy with who I am.  As for your attempts at insulting my intelligence, I merely laugh.  As for your degrade in respect towards me, I can only speculate as to the reason, but I think that you started to try and argue with me, and that you’re butthurt from losing.[/quote]</p>
<p>What exactly am I losing? What? Not a single thing. You’re acting as if you’re in some heated argument to where someone can win or lose. CodeForFame, how old are you?<br>
If you’re happy being an <span class="bbcode-u">arrogant</span>, stubborn human being then that is all on you. You will soon find out, you’ll get no where in life this way.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p>As for you not knowing what arrogance is, it is clear, since you said this, " Also what was the point of saying I don’t know what arrogant means, and then acknowledging that you were being arrogant."  I did not acknowledge being arrogant (seeing I wasn’t) I was simply explaining what had transpired, then stated there is a difference between being arrogant, and correct.[/quote]</p>
<p>You’re being arrogant, because you think you’re correct. You get pride out of <span class="bbcode-u">thinking</span> you’re correct, and then play it out by putting down ideas.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p>Additionally, there is something wrong with flexibility, especially when you’re trying to make constants flexible…  Furthermore, I don’t think you understand that the base xp establishes a relationship, between all the actions, and a relative difficulty for each action.  You get more xp, the harder/more advanced the task is.  Altering this ratio can easily cause an imbalance, which would negate all the work that went into balancing it…</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>That’s a very poor excuse to me. Just reading it made me nod my head. It seems as if it took some time for you just to come up with such an excuse.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>You’re losing because every single point you make is being countered.  An argument doesn’t need to be heated to win or lose, there is always a winner and a loser.  As for age, I don’t see how it’s relevant, in any way.  And again, you still haven’t figure out what arrogance is.  I will admit, I am stubborn, but I don’t see how requiring proof/facts/logic is a bad thing…  As for not getting anywhere in life, you make me laugh, I am successful because of my stubbornness.</p>
<p>Thinking your correct isn’t arrogance, but attempting to display superiority, or self-importance is, and I have done neither of those.  And I didn’t put down any ideas until the person presenting those ideas gave up on them, which I can only assume is because they saw flaws.</p>
<p>A poor excuse?  Lol, as I said, I don’t think you understand it.  The basic principle is that you’re trying to add flexibility to constants, which is stupid.  If you can’t understand that, I truly feel sorry for you.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>You’re an idiot dude. Countered how? Lmfao. I can’t help but laugh at you dude; You’re pathetic. I’m almost at a loss of words here. There’s not enough words in the English dictionary to explain how moronic you’re being right now; It’s hilarious.</p>
<p>Also that’s where you’re wrong; The reason why he quit was because you wouldn’t shut up thinking you’re ‘right’ all of the time (putting down his ideas). It’s pointless to keep arguing with people like you (take this for example; Re-read your responses and <span class="bbcode-u">hopefully</span> you will understand; Though I’m not going to count on it).</p>
<p><a href="http://google.com" rel="nofollow noopener">http://google.com</a> define: arrogant - Having excessive pride in oneself</p>
<p>Adding the EXP to their own class and modifying it via SQL will cause an imbalance? Seriously that doesn’t even sound like it fits. Get someone else here to corroborate this.<br>
Also it doesn’t matter, in ANY way, if you think it’s ‘stupid’. Period.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I am loving how your argument is boiling down to, “ur a idiot n i cant cum up wif a argument so i call u stoopid”</p>
<p>I didn’t put down his ideas, I simple asked a question, he answered, I offered a better solution, and asked why his was better, and he gave up.  Most people will gladly tell you why their idea is better, when they think it is indeed better.  But for some reason he didn’t, and when this happens, it generally means they don’t think their idea is better.  As for people arguing with me, ya, it pretty much is a lost cause, unless you’re right, in which case I will admit it, and respect you for it.  But, you aren’t right, so this will continue until you accept defeat, or you’ve had enough.  I am perfectly fine with this, seeing I enjoy arguing with people, and watching them try to win an argument when they’re wrong is rather funny.</p>
<p>The definition by Oxford (official dictionary of the English language) - having or revealing an exaggerated sense of one’s own importance or abilities.  Which goes along with exactly what I said…  The one you provided is from wiktionary, which is rather unreliable, seeing anyone can modify it.</p>
<p>If you had the ability to think, you’d see, very clearly, that skills would be unbalanced if you modified exp for a single action, instead of just multiplying the base xp by a certain value (giving you the xp rate).  Do you even realize that Jagex takes almost everything into account when it comes to skills?  They count the number of steps to a bank, from an anvil, and furnace, etc.  And if you mindlessly go and change the base xp given for an action, you’ve wasted the time, and effort they went through to balance skills.  Furthermore, I don’t think you understand the concept of a constant; they never change, therefore making them flexible is idiotic.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>That isn’t at all what my argument is boiling down to; How you came up with that is beyond me. Then again it’s typical for any of you Moparscape kids to randomly think of a random sentence and attempt to use it against someone when it makes no sense at all.</p>
<p>You can try and make what you said out to be something that you didn’t do. I can make what you say out to what you actually <span class="bbcode-u">did</span> do. Point of the matter is, you did do it, no matter how many times you deny it. Simple as that.<br>
I’m also perfectly fine with arguing to the bitter end. You obviously don’t know exactly who I am. We can drag this on to grammar for all I care; You will give up before I do and that’s a fact.</p>
<p>I just checked 3 sources, 3 of which supported “Overbearing pride”. Yes, someone modified 3 dictionaries and added a new definition for arrogance. Yep that must be the case. We have a bunch of outlaws running around changing definitions!</p>
<p>You don’t understand the concept of which he tried explaining to you. I honestly don’t feel like it either, but think of it like this;</p>
<p>-New game just starting, the owner isn’t sure about the EXP rate so he is constantly making changes to fit his needs. It’s easy update-able.</p>
<p>That is just 1 example. I can think of at least 3 why it would be a cool idea. Just because you find it idiotic (and I’m really sick of saying this) doesn’t mean it’s a bad idea; So really… Just shut it.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>The last few posts (besides this one) have been mainly about calling me an idiot, moron, etc…</p>
<p>Questioning someones idea is not putting it down…  And I don’t care who you are tbh…</p>
<p>It doesn’t matter which sources you checked, the Oxford dictionary is the official dictionary of the English language, you can’t argue the definition.</p>
<p>As for changing the XP rate, that’s fine and dandy, but you don’t need to change the XP of each action, for each skill…  And I’d like to hear all these reasons as to why it’d be cool…[/quote]</p>
<p>Read back, you may understand why. It still doesn’t matter; When I call you an idiot or moron, it’s because you completely made a fool out of yourself (which you did). It is not at all what my argument is coming down to (hence my last post), but damn if I’m not going to point out your stupidity.</p>
<p>Your first post was questioning. The rest was putting it down. You’ve still have been putting it down, even with me. Let me quote you; “they never change, therefore making them flexible is idiotic.”. If you STILL don’t see how that is an attempt to put it down.<br>
This is just like the last argument we were in. When you said I had intentions of making ‘Kryptix’ to look like a fool when I posted the piece of code. Where I’m from, that’s not insulting, yet you wouldn’t shut up about how it was insulting. SAME RULES APPLY HERE TOO BUDDY. Acting like your ideas are much better, passing it off just as an (and I quote) “idiotic” idea while being sarcastic about it is putting someone down, my friend.</p>
<p>Sarcasm isn’t arguing, it’s mocking according to your oxford dictionary. Regardless if some book doesn’t say what it means, I know what <span class="bbcode-b"><span class="bbcode-u">I</span></span> meant, and I’m pretty confident that you do too.</p>
<p>Actually my friend, you do. Each ore you smelt, each bar you smith has it’s own EXP. Prayers, agility, herblaw, need I go on? As you said yourself (you may have anyways), if they’re not correct it could be imbalanced. Why not make it easier on yourself with just a ‘point and click’ instead of ‘point, click, edit, save, compile’ for each skill?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/i-cant-find-the-file-which-has-the-prayer-xp-init/358918/31">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/i-cant-find-the-file-which-has-the-prayer-xp-init/358918/31</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 11 Sep 2010 01:56:25 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-358918-31</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/i-cant-find-the-file-which-has-the-prayer-xp-init/358918.rss">I cant find the file which has the prayer xp init</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>I cant find the file which has the prayer xp init</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@CodeForFame CodeForFame]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/codeforfame">@CodeForFame</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote no-group" data-post="29" data-topic="358918">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/pompano21/40/5_513041d5f7104045db30895d3b90af16.png" class="avatar"> Pompano21:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>To much quoting going on. My finger hurts from dragging down the page on my iphone!!</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/i-cant-find-the-file-which-has-the-prayer-xp-init/358918/30">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/i-cant-find-the-file-which-has-the-prayer-xp-init/358918/30</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 Sep 2010 22:03:19 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-358918-30</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/i-cant-find-the-file-which-has-the-prayer-xp-init/358918.rss">I cant find the file which has the prayer xp init</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>I cant find the file which has the prayer xp init</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Pompano21 Pompano21]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/pompano21">@Pompano21</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>To much quoting going on. My finger hurts from dragging down the page on my iphone!!</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/i-cant-find-the-file-which-has-the-prayer-xp-init/358918/29">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/i-cant-find-the-file-which-has-the-prayer-xp-init/358918/29</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 Sep 2010 21:56:34 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-358918-29</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/i-cant-find-the-file-which-has-the-prayer-xp-init/358918.rss">I cant find the file which has the prayer xp init</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>I cant find the file which has the prayer xp init</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@CodeForFame CodeForFame]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/codeforfame">@CodeForFame</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“Asylum, post:27, topic:358918”][quote author=CodeForFame link=topic=455416.msg3338250#msg3338250 date=1284146209]</p>
<p>[quote author=Asylum link=topic=455416.msg3338186#msg3338186 date=1284140864]</p>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p>I don’t care what anyone thinks of me, seeing it doesn’t matter, and I am happy with who I am.  As for your attempts at insulting my intelligence, I merely laugh.  As for your degrade in respect towards me, I can only speculate as to the reason, but I think that you started to try and argue with me, and that you’re butthurt from losing.[/quote]</p>
<p>What exactly am I losing? What? Not a single thing. You’re acting as if you’re in some heated argument to where someone can win or lose. CodeForFame, how old are you?<br>
If you’re happy being an <span class="bbcode-u">arrogant</span>, stubborn human being then that is all on you. You will soon find out, you’ll get no where in life this way.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p>As for you not knowing what arrogance is, it is clear, since you said this, " Also what was the point of saying I don’t know what arrogant means, and then acknowledging that you were being arrogant."  I did not acknowledge being arrogant (seeing I wasn’t) I was simply explaining what had transpired, then stated there is a difference between being arrogant, and correct.[/quote]</p>
<p>You’re being arrogant, because you think you’re correct. You get pride out of <span class="bbcode-u">thinking</span> you’re correct, and then play it out by putting down ideas.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p>Additionally, there is something wrong with flexibility, especially when you’re trying to make constants flexible…  Furthermore, I don’t think you understand that the base xp establishes a relationship, between all the actions, and a relative difficulty for each action.  You get more xp, the harder/more advanced the task is.  Altering this ratio can easily cause an imbalance, which would negate all the work that went into balancing it…</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>That’s a very poor excuse to me. Just reading it made me nod my head. It seems as if it took some time for you just to come up with such an excuse.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>You’re losing because every single point you make is being countered.  An argument doesn’t need to be heated to win or lose, there is always a winner and a loser.  As for age, I don’t see how it’s relevant, in any way.  And again, you still haven’t figure out what arrogance is.  I will admit, I am stubborn, but I don’t see how requiring proof/facts/logic is a bad thing…  As for not getting anywhere in life, you make me laugh, I am successful because of my stubbornness.</p>
<p>Thinking your correct isn’t arrogance, but attempting to display superiority, or self-importance is, and I have done neither of those.  And I didn’t put down any ideas until the person presenting those ideas gave up on them, which I can only assume is because they saw flaws.</p>
<p>A poor excuse?  Lol, as I said, I don’t think you understand it.  The basic principle is that you’re trying to add flexibility to constants, which is stupid.  If you can’t understand that, I truly feel sorry for you.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>You’re an idiot dude. Countered how? Lmfao. I can’t help but laugh at you dude; You’re pathetic. I’m almost at a loss of words here. There’s not enough words in the English dictionary to explain how moronic you’re being right now; It’s hilarious.</p>
<p>Also that’s where you’re wrong; The reason why he quit was because you wouldn’t shut up thinking you’re ‘right’ all of the time (putting down his ideas). It’s pointless to keep arguing with people like you (take this for example; Re-read your responses and <span class="bbcode-u">hopefully</span> you will understand; Though I’m not going to count on it).</p>
<p><a href="http://google.com" rel="nofollow noopener">http://google.com</a> define: arrogant - Having excessive pride in oneself</p>
<p>Adding the EXP to their own class and modifying it via SQL will cause an imbalance? Seriously that doesn’t even sound like it fits. Get someone else here to corroborate this.<br>
Also it doesn’t matter, in ANY way, if you think it’s ‘stupid’. Period.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I am loving how your argument is boiling down to, “ur a idiot n i cant cum up wif a argument so i call u stoopid”</p>
<p>I didn’t put down his ideas, I simple asked a question, he answered, I offered a better solution, and asked why his was better, and he gave up.  Most people will gladly tell you why their idea is better, when they think it is indeed better.  But for some reason he didn’t, and when this happens, it generally means they don’t think their idea is better.  As for people arguing with me, ya, it pretty much is a lost cause, unless you’re right, in which case I will admit it, and respect you for it.  But, you aren’t right, so this will continue until you accept defeat, or you’ve had enough.  I am perfectly fine with this, seeing I enjoy arguing with people, and watching them try to win an argument when they’re wrong is rather funny.</p>
<p>The definition by Oxford (official dictionary of the English language) - having or revealing an exaggerated sense of one’s own importance or abilities.  Which goes along with exactly what I said…  The one you provided is from wiktionary, which is rather unreliable, seeing anyone can modify it.</p>
<p>If you had the ability to think, you’d see, very clearly, that skills would be unbalanced if you modified exp for a single action, instead of just multiplying the base xp by a certain value (giving you the xp rate).  Do you even realize that Jagex takes almost everything into account when it comes to skills?  They count the number of steps to a bank, from an anvil, and furnace, etc.  And if you mindlessly go and change the base xp given for an action, you’ve wasted the time, and effort they went through to balance skills.  Furthermore, I don’t think you understand the concept of a constant; they never change, therefore making them flexible is idiotic.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>That isn’t at all what my argument is boiling down to; How you came up with that is beyond me. Then again it’s typical for any of you Moparscape kids to randomly think of a random sentence and attempt to use it against someone when it makes no sense at all.</p>
<p>You can try and make what you said out to be something that you didn’t do. I can make what you say out to what you actually <span class="bbcode-u">did</span> do. Point of the matter is, you did do it, no matter how many times you deny it. Simple as that.<br>
I’m also perfectly fine with arguing to the bitter end. You obviously don’t know exactly who I am. We can drag this on to grammar for all I care; You will give up before I do and that’s a fact.</p>
<p>I just checked 3 sources, 3 of which supported “Overbearing pride”. Yes, someone modified 3 dictionaries and added a new definition for arrogance. Yep that must be the case. We have a bunch of outlaws running around changing definitions!</p>
<p>You don’t understand the concept of which he tried explaining to you. I honestly don’t feel like it either, but think of it like this;</p>
<p>-New game just starting, the owner isn’t sure about the EXP rate so he is constantly making changes to fit his needs. It’s easy update-able.</p>
<p>That is just 1 example. I can think of at least 3 why it would be a cool idea. Just because you find it idiotic (and I’m really sick of saying this) doesn’t mean it’s a bad idea; So really… Just shut it.[/quote]</p>
<p>The last few posts (besides this one) have been mainly about calling me an idiot, moron, etc…</p>
<p>Questioning someones idea is not putting it down…  And I don’t care who you are tbh…</p>
<p>It doesn’t matter which sources you checked, the Oxford dictionary is the official dictionary of the English language, you can’t argue the definition.</p>
<p>As for changing the XP rate, that’s fine and dandy, but you don’t need to change the XP of each action, for each skill…  And I’d like to hear all these reasons as to why it’d be cool…</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/i-cant-find-the-file-which-has-the-prayer-xp-init/358918/28">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/i-cant-find-the-file-which-has-the-prayer-xp-init/358918/28</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 Sep 2010 21:38:49 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-358918-28</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/i-cant-find-the-file-which-has-the-prayer-xp-init/358918.rss">I cant find the file which has the prayer xp init</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>I cant find the file which has the prayer xp init</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Asylum Asylum]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/asylum">@Asylum</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“CodeForFame, post:24, topic:358918”][quote author=Asylum link=topic=455416.msg3338186#msg3338186 date=1284140864]</p>
<p>[quote author=CodeForFame link=topic=455416.msg3338147#msg3338147 date=1284137839]</p>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p>I don’t care what anyone thinks of me, seeing it doesn’t matter, and I am happy with who I am.  As for your attempts at insulting my intelligence, I merely laugh.  As for your degrade in respect towards me, I can only speculate as to the reason, but I think that you started to try and argue with me, and that you’re butthurt from losing.[/quote]</p>
<p>What exactly am I losing? What? Not a single thing. You’re acting as if you’re in some heated argument to where someone can win or lose. CodeForFame, how old are you?<br>
If you’re happy being an <span class="bbcode-u">arrogant</span>, stubborn human being then that is all on you. You will soon find out, you’ll get no where in life this way.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p>As for you not knowing what arrogance is, it is clear, since you said this, " Also what was the point of saying I don’t know what arrogant means, and then acknowledging that you were being arrogant."  I did not acknowledge being arrogant (seeing I wasn’t) I was simply explaining what had transpired, then stated there is a difference between being arrogant, and correct.[/quote]</p>
<p>You’re being arrogant, because you think you’re correct. You get pride out of <span class="bbcode-u">thinking</span> you’re correct, and then play it out by putting down ideas.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p>Additionally, there is something wrong with flexibility, especially when you’re trying to make constants flexible…  Furthermore, I don’t think you understand that the base xp establishes a relationship, between all the actions, and a relative difficulty for each action.  You get more xp, the harder/more advanced the task is.  Altering this ratio can easily cause an imbalance, which would negate all the work that went into balancing it…</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>That’s a very poor excuse to me. Just reading it made me nod my head. It seems as if it took some time for you just to come up with such an excuse.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>You’re losing because every single point you make is being countered.  An argument doesn’t need to be heated to win or lose, there is always a winner and a loser.  As for age, I don’t see how it’s relevant, in any way.  And again, you still haven’t figure out what arrogance is.  I will admit, I am stubborn, but I don’t see how requiring proof/facts/logic is a bad thing…  As for not getting anywhere in life, you make me laugh, I am successful because of my stubbornness.</p>
<p>Thinking your correct isn’t arrogance, but attempting to display superiority, or self-importance is, and I have done neither of those.  And I didn’t put down any ideas until the person presenting those ideas gave up on them, which I can only assume is because they saw flaws.</p>
<p>A poor excuse?  Lol, as I said, I don’t think you understand it.  The basic principle is that you’re trying to add flexibility to constants, which is stupid.  If you can’t understand that, I truly feel sorry for you.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>You’re an idiot dude. Countered how? Lmfao. I can’t help but laugh at you dude; You’re pathetic. I’m almost at a loss of words here. There’s not enough words in the English dictionary to explain how moronic you’re being right now; It’s hilarious.</p>
<p>Also that’s where you’re wrong; The reason why he quit was because you wouldn’t shut up thinking you’re ‘right’ all of the time (putting down his ideas). It’s pointless to keep arguing with people like you (take this for example; Re-read your responses and <span class="bbcode-u">hopefully</span> you will understand; Though I’m not going to count on it).</p>
<p><a href="http://google.com" rel="nofollow noopener">http://google.com</a> define: arrogant - Having excessive pride in oneself</p>
<p>Adding the EXP to their own class and modifying it via SQL will cause an imbalance? Seriously that doesn’t even sound like it fits. Get someone else here to corroborate this.<br>
Also it doesn’t matter, in ANY way, if you think it’s ‘stupid’. Period.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I am loving how your argument is boiling down to, “ur a idiot n i cant cum up wif a argument so i call u stoopid”</p>
<p>I didn’t put down his ideas, I simple asked a question, he answered, I offered a better solution, and asked why his was better, and he gave up.  Most people will gladly tell you why their idea is better, when they think it is indeed better.  But for some reason he didn’t, and when this happens, it generally means they don’t think their idea is better.  As for people arguing with me, ya, it pretty much is a lost cause, unless you’re right, in which case I will admit it, and respect you for it.  But, you aren’t right, so this will continue until you accept defeat, or you’ve had enough.  I am perfectly fine with this, seeing I enjoy arguing with people, and watching them try to win an argument when they’re wrong is rather funny.</p>
<p>The definition by Oxford (official dictionary of the English language) - having or revealing an exaggerated sense of one’s own importance or abilities.  Which goes along with exactly what I said…  The one you provided is from wiktionary, which is rather unreliable, seeing anyone can modify it.</p>
<p>If you had the ability to think, you’d see, very clearly, that skills would be unbalanced if you modified exp for a single action, instead of just multiplying the base xp by a certain value (giving you the xp rate).  Do you even realize that Jagex takes almost everything into account when it comes to skills?  They count the number of steps to a bank, from an anvil, and furnace, etc.  And if you mindlessly go and change the base xp given for an action, you’ve wasted the time, and effort they went through to balance skills.  Furthermore, I don’t think you understand the concept of a constant; they never change, therefore making them flexible is idiotic.[/quote]</p>
<p>That isn’t at all what my argument is boiling down to; How you came up with that is beyond me. Then again it’s typical for any of you Moparscape kids to randomly think of a random sentence and attempt to use it against someone when it makes no sense at all.</p>
<p>You can try and make what you said out to be something that you didn’t do. I can make what you say out to what you actually <span class="bbcode-u">did</span> do. Point of the matter is, you did do it, no matter how many times you deny it. Simple as that.<br>
I’m also perfectly fine with arguing to the bitter end. You obviously don’t know exactly who I am. We can drag this on to grammar for all I care; You will give up before I do and that’s a fact.</p>
<p>I just checked 3 sources, 3 of which supported “Overbearing pride”. Yes, someone modified 3 dictionaries and added a new definition for arrogance. Yep that must be the case. We have a bunch of outlaws running around changing definitions!</p>
<p>You don’t understand the concept of which he tried explaining to you. I honestly don’t feel like it either, but think of it like this;</p>
<p>-New game just starting, the owner isn’t sure about the EXP rate so he is constantly making changes to fit his needs. It’s easy update-able.</p>
<p>That is just 1 example. I can think of at least 3 why it would be a cool idea. Just because you find it idiotic (and I’m really sick of saying this) doesn’t mean it’s a bad idea; So really… Just shut it.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/i-cant-find-the-file-which-has-the-prayer-xp-init/358918/27">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/i-cant-find-the-file-which-has-the-prayer-xp-init/358918/27</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 Sep 2010 21:02:56 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-358918-27</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/i-cant-find-the-file-which-has-the-prayer-xp-init/358918.rss">I cant find the file which has the prayer xp init</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>I cant find the file which has the prayer xp init</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@CodeForFame CodeForFame]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/codeforfame">@CodeForFame</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote no-group quote-modified" data-post="25" data-topic="358918">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/massacrerunescape/40/5_513041d5f7104045db30895d3b90af16.png" class="avatar"> massacrerunescape:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Nice… someone asks for the location of player xp and this starts an argument,</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>The argument was started because someone came up with a moronic idea, and some other moron decided it was a good idea too…  Too bad they don’t know what constants are…</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/i-cant-find-the-file-which-has-the-prayer-xp-init/358918/26">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/i-cant-find-the-file-which-has-the-prayer-xp-init/358918/26</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 Sep 2010 20:37:11 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-358918-26</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/i-cant-find-the-file-which-has-the-prayer-xp-init/358918.rss">I cant find the file which has the prayer xp init</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>I cant find the file which has the prayer xp init</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@massacrerunescape massacrerunescape]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/massacrerunescape">@massacrerunescape</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Nice… someone asks for the location of player xp and this starts an argument,</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/i-cant-find-the-file-which-has-the-prayer-xp-init/358918/25">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/i-cant-find-the-file-which-has-the-prayer-xp-init/358918/25</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 Sep 2010 20:11:20 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-358918-25</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/i-cant-find-the-file-which-has-the-prayer-xp-init/358918.rss">I cant find the file which has the prayer xp init</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>I cant find the file which has the prayer xp init</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@CodeForFame CodeForFame]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/codeforfame">@CodeForFame</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“Asylum, post:22, topic:358918”][quote author=CodeForFame link=topic=455416.msg3338147#msg3338147 date=1284137839]</p>
<p>[quote author=Asylum link=topic=455416.msg3338116#msg3338116 date=1284135392]</p>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p>I don’t care what anyone thinks of me, seeing it doesn’t matter, and I am happy with who I am.  As for your attempts at insulting my intelligence, I merely laugh.  As for your degrade in respect towards me, I can only speculate as to the reason, but I think that you started to try and argue with me, and that you’re butthurt from losing.[/quote]</p>
<p>What exactly am I losing? What? Not a single thing. You’re acting as if you’re in some heated argument to where someone can win or lose. CodeForFame, how old are you?<br>
If you’re happy being an <span class="bbcode-u">arrogant</span>, stubborn human being then that is all on you. You will soon find out, you’ll get no where in life this way.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p>As for you not knowing what arrogance is, it is clear, since you said this, " Also what was the point of saying I don’t know what arrogant means, and then acknowledging that you were being arrogant."  I did not acknowledge being arrogant (seeing I wasn’t) I was simply explaining what had transpired, then stated there is a difference between being arrogant, and correct.[/quote]</p>
<p>You’re being arrogant, because you think you’re correct. You get pride out of <span class="bbcode-u">thinking</span> you’re correct, and then play it out by putting down ideas.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p>Additionally, there is something wrong with flexibility, especially when you’re trying to make constants flexible…  Furthermore, I don’t think you understand that the base xp establishes a relationship, between all the actions, and a relative difficulty for each action.  You get more xp, the harder/more advanced the task is.  Altering this ratio can easily cause an imbalance, which would negate all the work that went into balancing it…</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>That’s a very poor excuse to me. Just reading it made me nod my head. It seems as if it took some time for you just to come up with such an excuse.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>You’re losing because every single point you make is being countered.  An argument doesn’t need to be heated to win or lose, there is always a winner and a loser.  As for age, I don’t see how it’s relevant, in any way.  And again, you still haven’t figure out what arrogance is.  I will admit, I am stubborn, but I don’t see how requiring proof/facts/logic is a bad thing…  As for not getting anywhere in life, you make me laugh, I am successful because of my stubbornness.</p>
<p>Thinking your correct isn’t arrogance, but attempting to display superiority, or self-importance is, and I have done neither of those.  And I didn’t put down any ideas until the person presenting those ideas gave up on them, which I can only assume is because they saw flaws.</p>
<p>A poor excuse?  Lol, as I said, I don’t think you understand it.  The basic principle is that you’re trying to add flexibility to constants, which is stupid.  If you can’t understand that, I truly feel sorry for you.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>You’re an idiot dude. Countered how? Lmfao. I can’t help but laugh at you dude; You’re pathetic. I’m almost at a loss of words here. There’s not enough words in the English dictionary to explain how moronic you’re being right now; It’s hilarious.</p>
<p>Also that’s where you’re wrong; The reason why he quit was because you wouldn’t shut up thinking you’re ‘right’ all of the time (putting down his ideas). It’s pointless to keep arguing with people like you (take this for example; Re-read your responses and <span class="bbcode-u">hopefully</span> you will understand; Though I’m not going to count on it).</p>
<p><a href="http://google.com" rel="nofollow noopener">http://google.com</a> define: arrogant - Having excessive pride in oneself</p>
<p>Adding the EXP to their own class and modifying it via SQL will cause an imbalance? Seriously that doesn’t even sound like it fits. Get someone else here to corroborate this.<br>
Also it doesn’t matter, in ANY way, if you think it’s ‘stupid’. Period.[/quote]</p>
<p>I am loving how your argument is boiling down to, “ur a idiot n i cant cum up wif a argument so i call u stoopid”</p>
<p>I didn’t put down his ideas, I simple asked a question, he answered, I offered a better solution, and asked why his was better, and he gave up.  Most people will gladly tell you why their idea is better, when they think it is indeed better.  But for some reason he didn’t, and when this happens, it generally means they don’t think their idea is better.  As for people arguing with me, ya, it pretty much is a lost cause, unless you’re right, in which case I will admit it, and respect you for it.  But, you aren’t right, so this will continue until you accept defeat, or you’ve had enough.  I am perfectly fine with this, seeing I enjoy arguing with people, and watching them try to win an argument when they’re wrong is rather funny.</p>
<p>The definition by Oxford (official dictionary of the English language) - having or revealing an exaggerated sense of one’s own importance or abilities.  Which goes along with exactly what I said…  The one you provided is from wiktionary, which is rather unreliable, seeing anyone can modify it.</p>
<p>If you had the ability to think, you’d see, very clearly, that skills would be unbalanced if you modified exp for a single action, instead of just multiplying the base xp by a certain value (giving you the xp rate).  Do you even realize that Jagex takes almost everything into account when it comes to skills?  They count the number of steps to a bank, from an anvil, and furnace, etc.  And if you mindlessly go and change the base xp given for an action, you’ve wasted the time, and effort they went through to balance skills.  Furthermore, I don’t think you understand the concept of a constant; they never change, therefore making them flexible is idiotic.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/i-cant-find-the-file-which-has-the-prayer-xp-init/358918/24">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/i-cant-find-the-file-which-has-the-prayer-xp-init/358918/24</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 Sep 2010 19:16:49 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-358918-24</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/i-cant-find-the-file-which-has-the-prayer-xp-init/358918.rss">I cant find the file which has the prayer xp init</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>I cant find the file which has the prayer xp init</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Old_Rsc_Player Old Rsc Player]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/old_rsc_player">@Old_Rsc_Player</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Im not going read all of this shit.</p>
<p>/thread</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/i-cant-find-the-file-which-has-the-prayer-xp-init/358918/23">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/i-cant-find-the-file-which-has-the-prayer-xp-init/358918/23</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 Sep 2010 18:08:08 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-358918-23</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/i-cant-find-the-file-which-has-the-prayer-xp-init/358918.rss">I cant find the file which has the prayer xp init</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>I cant find the file which has the prayer xp init</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Asylum Asylum]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/asylum">@Asylum</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“CodeForFame, post:21, topic:358918”][quote author=Asylum link=topic=455416.msg3338116#msg3338116 date=1284135392]</p>
<p>[quote author=CodeForFame link=topic=455416.msg3338101#msg3338101 date=1284133821]<br>
I don’t care what anyone thinks of me, seeing it doesn’t matter, and I am happy with who I am.  As for your attempts at insulting my intelligence, I merely laugh.  As for your degrade in respect towards me, I can only speculate as to the reason, but I think that you started to try and argue with me, and that you’re butthurt from losing.[/quote]</p>
<p>What exactly am I losing? What? Not a single thing. You’re acting as if you’re in some heated argument to where someone can win or lose. CodeForFame, how old are you?<br>
If you’re happy being an <span class="bbcode-u">arrogant</span>, stubborn human being then that is all on you. You will soon find out, you’ll get no where in life this way.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p>As for you not knowing what arrogance is, it is clear, since you said this, " Also what was the point of saying I don’t know what arrogant means, and then acknowledging that you were being arrogant."  I did not acknowledge being arrogant (seeing I wasn’t) I was simply explaining what had transpired, then stated there is a difference between being arrogant, and correct.[/quote]</p>
<p>You’re being arrogant, because you think you’re correct. You get pride out of <span class="bbcode-u">thinking</span> you’re correct, and then play it out by putting down ideas.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p>Additionally, there is something wrong with flexibility, especially when you’re trying to make constants flexible…  Furthermore, I don’t think you understand that the base xp establishes a relationship, between all the actions, and a relative difficulty for each action.  You get more xp, the harder/more advanced the task is.  Altering this ratio can easily cause an imbalance, which would negate all the work that went into balancing it…</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>That’s a very poor excuse to me. Just reading it made me nod my head. It seems as if it took some time for you just to come up with such an excuse.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>You’re losing because every single point you make is being countered.  An argument doesn’t need to be heated to win or lose, there is always a winner and a loser.  As for age, I don’t see how it’s relevant, in any way.  And again, you still haven’t figure out what arrogance is.  I will admit, I am stubborn, but I don’t see how requiring proof/facts/logic is a bad thing…  As for not getting anywhere in life, you make me laugh, I am successful because of my stubbornness.</p>
<p>Thinking your correct isn’t arrogance, but attempting to display superiority, or self-importance is, and I have done neither of those.  And I didn’t put down any ideas until the person presenting those ideas gave up on them, which I can only assume is because they saw flaws.</p>
<p>A poor excuse?  Lol, as I said, I don’t think you understand it.  The basic principle is that you’re trying to add flexibility to constants, which is stupid.  If you can’t understand that, I truly feel sorry for you.[/quote]</p>
<p>You’re an idiot dude. Countered how? Lmfao. I can’t help but laugh at you dude; You’re pathetic. I’m almost at a loss of words here. There’s not enough words in the English dictionary to explain how moronic you’re being right now; It’s hilarious.</p>
<p>Also that’s where you’re wrong; The reason why he quit was because you wouldn’t shut up thinking you’re ‘right’ all of the time (putting down his ideas). It’s pointless to keep arguing with people like you (take this for example; Re-read your responses and <span class="bbcode-u">hopefully</span> you will understand; Though I’m not going to count on it).</p>
<p><a href="http://google.com" rel="nofollow noopener">http://google.com</a> define: arrogant - Having excessive pride in oneself</p>
<p>Adding the EXP to their own class and modifying it via SQL will cause an imbalance? Seriously that doesn’t even sound like it fits. Get someone else here to corroborate this.<br>
Also it doesn’t matter, in ANY way, if you think it’s ‘stupid’. Period.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/i-cant-find-the-file-which-has-the-prayer-xp-init/358918/22">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/i-cant-find-the-file-which-has-the-prayer-xp-init/358918/22</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 Sep 2010 17:47:44 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-358918-22</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/i-cant-find-the-file-which-has-the-prayer-xp-init/358918.rss">I cant find the file which has the prayer xp init</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>I cant find the file which has the prayer xp init</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@CodeForFame CodeForFame]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/codeforfame">@CodeForFame</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“Asylum, post:20, topic:358918”][quote author=CodeForFame link=topic=455416.msg3338101#msg3338101 date=1284133821]<br>
I don’t care what anyone thinks of me, seeing it doesn’t matter, and I am happy with who I am.  As for your attempts at insulting my intelligence, I merely laugh.  As for your degrade in respect towards me, I can only speculate as to the reason, but I think that you started to try and argue with me, and that you’re butthurt from losing.[/quote]</p>
<p>What exactly am I losing? What? Not a single thing. You’re acting as if you’re in some heated argument to where someone can win or lose. CodeForFame, how old are you?<br>
If you’re happy being an <span class="bbcode-u">arrogant</span>, stubborn human being then that is all on you. You will soon find out, you’ll get no where in life this way.</p>
<p>[quote author=CodeForFame link=topic=455416.msg3338101#msg3338101 date=1284133821]<br>
As for you not knowing what arrogance is, it is clear, since you said this, " Also what was the point of saying I don’t know what arrogant means, and then acknowledging that you were being arrogant."  I did not acknowledge being arrogant (seeing I wasn’t) I was simply explaining what had transpired, then stated there is a difference between being arrogant, and correct.[/quote]</p>
<p>You’re being arrogant, because you think you’re correct. You get pride out of <span class="bbcode-u">thinking</span> you’re correct, and then play it out by putting down ideas.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p>Additionally, there is something wrong with flexibility, especially when you’re trying to make constants flexible…  Furthermore, I don’t think you understand that the base xp establishes a relationship, between all the actions, and a relative difficulty for each action.  You get more xp, the harder/more advanced the task is.  Altering this ratio can easily cause an imbalance, which would negate all the work that went into balancing it…</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>That’s a very poor excuse to me. Just reading it made me nod my head. It seems as if it took some time for you just to come up with such an excuse.[/quote]</p>
<p>You’re losing because every single point you make is being countered.  An argument doesn’t need to be heated to win or lose, there is always a winner and a loser.  As for age, I don’t see how it’s relevant, in any way.  And again, you still haven’t figure out what arrogance is.  I will admit, I am stubborn, but I don’t see how requiring proof/facts/logic is a bad thing…  As for not getting anywhere in life, you make me laugh, I am successful because of my stubbornness.</p>
<p>Thinking your correct isn’t arrogance, but attempting to display superiority, or self-importance is, and I have done neither of those.  And I didn’t put down any ideas until the person presenting those ideas gave up on them, which I can only assume is because they saw flaws.</p>
<p>A poor excuse?  Lol, as I said, I don’t think you understand it.  The basic principle is that you’re trying to add flexibility to constants, which is stupid.  If you can’t understand that, I truly feel sorry for you.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/i-cant-find-the-file-which-has-the-prayer-xp-init/358918/21">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/i-cant-find-the-file-which-has-the-prayer-xp-init/358918/21</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 Sep 2010 16:57:19 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-358918-21</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/i-cant-find-the-file-which-has-the-prayer-xp-init/358918.rss">I cant find the file which has the prayer xp init</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>I cant find the file which has the prayer xp init</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Asylum Asylum]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/asylum">@Asylum</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote no-group quote-modified" data-post="19" data-topic="358918">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/user_avatar/forum.moparisthebest.com/codeforfame/40/3743_1.png" class="avatar"> CodeForFame:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>I don’t care what anyone thinks of me, seeing it doesn’t matter, and I am happy with who I am.  As for your attempts at insulting my intelligence, I merely laugh.  As for your degrade in respect towards me, I can only speculate as to the reason, but I think that you started to try and argue with me, and that you’re butthurt from losing.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>What exactly am I losing? What? Not a single thing. You’re acting as if you’re in some heated argument to where someone can win or lose. CodeForFame, how old are you?<br>
If you’re happy being an <span class="bbcode-u">arrogant</span>, stubborn human being then that is all on you. You will soon find out, you’ll get no where in life this way.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group quote-modified" data-post="19" data-topic="358918">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/user_avatar/forum.moparisthebest.com/codeforfame/40/3743_1.png" class="avatar"> CodeForFame:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>As for you not knowing what arrogance is, it is clear, since you said this, " Also what was the point of saying I don’t know what arrogant means, and then acknowledging that you were being arrogant."  I did not acknowledge being arrogant (seeing I wasn’t) I was simply explaining what had transpired, then stated there is a difference between being arrogant, and correct.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>You’re being arrogant, because you think you’re correct. You get pride out of <span class="bbcode-u">thinking</span> you’re correct, and then play it out by putting down ideas.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group quote-modified" data-post="19" data-topic="358918">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/user_avatar/forum.moparisthebest.com/codeforfame/40/3743_1.png" class="avatar"> CodeForFame:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Additionally, there is something wrong with flexibility, especially when you’re trying to make constants flexible…  Furthermore, I don’t think you understand that the base xp establishes a relationship, between all the actions, and a relative difficulty for each action.  You get more xp, the harder/more advanced the task is.  Altering this ratio can easily cause an imbalance, which would negate all the work that went into balancing it…</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>That’s a very poor excuse to me. Just reading it made me nod my head. It seems as if it took some time for you just to come up with such an excuse.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/i-cant-find-the-file-which-has-the-prayer-xp-init/358918/20">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/i-cant-find-the-file-which-has-the-prayer-xp-init/358918/20</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 Sep 2010 16:16:32 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-358918-20</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/i-cant-find-the-file-which-has-the-prayer-xp-init/358918.rss">I cant find the file which has the prayer xp init</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>I cant find the file which has the prayer xp init</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@CodeForFame CodeForFame]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/codeforfame">@CodeForFame</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“Asylum, post:18, topic:358918”][quote author=CodeForFame link=topic=455416.msg3338058#msg3338058 date=1284128625]</p>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p>I never understood why experience is handled inside their own methods, why not establish all experience arrays in their own class then modified at the SQL level?</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>How often do you modify the xp of specific actions?</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Depends, say I was doing a daily event for example. During specified event, the amount of exp (say combat, prayer, magic), is doubled or tripled. Once the event ends, exp returns to normal.</p>
<p>I just don’t see why some things need to be listed in static context, why not manipulate data both on the server and client dynamically? Formulas for example, why not change certain variables instantly rather than reloading the entire server?</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I hope you do realize, that you can just check for the skill id and multiply it by whatever factor you want in the method that actually adds the xp.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I already know this, but it seems you missed the point.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Ok, so explain your amazing idea, then come up with a pro-con list for both, and then come tell me why your idea is so much better…</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>It’s not really an amazing idea, was just wondering why we can’t transition from setting everything in a static form and move on to flexible data management. Since you’re gonna be an arrogant dick about it, not going to waste my time.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Because it doesn’t need to be flexible; they’re meant to be constants, as they’re baseline numbers.  If you’re going to propose something, be prepared to explain the pros and cons…</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>You are far too arrogant for your own good. You need to set your ego on the ground for a second and look at things differently for a change.</p>
<p><a class="mention" href="/u/old">@Old</a> rsc player: You don’t understand this concept either. It isn’t making anything more complicated. In fact it would be making it easier as far as management goes.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>You obviously don’t know what arrogance is…  I asked a question, and he gave me response, then I provided an easier solution to the same problem.  Then, he claimed I missed some point (which he has failed to back up), so I asked him to back up his idea with a list of pro/cons (I didn’t ask for a paper analyzing the cost/benefits, I asked for a simple pro/con chart…), and after he decides to not back  up his idea, proceeds to ask a question that has already been answered…  So, I proceed to answer the question, even though it has been answered.</p>
<p>There is a difference between being arrogant and being correct…</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>It’s pointless to argue with someone who thinks they’re always right, which is why he didn’t bother. Also what was the point of saying I don’t know what arrogant means, and then acknowledging that you were being arrogant.</p>
<p>It doesn’t matter if it “doesn’t need” to be flexible. It’s all about customizing. That is all.</p>
<p><a class="mention" href="/u/kryptix">@Kryptix</a>: I’m sorry to say… Well no I’m not. You’re an idiot for thinking The_AFKer is Tewl.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I think I’m always right, because if I didn’t I wouldn’t say anything…  I also know when I’m wrong, and respect people that can prove me wrong.  Furthermore, you just proved that you don’t know the difference.<br>
[/quote]</p>
<p>You’re a moron. Simple as that. I use to respect you, but holy shit, the past week or so you’ve really shown me how big of an idiot you can be.<br>
Nothing that I just said doesn’t even remotely suggest that I don’t know what arrogance is. “Furthermore”, there is nothing <span class="bbcode-u">wrong</span> about a little flexibility. Nothing at all. There isn’t a decrease in performance; Nothing. It just depends if the person bothers to actually implement it or not. Just because you feel that it is not needed does <span class="bbcode-u">not</span> make you “correct”.[/quote]</p>
<p>I don’t care what anyone thinks of me, seeing it doesn’t matter, and I am happy with who I am.  As for your attempts at insulting my intelligence, I merely laugh.  As for your degrade in respect towards me, I can only speculate as to the reason, but I think that you started to try and argue with me, and that you’re butthurt from losing.</p>
<p>As for you not knowing what arrogance is, it is clear, since you said this, " Also what was the point of saying I don’t know what arrogant means, and then acknowledging that you were being arrogant."  I did not acknowledge being arrogant (seeing I wasn’t) I was simply explaining what had transpired, then stated there is a difference between being arrogant, and correct.</p>
<p>Additionally, there is something wrong with flexibility, especially when you’re trying to make constants flexible…  Furthermore, I don’t think you understand that the base xp establishes a relationship, between all the actions, and a relative difficulty for each action.  You get more xp, the harder/more advanced the task is.  Altering this ratio can easily cause an imbalance, which would negate all the work that went into balancing it…</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/i-cant-find-the-file-which-has-the-prayer-xp-init/358918/19">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/i-cant-find-the-file-which-has-the-prayer-xp-init/358918/19</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 Sep 2010 15:50:21 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-358918-19</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/i-cant-find-the-file-which-has-the-prayer-xp-init/358918.rss">I cant find the file which has the prayer xp init</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>I cant find the file which has the prayer xp init</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Asylum Asylum]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/asylum">@Asylum</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“CodeForFame, post:17, topic:358918”][quote author=Asylum link=topic=455416.msg3338037#msg3338037 date=1284126902]</p>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p>I never understood why experience is handled inside their own methods, why not establish all experience arrays in their own class then modified at the SQL level?</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>How often do you modify the xp of specific actions?</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Depends, say I was doing a daily event for example. During specified event, the amount of exp (say combat, prayer, magic), is doubled or tripled. Once the event ends, exp returns to normal.</p>
<p>I just don’t see why some things need to be listed in static context, why not manipulate data both on the server and client dynamically? Formulas for example, why not change certain variables instantly rather than reloading the entire server?</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I hope you do realize, that you can just check for the skill id and multiply it by whatever factor you want in the method that actually adds the xp.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I already know this, but it seems you missed the point.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Ok, so explain your amazing idea, then come up with a pro-con list for both, and then come tell me why your idea is so much better…</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>It’s not really an amazing idea, was just wondering why we can’t transition from setting everything in a static form and move on to flexible data management. Since you’re gonna be an arrogant dick about it, not going to waste my time.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Because it doesn’t need to be flexible; they’re meant to be constants, as they’re baseline numbers.  If you’re going to propose something, be prepared to explain the pros and cons…</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>You are far too arrogant for your own good. You need to set your ego on the ground for a second and look at things differently for a change.</p>
<p><a class="mention" href="/u/old">@Old</a> rsc player: You don’t understand this concept either. It isn’t making anything more complicated. In fact it would be making it easier as far as management goes.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>You obviously don’t know what arrogance is…  I asked a question, and he gave me response, then I provided an easier solution to the same problem.  Then, he claimed I missed some point (which he has failed to back up), so I asked him to back up his idea with a list of pro/cons (I didn’t ask for a paper analyzing the cost/benefits, I asked for a simple pro/con chart…), and after he decides to not back  up his idea, proceeds to ask a question that has already been answered…  So, I proceed to answer the question, even though it has been answered.</p>
<p>There is a difference between being arrogant and being correct…</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>It’s pointless to argue with someone who thinks they’re always right, which is why he didn’t bother. Also what was the point of saying I don’t know what arrogant means, and then acknowledging that you were being arrogant.</p>
<p>It doesn’t matter if it “doesn’t need” to be flexible. It’s all about customizing. That is all.</p>
<p><a class="mention" href="/u/kryptix">@Kryptix</a>: I’m sorry to say… Well no I’m not. You’re an idiot for thinking The_AFKer is Tewl.</p>
<p>[/quote]</p>
<p>I think I’m always right, because if I didn’t I wouldn’t say anything…  I also know when I’m wrong, and respect people that can prove me wrong.  Furthermore, you just proved that you don’t know the difference.[/quote]</p>
<p>You’re a moron. Simple as that. I use to respect you, but holy shit, the past week or so you’ve really shown me how big of an idiot you can be.<br>
Nothing that I just said doesn’t even remotely suggest that I don’t know what arrogance is. “Furthermore”, there is nothing <span class="bbcode-u">wrong</span> about a little flexibility. Nothing at all. There isn’t a decrease in performance; Nothing. It just depends if the person bothers to actually implement it or not. Just because you feel that it is not needed does <span class="bbcode-u">not</span> make you “correct”.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/i-cant-find-the-file-which-has-the-prayer-xp-init/358918/18">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/i-cant-find-the-file-which-has-the-prayer-xp-init/358918/18</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 Sep 2010 14:38:30 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-358918-18</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/i-cant-find-the-file-which-has-the-prayer-xp-init/358918.rss">I cant find the file which has the prayer xp init</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>I cant find the file which has the prayer xp init</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@CodeForFame CodeForFame]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/codeforfame">@CodeForFame</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“Asylum, post:16, topic:358918”][quote author=CodeForFame link=topic=455416.msg3338016#msg3338016 date=1284125139]</p>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p>I never understood why experience is handled inside their own methods, why not establish all experience arrays in their own class then modified at the SQL level?</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>How often do you modify the xp of specific actions?</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Depends, say I was doing a daily event for example. During specified event, the amount of exp (say combat, prayer, magic), is doubled or tripled. Once the event ends, exp returns to normal.</p>
<p>I just don’t see why some things need to be listed in static context, why not manipulate data both on the server and client dynamically? Formulas for example, why not change certain variables instantly rather than reloading the entire server?</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I hope you do realize, that you can just check for the skill id and multiply it by whatever factor you want in the method that actually adds the xp.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I already know this, but it seems you missed the point.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Ok, so explain your amazing idea, then come up with a pro-con list for both, and then come tell me why your idea is so much better…</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>It’s not really an amazing idea, was just wondering why we can’t transition from setting everything in a static form and move on to flexible data management. Since you’re gonna be an arrogant dick about it, not going to waste my time.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Because it doesn’t need to be flexible; they’re meant to be constants, as they’re baseline numbers.  If you’re going to propose something, be prepared to explain the pros and cons…</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>You are far too arrogant for your own good. You need to set your ego on the ground for a second and look at things differently for a change.</p>
<p><a class="mention" href="/u/old">@Old</a> rsc player: You don’t understand this concept either. It isn’t making anything more complicated. In fact it would be making it easier as far as management goes.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>You obviously don’t know what arrogance is…  I asked a question, and he gave me response, then I provided an easier solution to the same problem.  Then, he claimed I missed some point (which he has failed to back up), so I asked him to back up his idea with a list of pro/cons (I didn’t ask for a paper analyzing the cost/benefits, I asked for a simple pro/con chart…), and after he decides to not back  up his idea, proceeds to ask a question that has already been answered…  So, I proceed to answer the question, even though it has been answered.</p>
<p>There is a difference between being arrogant and being correct…<br>
[/quote]</p>
<p>It’s pointless to argue with someone who thinks they’re always right, which is why he didn’t bother. Also what was the point of saying I don’t know what arrogant means, and then acknowledging that you were being arrogant.</p>
<p>It doesn’t matter if it “doesn’t need” to be flexible. It’s all about customizing. That is all.</p>
<p><a class="mention" href="/u/kryptix">@Kryptix</a>: I’m sorry to say… Well no I’m not. You’re an idiot for thinking The_AFKer is Tewl.[/quote]</p>
<p>I think I’m always right, because if I didn’t I wouldn’t say anything…  I also know when I’m wrong, and respect people that can prove me wrong.  Furthermore, you just proved that you don’t know the difference.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/i-cant-find-the-file-which-has-the-prayer-xp-init/358918/17">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/i-cant-find-the-file-which-has-the-prayer-xp-init/358918/17</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 Sep 2010 14:23:45 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-358918-17</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/i-cant-find-the-file-which-has-the-prayer-xp-init/358918.rss">I cant find the file which has the prayer xp init</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>I cant find the file which has the prayer xp init</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Asylum Asylum]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/asylum">@Asylum</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“CodeForFame, post:15, topic:358918”][quote author=Asylum link=topic=455416.msg3337838#msg3337838 date=1284098801]</p>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p>I never understood why experience is handled inside their own methods, why not establish all experience arrays in their own class then modified at the SQL level?</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>How often do you modify the xp of specific actions?</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Depends, say I was doing a daily event for example. During specified event, the amount of exp (say combat, prayer, magic), is doubled or tripled. Once the event ends, exp returns to normal.</p>
<p>I just don’t see why some things need to be listed in static context, why not manipulate data both on the server and client dynamically? Formulas for example, why not change certain variables instantly rather than reloading the entire server?</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I hope you do realize, that you can just check for the skill id and multiply it by whatever factor you want in the method that actually adds the xp.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I already know this, but it seems you missed the point.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Ok, so explain your amazing idea, then come up with a pro-con list for both, and then come tell me why your idea is so much better…</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>It’s not really an amazing idea, was just wondering why we can’t transition from setting everything in a static form and move on to flexible data management. Since you’re gonna be an arrogant dick about it, not going to waste my time.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Because it doesn’t need to be flexible; they’re meant to be constants, as they’re baseline numbers.  If you’re going to propose something, be prepared to explain the pros and cons…</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>You are far too arrogant for your own good. You need to set your ego on the ground for a second and look at things differently for a change.</p>
<p><a class="mention" href="/u/old">@Old</a> rsc player: You don’t understand this concept either. It isn’t making anything more complicated. In fact it would be making it easier as far as management goes.<br>
[/quote]</p>
<p>You obviously don’t know what arrogance is…  I asked a question, and he gave me response, then I provided an easier solution to the same problem.  Then, he claimed I missed some point (which he has failed to back up), so I asked him to back up his idea with a list of pro/cons (I didn’t ask for a paper analyzing the cost/benefits, I asked for a simple pro/con chart…), and after he decides to not back  up his idea, proceeds to ask a question that has already been answered…  So, I proceed to answer the question, even though it has been answered.</p>
<p>There is a difference between being arrogant and being correct…[/quote]</p>
<p>It’s pointless to argue with someone who thinks they’re always right, which is why he didn’t bother. Also what was the point of saying I don’t know what arrogant means, and then acknowledging that you were being arrogant.</p>
<p>It doesn’t matter if it “doesn’t need” to be flexible. It’s all about customizing. That is all.</p>
<p><a class="mention" href="/u/kryptix">@Kryptix</a>: I’m sorry to say… Well no I’m not. You’re an idiot for thinking The_AFKer is Tewl.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/i-cant-find-the-file-which-has-the-prayer-xp-init/358918/16">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/i-cant-find-the-file-which-has-the-prayer-xp-init/358918/16</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 Sep 2010 13:55:02 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-358918-16</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/i-cant-find-the-file-which-has-the-prayer-xp-init/358918.rss">I cant find the file which has the prayer xp init</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>I cant find the file which has the prayer xp init</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@CodeForFame CodeForFame]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/codeforfame">@CodeForFame</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“Asylum, post:14, topic:358918”][quote author=CodeForFame link=topic=455416.msg3337774#msg3337774 date=1284089309]</p>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p>I never understood why experience is handled inside their own methods, why not establish all experience arrays in their own class then modified at the SQL level?</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>How often do you modify the xp of specific actions?</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Depends, say I was doing a daily event for example. During specified event, the amount of exp (say combat, prayer, magic), is doubled or tripled. Once the event ends, exp returns to normal.</p>
<p>I just don’t see why some things need to be listed in static context, why not manipulate data both on the server and client dynamically? Formulas for example, why not change certain variables instantly rather than reloading the entire server?</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I hope you do realize, that you can just check for the skill id and multiply it by whatever factor you want in the method that actually adds the xp.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I already know this, but it seems you missed the point.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Ok, so explain your amazing idea, then come up with a pro-con list for both, and then come tell me why your idea is so much better…</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>It’s not really an amazing idea, was just wondering why we can’t transition from setting everything in a static form and move on to flexible data management. Since you’re gonna be an arrogant dick about it, not going to waste my time.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Because it doesn’t need to be flexible; they’re meant to be constants, as they’re baseline numbers.  If you’re going to propose something, be prepared to explain the pros and cons…<br>
[/quote]</p>
<p>You are far too arrogant for your own good. You need to set your ego on the ground for a second and look at things differently for a change.</p>
<p><a class="mention" href="/u/old">@Old</a> rsc player: You don’t understand this concept either. It isn’t making anything more complicated. In fact it would be making it easier as far as management goes.[/quote]</p>
<p>You obviously don’t know what arrogance is…  I asked a question, and he gave me response, then I provided an easier solution to the same problem.  Then, he claimed I missed some point (which he has failed to back up), so I asked him to back up his idea with a list of pro/cons (I didn’t ask for a paper analyzing the cost/benefits, I asked for a simple pro/con chart…), and after he decides to not back  up his idea, proceeds to ask a question that has already been answered…  So, I proceed to answer the question, even though it has been answered.</p>
<p>There is a difference between being arrogant and being correct…</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/i-cant-find-the-file-which-has-the-prayer-xp-init/358918/15">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/i-cant-find-the-file-which-has-the-prayer-xp-init/358918/15</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 Sep 2010 13:25:39 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-358918-15</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/i-cant-find-the-file-which-has-the-prayer-xp-init/358918.rss">I cant find the file which has the prayer xp init</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>I cant find the file which has the prayer xp init</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Asylum Asylum]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/asylum">@Asylum</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“CodeForFame, post:13, topic:358918”][quote author=The_AFKer link=topic=455416.msg3337618#msg3337618 date=1284077150]</p>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p>I never understood why experience is handled inside their own methods, why not establish all experience arrays in their own class then modified at the SQL level?</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>How often do you modify the xp of specific actions?</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Depends, say I was doing a daily event for example. During specified event, the amount of exp (say combat, prayer, magic), is doubled or tripled. Once the event ends, exp returns to normal.</p>
<p>I just don’t see why some things need to be listed in static context, why not manipulate data both on the server and client dynamically? Formulas for example, why not change certain variables instantly rather than reloading the entire server?</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I hope you do realize, that you can just check for the skill id and multiply it by whatever factor you want in the method that actually adds the xp.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I already know this, but it seems you missed the point.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Ok, so explain your amazing idea, then come up with a pro-con list for both, and then come tell me why your idea is so much better…</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>It’s not really an amazing idea, was just wondering why we can’t transition from setting everything in a static form and move on to flexible data management. Since you’re gonna be an arrogant dick about it, not going to waste my time.<br>
[/quote]</p>
<p>Because it doesn’t need to be flexible; they’re meant to be constants, as they’re baseline numbers.  If you’re going to propose something, be prepared to explain the pros and cons…[/quote]</p>
<p>You are far too arrogant for your own good. You need to set your ego on the ground for a second and look at things differently for a change.</p>
<p><a class="mention" href="/u/old">@Old</a> rsc player: You don’t understand this concept either. It isn’t making anything more complicated. In fact it would be making it easier as far as management goes.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/i-cant-find-the-file-which-has-the-prayer-xp-init/358918/14">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/i-cant-find-the-file-which-has-the-prayer-xp-init/358918/14</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 Sep 2010 06:06:41 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-358918-14</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/i-cant-find-the-file-which-has-the-prayer-xp-init/358918.rss">I cant find the file which has the prayer xp init</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>I cant find the file which has the prayer xp init</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@CodeForFame CodeForFame]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/codeforfame">@CodeForFame</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“The_AFKer, post:11, topic:358918”][quote author=CodeForFame link=topic=455416.msg3337580#msg3337580 date=1284074125]</p>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p>I never understood why experience is handled inside their own methods, why not establish all experience arrays in their own class then modified at the SQL level?</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>How often do you modify the xp of specific actions?</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Depends, say I was doing a daily event for example. During specified event, the amount of exp (say combat, prayer, magic), is doubled or tripled. Once the event ends, exp returns to normal.</p>
<p>I just don’t see why some things need to be listed in static context, why not manipulate data both on the server and client dynamically? Formulas for example, why not change certain variables instantly rather than reloading the entire server?</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I hope you do realize, that you can just check for the skill id and multiply it by whatever factor you want in the method that actually adds the xp.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I already know this, but it seems you missed the point.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Ok, so explain your amazing idea, then come up with a pro-con list for both, and then come tell me why your idea is so much better…<br>
[/quote]</p>
<p>It’s not really an amazing idea, was just wondering why we can’t transition from setting everything in a static form and move on to flexible data management. Since you’re gonna be an arrogant dick about it, not going to waste my time.[/quote]</p>
<p>Because it doesn’t need to be flexible; they’re meant to be constants, as they’re baseline numbers.  If you’re going to propose something, be prepared to explain the pros and cons…</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/i-cant-find-the-file-which-has-the-prayer-xp-init/358918/13">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/i-cant-find-the-file-which-has-the-prayer-xp-init/358918/13</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 Sep 2010 03:28:29 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-358918-13</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/i-cant-find-the-file-which-has-the-prayer-xp-init/358918.rss">I cant find the file which has the prayer xp init</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
