<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Requesting a 474 [WORKING CLIENT]</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/requesting-a-474-working-client/518255</link>
    <description>now i have been looking for a WORKING 474 CLIENT.. and iv checked many and mainly the runs and main.class are loveed.. so can somone please loveing release a 474 with WORKING client please? or if somone has a 474 client [non jarred] or jared.. non jared wud be better.. cud you share it with me? blank or completely empty but i need a working 474 client.. please contact me asap. o well the clients i have tried.. are loveed to me but you might be able to fix idk but i am not a newby coder so i know wat im doin. point remains please send me a legitement 474 client-download and make sure that the client is runable. thank you :)
P.S if you want to join my coding team for making a near-reality reborn rsps.. pm me[thats why i need a 474 client] :P</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2013 05:37:22 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>General Discussion</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/requesting-a-474-working-client/518255.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Requesting a 474 [WORKING CLIENT]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@1337_c0d3r 1337 c0d3r]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/1337_c0d3r">@1337_c0d3r</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>now i have been looking for a WORKING 474 CLIENT… and iv checked many and mainly the runs and main.class are loveed… so can somone please loveing release a 474 with WORKING client please? or if somone has a 474 client [non jarred] or jared… non jared wud be better… cud you share it with me? blank or completely empty but i need a working 474 client… please contact me asap. o well the clients i have tried… are loveed to me but you might be able to fix idk but i am not a newby coder so i know wat im doin. point remains please send me a legitement 474 client-download and make sure that the client is runable. thank you <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=5" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"><br>
P.S if you want to join my coding team for making a near-reality reborn rsps… pm me[thats why i need a 474 client] <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=5" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/requesting-a-474-working-client/518255/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/requesting-a-474-working-client/518255/1</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2013 05:37:22 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-518255-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/requesting-a-474-working-client/518255.rss">Requesting a 474 [WORKING CLIENT]</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
