<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Fuck You(Tube)</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/fuck-you-tube/16326</link>
    <description>YouTube just plain sucks.
 
You know it&#39;s not a hip trend anymore when old people on the television start throwing in random references to it just to show they&#39;re in on the latest hip trends. 

Why is everyone falling over themselves to lick YouTubes nuts? I checked out Yahoo Video the other day, and about half the clips on Yahoo Video were videos about clips on YouTube. What the fuck is wrong with the people at Yahoo, didn&#39;t anybody ever tell them the way to get ahead on the internet is to [b]steal[/b] your competitors content, not link to it? 

Google Video provides free, giant, blurry video, which I much prefer to YouTube. Also, I own a lot of google stock, so if I didn&#39;t say I preferred their service, they would probably come to my house and kill me. But they would kill me super efficiently. With robots. Robots that also cleaned my house, walked my dogs, and then raped my girlfriend. Because that&#39;s how they do things at google: Clean. Googley.

YouTube is a piece of shit website. They censor videos they don&#39;t like, require an annoying registration to look at the few good videos they do have, and they just generally suck the proverbial monkey nut in the sky. Please tell me Jesus didn&#39;t die for these assholes, so they can browse YouTube and tell me how new and exciting it is, over, and over, and fucking over again.

YouTube has seen massive success (or at least, massive buzz, because the only way it would be a success is if it managed to pull all the US troops out of Iraq, invade Poland, and grow a new strain of hybrid marijuana) in large part due to the number of people who own a computer, and have access to the internet, and are mentally retarded. These idiot savantes, as they are so often incorrectly labelled,  use the internet constantly, and yet only manage to do a few things with it. They chat on IM, or do a few google searches, or look at urban dictionary, and they think they&#39;re the cats pajamas. Well, fuck them. Back in the day we interneted with style. We found the funny movies ourselves. We could make our own fun.

Any website that can convince people they are on the cutting edge can easily sell itself to the masses. However, the apex of funny videos on the internet, in terms of the actual amount of laughter per minute that could be attained on average, has already come and gone. Youtube is actually ancient history, and the [b]real[/b] web hipsters have moved on to bigger and better things.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 30 Sep 2006 15:17:56 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>General Discussion</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/fuck-you-tube/16326.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Fuck You(Tube)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@The_Un-Named The Un-Named]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/the_un-named">@The_Un-Named</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“Ron, post:24, topic:16326”]Yeah, YouTube is not the best place to go for videos.</p>
<p>Google Videos is the best. :)[/quote]</p>
<p>Yeah but alot of them are crap. <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/frowning.png?v=9" title=":frowning:" class="emoji" alt=":frowning:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/fuck-you-tube/16326/25">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/fuck-you-tube/16326/25</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 30 Sep 2006 15:17:56 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-16326-25</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/fuck-you-tube/16326.rss">Fuck You(Tube)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Fuck You(Tube)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Ron Ron]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/ron">@Ron</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Yeah, YouTube is not the best place to go for videos.</p>
<p>Google Videos is the best. <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=9" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/fuck-you-tube/16326/24">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/fuck-you-tube/16326/24</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 30 Sep 2006 10:30:16 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-16326-24</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/fuck-you-tube/16326.rss">Fuck You(Tube)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Fuck You(Tube)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@mass-art mass-art]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/mass-art">@mass-art</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>did you know that youtube use 45 terabyte of bandwidth a month!!! and it costs them something like 7 million a month to maintain it, and that they reckon that people have allready watched over 4000 years of video from it, this is just crazy!</p>
<p>in my opinion youtube is awesome</p>
<p>facts from <a href="http://www.torrentfreak.com" rel="nofollow noopener">www.torrentfreak.com</a></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/fuck-you-tube/16326/23">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/fuck-you-tube/16326/23</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 30 Sep 2006 10:07:29 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-16326-23</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/fuck-you-tube/16326.rss">Fuck You(Tube)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Fuck You(Tube)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@PaulT PaulT]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/pault">@PaulT</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <blockquote>NEW YORK (Reuters) - Billionaire investor and dot-com veteran Mark Cuban had harsh words on Thursday for YouTube, the online site that lets people share video clips, saying only a "moron" would purchase the wildly popular start-up.</blockquote>
<aside class="onebox whitelistedgeneric">
  <header class="source">
      <img src="https://s3.reutersmedia.net/resources_v2/images/favicon/favicon.ico" class="site-icon" width="48" height="48">
      <a href="https://de.reuters.com/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">DE</a>
  </header>
  <article class="onebox-body">
    <div class="aspect-image" style="--aspect-ratio:690/362;"><img src="https://s4.reutersmedia.net/resources_v2/images/rcom-default.png" class="thumbnail"></div>

<h3><a href="https://de.reuters.com/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Wirtschafts &amp; Finanz-Nachrichten, aktuelle US &amp; Internationale...</a></h3>

<p>Reuters.de versorgt Sie mit  Nachrichten aus aller Welt und berichtet über die neuesten Entwicklungen in Wirtschaft, Politik und Technologie, auch in den Formaten Video und Foto. (we don't do Entertainment; that would be Unterhaltung)</p>


  </article>
  <div class="onebox-metadata">
    
    
  </div>
  <div style="clear: both"></div>
</aside>

<blockquote>Last week, the New York Post put a $1.5 billion rumored for sale price tag on YouTube, up 50% from its $1 billion “name your YouTube sales price” target from a few months earlier.</blockquote>
<aside class="onebox whitelistedgeneric">
  <header class="source">
      <img src="https://zdnet2.cbsistatic.com/fly/bundles/zdnetcss/images/logos/logo-192x192.png" class="site-icon" width="192" height="192">
      <a href="https://www.zdnet.com/blog/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">ZDNet</a>
  </header>
  <article class="onebox-body">
    <div class="aspect-image" style="--aspect-ratio:521/400;"><img src="https://zdnet2.cbsistatic.com/fly/bundles/zdnetcore/images/logos/zdnet-logo-large.png" class="thumbnail"></div>

<h3><a href="https://www.zdnet.com/blog/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Blogs | ZDNet</a></h3>

<p>ZDNet's technology experts deliver the best tech news and analysis on the latest issues and events in IT for business technology professionals, IT managers and tech-savvy business people.</p>


  </article>
  <div class="onebox-metadata">
    
    
  </div>
  <div style="clear: both"></div>
</aside>

<blockquote>When Fox News’ ever-popular interview with former President Bill Clinton hit YouTube, the Wall Street Journal’s Law Blog wondered what was up: “Did you see Chris Wallace’s interview with Bill Clinton? If not, you can watch it here, thanks to YouTube. But wait a minute, doesn’t Fox News own a copyright on this content? Is the video-sharing site breaking the law?”
<p>Actually, that’s pretty much what Fox News thought when they contacted YouTube and requested that the clips be removed from the site. Ever the dispenser of new media wisdom, BuzzMachiner Jeff Jarvis concluded that was an idiot move: “Fools. They would be getting a whole new audience. They’d be even more part of the conversation.”</p>
<p>Well, apparently Fox News agreed with that too, because the following day, the clips reappeared on YouTube. Fox News told digital news site dmwmedia (via TVNewser) that the move was a mistake.</p>
<pre><code>“In an official statement, Fox News claims that their Internet division used ‘poor judgment’ when going after YouTubers. Strategically, Fox News recognizes that the clips are of great PR value and that the company is ‘thrilled’ that the interview received so much publicity.&lt;/blockquote&gt;
</code></pre>
<aside class="onebox whitelistedgeneric">
  <header class="source">
      <img src="https://cbsnews4.cbsistatic.com/fly/bundles/cbsnewscore/icons/favicon.ico?v=1.764559b90627d43d03741a36ec5d9da29d5b5c98" class="site-icon" width="16" height="16">
      <a href="https://www.cbsnews.com/news/the-trouble-with-youtube/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">cbsnews.com</a>
  </header>
  <article class="onebox-body">
    <div class="aspect-image" style="--aspect-ratio:690/362;"><img src="https://cbsnews1.cbsistatic.com/hub/i/r/2017/12/12/77e5d36d-5915-46ce-b496-218c87d98c5d/thumbnail/1200x630/15dcb72c6fdec4125306ed9638345480/cbsnews-1600x900.jpg" class="thumbnail"></div>

<h3><a href="https://www.cbsnews.com/news/the-trouble-with-youtube/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">The Trouble With YouTube</a></h3>

<p>Fox News Gets Into The Weeds With YouTube</p>


  </article>
  <div class="onebox-metadata">
    
    
  </div>
  <div style="clear: both"></div>
</aside>

<p><aside class="onebox whitelistedgeneric">
  <header class="source">
      <img src="https://s.ytimg.com/yts/img/favicon-vfl8qSV2F.ico" class="site-icon" width="16" height="16">
      <a href="https://www.youtube.com/profile?user=ONDCPstaff" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">YouTube</a>
  </header>
  <article class="onebox-body">
    <img src="https://yt3.ggpht.com/a/AGF-l78yd4_2PaTMkYVpYYEW-xgUXRoOqCV9XjygEg=s900-mo-c-c0xffffffff-rj-k-no" class="thumbnail onebox-avatar" width="500" height="500">

<h3><a href="https://www.youtube.com/profile?user=ONDCPstaff" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Office of National Drug Control Policy</a></h3>

<p>The official channel of the Office of National Drug Control Policy</p>


  </article>
  <div class="onebox-metadata">
    
    
  </div>
  <div style="clear: both"></div>
</aside>
<br>
<div class="lazyYT" data-youtube-id="flGqaHYcKog" data-youtube-title="" data-width="480" data-height="270" data-parameters="feature=oembed&amp;wmode=opaque"></div></p>
</blockquote>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/fuck-you-tube/16326/22">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/fuck-you-tube/16326/22</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 29 Sep 2006 09:20:30 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-16326-22</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/fuck-you-tube/16326.rss">Fuck You(Tube)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Fuck You(Tube)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Got_Shine Got_Shine]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/got_shine">@Got_Shine</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“davidude36, post:15, topic:16326”]paulT your beggining to sound like one of them old people who start nearly every conversation with “back in my day we didnt have…[insert something we have today that they are jellous they didnt have it back then]”<br>
but anyways good argument…<br>
&lt;3bill gates mugshot btw.[/quote]</p>
<p>I think the point he’s trying to make is that youtube is an extremelly medicore site, just like myspace. It doesn’t have anything to do with jealosy.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/fuck-you-tube/16326/21">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/fuck-you-tube/16326/21</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 29 Sep 2006 04:11:27 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-16326-21</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/fuck-you-tube/16326.rss">Fuck You(Tube)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Fuck You(Tube)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Mr.Chris Mr.Chris]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/mr.chris">@Mr.Chris</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“PaulT, post:1, topic:16326”]YouTube just plain sucks.</p>
<p>You know it’s not a hip trend anymore when old people on the television start throwing in random references to it just to show they’re in on the latest hip trends.</p>
<p>Why is everyone falling over themselves to lick YouTubes nuts? I checked out Yahoo Video the other day, and about half the clips on Yahoo Video were videos about clips on YouTube. What the fuck is wrong with the people at Yahoo, didn’t anybody ever tell them the way to get ahead on the internet is to <span class="bbcode-b">steal</span> your competitors content, not link to it?</p>
<p>Google Video provides free, giant, blurry video, which I much prefer to YouTube. Also, I own a lot of google stock, so if I didn’t say I preferred their service, they would probably come to my house and kill me. But they would kill me super efficiently. With robots. Robots that also cleaned my house, walked my dogs, and then raped my girlfriend. Because that’s how they do things at google: Clean. Googley.</p>
<p>YouTube is a piece of shit website. They censor videos they don’t like, require an annoying registration to look at the few good videos they do have, and they just generally suck the proverbial monkey nut in the sky. Please tell me Jesus didn’t die for these assholes, so they can browse YouTube and tell me how new and exciting it is, over, and over, and fucking over again.</p>
<p>YouTube has seen massive success (or at least, massive buzz, because the only way it would be a success is if it managed to pull all the US troops out of Iraq, invade Poland, and grow a new strain of hybrid marijuana) in large part due to the number of people who own a computer, and have access to the internet, and are mentally retarded. These idiot savantes, as they are so often incorrectly labelled,  use the internet constantly, and yet only manage to do a few things with it. They chat on IM, or do a few google searches, or look at urban dictionary, and they think they’re the cats pajamas. Well, fuck them. Back in the day we interneted with style. We found the funny movies ourselves. We could make our own fun.</p>
<p>Any website that can convince people they are on the cutting edge can easily sell itself to the masses. However, the apex of funny videos on the internet, in terms of the actual amount of laughter per minute that could be attained on average, has already come and gone. Youtube is actually ancient history, and the <span class="bbcode-b">real</span> web hipsters have moved on to bigger and better things.[/quote]</p>
<p>I &lt;3 you</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/fuck-you-tube/16326/20">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/fuck-you-tube/16326/20</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 29 Sep 2006 02:12:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-16326-20</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/fuck-you-tube/16326.rss">Fuck You(Tube)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Fuck You(Tube)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@PaulT PaulT]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/pault">@PaulT</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote]Youtube enables people who don’t have access to large amounts of bandwidth to show their videos to the world for free.<br>
Where’s the bad side?/quote]</p>
<p>As I’ve said, it’s over promoted, especially by people who have no idea what they’re talking about. Traditional sources for finding videos on the internet (filesharing apps, forums, news groups, random websites) yield funnier and fresher content. It’s not cool to fight popular things, but we have to fight the man, and the man wants us to use YouTube.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/fuck-you-tube/16326/19">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/fuck-you-tube/16326/19</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 29 Sep 2006 02:07:28 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-16326-19</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/fuck-you-tube/16326.rss">Fuck You(Tube)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Fuck You(Tube)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Mmmk Mmmk]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/mmmk">@Mmmk</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Lol, adblock ads dudes. Its just like the simplest thing ever known on the internet.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/fuck-you-tube/16326/18">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/fuck-you-tube/16326/18</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 28 Sep 2006 21:50:52 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-16326-18</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/fuck-you-tube/16326.rss">Fuck You(Tube)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Fuck You(Tube)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Mopman Mopman]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/mopman">@Mopman</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Youtube enables people who don’t have access to large amounts of bandwidth to show their videos to the world for free.<br>
Where’s the bad side? Other people’s videos suck balls? Don’t fuckin’ watch 'em then!</p>
<p>Oh, but I forgot, it’s cool to hate popular things isn’t it.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/fuck-you-tube/16326/17">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/fuck-you-tube/16326/17</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 28 Sep 2006 17:43:47 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-16326-17</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/fuck-you-tube/16326.rss">Fuck You(Tube)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Fuck You(Tube)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@xerozcheez xerozcheez]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/xerozcheez">@xerozcheez</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>YouTube isn’t that bad, but google video is a lot better, as it has a much bigger picture so I don’t have to look 1cm away from the screen to see what’s going on ^^</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/fuck-you-tube/16326/16">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/fuck-you-tube/16326/16</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 28 Sep 2006 17:22:42 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-16326-16</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/fuck-you-tube/16326.rss">Fuck You(Tube)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Fuck You(Tube)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@davidude36 Brolapse]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/davidude36">@davidude36</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>paulT your beggining to sound like one of them old people who start nearly every conversation with “back in my day we didnt have…[insert something we have today that they are jellous they didnt have it back then]”<br>
but anyways good argument…<br>
&lt;3bill gates mugshot btw.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/fuck-you-tube/16326/15">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/fuck-you-tube/16326/15</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 28 Sep 2006 16:34:20 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-16326-15</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/fuck-you-tube/16326.rss">Fuck You(Tube)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Fuck You(Tube)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@lizhang lizhang]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/lizhang">@lizhang</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>lol did google pay you to dis you tube?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/fuck-you-tube/16326/14">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/fuck-you-tube/16326/14</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 28 Sep 2006 16:02:21 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-16326-14</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/fuck-you-tube/16326.rss">Fuck You(Tube)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Fuck You(Tube)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@james james]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/james">@james</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>rune nuze dont work anymore!!!</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/fuck-you-tube/16326/13">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/fuck-you-tube/16326/13</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 28 Sep 2006 14:40:03 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-16326-13</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/fuck-you-tube/16326.rss">Fuck You(Tube)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Fuck You(Tube)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@rabcarl rabcarl]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/rabcarl">@rabcarl</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Couldn’t agree more, youtube is full of nasty pedofiles and perverts.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/fuck-you-tube/16326/12">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/fuck-you-tube/16326/12</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 28 Sep 2006 10:13:48 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-16326-12</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/fuck-you-tube/16326.rss">Fuck You(Tube)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Fuck You(Tube)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@googlethis googlethis]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/googlethis">@googlethis</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <blockquote>But they would kill me super efficiently. With robots. Robots that also cleaned my house, walked my dogs, and then raped my girlfriend. Because that's how they do things at google: Clean. Googley.</blockquote>
Indeed, they would. And they'd put pictures of your dead body on images as an example.
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/fuck-you-tube/16326/11">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/fuck-you-tube/16326/11</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 28 Sep 2006 09:43:08 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-16326-11</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/fuck-you-tube/16326.rss">Fuck You(Tube)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Fuck You(Tube)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Thebeanie TheBeanie]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/thebeanie">@Thebeanie</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>yea it used to be ok then big people started posting vids like paris hilten and like the news and stuff</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/fuck-you-tube/16326/10">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/fuck-you-tube/16326/10</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 28 Sep 2006 04:31:09 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-16326-10</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/fuck-you-tube/16326.rss">Fuck You(Tube)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Fuck You(Tube)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Drunk_On_Java Drunk On Java]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/drunk_on_java">@Drunk_On_Java</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I have to agree that YouTube is just plain gay.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/fuck-you-tube/16326/9">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/fuck-you-tube/16326/9</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 28 Sep 2006 00:22:25 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-16326-9</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/fuck-you-tube/16326.rss">Fuck You(Tube)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Fuck You(Tube)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@PaulT PaulT]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/pault">@PaulT</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Wrong. It was a traffic stop in 1977, do your research.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/fuck-you-tube/16326/8">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/fuck-you-tube/16326/8</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 27 Sep 2006 21:25:30 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-16326-8</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/fuck-you-tube/16326.rss">Fuck You(Tube)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Fuck You(Tube)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@pko pko]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/pko">@pko</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Its fake …</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/fuck-you-tube/16326/7">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/fuck-you-tube/16326/7</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 27 Sep 2006 18:51:58 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-16326-7</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/fuck-you-tube/16326.rss">Fuck You(Tube)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Fuck You(Tube)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@pookey71 Pookey71]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/pookey71">@pookey71</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>He is smiling becuase he got caught for doing something illegal man he must be a stoner :|.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/fuck-you-tube/16326/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/fuck-you-tube/16326/6</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 27 Sep 2006 15:29:54 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-16326-6</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/fuck-you-tube/16326.rss">Fuck You(Tube)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Fuck You(Tube)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@PaulT PaulT]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/pault">@PaulT</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <blockquote>(Please correct me if i am wrong).</blockquote>
<p>Do I have to? It seems the amount of information you don’t know may be enough to fill several thick volumes.</p>
<p>I think laughing at Bill Gates mugshot may be a better use of your time than being educated by me:<br>
<img src="http://img205.imageshack.us/img205/7030/gatesmugrx6.jpg" alt width="" height=""></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/fuck-you-tube/16326/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/fuck-you-tube/16326/5</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 27 Sep 2006 15:26:16 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-16326-5</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/fuck-you-tube/16326.rss">Fuck You(Tube)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Fuck You(Tube)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@pookey71 Pookey71]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/pookey71">@pookey71</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>No problem.I’m just bored <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=9" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"> only reason i would go onto youtube is becuase a friend is over and doesn’t know as much as he should <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=9" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"> But i didn’t know that computers where made that long ago i ment when Bill"Fag"Gates devoloped the computer screen (Please correct me if i am wrong).</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/fuck-you-tube/16326/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/fuck-you-tube/16326/4</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 27 Sep 2006 15:17:33 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-16326-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/fuck-you-tube/16326.rss">Fuck You(Tube)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Fuck You(Tube)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@PaulT PaulT]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/pault">@PaulT</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <blockquote>hey when computers came out didn't you have to access things through the command propmt?Like "Internetexploarisgaqymozzilarock thingo"My mum would know but seeing Paul you are a community member you know^.^</blockquote>
<p>I wasn’t alive <a href="http://www.officemuseum.com/data_processing_machines.htm" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">when</a> computers came out, and I hope to god your mother wasn’t either.</p>
<p>As to the lonelygirl15 stupidity, I am happy to say I have never heard of it untill you told me about it and I did some <a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Lonelygirl15" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">research</a> (so I don’t think it’s the major reason, there is no reason, YouTube is shit). It seems like just the kind of bullshit that YouTube promotes. Thanks for helping me out here, the more evidence of YouTubes lack of tangible quality content we can gather the better.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/fuck-you-tube/16326/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/fuck-you-tube/16326/3</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 27 Sep 2006 14:59:32 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-16326-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/fuck-you-tube/16326.rss">Fuck You(Tube)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Fuck You(Tube)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@pookey71 Pookey71]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/pookey71">@pookey71</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Hey,i’m the bees knees,the cats pajamas,cool fly daddo(Sorry i just understood the cats pajamas thing)But the "Real"reason Youtube(They shouldn’t deserve a capitalizing anyways)is because of the lonelygirl15 chick.She was all over the news and since Nbc(Or something i’m Australian so yeah)has offered a partnership with Youtube it’s become widely known,hey when computers came out didn’t you have to access things through the command propmt?Like "Internetexploarisgaqymozzilarock thingo"My mum would know but seeing Paul you are a community member you know^.^</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/fuck-you-tube/16326/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/fuck-you-tube/16326/2</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 27 Sep 2006 14:53:31 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-16326-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/fuck-you-tube/16326.rss">Fuck You(Tube)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Fuck You(Tube)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@PaulT PaulT]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/pault">@PaulT</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>YouTube just plain sucks.</p>
<p>You know it’s not a hip trend anymore when old people on the television start throwing in random references to it just to show they’re in on the latest hip trends.</p>
<p>Why is everyone falling over themselves to lick YouTubes nuts? I checked out Yahoo Video the other day, and about half the clips on Yahoo Video were videos about clips on YouTube. What the fuck is wrong with the people at Yahoo, didn’t anybody ever tell them the way to get ahead on the internet is to <span class="bbcode-b">steal</span> your competitors content, not link to it?</p>
<p>Google Video provides free, giant, blurry video, which I much prefer to YouTube. Also, I own a lot of google stock, so if I didn’t say I preferred their service, they would probably come to my house and kill me. But they would kill me super efficiently. With robots. Robots that also cleaned my house, walked my dogs, and then raped my girlfriend. Because that’s how they do things at google: Clean. Googley.</p>
<p>YouTube is a piece of shit website. They censor videos they don’t like, require an annoying registration to look at the few good videos they do have, and they just generally suck the proverbial monkey nut in the sky. Please tell me Jesus didn’t die for these assholes, so they can browse YouTube and tell me how new and exciting it is, over, and over, and fucking over again.</p>
<p>YouTube has seen massive success (or at least, massive buzz, because the only way it would be a success is if it managed to pull all the US troops out of Iraq, invade Poland, and grow a new strain of hybrid marijuana) in large part due to the number of people who own a computer, and have access to the internet, and are mentally retarded. These idiot savantes, as they are so often incorrectly labelled,  use the internet constantly, and yet only manage to do a few things with it. They chat on IM, or do a few google searches, or look at urban dictionary, and they think they’re the cats pajamas. Well, fuck them. Back in the day we interneted with style. We found the funny movies ourselves. We could make our own fun.</p>
<p>Any website that can convince people they are on the cutting edge can easily sell itself to the masses. However, the apex of funny videos on the internet, in terms of the actual amount of laughter per minute that could be attained on average, has already come and gone. Youtube is actually ancient history, and the <span class="bbcode-b">real</span> web hipsters have moved on to bigger and better things.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/fuck-you-tube/16326/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/fuck-you-tube/16326/1</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 27 Sep 2006 14:11:14 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-16326-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/fuck-you-tube/16326.rss">Fuck You(Tube)</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
