<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>HELP! I need this patched!</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/help-i-need-this-patched/356553</link>
    <description>This guy keeps logging in my server and making himself owner some how.. he makes his name &quot;    1 3 3  7&quot; every time.. and it won&#39;t let me ban him! he ipbans me and everyone else and spawns and hands out items.. and when he&#39;s done he crashes it.. idk how he does this! anyone know how to patch it?Btw I checked his ip and its 0.0.0.0 -.-

I think if I could get his real ip i could fix it.. cuz when i do ::banip     1 3 3  7     it says &quot;you have banned the use with the host of: 0.0.0.0. And right after that he just logs right back in.. if I could ipban his real ip then I could ipban him for sure :D</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 23 Aug 2010 12:53:09 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/help-i-need-this-patched/356553.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>HELP! I need this patched!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@jake_cake jake cake]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/jake_cake">@jake_cake</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>This guy keeps logging in my server and making himself owner some how… he makes his name "    1 3 3  7" every time… and it won’t let me ban him! he ipbans me and everyone else and spawns and hands out items… and when he’s done he crashes it… idk how he does this! anyone know how to patch it?Btw I checked his ip and its 0.0.0.0 -.-</p>
<p>I think if I could get his real ip i could fix it… cuz when i do ::banip     1 3 3  7     it says "you have banned the use with the host of: 0.0.0.0. And right after that he just logs right back in… if I could ipban his real ip then I could ipban him for sure <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/smiley.png?v=5" title=":smiley:" class="emoji" alt=":smiley:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/help-i-need-this-patched/356553/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/help-i-need-this-patched/356553/1</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 23 Aug 2010 12:53:09 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-356553-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/help-i-need-this-patched/356553.rss">HELP! I need this patched!</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
