<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Out Of Interest #1</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/out-of-interest-1/72687</link>
    <description>[center][b]Hi, this quiz is just simply out of interest, these are questions related to Moparscape and why you chose to become a member of the Moparscape community.[/b][/center]

1.  Why did you join Moparscape?

2.  What interests you most? Playing on other people&#39;s servers or creating your own

3. Do you own a server of your own? If so what is the ip and port?

4. Did you, honestly, read Mod Thaorak&#39;s ultimate guide to creating a server, before actually attempting one?

5. Did you, honestly, read the rules when you first registered? and read the new ones?

6. Is there a question stuck at the back of your mind that you have always wondered about Private Servers?

7. Have you ever broken any of the forum&#39;s rules?

8. Do you want any information about creating a server or perhaps editing?

9. Do you prefer Moparscape to Runescape? If so, tell us why.

10. Do you understand the Java language?

Simply Copy + Paste this and write your answer underneath the questions.

_____________________________________________________________________

Mods, please do not lock, if you feel this is in the wrong section, please move. Thank you.
_____________________________________________________________________</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 01 Apr 2007 03:33:29 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/out-of-interest-1/72687.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Out Of Interest #1</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@I_Br3ndan_I I Br3ndan I]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/i_br3ndan_i">@I_Br3ndan_I</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <ol>
<li>
<p>Why did you join Moparscape? <span class="bbcode-u">I heard of a ‘RuneScape’ where you could get free PHats etc, after hours of searching I found MoparScape</span></p>
</li>
<li>
<p>What interests you most? Playing on other people’s servers or creating your own <span class="bbcode-u">Playing on other people’s and browsing the forums.</span></p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Do you own a server of your own? If so what is the ip and port?</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Did you, honestly, read Mod Thaorak’s ultimate guide to creating a server, before actually attempting one? <span class="bbcode-u">I’ve never made a server.</span></p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Did you, honestly, read the rules when you first registered? and read the new ones? <span class="bbcode-u">I read the rules when I registered briefly, never read the new ones.</span></p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Is there a question stuck at the back of your mind that you have always wondered about Private Servers? <span class="bbcode-u">Many questions.</span></p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Have you ever broken any of the forum’s rules? <span class="bbcode-u">Yes, the reason I am warned today is because I broke a rule.</span></p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Do you want any information about creating a server or perhaps editing? <span class="bbcode-u">Maybe some other day.</span></p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Do you prefer Moparscape to Runescape? If so, tell us why. MoparScape.  <span class="bbcode-u">I don’t know the reason, mostly because certain rules on RuneScape aren’t rules on here, swearing etc.  Fuck :).  Plus the people here are more friendly, it’s a much more exciting enviroment to be in.</span></p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Do you understand the Java language? <span class="bbcode-u">Nope, not one part of it whatsoever.</span></p>
</li>
</ol>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/out-of-interest-1/72687/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/out-of-interest-1/72687/6</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 01 Apr 2007 03:33:29 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-72687-6</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/out-of-interest-1/72687.rss">Out Of Interest #1</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Out Of Interest #1</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Eportal Eportal]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/eportal">@Eportal</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <ol>
<li>
<p>Why did you join Moparscape? found it randomly then I decided it would be fun to make a server.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>What interests you most? Playing on other people’s servers or creating your own? Totally creating my own it’s so fun</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Do you own a server of your own? If so what is the ip and port? Yes, Im not officialy releasing yet, just got the forums and website, and of course the server and client, but i didnt release it yet. Oh yeah, it’s in my signiture lolz.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Did you, honestly, read Mod Thaorak’s ultimate guide to creating a server, before actually attempting one? yes, didn’t help me a lot though, no-ip was so complicated with the port forward and all, so i just used hamachi</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Did you, honestly, read the rules when you first registered? and read the new ones?<em>clears throught</em> no, <em>coughs</em> but the new ones yes.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Is there a question stuck at the back of your mind that you have always wondered about Private Servers? YES! How the hell do you make a webclient…?</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Have you ever broken any of the forum’s rules? When i was a noob, yes</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Do you want any information about creating a server or perhaps editing? No, and the info i know right now, i learned myself.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Do you prefer Moparscape to Runescape? If so, tell us why. Moparscape, so much to do, convert npc’s, items, objects, ::noclip ect and runescape is boring like hell.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Do you understand the Java language? I consider myself a noob in java, but making myself around a not so noobish rank but I am always learning more.</p>
</li>
</ol>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/out-of-interest-1/72687/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/out-of-interest-1/72687/5</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 01 Apr 2007 03:08:47 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-72687-5</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/out-of-interest-1/72687.rss">Out Of Interest #1</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Out Of Interest #1</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@zammyking111 zammyking111]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/zammyking111">@zammyking111</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p><span class="bbcode-b">1. Why did you join Moparscape?</span> Because of runescape private servers and runescape got gay</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">2. What interests you most? Playing on other people’s servers or creating your own</span> Creating</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">3. Do you own a server of your own? If so what is the ip and port?</span> Yes dont have the ip still creating <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/wink.png?v=6" title=":wink:" class="emoji" alt=":wink:"></p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">4. Did you, honestly, read Mod Thaorak’s ultimate guide to creating a server, before actually attempting one?</span> Nope never read it waste of time <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=6" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">5. Did you, honestly, read the rules when you first registered? and read the new ones?</span> Yes</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">6. Is there a question stuck at the back of your mind that you have always wondered about Private Servers?</span> Nope</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">7. Have you ever broken any of the forum’s rules?</span> umm on my old account I did I accidently spammed</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">8. Do you want any information about creating a server or perhaps editing?</span> umm i got it by myself</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">9. Do you prefer Moparscape to Runescape?</span> Private servers becuase there is no freedom of speech in gayscape</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">10. Do you understand the Java language?</span> yes pretty well</p>
<p>Also nov9862 i reported you for spam <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=6" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/out-of-interest-1/72687/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/out-of-interest-1/72687/4</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 01 Apr 2007 01:48:24 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-72687-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/out-of-interest-1/72687.rss">Out Of Interest #1</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Out Of Interest #1</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@nov9862 nov9862]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/nov9862">@nov9862</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Summary - x spike x  Picture/Text<br>
Name:  x spike x<br>
Posts:  197 (1.288 per day)<span class="bbcode-b"> &lt;—197 posts of complete SPAM</span><br>
Position:  Senior Member<br>
Rep:  10</p>
<p>Date Registered:  October 28, 2006, 05:03:20 PM<br>
Last Active:  Today at 02:41:36 PM</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/out-of-interest-1/72687/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/out-of-interest-1/72687/3</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 01 Apr 2007 01:46:58 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-72687-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/out-of-interest-1/72687.rss">Out Of Interest #1</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Out Of Interest #1</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@system system]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/system">@system</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <ol>
<li>
<p>Why did you join Moparscape? RuneScape was boring the hell outta me, i was a pmod and tried muting a Jagex mod permenantly, …moral is don’t try it -.-</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>What interests you most? Playing on other people’s servers or creating your own : Creating my own, got one in development now, set up all the forums, got 65+ things added to it</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Do you own a server of your own? If so what is the ip and port? Aye, i aint releasing yet, i just have a forum.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Did you, honestly, read Mod Thaorak’s ultimate guide to creating a server, before actually attempting one? Yup, i respect others wishes.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Did you, honestly, read the rules when you first registered? and read the new ones? Yes.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Is there a question stuck at the back of your mind that you have always wondered about Private Servers? Yes.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Have you ever broken any of the forum’s rules? Yes, my own fault though.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Do you want any information about creating a server or perhaps editing? A nice team helping me would be nice <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=6" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"> Currently got 2 others =/</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Do you prefer Moparscape to Runescape? If so, tell us why. MoparScape, i used to love RuneScape, became a pmod, enjoyed it for about a month, then started boring the hell outta me, decided to perm mute a j mod, and quit. With MoparScape, non of the Gold mods are so far up there own ass’s theyl ban you for anything -.-</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Do you understand the Java language? Could learn more <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=6" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
</li>
</ol>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/out-of-interest-1/72687/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/out-of-interest-1/72687/2</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 01 Apr 2007 01:41:48 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-72687-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/out-of-interest-1/72687.rss">Out Of Interest #1</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Out Of Interest #1</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@x_spike_x x spike x]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/x_spike_x">@x_spike_x</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[center]<span class="bbcode-b">Hi, this quiz is just simply out of interest, these are questions related to Moparscape and why you chose to become a member of the Moparscape community.</span>[/center]</p>
<ol>
<li>
<p>Why did you join Moparscape?</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>What interests you most? Playing on other people’s servers or creating your own</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Do you own a server of your own? If so what is the ip and port?</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Did you, honestly, read Mod Thaorak’s ultimate guide to creating a server, before actually attempting one?</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Did you, honestly, read the rules when you first registered? and read the new ones?</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Is there a question stuck at the back of your mind that you have always wondered about Private Servers?</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Have you ever broken any of the forum’s rules?</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Do you want any information about creating a server or perhaps editing?</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Do you prefer Moparscape to Runescape? If so, tell us why.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Do you understand the Java language?</p>
</li>
</ol>
<p>Simply Copy + Paste this and write your answer underneath the questions.</p>
<hr>
<p>Mods, please do not lock, if you feel this is in the wrong section, please move. Thank you.</p>
<hr>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/out-of-interest-1/72687/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/out-of-interest-1/72687/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 31 Mar 2007 23:30:19 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-72687-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/out-of-interest-1/72687.rss">Out Of Interest #1</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
