<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Moparscape Rules</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/moparscape-rules/65063</link>
    <description>admins and mods i know you will think this is mean,hurtfull, and maby spam but this is huge there are loads of players on moparscape and there forums i know you all want to keep the forums as clean as possible, all this i understand but what i am so confused about is the rule that states there is to be no spinoff tuts well why would modisland be considerd a spin off tut... &quot;i made a awsome modisland it created very little lag and yea&quot; there were not many Npcs and it was not even on the same ground as any other modislands it was great. now this may be my own oppion but this forums is getting way to strick expecually with that rule now if i know exactically why that rule is there and inforced so hard i might change my oppion but the way i see it the strickness of these forums is going to cost mopar a lot of players and i know that mopar is thining about making the forums read only.. well these are great forums they are what i want my programing community to live up to, proboly not as strickt but still these forums are legend in my book. mods and admins if you feel like this is mean and not true please dont lock/delete it, for it contains a question and it may only be my oppion but if you must delete it do.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 07 Mar 2007 08:15:22 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/moparscape-rules/65063.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Moparscape Rules</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@jma0710 jma0710]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/jma0710">@jma0710</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>thanks guys i think im understanding it more now</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/moparscape-rules/65063/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/moparscape-rules/65063/4</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 07 Mar 2007 08:15:22 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-65063-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/moparscape-rules/65063.rss">Moparscape Rules</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Moparscape Rules</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Owned_Irl1 Owned  Irl]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/owned_irl1">@Owned_Irl1</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>People constantly make tutorials that branch off up other tutorials…</p>
<p>For instance… The Tutorial on adding a shop…</p>
<p>When someone makes a tutorial on adding a certain shop or shops in general then they are copy righting and not posting new information or tutorials…</p>
<p>In your case, there are many mod islands posted… For yours to stand out and not be brushed by… you have to change the name of your mod island to something no one else has created…</p>
<p>Hopefully this helps…</p>
<p>Rules are posted to create less stress… People have to enforced the rules… We dont want a million of the same topic…</p>
<p>Stand out and be unique compared to the rest of the mod islands…</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/moparscape-rules/65063/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/moparscape-rules/65063/3</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 07 Mar 2007 01:07:05 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-65063-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/moparscape-rules/65063.rss">Moparscape Rules</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Moparscape Rules</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Click_Here Click Here]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/click_here">@Click_Here</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>we have to make the rules more striked, only because more and more people are breaking the rules. if we just had like 5 rules, the whole forum would be a nightmare.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/moparscape-rules/65063/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/moparscape-rules/65063/2</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 07 Mar 2007 00:15:30 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-65063-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/moparscape-rules/65063.rss">Moparscape Rules</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Moparscape Rules</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@jma0710 jma0710]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/jma0710">@jma0710</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>admins and mods i know you will think this is mean,hurtfull, and maby spam but this is huge there are loads of players on moparscape and there forums i know you all want to keep the forums as clean as possible, all this i understand but what i am so confused about is the rule that states there is to be no spinoff tuts well why would modisland be considerd a spin off tut… “i made a awsome modisland it created very little lag and yea” there were not many Npcs and it was not even on the same ground as any other modislands it was great. now this may be my own oppion but this forums is getting way to strick expecually with that rule now if i know exactically why that rule is there and inforced so hard i might change my oppion but the way i see it the strickness of these forums is going to cost mopar a lot of players and i know that mopar is thining about making the forums read only… well these are great forums they are what i want my programing community to live up to, proboly not as strickt but still these forums are legend in my book. mods and admins if you feel like this is mean and not true please dont lock/delete it, for it contains a question and it may only be my oppion but if you must delete it do.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/moparscape-rules/65063/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/moparscape-rules/65063/1</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 07 Mar 2007 00:08:09 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-65063-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/moparscape-rules/65063.rss">Moparscape Rules</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
