<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Section Rules</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/section-rules/265535</link>
    <description>Welcome to the Client Help section. :)

When posting your topic, please use a clear and easily understandable title. In your post, provide as much information as possible (stack traces in particular if some sort of exception is being thrown, and any other information you may be able to provide).

It&#39;s important to realise that, in the interest of encouraging self-sufficiency from users, we expect you to have tried to resolve your problem yourself. Alternatively, if you&#39;re looking to implement some nifty new feature then we expect you to have tried to do so yourself. 
In short, this isn&#39;t a section where we&#39;ll do your work for you; it&#39;s a section where we&#39;ll correct you and put you back on the right path after you&#39;ve taken a left turn instead of a right turn while doing it yourself. :)

Finally, this section isn&#39;t for help related to correctly setting the Java Development Kit (&#39;JDK&#39;) up. Don&#39;t post requests for help that are related to not being able to compile or run your program.

Thanks guys.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 03 Mar 2009 14:21:57 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Game Development</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/section-rules/265535.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Section Rules</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@m.dog311 m.dog311]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/m.dog311">@m.dog311</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Welcome to the Client Help section. <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=6" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
<p>When posting your topic, please use a clear and easily understandable title. In your post, provide as much information as possible (stack traces in particular if some sort of exception is being thrown, and any other information you may be able to provide).</p>
<p>It’s important to realise that, in the interest of encouraging self-sufficiency from users, we expect you to have tried to resolve your problem yourself. Alternatively, if you’re looking to implement some nifty new feature then we expect you to have tried to do so yourself.<br>
In short, this isn’t a section where we’ll do your work for you; it’s a section where we’ll correct you and put you back on the right path after you’ve taken a left turn instead of a right turn while doing it yourself. <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=6" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
<p>Finally, this section isn’t for help related to correctly setting the Java Development Kit (‘JDK’) up. Don’t post requests for help that are related to not being able to compile or run your program.</p>
<p>Thanks guys.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/section-rules/265535/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/section-rules/265535/1</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 03 Mar 2009 14:21:57 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-265535-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/section-rules/265535.rss">Section Rules</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
