<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Private server problems</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/private-server-problems/217283</link>
    <description>When i first got my computer, i was able to use the silabs webclient until one day when i restarted my computer. i got back on and i went to the webclient but it said that the cache could not be downloaded. then when i tried to use the mopar webclient, the client opens for 5 seconds and then the window closes itself. Then i downloaded another client that ive used before and this one works except that i cant get on ANY server weather its on or offline. ill type in the correct IP address and port but when i click log-in, it says &quot;error connecting to server&quot;. then the next times i try to get on, it doesnt even attempt to connect and still says error connecting to server. it also does this with all my downloadble clients. The only private server i was ever able to connect to was dodian on their own webclient. Any help?</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 04 Jul 2008 03:44:56 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/private-server-problems/217283.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Private server problems</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@revengr revengr]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/revengr">@revengr</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>im kinda sure its not firewall settings cause temporarily i turned the firewall off (which probably wasnt a good idea…) but that didnt help at all, i still had the same problems.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/private-server-problems/217283/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/private-server-problems/217283/3</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 04 Jul 2008 03:44:56 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-217283-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/private-server-problems/217283.rss">Private server problems</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Private server problems</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@jandascape90 jandascape90]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/jandascape90">@jandascape90</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I honestly have no idea, but perhaps something with your firewall settings? Sorry i couldn’t help more.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/private-server-problems/217283/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/private-server-problems/217283/2</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 04 Jul 2008 03:43:31 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-217283-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/private-server-problems/217283.rss">Private server problems</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Private server problems</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@revengr revengr]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/revengr">@revengr</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>When i first got my computer, i was able to use the silabs webclient until one day when i restarted my computer. i got back on and i went to the webclient but it said that the cache could not be downloaded. then when i tried to use the mopar webclient, the client opens for 5 seconds and then the window closes itself. Then i downloaded another client that ive used before and this one works except that i cant get on ANY server weather its on or offline. ill type in the correct IP address and port but when i click log-in, it says “error connecting to server”. then the next times i try to get on, it doesnt even attempt to connect and still says error connecting to server. it also does this with all my downloadble clients. The only private server i was ever able to connect to was dodian on their own webclient. Any help?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/private-server-problems/217283/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/private-server-problems/217283/1</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 04 Jul 2008 03:38:15 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-217283-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/private-server-problems/217283.rss">Private server problems</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
