<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Quick Question</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/quick-question/263744</link>
    <description>Correct me if Im wrong, and i&#39;m not judging anyone who does this. Lets say i love playing a game, yet I&#39;d like the game to be a bit more fun, so i find out ways to alter codes within the game (an online game) so itd be more challenging or even more easy. So after Getting the codes the way i want them to be, I realize I shouldn&#39;t disrupt other players way of fun of playing the game the original way it was intended. so I create my own server, A private one for me and my friends. Seeing as its not a game i created from scratch, but a game i downloaded and tweaked with it a bit to my liking, is this considered hacking? i personally believe so, but in all honesty is it? you know seeing as it wasn&#39;t mine to begin with and me just tweaking it a bit. I am playing on my own server and all, but is this a FORM of hacking?

PS please dont sugar coat the answer. i wont get offended and it wont make me change my mind about the way i play my videogames.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2009 10:46:17 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/quick-question/263744.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Quick Question</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@primadude Primadude]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/primadude">@primadude</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>It’s called Customization.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/quick-question/263744/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/quick-question/263744/2</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2009 10:46:17 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-263744-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/quick-question/263744.rss">Quick Question</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Quick Question</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@alexc37 alexc37]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/alexc37">@alexc37</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Correct me if Im wrong, and i’m not judging anyone who does this. Lets say i love playing a game, yet I’d like the game to be a bit more fun, so i find out ways to alter codes within the game (an online game) so itd be more challenging or even more easy. So after Getting the codes the way i want them to be, I realize I shouldn’t disrupt other players way of fun of playing the game the original way it was intended. so I create my own server, A private one for me and my friends. Seeing as its not a game i created from scratch, but a game i downloaded and tweaked with it a bit to my liking, is this considered hacking? i personally believe so, but in all honesty is it? you know seeing as it wasn’t mine to begin with and me just tweaking it a bit. I am playing on my own server and all, but is this a FORM of hacking?</p>
<p>PS please dont sugar coat the answer. i wont get offended and it wont make me change my mind about the way i play my videogames.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/quick-question/263744/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/quick-question/263744/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2009 09:40:13 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-263744-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/quick-question/263744.rss">Quick Question</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
