<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Training Guide to a F2P Main</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/training-guide-to-a-f2p-main/180175</link>
    <description>Yes I know there are lots out there but this i made (BTW ty xxlegitxx for the start)
will update for looks later :)

In this guide I will tell you how to go from a newb off the tut island to a Small F2P main. All the quests will be done and the stats will be:
Attack: 40
Strenght: 40
Defence: 40
Range: 40
Magic: 40
Prayer: not calculated yet.
Health Points: ---&quot;---

Green is a quest
Blue is leveling...


[b]There will be more to raise melee.[/b]

[size=20pt][b]Training Magic[/b][/size]

[u][b]By levelling magic up this way you will not gain very many HP levels[/b][/u]

[u][b]Items for 40 Magic:[/b][/u] Bow, 25 arrows, raw meat, eye of newt, onion, Red bead, White bead, Black bead, Yellow bead, 795 mind runes, 795 air runes, wooden staff, Iron helm, iron plate, iron legs, Air staff, 712 Law runes, 199 Fire runes, 1236 Water runes, 1587 Earth runes, 516 body runes, wizard hat, Wizard body, amulet of magic

[font=Verdana](Quest)[/font] [b]Witch&#39;s Potion[/b]:  [quote=&quot;xxlegitxx, post:1, topic:131312&quot;]Bring 3gp, a bow, and some arrows, and go south from Falador.  Pick up a piece of raw meat and cook it on the stove.  If it burns it, good.  Otherwise, cook it again to burn it.  From there, go south until you see the flame symbol of the mage shop.  Enter and buy yourself a nice eye of newt for 3 gp.  Walk in the direction of Rimmington, past the mines, into the onion fields.  Pick an onion.  Now enter Hetty&#39;s house in Rimmington.  Talk to her and accept the quest.  Now to south-west a tiny bit into Brian&#39;s Archery Supplies and range a rat for its tail.  Return to Hetty for your prize.  Enjoy that level 4 mage.[/quote]

[b][b](Quest)[/b] Imp Catcher:[/b] Talk to Wizard Mizgog. He will tell you he has lost his beads. Which are Red bead, White bead, Black bead and the Yellow bead.
Kill some regular Imps to obtain the four beads. You can also buy them; this can help to save time. After you have collected all the beads, return to Wizard Mizgog. He will reward you with 875 magic xp, 1 quest point and an amulet of accuracy. This brings you to 10 Magic.

[b](Levelling 10-19)[/b] You will need: 795 mind runes and 795 air runes, wooden staff, Iron helm, iron plate, iron legs a partner with what you have.
Go to the duel arena and fight each other with the air blasts, the trick is to splash (not hit) your opponent by doing this with the 795 air and mind runes you 
Have you will achieve level 19 magic!

[b](Levelling 19-25)[/b] You will need: wooden staff, Iron helm, iron plate, iron legs, 1032 Water runes, 1548 Earth runes, 516 body runes.
Cast curse; the trick is to splash (not hit) your opponent. By doing this you will achieve level 25 magic!
[b]
(Levelling 25-31)[/b] You will need: Air staff, 199 Law runes, 199 Fire runes, wizard hat, wizard body, and amulet of magic.
Hit that Varrock Teleport.  Don&#39;t you feel all fuzzy inside? Do Varrock teleport until 31 magic. (199 Teleports)

[b](Levelling 31-37)[/b] You will need: Air staff, 309 Law runes, 309 Earth runes, wizard hat, wizard body, and amulet of magic.
Now hit that Lumbridge Teleport, until you reach 37 mage (309 Lumby Teleports).

[b](Levelling 37-40)[/b] You will need: Air staff, 204 Law runes, 204 Water runes, wizard hat, wizard body, and amulet of magic.
Finally press that Falador Teleport; you can do this until 40.

Wow wasn&#39;t that was quick?



[b][size=20pt]Training range[/size][/b]
By levelling this way you will get range levels and any hp levels.

[u][b]Items for 40 range:[/b][/u] A bow, Oak bow, Willow bow, 300 Bronze arrows, 4427 Iron arrows

(leveling 1-10), you will need: A bow, 300 bronze arrows and an amulet of accuracy. Assuming you hit 1 every time and get 4xp. Attack goblins at Lumbridge.

(leveling 10-20) you will need: An Oak bow, 332 Iron arrows and an amulet of accuracy. Assuming you hit 2.5 every time and get 10 xp. Attack level 12 Minotaurs at Stronghold of Security

(leveling 20-40), you will need: A Willow bow, 4095 Iron arrows (iron because we won&#39;t collect them) and an amulet of accuracy. Assuming you hit 3 Every time and get 8xp Kill the level 82 lesser demon In the wizards tower, take some telekinetic grabs just in case of rare drops 4095 hits of 8 is 32760 which gets us to level 40 range!

[size=20pt]Training melee[/size]

In training our melee stats (attack, strenght, defence) we will need to do quests, fight monsters, do quests and well, fight monsters.

[u][b]Items for 40/40/40:[/b][/u] A hammer, Garlic, Stake (found in quest) #magic or range wepons#

#You have two choices to mage the vampire or range the vampire [(Range) ### Mithril Arrows Maple bow] [(magic) ### Chaos runes, fire staff, ### air runes]# 

[b]Quest:[/b] [b]Vampire Slayer[/b] Find Morgan in Draynor, He&#39;ll tell you about the Vampire and that he wants you to kill it. He&#39;ll also tell you to go find his friend Dr. Harlow at the (Blue Moon Inn), go to varrock and speak to Dr. Harlow; when he wants a beer get him one. Dr Harlow will then tell you how to beat the Vampire and give you a Stake. Now take the hammer, stake, your choice of wepons to draynor manor and go to the stairs that go down. Open the coffin and the vampire should come out and start attacking you, go round the coffin untill one of you if on one side and the other is on the other side now mage or range the vampire, when the vampire is at 0 health he will not die untill the stake is driven though him. this can be done manully or automaticly.
When he is dead the quest will finish, savour that SWEET SWEET 20 attack.

[b](Leveling attack 20-30)[/b] Go to the monks near Barbarine village with a mithril scimitar full iron and a strenght ammy and kill the monks untill 30 attack, this can take a while so you may have to be here for a long time, or you could skip this step for later!

[b]Quest:[/b] [b]Romeo and Juliet[/b] &lt;blockquote&gt;# Talk to Juliet on her second floor balcony to learn about the love affair with Romeo and the complications that have set in. She asks you to take a message to Romeo in Varrock square. You can also Talk to Romeo in Varrock Square. Romeo will ask you to talk to Juliet.

# Juliet will give you a message to give to Romeo.

Message Romeo

# Take the message to Romeo and he will send you off to Father Lawrence who is in the chapel in the north-east part of Varrock.

# Father Lawrence is in the middle of a sermon, and he is reluctant to talk to you, but your character persists to the end. After you relate the situation he will tell you that you need a Cadava Potion, and to get one you need to talk to the Apothecary in south-west Varrock.

# The Apothecary will say that all he needs for the potion is a Cadava berry, which can be found south-east of varrock near the mining pits.

# Get the Cadava berries and bring them to the Apothecary, he will make you a Cadava potion.

# Bring the potion to Juliet, she will drink it and a cutscene will appear.

# Go and talk to Romeo and tell him the plan. Another cutscene will appear. Romeo forgets Juliet and meets her cousin, they live happy ever after (Romeo and Juliet&#39;s Cousin).
Quest Complete!

Who cares about a bad ending, as long as you get your reward, right?&lt;/blockquote&gt;

[b]Quest:[/b] [b]Pirate Treasure[/b] &lt;blockquote&gt;# Talk to Redbeard Frank the pirate, he will tell you about the treasure. Say that you want to get the treasure. He will ask you to get him a rum.

# Travel to Karamja and get off the ship. Go to the bar and buy a Karamjan rum which costs 30 coins.

# Now talk to Luthas in the house northeast of the bar. Talk to him and say that you want to help him. He will give you a job.

# Go to the banana field west of this house. Pick 10 bananas and go back to Luthas&#39;s house. Just east of it you will see a crate. Use some (not all) bananas in the crate then use the Karamjan rum on the crate. The rum is now inside. Put the remaining bananas in the crate until it&#39;s full. After it&#39;s full, talk to Luthas and he will pay you 30 coins.

# Travel back to Port Sarim and walk west. You will see a man called Wydin who owns a food shop. If you have the White apron now, put it on. If you don&#39;t, go to the Fish shop just north of you and there you will find a White apron hanging on the wall.

# Talk to Wydin and ask him to hire you, if you are wearing the White apron, he will hire you. When you need to get hired by Wydin he won&#39;t hire you if you talk to him. Instead you must try to open the storeroom door and he will tell that you can&#39;t go in unless you are an employee; then if you have the apron on and ask him, he will hire you.

# Search the all crates that are in the storeroom. One of them contains bananas and your Karamjan rum, take the Karamjan rum out.

# Talk to Redbeard Frank and he will be pleased and give you a key. He will say that a chest in Varrock contains the treasure.

# Go to Varrock and and go inside the Blue Moon Inn which is south of the General Stall. Go up to the second floor and into the west room. Use the key on the chest. You will get a note. Read it and it will tell you that the treasure is in Falador&#39;s park.

# Now it&#39;s time to dig up the treasure. Go into the park and find a statue. West of it is a large &quot;X&quot; on the ground. If you have the spade, dig at the center of the &quot;X&quot;. If you don&#39;t, find one in Falador in the house east of the Furnace. If you dig the flowers, a Gardener may attack you. Kill him and dig again. You will get 450 coins, a Gold ring and an Emerald, the quest rewards. The quest is now finished.&lt;/blockquote&gt;

[b]Quest[/b][b]Cooks Assistant[/b]&lt;blockquote&gt;# Talk to the Cook in Lumbridge Castle. He will ask you to help him get the ingredients for the cake because he has forgotten to buy them. Tell him that you will help.

# Getting the ingredients.

Flour: Get a Pot in Lumbridge Castle. Then head northwest. You should find a windmill. There is a grain field west of the windmill. Pick one Grain and go into the windmill. Go up to the top floor and use your Grain on the hopper. Operate the hopper and go back down. Use your Pot with the Flour.

Egg: You can find some eggs at a farm located northeast of Lumbridge. After you find the farm, there should be some chickens there. You can find some eggs near the chickens.

Milk: There should be a house near the chickens at the farm. Enter the house and get a bucket. Exit the farm and go to the east of this farm. You will find some cows there. Use the bucket on a Dairy cow and you will get a bucket of milk.

# After you get all the ingredients, return to the Cook and he will reward you. &lt;/blockquote&gt;

[b](Quest)[/b] [b]Demon Slayer:[/b] &lt;blockquote&gt;# Speak with Gypsy Aris. She will tell you about an ancient demon, Delrith, who was defeated long ago, by a a hero named Wally, who wielded the Silverlight sword. She tells you that the demon is returning, and is going to attempt to destroy Varrock. She prophesies that you are the one that can defeat the demon, and save the city. She also tells you the incantation that Wally used to defeat the demon. Make sure to write this down, as the incantation is different for each person.

# To get Silverlight, The Gypsy tells you to go and speak with Sir Prysin, in Varrock Castle.

# Sir Prysin is on the first floor of the castle, near the entrance. Speak with him.


# He will tell you that his grandfather was Wally, and the Sir Prysin has the sword in his possesion. However, there are three keys needed to unlock the case in which the sword is held. One key is with Captain Rovin, one with Wizard Traiborn, and another, Sir Prysin accidently dropped down the drain.

# Walk to the northwest end of the castle, and climb to the third floor, Rovin&#39;s Chamber. Speak with Rovin about the key. After a conversation, he will agree to give the key to you.


# Go back to the first floor, and head to the northeast side of the building. Climb up the stairs, and pick up a bucket.

# Go back down stairs, and fill the bucket up with water, at the sink. Then, go outside, and use the bucket of water with the drain. The key will fall down into the sewers.

# Walk out of the east castle walls, and climb down into the manhole (if the manhole is closed, simply open the lid).

#Walk towards the back, and pick up the key from the ground.

# Take your 25 bones, and head to the Wizards Tower, south of Draynor Village. Take them to the second floor, and speak with Traiborn. He will request 25 bones to preform a ritual so that he can get the key from his safekeeping.

# Talk to him again, and give him the 25 bones. He will perform the ritual, and give you the key.

# Take all 3 keys back to Sir Prysin in Varrock.

#He will give you Silverlight.

# Stock up on some food, and head to the ancient ruins just south of Varrock. Walk into the center of the ruins, and a cutscene will happen. After the cutscene, kill Delrith using Silverlight. Do not worry, he only has 7 hitpoints.

# Once he has been weakened enough, it will ask you for the incantation. Select the correct sequence of words.

# Once you say the incantation, Delrith will be sucked through a void.

Congratulations! Quest Complete!&lt;/blockquote&gt;</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 18 Feb 2008 20:04:03 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/training-guide-to-a-f2p-main/180175.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Training Guide to a F2P Main</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@bootnecklad bootnecklad]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/bootnecklad">@bootnecklad</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“Taharok, post:12, topic:180175”][quote author=bootnecklad link=topic=241426.msg2060287#msg2060287 date=1203303876]</p>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<ol>
<li>
<p>Did you ever try this yourself?</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Did you ever read the warning on <a href="http://runehq.com" rel="nofollow noopener">runehq.com</a>? All their guides are owned by them and if they find anyone else with them they will go to lawsuit measures, so perhaps you better l2make quest guides yourself.</p>
</li>
</ol>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<ol>
<li>
<p>I made this guide after planning, researching and stuff so no I haven’t done it but It would work.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>I’ll get round to it.<br>
[/quote]</p>
</li>
</ol>
<p>From personal experience, planning and then “helping” doesn’t work. Neither does “getting round to it”. No, you either plan and do or do not at all.[/quote]</p>
<p>Fuck you, just fuck you. Sorry thats all I have to say. IN a way thats all you do give to much constructive critisism; I know things like that help but just fuck off for once.<br>
Kthnxbi. comes to mind?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/training-guide-to-a-f2p-main/180175/13">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/training-guide-to-a-f2p-main/180175/13</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 18 Feb 2008 20:04:03 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-180175-13</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/training-guide-to-a-f2p-main/180175.rss">Training Guide to a F2P Main</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Training Guide to a F2P Main</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@mod_taharok Taharok]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/mod_taharok">@mod_taharok</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“bootnecklad, post:11, topic:180175”][quote author=Taharok link=topic=241426.msg2060224#msg2060224 date=1203301791]</p>
<ol>
<li>
<p>Did you ever try this yourself?</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Did you ever read the warning on <a href="http://runehq.com" rel="nofollow noopener">runehq.com</a>? All their guides are owned by them and if they find anyone else with them they will go to lawsuit measures, so perhaps you better l2make quest guides yourself.<br>
[/quote]</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>I made this guide after planning, researching and stuff so no I haven’t done it but It would work.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>I’ll get round to it.[/quote]</p>
</li>
</ol>
<p>From personal experience, planning and then “helping” doesn’t work. Neither does “getting round to it”. No, you either plan and do or do not at all.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/training-guide-to-a-f2p-main/180175/12">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/training-guide-to-a-f2p-main/180175/12</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 18 Feb 2008 06:54:25 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-180175-12</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/training-guide-to-a-f2p-main/180175.rss">Training Guide to a F2P Main</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Training Guide to a F2P Main</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@bootnecklad bootnecklad]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/bootnecklad">@bootnecklad</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“Taharok, post:10, topic:180175”]1. Did you ever try this yourself?</p>
<ol start="2">
<li>
<p>Did you ever read the warning on <a href="http://runehq.com" rel="nofollow noopener">runehq.com</a>? All their guides are owned by them and if they find anyone else with them they will go to lawsuit measures, so perhaps you better l2make quest guides yourself.[/quote]</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>I made this guide after planning, researching and stuff so no I haven’t done it but It would work.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>I’ll get round to it.</p>
</li>
</ol>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/training-guide-to-a-f2p-main/180175/11">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/training-guide-to-a-f2p-main/180175/11</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 18 Feb 2008 03:04:36 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-180175-11</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/training-guide-to-a-f2p-main/180175.rss">Training Guide to a F2P Main</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Training Guide to a F2P Main</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@mod_taharok Taharok]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/mod_taharok">@mod_taharok</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <ol>
<li>
<p>Did you ever try this yourself?</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Did you ever read the warning on <a href="http://runehq.com" rel="nofollow noopener">runehq.com</a>? All their guides are owned by them and if they find anyone else with them they will go to lawsuit measures, so perhaps you better l2make quest guides yourself.</p>
</li>
</ol>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/training-guide-to-a-f2p-main/180175/10">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/training-guide-to-a-f2p-main/180175/10</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 18 Feb 2008 02:29:51 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-180175-10</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/training-guide-to-a-f2p-main/180175.rss">Training Guide to a F2P Main</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Training Guide to a F2P Main</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@billygotshot billygotshot]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/billygotshot">@billygotshot</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“exe626, post:2, topic:180175”]40 ranged and magic at the same time for a pure? I smell failure. Any pure that decided to go straight range would kill a 40 range/40 magic hybrid combo. How many times do I gotta tell these people, pure is sticking to 1 fighting style. Being hybrid is great, it gives you a special edge the other pure may not have. But, if you plan to be hybrid, why ruin yourself so low? If you plan to be hybrid, play it smart.</p>
<p>Get 60-70 ranged, pure. Stick with ranged souly as long as possibly. When you feel the time is finally right, get some quick magic levels. Don’t cut short, because you’ll regret it. Go for what you’re going for. You want 90 ranged and 82 magic? Get 70 ranged, then 60 magic, then 80 ranged and 70 magic, then 90 ranged and 82 magic. It will control your combat to stay low, while being able to at least fight with a skill that means something(range).[/quote]<br>
best hybrid i have ever seen had 60 range 88 str 1 att 1 def… range until low whip out obby maul. level 56 combat or something like that…</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/training-guide-to-a-f2p-main/180175/9">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/training-guide-to-a-f2p-main/180175/9</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 17 Feb 2008 19:19:43 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-180175-9</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/training-guide-to-a-f2p-main/180175.rss">Training Guide to a F2P Main</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Training Guide to a F2P Main</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@jac jac]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/jac">@jac</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Woah, the monk training actually worked … pretty fast aswell</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/training-guide-to-a-f2p-main/180175/8">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/training-guide-to-a-f2p-main/180175/8</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 16 Feb 2008 19:26:51 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-180175-8</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/training-guide-to-a-f2p-main/180175.rss">Training Guide to a F2P Main</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Training Guide to a F2P Main</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Algas Algas]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/algas">@Algas</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“bootnecklad, post:3, topic:180175”]Its not for a pure, its for a general account, I just havn’t done the melee part. <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=6" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"></p>
<p>EDIT - What would you train against to get from 40-50 range(stays F2P)[/quote]<br>
If you are F2P ranger just train at lessers inside Volcano in Karamja</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/training-guide-to-a-f2p-main/180175/7">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/training-guide-to-a-f2p-main/180175/7</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 16 Feb 2008 19:18:40 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-180175-7</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/training-guide-to-a-f2p-main/180175.rss">Training Guide to a F2P Main</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Training Guide to a F2P Main</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@jac jac]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/jac">@jac</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Cool, i might do this … i got a lvl 28 or something with 20 atk ( somut like that ) 38 str and 1 def … But aftr see’ing this tutorial i might do my mage &amp; range aswell.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/training-guide-to-a-f2p-main/180175/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/training-guide-to-a-f2p-main/180175/6</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 16 Feb 2008 18:10:19 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-180175-6</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/training-guide-to-a-f2p-main/180175.rss">Training Guide to a F2P Main</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Training Guide to a F2P Main</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@bootnecklad bootnecklad]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/bootnecklad">@bootnecklad</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>It goes in the order to train; Magic, range then I will do melee</p>
<p>EDIT - And also I like low hp level accouns.[br][br][size=1]Posted on: February 15, 2008, 10:38:06 AM[/size][hr]Updated a bit.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/training-guide-to-a-f2p-main/180175/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/training-guide-to-a-f2p-main/180175/5</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 10 Feb 2008 16:13:07 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-180175-5</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/training-guide-to-a-f2p-main/180175.rss">Training Guide to a F2P Main</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Training Guide to a F2P Main</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@exe626 exe626]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/exe626">@exe626</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I must have miss read all the steps that claim the only thing you’re training is ranged and magic. While also maintaining a low hp(curse magic).</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/training-guide-to-a-f2p-main/180175/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/training-guide-to-a-f2p-main/180175/4</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 10 Feb 2008 16:08:01 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-180175-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/training-guide-to-a-f2p-main/180175.rss">Training Guide to a F2P Main</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Training Guide to a F2P Main</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@bootnecklad bootnecklad]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/bootnecklad">@bootnecklad</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Its not for a pure, its for a general account, I just havn’t done the melee part. <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=6" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"></p>
<p>EDIT - What would you train against to get from 40-50 range(stays F2P)</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/training-guide-to-a-f2p-main/180175/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/training-guide-to-a-f2p-main/180175/3</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 10 Feb 2008 16:06:16 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-180175-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/training-guide-to-a-f2p-main/180175.rss">Training Guide to a F2P Main</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Training Guide to a F2P Main</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@exe626 exe626]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/exe626">@exe626</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>40 ranged and magic at the same time for a pure? I smell failure. Any pure that decided to go straight range would kill a 40 range/40 magic hybrid combo. How many times do I gotta tell these people, pure is sticking to 1 fighting style. Being hybrid is great, it gives you a special edge the other pure may not have. But, if you plan to be hybrid, why ruin yourself so low? If you plan to be hybrid, play it smart.</p>
<p>Get 60-70 ranged, pure. Stick with ranged souly as long as possibly. When you feel the time is finally right, get some quick magic levels. Don’t cut short, because you’ll regret it. Go for what you’re going for. You want 90 ranged and 82 magic? Get 70 ranged, then 60 magic, then 80 ranged and 70 magic, then 90 ranged and 82 magic. It will control your combat to stay low, while being able to at least fight with a skill that means something(range).</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/training-guide-to-a-f2p-main/180175/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/training-guide-to-a-f2p-main/180175/2</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 10 Feb 2008 16:05:26 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-180175-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/training-guide-to-a-f2p-main/180175.rss">Training Guide to a F2P Main</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Training Guide to a F2P Main</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@bootnecklad bootnecklad]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/bootnecklad">@bootnecklad</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Yes I know there are lots out there but this i made (BTW ty xxlegitxx for the start)<br>
will update for looks later <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=6" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
<p>In this guide I will tell you how to go from a newb off the tut island to a Small F2P main. All the quests will be done and the stats will be:<br>
Attack: 40<br>
Strenght: 40<br>
Defence: 40<br>
Range: 40<br>
Magic: 40<br>
Prayer: not calculated yet.<br>
Health Points: —"---</p>
<p>Green is a quest<br>
Blue is leveling…</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">There will be more to raise melee.</span></p>
<p>[size=20pt]<span class="bbcode-b">Training Magic</span>[/size]</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-u"><span class="bbcode-b">By levelling magic up this way you will not gain very many HP levels</span></span></p>
<p><span class="bbcode-u"><span class="bbcode-b">Items for 40 Magic:</span></span> Bow, 25 arrows, raw meat, eye of newt, onion, Red bead, White bead, Black bead, Yellow bead, 795 mind runes, 795 air runes, wooden staff, Iron helm, iron plate, iron legs, Air staff, 712 Law runes, 199 Fire runes, 1236 Water runes, 1587 Earth runes, 516 body runes, wizard hat, Wizard body, amulet of magic</p>
<p><a>font=Verdana</a>[/font] <span class="bbcode-b">Witch’s Potion</span>:  [quote=“xxlegitxx, post:1, topic:131312”]Bring 3gp, a bow, and some arrows, and go south from Falador.  Pick up a piece of raw meat and cook it on the stove.  If it burns it, good.  Otherwise, cook it again to burn it.  From there, go south until you see the flame symbol of the mage shop.  Enter and buy yourself a nice eye of newt for 3 gp.  Walk in the direction of Rimmington, past the mines, into the onion fields.  Pick an onion.  Now enter Hetty’s house in Rimmington.  Talk to her and accept the quest.  Now to south-west a tiny bit into Brian’s Archery Supplies and range a rat for its tail.  Return to Hetty for your prize.  Enjoy that level 4 mage.[/quote]</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b"><a>b</a></span> Imp Catcher:[/b] Talk to Wizard Mizgog. He will tell you he has lost his beads. Which are Red bead, White bead, Black bead and the Yellow bead.<br>
Kill some regular Imps to obtain the four beads. You can also buy them; this can help to save time. After you have collected all the beads, return to Wizard Mizgog. He will reward you with 875 magic xp, 1 quest point and an amulet of accuracy. This brings you to 10 Magic.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">(Levelling 10-19)</span> You will need: 795 mind runes and 795 air runes, wooden staff, Iron helm, iron plate, iron legs a partner with what you have.<br>
Go to the duel arena and fight each other with the air blasts, the trick is to splash (not hit) your opponent by doing this with the 795 air and mind runes you<br>
Have you will achieve level 19 magic!</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">(Levelling 19-25)</span> You will need: wooden staff, Iron helm, iron plate, iron legs, 1032 Water runes, 1548 Earth runes, 516 body runes.<br>
Cast curse; the trick is to splash (not hit) your opponent. By doing this you will achieve level 25 magic!<br>
<span class="bbcode-b"><br>
(Levelling 25-31)</span> You will need: Air staff, 199 Law runes, 199 Fire runes, wizard hat, wizard body, and amulet of magic.<br>
Hit that Varrock Teleport.  Don’t you feel all fuzzy inside? Do Varrock teleport until 31 magic. (199 Teleports)</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">(Levelling 31-37)</span> You will need: Air staff, 309 Law runes, 309 Earth runes, wizard hat, wizard body, and amulet of magic.<br>
Now hit that Lumbridge Teleport, until you reach 37 mage (309 Lumby Teleports).</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">(Levelling 37-40)</span> You will need: Air staff, 204 Law runes, 204 Water runes, wizard hat, wizard body, and amulet of magic.<br>
Finally press that Falador Teleport; you can do this until 40.</p>
<p>Wow wasn’t that was quick?</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">[size=20pt]Training range[/size]</span><br>
By levelling this way you will get range levels and any hp levels.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-u"><span class="bbcode-b">Items for 40 range:</span></span> A bow, Oak bow, Willow bow, 300 Bronze arrows, 4427 Iron arrows</p>
<p>(leveling 1-10), you will need: A bow, 300 bronze arrows and an amulet of accuracy. Assuming you hit 1 every time and get 4xp. Attack goblins at Lumbridge.</p>
<p>(leveling 10-20) you will need: An Oak bow, 332 Iron arrows and an amulet of accuracy. Assuming you hit 2.5 every time and get 10 xp. Attack level 12 Minotaurs at Stronghold of Security</p>
<p>(leveling 20-40), you will need: A Willow bow, 4095 Iron arrows (iron because we won’t collect them) and an amulet of accuracy. Assuming you hit 3 Every time and get 8xp Kill the level 82 lesser demon In the wizards tower, take some telekinetic grabs just in case of rare drops 4095 hits of 8 is 32760 which gets us to level 40 range!</p>
<p>[size=20pt]Training melee[/size]</p>
<p>In training our melee stats (attack, strenght, defence) we will need to do quests, fight monsters, do quests and well, fight monsters.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-u"><span class="bbcode-b">Items for 40/40/40:</span></span> A hammer, Garlic, Stake (found in quest) <span class="hashtag">#magic</span> or range wepons#</p>
<p><span class="hashtag">#You</span> have two choices to mage the vampire or range the vampire [(Range) ### Mithril Arrows Maple bow] [(magic) ### Chaos runes, fire staff, ### air runes]#</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Quest:</span> <span class="bbcode-b">Vampire Slayer</span> Find Morgan in Draynor, He’ll tell you about the Vampire and that he wants you to kill it. He’ll also tell you to go find his friend Dr. Harlow at the (Blue Moon Inn), go to varrock and speak to Dr. Harlow; when he wants a beer get him one. Dr Harlow will then tell you how to beat the Vampire and give you a Stake. Now take the hammer, stake, your choice of wepons to draynor manor and go to the stairs that go down. Open the coffin and the vampire should come out and start attacking you, go round the coffin untill one of you if on one side and the other is on the other side now mage or range the vampire, when the vampire is at 0 health he will not die untill the stake is driven though him. this can be done manully or automaticly.<br>
When he is dead the quest will finish, savour that SWEET SWEET 20 attack.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">(Leveling attack 20-30)</span> Go to the monks near Barbarine village with a mithril scimitar full iron and a strenght ammy and kill the monks untill 30 attack, this can take a while so you may have to be here for a long time, or you could skip this step for later!</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Quest:</span> <span class="bbcode-b">Romeo and Juliet</span> </p><blockquote># Talk to Juliet on her second floor balcony to learn about the love affair with Romeo and the complications that have set in. She asks you to take a message to Romeo in Varrock square. You can also Talk to Romeo in Varrock Square. Romeo will ask you to talk to Juliet.
<h1>Juliet will give you a message to give to Romeo.</h1>
<p>Message Romeo</p>
<h1>Take the message to Romeo and he will send you off to Father Lawrence who is in the chapel in the north-east part of Varrock.</h1>
<h1>Father Lawrence is in the middle of a sermon, and he is reluctant to talk to you, but your character persists to the end. After you relate the situation he will tell you that you need a Cadava Potion, and to get one you need to talk to the Apothecary in south-west Varrock.</h1>
<h1>The Apothecary will say that all he needs for the potion is a Cadava berry, which can be found south-east of varrock near the mining pits.</h1>
<h1>Get the Cadava berries and bring them to the Apothecary, he will make you a Cadava potion.</h1>
<h1>Bring the potion to Juliet, she will drink it and a cutscene will appear.</h1>
<h1>Go and talk to Romeo and tell him the plan. Another cutscene will appear. Romeo forgets Juliet and meets her cousin, they live happy ever after (Romeo and Juliet’s Cousin).</h1>
<p>Quest Complete!</p>
<p>Who cares about a bad ending, as long as you get your reward, right?</p>
</blockquote>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Quest:</span> <span class="bbcode-b">Pirate Treasure</span> </p><blockquote># Talk to Redbeard Frank the pirate, he will tell you about the treasure. Say that you want to get the treasure. He will ask you to get him a rum.
<h1>Travel to Karamja and get off the ship. Go to the bar and buy a Karamjan rum which costs 30 coins.</h1>
<h1>Now talk to Luthas in the house northeast of the bar. Talk to him and say that you want to help him. He will give you a job.</h1>
<h1>Go to the banana field west of this house. Pick 10 bananas and go back to Luthas’s house. Just east of it you will see a crate. Use some (not all) bananas in the crate then use the Karamjan rum on the crate. The rum is now inside. Put the remaining bananas in the crate until it’s full. After it’s full, talk to Luthas and he will pay you 30 coins.</h1>
<h1>Travel back to Port Sarim and walk west. You will see a man called Wydin who owns a food shop. If you have the White apron now, put it on. If you don’t, go to the Fish shop just north of you and there you will find a White apron hanging on the wall.</h1>
<h1>Talk to Wydin and ask him to hire you, if you are wearing the White apron, he will hire you. When you need to get hired by Wydin he won’t hire you if you talk to him. Instead you must try to open the storeroom door and he will tell that you can’t go in unless you are an employee; then if you have the apron on and ask him, he will hire you.</h1>
<h1>Search the all crates that are in the storeroom. One of them contains bananas and your Karamjan rum, take the Karamjan rum out.</h1>
<h1>Talk to Redbeard Frank and he will be pleased and give you a key. He will say that a chest in Varrock contains the treasure.</h1>
<h1>Go to Varrock and and go inside the Blue Moon Inn which is south of the General Stall. Go up to the second floor and into the west room. Use the key on the chest. You will get a note. Read it and it will tell you that the treasure is in Falador’s park.</h1>
<h1>Now it’s time to dig up the treasure. Go into the park and find a statue. West of it is a large “X” on the ground. If you have the spade, dig at the center of the “X”. If you don’t, find one in Falador in the house east of the Furnace. If you dig the flowers, a Gardener may attack you. Kill him and dig again. You will get 450 coins, a Gold ring and an Emerald, the quest rewards. The quest is now finished.</h1>
</blockquote>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Quest</span><span class="bbcode-b">Cooks Assistant</span></p><blockquote># Talk to the Cook in Lumbridge Castle. He will ask you to help him get the ingredients for the cake because he has forgotten to buy them. Tell him that you will help.
<h1>Getting the ingredients.</h1>
<p>Flour: Get a Pot in Lumbridge Castle. Then head northwest. You should find a windmill. There is a grain field west of the windmill. Pick one Grain and go into the windmill. Go up to the top floor and use your Grain on the hopper. Operate the hopper and go back down. Use your Pot with the Flour.</p>
<p>Egg: You can find some eggs at a farm located northeast of Lumbridge. After you find the farm, there should be some chickens there. You can find some eggs near the chickens.</p>
<p>Milk: There should be a house near the chickens at the farm. Enter the house and get a bucket. Exit the farm and go to the east of this farm. You will find some cows there. Use the bucket on a Dairy cow and you will get a bucket of milk.</p>
<h1>After you get all the ingredients, return to the Cook and he will reward you. </h1>
</blockquote>
<p><a>b</a>[/b] <span class="bbcode-b">Demon Slayer:</span> </p><blockquote># Speak with Gypsy Aris. She will tell you about an ancient demon, Delrith, who was defeated long ago, by a a hero named Wally, who wielded the Silverlight sword. She tells you that the demon is returning, and is going to attempt to destroy Varrock. She prophesies that you are the one that can defeat the demon, and save the city. She also tells you the incantation that Wally used to defeat the demon. Make sure to write this down, as the incantation is different for each person.
<h1>To get Silverlight, The Gypsy tells you to go and speak with Sir Prysin, in Varrock Castle.</h1>
<h1>Sir Prysin is on the first floor of the castle, near the entrance. Speak with him.</h1>
<h1>He will tell you that his grandfather was Wally, and the Sir Prysin has the sword in his possesion. However, there are three keys needed to unlock the case in which the sword is held. One key is with Captain Rovin, one with Wizard Traiborn, and another, Sir Prysin accidently dropped down the drain.</h1>
<h1>Walk to the northwest end of the castle, and climb to the third floor, Rovin’s Chamber. Speak with Rovin about the key. After a conversation, he will agree to give the key to you.</h1>
<h1>Go back to the first floor, and head to the northeast side of the building. Climb up the stairs, and pick up a bucket.</h1>
<h1>Go back down stairs, and fill the bucket up with water, at the sink. Then, go outside, and use the bucket of water with the drain. The key will fall down into the sewers.</h1>
<h1>Walk out of the east castle walls, and climb down into the manhole (if the manhole is closed, simply open the lid).</h1>
<p><span class="hashtag">#Walk</span> towards the back, and pick up the key from the ground.</p>
<h1>Take your 25 bones, and head to the Wizards Tower, south of Draynor Village. Take them to the second floor, and speak with Traiborn. He will request 25 bones to preform a ritual so that he can get the key from his safekeeping.</h1>
<h1>Talk to him again, and give him the 25 bones. He will perform the ritual, and give you the key.</h1>
<h1>Take all 3 keys back to Sir Prysin in Varrock.</h1>
<p><span class="hashtag">#He</span> will give you Silverlight.</p>
<h1>Stock up on some food, and head to the ancient ruins just south of Varrock. Walk into the center of the ruins, and a cutscene will happen. After the cutscene, kill Delrith using Silverlight. Do not worry, he only has 7 hitpoints.</h1>
<h1>Once he has been weakened enough, it will ask you for the incantation. Select the correct sequence of words.</h1>
<h1>Once you say the incantation, Delrith will be sucked through a void.</h1>
<p>Congratulations! Quest Complete!</p>
</blockquote>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/training-guide-to-a-f2p-main/180175/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/training-guide-to-a-f2p-main/180175/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 10 Feb 2008 15:42:56 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-180175-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/training-guide-to-a-f2p-main/180175.rss">Training Guide to a F2P Main</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
