<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>My VERY Problem</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-very-problem/320286</link>
    <description>Hey, this I posted at http://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php/topic,413135.0/all.html

And now I&#39;m posting it here because no one reads it there.. 
If a mod or a nice guy (hopefully will be mod after helping me out) can help me, check out the thread at the URL and answer my questions and help me out.  ;)




&lt;blockquote&gt;Well, this is my VERY problem. 

Listening on port 43594.

NOOOOOTHING HAPPENING! 

If SOMEONE could EVER help me... Then I will cry, so geek am I. I pray for GOD, dudes! I just do SO MUCH want to host a fully working server that I can edit! I will share everything with me if you want! I will invite my whole school and everything! 

If you want me to take screenshots or anything else, I will really. I do anything for this!! I will help you people to help me! 
I am using Windows XP. 

Please give feedback or whatever it&#39;s called! 

Maybe I forgot that you connect whit Moparscape client? Well, if so, I still wonder why it just says that error..

Listening on port 43594. 

I&#39;m still trying to solve this problem myself to 110% but I don&#39;t really suceed, I&#39;m active nerd. 
Or do I need the client you posted under the source? Or is it your server? Well, if so I will check that out too. 
I will give you reputation so much you ever may take to the first person who helps me out whit this. 

[Day 1]

Trying to connect from the client u posted.. I also followed the tut about how to change IP. I aslo discovered u may change the port. Any ways it says error_js5connect or something like that and I think it&#39;s about the port? What u guys recomend? portforwarding through router (I can&#39;t connect to the router, don&#39;t know how to find out really much information needed about it)? Or µtorrent or similiar? Then howto? 

Also: If I connect through that Jagex client.. Then how do I edit source and such? Maybe you just think I&#39;m newbie but I really need help, I will be greatful or however it&#39;s spelled.. 

[Day 2]

Trying to download some portforwarder program, today our network crashed, now I&#39;m using someone else network. 
We will get help from Telia, our rooter is their product, I think.. 
//Lolle

________________________
Love is my name IRL!!!! &lt;3&lt;3&lt;3333
OMG! 

you may also email me at [mr.lolle@live.se]&lt;/blockquote&gt;</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 18 Dec 2009 10:01:26 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-very-problem/320286.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>My VERY Problem</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Ifalldownalot Ifalldownalot]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/ifalldownalot">@Ifalldownalot</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Hey, this I posted at <a href="http://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php/topic,413135.0/all.html" rel="nofollow noopener">http://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php/topic,413135.0/all.html</a></p>
<p>And now I’m posting it here because no one reads it there…<br>
If a mod or a nice guy (hopefully will be mod after helping me out) can help me, check out the thread at the URL and answer my questions and help me out.  <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/wink.png?v=5" title=":wink:" class="emoji" alt=":wink:"></p>
<blockquote>Well, this is my VERY problem. 
<p>Listening on port 43594.</p>
<p>NOOOOOTHING HAPPENING!</p>
<p>If SOMEONE could EVER help me… Then I will cry, so geek am I. I pray for GOD, dudes! I just do SO MUCH want to host a fully working server that I can edit! I will share everything with me if you want! I will invite my whole school and everything!</p>
<p>If you want me to take screenshots or anything else, I will really. I do anything for this!! I will help you people to help me!<br>
I am using Windows XP.</p>
<p>Please give feedback or whatever it’s called!</p>
<p>Maybe I forgot that you connect whit Moparscape client? Well, if so, I still wonder why it just says that error…</p>
<p>Listening on port 43594.</p>
<p>I’m still trying to solve this problem myself to 110% but I don’t really suceed, I’m active nerd.<br>
Or do I need the client you posted under the source? Or is it your server? Well, if so I will check that out too.<br>
I will give you reputation so much you ever may take to the first person who helps me out whit this.</p>
<p>[Day 1]</p>
<p>Trying to connect from the client u posted… I also followed the tut about how to change IP. I aslo discovered u may change the port. Any ways it says error_js5connect or something like that and I think it’s about the port? What u guys recomend? portforwarding through router (I can’t connect to the router, don’t know how to find out really much information needed about it)? Or µtorrent or similiar? Then howto?</p>
<p>Also: If I connect through that Jagex client… Then how do I edit source and such? Maybe you just think I’m newbie but I really need help, I will be greatful or however it’s spelled…</p>
<p>[Day 2]</p>
<p>Trying to download some portforwarder program, today our network crashed, now I’m using someone else network.<br>
We will get help from Telia, our rooter is their product, I think…<br>
//Lolle</p>
<hr>
<p>Love is my name IRL!!! &lt;3&lt;3&lt;3333<br>
OMG!</p>
<p>you may also email me at [mr.lolle@live.se]</p>
</blockquote>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-very-problem/320286/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-very-problem/320286/1</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 18 Dec 2009 10:01:26 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-320286-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-very-problem/320286.rss">My VERY Problem</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
