<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Suggestion Compilation</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/suggestion-compilation/519785</link>
    <description>This is a bunch of suggestions I have pertaining to rule enforcement as well as community involvement.

[u]Server &amp; Client Help Sections[/u]
 - [b]Thread Naming[/b]
The need for descriptive thread titles is an apparently overlooked guideline in the help sections. To have to look through these topics as well, and then having to report them if they are not in the right section, is not a very fun task. For those that will say &#39;Nobody says you have to,&#39; well, that is one of the main reasons I joined this forum - to help people in the help sections.
My suggestion is to create a forum mod that will prompt the user after clicking the post button, asking that they make sure the title is descriptive enough. This will at least let the user know that more descriptive thread naming will have their problem solved faster.
 - [b]Payment Within Threads[/b]
All users that offer payment within their threads should be given a verbal warning by a moderator, and the contents of their thread edited. Every offense afterwords should result in a +5 warning level to their account. This is not too strong of an infraction, yet heavy enough that they will at least learn not to do it again, if not from the first time.
 - [b]Duplicate Posting[/b]
Obviously this rule is not enforced heavily. The most I&#39;ve ever seen a user penalized for duplicate posting is a thread lock. The large majority of users that post duplicates are those that have been verbally warned for it in the past. They obviously do not learn their lesson. I request that all users that post duplicate threads should be warned on first abuse, and have a +5 on second abuse, along with one of their threads locked.

[u]Badges and Awards[/u]
 - [b]The Server Helper Award[/b]
The Server Helper award is not used in the slightest. I know of three members at most who have the award on these forums, and I rarely ever see more than one of them make any posts in these sections anymore. Of course helping should come from the kindness of another user, yet, when there is something to be earned from being a very helpful user, at least use it. At the very least, a set of specific guidelines should be published.

That&#39;s about it for this thread, please leave some feedback below.
A thread that I&#39;ve based some of my ideas on, as well as more points commenters might like to bring up: http://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php/topic,637962.0.html</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 22 May 2013 03:22:04 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Community Suggestions</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/suggestion-compilation/519785.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Suggestion Compilation</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Flame3 John]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/flame3">@Flame3</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote" data-post="16" data-topic="519785">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/user_avatar/forum.moparisthebest.com/davidi2/40/2579_1.png" class="avatar"> Davidi2:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>I always felt like the nominations board was a horrible idea. I fear that people would work hard for a few weeks and then get a friend to put them up for nomination, and then once they get the award they will stop caring about helping anymore.  This is only an issue because of how we are with awards. So selective choosing them, but then they are basically never removed. Making it that easy to get one (just help a lot for X weeks) and then not having any criteria to keep it seems like a bad idea.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>People were also skeptical about this board. Yet it is used properly for the most part, and mature discussion is not a rare occurrence in this section.<br>
Once you earn the award, you should be held accountable towards living up to your name, as well.</p>
<aside class="quote" data-post="16" data-topic="519785">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/user_avatar/forum.moparisthebest.com/davidi2/40/2579_1.png" class="avatar"> Davidi2:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Basically: If you have clear criteria to get an award, you should have similar criteria to lose the award.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I couldn’t say it better myself.</p>
<aside class="quote quote-modified" data-post="16" data-topic="519785">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/user_avatar/forum.moparisthebest.com/davidi2/40/2579_1.png" class="avatar"> Davidi2:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Anyways… more on topic… your ideas are extreme. And that’s coming from me. Especially the payment within threads. I like what staff have been doing a lot more. “We do not allow people to pay for help on this forum”, and editing the topic to remove the payment offer. However, I do agree that thread naming is a problem, but I don’t think heavier moderation  (don’t have the manpower) or a forum mod is the solution. The real solution would be to have people just not reply to those threads so they get buried, but alas I don’t think that would happen.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I had worded the OP a bit aggressively, so excuse any extremities that may be present. My opinion on the matter has changed since I’ve posted this simply because of getting a first-hand discussion with a mod. I don’t feel that what I’ve said about giving warnings for misnamed topics is the best decision anymore, simply because now I’m seeing it as unfair. When a user comes here to post a topic, and they don’t plan on sticking around afterwords, to have a punishment waiting for them is not good. As for what I’ve said towards payment, I think that the only reason for an infraction should be when the user has multiple offenses and has been warned in the past. My reasoning behind the naming prompt was so that we could at least hold the user accountable for not having a descriptive title, and they wouldn’t be able to say ‘I didn’t know.’</p>
<p>I’d like to apologize for the previous wording of the thread. It was aggressive as well as unnecessary. I’ve reworded most of the thread. If I could get more feedback now on the newer version, I’d appreciate it.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/suggestion-compilation/519785/17">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/suggestion-compilation/519785/17</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2013 03:22:04 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-519785-17</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/suggestion-compilation/519785.rss">Suggestion Compilation</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Suggestion Compilation</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@davidi2 Davidi2]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/davidi2">@davidi2</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I always felt like the nominations board was a horrible idea. I fear that people would work hard for a few weeks and then get a friend to put them up for nomination, and then once they get the award they will stop caring about helping anymore.  This is only an issue because of how we are with awards. So selective choosing them, but then they are basically never removed. Making it that easy to get one (just help a lot for X weeks) and then not having any criteria to keep it seems like a bad idea.</p>
<p>Basically: If you have clear criteria to get an award, you should have similar criteria to lose the award.</p>
<p>Anyways… more on topic… your ideas are extreme. And that’s coming from me. Especially the payment within threads. I like what staff have been doing a lot more. “We do not allow people to pay for help on this forum”, and editing the topic to remove the payment offer. However, I do agree that thread naming is a problem, but I don’t think heavier moderation  (don’t have the manpower) or a forum mod is the solution. The real solution would be to have people just not reply to those threads so they get buried, but alas I don’t think that would happen.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/suggestion-compilation/519785/16">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/suggestion-compilation/519785/16</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2013 00:57:26 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-519785-16</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/suggestion-compilation/519785.rss">Suggestion Compilation</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Suggestion Compilation</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Flame3 John]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/flame3">@Flame3</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote quote-modified" data-post="14" data-topic="519785">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 Taharok:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>To you it may seem that putting in more moderated effort will be a catch-all solution to this problems. That’s not actually the case. One, it requires more manpower that’s not available or exclusively available in the short-term (activity in moderators for long periods of time is incredibly rare). Second, people hate having sticks shoved up their asses, so to speak. By shoving hard enforcement down on people, it discourages them from actually posting. You may see that as a benefit, since the people not posting are probably the people you’re talking about, anyway. I see it as losing a lot of activity and members to other forums that aren’t so stringent on layout and policy.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>You have multitudes of experience over me, so I will not attempt to sway your opinion any farther than I feel necessary. Assuming that you’ve read the other replies in this topic, you can understand that I see it happening time upon time again with the same users, and no action is taken against them. (I’m referring to payments within threads)</p>
<aside class="quote quote-modified" data-post="14" data-topic="519785">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 Taharok:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>This is foremost why the system is the way it is. We have ideals that a lot of the members of our community highly adhere to (obvious if you read the replies to this topic). If people don’t adhere to these ideals, ie: posting a descriptive title for a help topic, they aren’t going to receive help, they may be flamed, or overall they will not receive a satisfactory response. This is fine by me (perhaps minus the amount of flaming). The system works better than you think.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>What happens when community dissatisfaction is not enough? I see it quite evidently not enough when the same users infringe rules time after time again and walk away without a single moderating action taken against them.</p>
<aside class="quote" data-post="14" data-topic="519785">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 Taharok:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>I do agree we need more server helpers awarded for those who are very helpful individuals. Do you have any suggestion as to how we can go about that effectively?</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I’ll be glad to chat with you sometime.<br>
Two ideas that I’m willing to summarize openly, I can talk more in depth in private:</p>
<p>[ul][li]Once every two weeks or so - up to you - the staff team can read through the help sections and see who is being a very notably helpful individual. A user whose name is seen perhaps for a month or two in a row, or whose name is discussed many times, yet perhaps not subsequently, should be nominated and then discussed.[/li]<br>
[li]Return of the nominations board? Or, since I’ve not been here long enough to know if that ever existed, perhaps add one? The reason this is an advantage over simply private messaging a moderator to request a nomination is so we can get public input. Of course, we would need to have strict posting guidelines to ensure that a mature discussion is held within each nomination’s thread. If necessary, I could write a set of guidelines for the staff team to work off of.[/li][/ul]</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/suggestion-compilation/519785/15">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/suggestion-compilation/519785/15</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 21 May 2013 21:27:29 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-519785-15</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/suggestion-compilation/519785.rss">Suggestion Compilation</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Suggestion Compilation</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@mod_taharok Taharok]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/mod_taharok">@mod_taharok</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>To you it may seem that putting in more moderated effort will be a catch-all solution to this problems. That’s not actually the case. One, it requires more manpower that’s not available or exclusively available in the short-term (activity in moderators for long periods of time is incredibly rare). Second, people hate having sticks shoved up their asses, so to speak. By shoving hard enforcement down on people, it discourages them from actually posting. You may see that as a benefit, since the people not posting are probably the people you’re talking about, anyway. I see it as losing a lot of activity and members to other forums that aren’t so stringent on layout and policy.</p>
<p>This is foremost why the system is the way it is. We have ideals that a lot of the members of our community highly adhere to (obvious if you read the replies to this topic). If people don’t adhere to these ideals, ie: posting a descriptive title for a help topic, they aren’t going to receive help, they may be flamed, or overall they will not receive a satisfactory response. This is fine by me (perhaps minus the amount of flaming). The system works better than you think.</p>
<p>I do agree we need more server helpers awarded for those who are very helpful individuals. Do you have any suggestion as to how we can go about that effectively?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/suggestion-compilation/519785/14">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/suggestion-compilation/519785/14</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 21 May 2013 21:00:40 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-519785-14</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/suggestion-compilation/519785.rss">Suggestion Compilation</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Suggestion Compilation</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Flame3 John]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/flame3">@Flame3</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote quote-modified" data-post="9" data-topic="519785">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/loveandpower/40/5_e05bb34c421432ee4d40de30c10af3e5.png" class="avatar"> Loveandpower:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>I agree with the thread naming. It’s ridiculous they expect us to help yet they can’t help their own self first.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>That was one of the points I was trying to make earlier.</p>
<aside class="quote quote-modified" data-post="9" data-topic="519785">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/loveandpower/40/5_e05bb34c421432ee4d40de30c10af3e5.png" class="avatar"> Loveandpower:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>I believe the “no spoonfeeding” rule should be applied and enforced more often. I can’t even start to list the amount of times I have had to help hold somebodies hand in a help topic.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Spoonfeeding is not encouraged, but to make a rule saying that you aren’t allowed to give an answer directly is sort of rendering the help section useless, because unfortunately most users will not be able to find their answer within the reply of 'Settings.java." It is up to the commenter to help the user, to spoon-feed would not be allowing the user to learn from their mistakes.</p>
<aside class="quote quote-modified" data-post="9" data-topic="519785">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/loveandpower/40/5_e05bb34c421432ee4d40de30c10af3e5.png" class="avatar"> Loveandpower:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Hell, when I ask for help I normally say on there I just need a reference and not actual help and that’s about what every help topic should be. We expect you to learn on your own and to do your own research.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>So do that, and rely on yourself to not spoon-feed a user. Helping requires patience, and you need to take your time and carefully explain to the user what their problem was, and give hints on how to solve the problem at hand.</p>
<aside class="quote quote-modified" data-post="9" data-topic="519785">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/loveandpower/40/5_e05bb34c421432ee4d40de30c10af3e5.png" class="avatar"> Loveandpower:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>I also posted about the server helper award and the others that aren’t used properly. People like Ryley used to actually help in the server help section before he got bored of the whole drama scene and moved on.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Which is why I’m saying that the award should be used again.[quote author=Bowser jr link=topic=638280.msg4301902#msg4301902 date=1369147036]</p>
<p>[quote author=Flame_ link=topic=638280.msg4301893#msg4301893 date=1369145155]</p>
<aside class="quote quote-modified" data-post="7" data-topic="519785">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 Bowser jr:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>If they can’t write a proper title I’m sure the content isn’t good either. If they post a new topic about the same thing, they should be awarded with an infraction.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>One of the points I am trying to make is that exactly.</p>
<p>[quote=“Si Force, post:11, topic:519785”]A forum mod wouldn’t be the best solution to this problem either, considering no modification can gauge how descriptive the title/post is. Even if it was just a reminder, they can chose to ignore it also. It honestly seems like more work than it’s worth to implement a forum mod.[/quote] At least then, the user can and will be the only one held responsible for having a useless thread title. This way, we can confirm that they at least read that the title should be descriptive.</p>
<aside class="quote quote-modified" data-post="11" data-topic="519785">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 Si Force:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>If users want to receive quality help then it’s up to them to create a quality post. We can create ideals to guide them, however it should be up to them to give us enough information about the topic.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Correct.</p>
<aside class="quote quote-modified" data-post="11" data-topic="519785">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 Si Force:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>I remember there was discussion taking place about thread tags like I mentioned earlier, but I’m not too sure what was concluded on the subject. I’ll try and find that discussion now…</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>That would be good.[quote=“Loveandpower, post:12, topic:519785”]I am all for a mod of some kind that shows tags but the issue there is they wouldn’t be used. A sticky that tells people to make proper titles wouldn’t do any good either cause well as he already said mods wouldn’t enforce the rule and quite frankly most of the help section are first time posters and I doubt they give a two hoots about the rules…[/quote]<br>
Again, the forum mod prompt.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/suggestion-compilation/519785/13">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/suggestion-compilation/519785/13</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 21 May 2013 19:05:07 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-519785-13</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/suggestion-compilation/519785.rss">Suggestion Compilation</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Suggestion Compilation</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Loveandpower Loveandpower]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/loveandpower">@Loveandpower</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“Si Force, post:11, topic:519785”]A forum mod wouldn’t be the best solution to this problem either, considering no modification can gauge how descriptive the title/post is. Even if it was just a reminder, they can chose to ignore it also. It honestly seems like more work than it’s worth to implement a forum mod.</p>
<p>If users want to receive quality help then it’s up to them to create a quality post. We can create ideals to guide them, however it should be up to them to give us enough information about the topic.</p>
<p>I remember there was discussion taking place about thread tags like I mentioned earlier, but I’m not too sure what was concluded on the subject. I’ll try and find that discussion now…[/quote]IT was 50/50 discussion if I remember correct :s</p>
<p>I am all for a mod of some kind that shows tags but the issue there is they wouldn’t be used. A sticky that tells people to make proper titles wouldn’t do any good either cause well as he already said mods wouldn’t enforce the rule and quite frankly most of the help section are first time posters and I doubt they give a two hoots about the rules…</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/suggestion-compilation/519785/12">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/suggestion-compilation/519785/12</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 21 May 2013 14:51:25 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-519785-12</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/suggestion-compilation/519785.rss">Suggestion Compilation</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Suggestion Compilation</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@si_force Si Force]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/si_force">@si_force</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>A forum mod wouldn’t be the best solution to this problem either, considering no modification can gauge how descriptive the title/post is. Even if it was just a reminder, they can chose to ignore it also. It honestly seems like more work than it’s worth to implement a forum mod.</p>
<p>If users want to receive quality help then it’s up to them to create a quality post. We can create ideals to guide them, however it should be up to them to give us enough information about the topic.</p>
<p>I remember there was discussion taking place about thread tags like I mentioned earlier, but I’m not too sure what was concluded on the subject. I’ll try and find that discussion now…</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/suggestion-compilation/519785/11">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/suggestion-compilation/519785/11</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 21 May 2013 14:39:56 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-519785-11</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/suggestion-compilation/519785.rss">Suggestion Compilation</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Suggestion Compilation</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@bowserjr2 Bowser jr]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/bowserjr2">@bowserjr2</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“Flame_, post:8, topic:519785”][quote author=Bowser jr link=topic=638280.msg4301892#msg4301892 date=1369144937]<br>
In my experience you get better responses the better you explain your problem. People are just punishing themselves by making badly written thread names. Let them learn when noboby wants to help them.<br>
[/quote]<br>
This is how I will see it play out:</p>
<p>[ul][li]New user posts a thread, non descriptive thread title[/li]<br>
[li]Nobody helps the new user, so he posts another thread[/li]<br>
[li]Thread is locked[/li]<br>
[li]Issue is not solved[/li][/ul]</p>
<p>My suggestion was not meant to just completely disregard users who do this. Something needs to be done in order to let users understand that their thread titles need to be more descriptive. As I said earlier, perhaps a forum mod where the user is prompted ‘Are you sure this thread title is descriptive enough?’ before confirming the post.[/quote]<br>
If they can’t write a proper title I’m sure the content isn’t good either. If they post a new topic about the same thing, they should be awarded with an infraction.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/suggestion-compilation/519785/10">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/suggestion-compilation/519785/10</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 21 May 2013 14:37:16 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-519785-10</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/suggestion-compilation/519785.rss">Suggestion Compilation</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Suggestion Compilation</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Loveandpower Loveandpower]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/loveandpower">@Loveandpower</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I agree with the thread naming. It’s ridiculous they expect us to help yet they can’t help their own self first. I believe the “no spoonfeeding” rule should be applied and enforced more often. I can’t even start to list the amount of times I have had to help hold somebodies hand in a help topic. Hell, when I ask for help I normally say on there I just need a reference and not actual help and that’s about what every help topic should be. We expect you to learn on your own and to do your own research.</p>
<p>Duplicate help threads…yeah it’s a horror story really. I’m not going to explain more than once how to do something are you?</p>
<p>I also posted about the server helper award and the others that aren’t used properly. People like Ryley used to actually help in the server help section before he got bored of the whole drama scene and moved on.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/suggestion-compilation/519785/9">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/suggestion-compilation/519785/9</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 21 May 2013 14:26:22 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-519785-9</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/suggestion-compilation/519785.rss">Suggestion Compilation</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Suggestion Compilation</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Flame3 John]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/flame3">@Flame3</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote" data-post="7" data-topic="519785">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 Bowser jr:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>In my experience you get better responses the better you explain your problem. People are just punishing themselves by making badly written thread names. Let them learn when noboby wants to help them.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>This is how I will see it play out:</p>
<p>[ul][li]New user posts a thread, non descriptive thread title[/li]<br>
[li]Nobody helps the new user, so he posts another thread[/li]<br>
[li]Thread is locked[/li]<br>
[li]Issue is not solved[/li][/ul]</p>
<p>My suggestion was not meant to just completely disregard users who do this. Something needs to be done in order to let users understand that their thread titles need to be more descriptive. As I said earlier, perhaps a forum mod where the user is prompted ‘Are you sure this thread title is descriptive enough?’ before confirming the post.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/suggestion-compilation/519785/8">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/suggestion-compilation/519785/8</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 21 May 2013 14:05:55 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-519785-8</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/suggestion-compilation/519785.rss">Suggestion Compilation</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Suggestion Compilation</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@bowserjr2 Bowser jr]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/bowserjr2">@bowserjr2</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>In my experience you get better responses the better you explain your problem. People are just punishing themselves by making badly written thread names. Let them learn when noboby wants to help them.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/suggestion-compilation/519785/7">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/suggestion-compilation/519785/7</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 21 May 2013 14:02:17 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-519785-7</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/suggestion-compilation/519785.rss">Suggestion Compilation</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Suggestion Compilation</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Flame3 John]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/flame3">@Flame3</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote quote-modified" data-post="5" data-topic="519785">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 Si Force:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>There may be a rule on that, and I do enforce it, but I have no intention on enforcing a rule on a thread title that’s like “help quickly, client not working”. I do occasionally edit topic titles though due to misleading tiles or else if the title is a bit ridiculous. I won’t, however, warn a person for this ever. It does not state that in the rules and I would be against it being there at all.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>You are the moderator and I will not make you change your opinion. In my last post I stated how even though a thread lock/infraction may not be the right direction, something does need to be enforced/implemented in order to help stop misuse of thread titles. Perhaps a forum mod where the user is prompted ‘Are you sure this thread title is descriptive enough?’ before confirming the post?</p>
<aside class="quote quote-modified" data-post="5" data-topic="519785">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 Si Force:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>As for payments, if a user posts a thread more than once offering payment, and they were a previous infringer, then I would have no problem placing a minor infraction on their account. I wouldn’t be inclined to go further than that though.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Pardon me for being very pushy, but I haven’t been seeing this happen.</p>
<p>EDIT: From the IRC:</p>
<blockquote>[09:41:44] 	 how on almost every decent q &amp; a site
[09:41:48] 	 (e.g. stackoverflow)
[09:41:53] 	 questions need to have relevant titles</blockquote>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/suggestion-compilation/519785/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/suggestion-compilation/519785/6</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 21 May 2013 13:30:27 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-519785-6</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/suggestion-compilation/519785.rss">Suggestion Compilation</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Suggestion Compilation</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@si_force Si Force]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/si_force">@si_force</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I had to edit my original post a bit too, I worded it more aggressively that I would have liked to. <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=5" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"></p>
<p>There may be a rule on that, and I do enforce it, but I have no intention on enforcing a rule on a thread title that’s like “help quickly, client not working”. I do occasionally edit topic titles though due to misleading tiles or else if the title is a bit ridiculous. I won’t, however, warn a person for this ever. It does not state that in the rules and I would be against it being there at all.</p>
<p>As for payments, if a user posts a thread more than once offering payment, and they were a previous infringer, then I would have no problem placing a minor infraction on their account. I wouldn’t be inclined to go further than that though.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/suggestion-compilation/519785/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/suggestion-compilation/519785/5</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 21 May 2013 13:26:04 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-519785-5</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/suggestion-compilation/519785.rss">Suggestion Compilation</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Suggestion Compilation</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@HcoJustin HcoJustin]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/hcojustin">@HcoJustin</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I like the threads that are titled HELP WHY WONT IT WORK!!! Perfect way to waste the time browsing</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/suggestion-compilation/519785/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/suggestion-compilation/519785/4</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 21 May 2013 13:18:29 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-519785-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/suggestion-compilation/519785.rss">Suggestion Compilation</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Suggestion Compilation</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Flame3 John]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/flame3">@Flame3</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I worded that a bit aggressively, excuse me.</p>
<ol>
<li>Rule 5 of the sectional rules: <blockquote>5. Make sure the titles of your topics are easy to read and are completely relevant to the topic at hand. Though this rule may be bent from time to time, make sure you follow it. A moderator on a bad day could easily lock a topic for breaking this rule.</blockquote> This is a guideline that moderators can follow, yet the average moderator does not from what I’ve seen. And newer members become confused when nobody helps them. I enjoy helping, yet when a topic is not labeled correctly, and nobody helps them, that leads to duplicate posting. As aggressive as the rule seems, this will provoke more help within the help sections, as well as more issues being resolved. Perhaps a warn is not necessary, or a thread lock. But something needs to be enforced in order to have users understand that a thread title is one of the most important parts of a topic.<br>
Another:<blockquote>A large majority of topics in this section are not explained very well, easily seen by the first few posters asking to elaborate.  From now on, if you fail to be as specific as possible, your topic may be locked.  It is a complete waste of time for those who are trying to help if they have to post asking for you to elaborate. </blockquote>
<br>
Backing up my previous point, and again, this is not enforced heavily at all.</li>
</ol>
<blockquote>Edit: One thing I may agree with you on with regards to help topics is the use of tags in the title. For example, using a [317] tag or whatever is related to the topic, that would be useful.</blockquote>
Of course. That would be very helpful.
<ol start="2">
<li>Newer users might not read the rules, correct. So your point of simply removing the sentence and giving them the heads up is fine, but what about the users who have been told in the past? I could name 3 users right now that have never received an infraction even after being warned multiple times.</li>
</ol>
<blockquote>We do not sell anything on this site, period.</blockquote>
So why are users constantly able to post a thread with a payment involved, yet only walk away with part of their thread edited? I now agree that a thread lock might not be the best choice, but an infraction is in order if a user continues to post a reward in a topic time and time again. After all, that is an infringement of the global and sectional rules, is it not?
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/suggestion-compilation/519785/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/suggestion-compilation/519785/3</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 21 May 2013 13:16:17 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-519785-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/suggestion-compilation/519785.rss">Suggestion Compilation</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Suggestion Compilation</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@si_force Si Force]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/si_force">@si_force</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“Flame_, post:1, topic:519785”]- <span class="bbcode-b">Thread Naming</span><br>
All threads that do not have a name which pertains to the issue they are experiencing should be locked, or the user warned. I spend more than enough time looking through threads with decent names as is. To have to look through these topics as well, and then having to report them if they are not in the right section, is not a very fun task. For those that will say ‘Nobody says you have to,’ well, that is one of the main reasons I joined this forum - to help people in the help sections.</p>
<ul>
<li>
<span class="bbcode-b">Payment Within Threads</span><br>
All users that offer payment within their threads should be warned and their threads locked. Someone who does not have the patience to read the section rules and abide by them does not deserve help, especially when the majority of users offering payment within these sections have been warned before, and walked away unscathed.[/quote]</li>
</ul>
<p>If you’re suggesting that we warn people for not having a name that lives up to your expectations, you’re delusional. We’re not about to start warning people for their word choice in topics, nor should they be locked. That’s honestly one of the more ridiculous suggestions I’ve read on this website. If you’re getting tired of sifting through poorly worded threads/thread titles, then I’d recommend that you ignore them. It’s a much simpler solution.</p>
<p>With regards to payments, most users are not aware that they cannot offer payment on their thread and they learn when we lock them. Most, if not all threads offering payment are subsequently edited. Locking the threads would be counter-productive as they would have to create a new thread to receive help, where as if we leave the current thread open they can continue to receive assistance through that.</p>
<p>Edit: One thing I may agree with you on with regards to help topics is the use of tags in the title. For example, using a [317] tag or whatever is related to the topic, that would be useful.</p>
<p>Just my two cents.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/suggestion-compilation/519785/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/suggestion-compilation/519785/2</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 21 May 2013 13:02:47 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-519785-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/suggestion-compilation/519785.rss">Suggestion Compilation</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Suggestion Compilation</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Flame3 John]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/flame3">@Flame3</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>This is a bunch of suggestions I have pertaining to rule enforcement as well as community involvement.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-u">Server &amp; Client Help Sections</span></p>
<ul>
<li>
<span class="bbcode-b">Thread Naming</span><br>
The need for descriptive thread titles is an apparently overlooked guideline in the help sections. To have to look through these topics as well, and then having to report them if they are not in the right section, is not a very fun task. For those that will say ‘Nobody says you have to,’ well, that is one of the main reasons I joined this forum - to help people in the help sections.<br>
My suggestion is to create a forum mod that will prompt the user after clicking the post button, asking that they make sure the title is descriptive enough. This will at least let the user know that more descriptive thread naming will have their problem solved faster.</li>
<li>
<span class="bbcode-b">Payment Within Threads</span><br>
All users that offer payment within their threads should be given a verbal warning by a moderator, and the contents of their thread edited. Every offense afterwords should result in a +5 warning level to their account. This is not too strong of an infraction, yet heavy enough that they will at least learn not to do it again, if not from the first time.</li>
<li>
<span class="bbcode-b">Duplicate Posting</span><br>
Obviously this rule is not enforced heavily. The most I’ve ever seen a user penalized for duplicate posting is a thread lock. The large majority of users that post duplicates are those that have been verbally warned for it in the past. They obviously do not learn their lesson. I request that all users that post duplicate threads should be warned on first abuse, and have a +5 on second abuse, along with one of their threads locked.</li>
</ul>
<p><span class="bbcode-u">Badges and Awards</span></p>
<ul>
<li>
<span class="bbcode-b">The Server Helper Award</span><br>
The Server Helper award is not used in the slightest. I know of three members at most who have the award on these forums, and I rarely ever see more than one of them make any posts in these sections anymore. Of course helping should come from the kindness of another user, yet, when there is something to be earned from being a very helpful user, at least use it. At the very least, a set of specific guidelines should be published.</li>
</ul>
<p>That’s about it for this thread, please leave some feedback below.<br>
A thread that I’ve based some of my ideas on, as well as more points commenters might like to bring up: <a href="http://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php/topic,637962.0.html" rel="nofollow noopener">http://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php/topic,637962.0.html</a></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/suggestion-compilation/519785/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/suggestion-compilation/519785/1</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 21 May 2013 12:56:16 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-519785-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/suggestion-compilation/519785.rss">Suggestion Compilation</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
