<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>[How To Debate] Section Rules &amp; Guidelines</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-debate-section-rules-guidelines/451527</link>
    <description>[u][b]Purpose of the thread[/b][/u]
The purpose of this thread is to preserve the quality of discussion and debate in this section.  Throughout this thread, there will be material on various topics that shall enable you to post constructive, concise, and meaningful replies.  This section contains material which can be seen as offensive to some, and it&#39;s for this reason we employ laws and regulations on what can be posted here.  You&#39;ll learn about the various rules and associated punishments that are in place in this forum.  Moparscape Staff take the content being posted here very seriously, so it&#39;s imperative that you don&#39;t blunder, as the consequences may be unforeseen.

[u][b]How to debate[/b][/u]
Believe it or not, knowing how to debate is a sure-fire way of boosting your reputation within this forum. Too many times, you&#39;ll see people posting threads with no actual intent to provide for debate. The purpose of this section is to discuss, debate, educate, influence, persuade, or inform. As the original poster, you can ensure your thread stays alive and flourishes simply by the hypothesis you put forth. Let&#39;s take a look at a couple of examples.

[u][b]Thread With No Potential Or Purpose[/b][/u]
[code]abortion is fucking sick. all you peopol who would purposly kill your own baby are mental.[/code]

[u][b]Thread With Meaningful Content &amp; Quality Hypothesis[/b][/u]
[code]Hi,

I&#39;d like to discuss the hot topic of abortion with everyone today. Personally, I don&#39;t think abortion is right and I believe it should be made illegal. I don&#39;t see how you can intentionally kill an alive human embryo for your own selfish needs.

What are your thoughts on abortion? Have you ever had any real-life experience with abortion? And why do you feel the way you do?

Thanks[/code]

You can immediately see the difference here. The second thread would be acceptable and would, most likely, stay alive for quite some time. The first thread would probably be locked by the site&#39;s staff, as it can be deemed offensive.

Offensive posting in this section is a really big issue. People will often post in the Intellectual Discussions &amp; Debates forum because they&#39;re passionate about something. Or, other times, they&#39;ll post simply out of anger or frustration. The first example was, as I&#39;d like to say, an angry thread. The user did not think about what they were saying and just said what they were thinking at the time. Warnings, bans, and negative reputation are the most common results from creating such ranting threads.

When creating a topic for debate, you should remember a few things. Don&#39;t make your side of the argument too overpowering. If possible, start with a fairly neutral statement on the topic, and then pose your hypothesis or opinion. Use evidence, examples, and thought out material in your thread. You might like to use the following structure.

[code]Abortion is one of the most commonly discussed topics in today&#39;s society. It&#39;s so commonly discussed because the results of abortion can effect so many lives; people will spend hours tearing their hair out deciding what the best option for themselves is. [b]&lt;&lt;&lt;The above is the introduction to our argument. It gives some background information on the topic and remains completely neutral.&gt;&gt;&gt;[/b]

Personally, I feel as though abortion is a good option for those who have mistakenly fallen pregnant and feel as though they couldn&#39;t or shouldn&#39;t give birth to or care for a baby. [b]&lt;&lt;&lt;This section goes over your personal opinion and doesn&#39;t ever escalate to the point of offensiveness.&gt;&gt;&gt;[/b]

I feel this way because I&#39;ve been through the abortion process a number of times. I&#39;ve had tough times contemplating what option is right, but each time I&#39;ve come out at the end thinking I did the right thing. The International Federation of Birth and Parenthood has proven that 90% of people will carry out an abortion if they have to (2010). [b]&lt;&lt;&lt;This section goes over evidence and examples. Use correct methods of referencing and quoting.&gt;&gt;&gt;[/b]

What are your thoughts on abortion? Do you think you&#39;d kill your own baby, or would you put up with the labour and give up your personal aspirations to parent the child? [b]&lt;&lt;&lt;In a relatively neutral statement or two, pose your question to the audience.&gt;&gt;&gt;[/b][/code]
You aren&#39;t required to post using this structure: this is simply a guideline you might like to adopt.

If you want to become a reputable member in this section, there&#39;s a few things you should strive to maintain.

[u][b]Grammatical Accuracy[/b][/u]
This is really easy to do. Proofread everything you post. If you&#39;re unsure of something, use Google. There&#39;s hundreds of excellent resources available on the Internet that will help you correct your spelling and grammar. Being able to post with grammatical accuracy not only saves you from lingering in the low quality area, but it also makes people take you more seriously. No one&#39;s going to actually care about what you&#39;re saying if you can&#39;t even spell it correctly.

[u][b]Remain Neutral[/b][/u]
You&#39;re allowed to post your opinion. You&#39;re allowed to argue your point. You&#39;re allowed to say your point of view is better than theirs [b]but only if you are able to back up your argument[/b]. Don&#39;t expect everyone to believe you when you say, &quot;Abortion is the only way&quot; unless you legitimately know for a fact (and provide examples and evidence) that you&#39;re correct.

[u][b]Remain Calm[/b][/u]
People are always going to troll you. People are always going to get angry at you for having an opinion. Let the staff take care of these individuals. Simply report their post and it&#39;ll be dealt with. Do not reply to these people, as you&#39;ll derail your own thread and end up in the wrong with them.

[u][b]Keep It On Track![/b][/u]
You&#39;re the boss. It&#39;s your thread, so you need to maintain it. If someone has said something, and there&#39;s a few replies relating to what they&#39;d said instead of the original topic, the chances are, the thread&#39;s going to be derailed sooner or later. Simply post telling everyone to stay on topic.

[u][b]My unofficial rules[/b][/u]
[b]Respect other peoples&#39; opinions[/b]. If you don&#39;t agree with them, that&#39;s your own prerogative, however, you must respect others&#39; thoughts and feelings.

[b]Don&#39;t mindlessly rant[/b]. I&#39;ve seen a lot of people going on about how they hate a particular religion or race. No one cares unless you&#39;re making a valid point, which you&#39;re not.

[b]If you&#39;re going to use someone else&#39;s article, for god&#39;s sake, reference it[/b]. Leeching is not permitted on Mopar. Also, if you&#39;re going to do this, don&#39;t just quote the whole thing and hit Post. Actually make a point or valid argument that will spark discussion.

[b]Low quality posting &amp; flaming is not allowed[/b]. This doesn&#39;t just apply to this section, but perhaps it&#39;s taken a little more seriously here. Pointless, mindless, or just plain stupid threads will be closed or moved.

Now I think you&#39;re ready.

http://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php?action=post;board=229.0</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 28 Jul 2012 14:15:12 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>General Discussion</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-debate-section-rules-guidelines/451527.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>[How To Debate] Section Rules &amp; Guidelines</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@mod_taharok Taharok]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/mod_taharok">@mod_taharok</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“NumberEleven, post:15, topic:451527”]I am the same member on HF.</p>
<p>If you want I can PM you with some proof, or message you on it?[/quote]</p>
<p>That’s fine for me. I’ll sticky this unless someone can verify he’s not who he says he is. Otherwise, I think it’s a splendid post. <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=5" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-debate-section-rules-guidelines/451527/16">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-debate-section-rules-guidelines/451527/16</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 28 Jul 2012 14:15:12 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-451527-16</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-debate-section-rules-guidelines/451527.rss">[How To Debate] Section Rules &amp; Guidelines</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[How To Debate] Section Rules &amp; Guidelines</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@NumberEleven NumberEleven]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/numbereleven">@NumberEleven</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I am the same member on HF.</p>
<p>If you want I can PM you with some proof, or message you on it?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-debate-section-rules-guidelines/451527/15">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-debate-section-rules-guidelines/451527/15</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 28 Jul 2012 05:18:42 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-451527-15</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-debate-section-rules-guidelines/451527.rss">[How To Debate] Section Rules &amp; Guidelines</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[How To Debate] Section Rules &amp; Guidelines</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@the_elve_age the elve age]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/the_elve_age">@the_elve_age</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p><span class="mention">@OP</span> for someone who tries to stay neutral, your topics are swayed towards one side. (Random quotes supporting arguments, personal opinions, ect).</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-debate-section-rules-guidelines/451527/14">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-debate-section-rules-guidelines/451527/14</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 28 Jul 2012 02:26:02 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-451527-14</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-debate-section-rules-guidelines/451527.rss">[How To Debate] Section Rules &amp; Guidelines</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[How To Debate] Section Rules &amp; Guidelines</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@davidi2 Davidi2]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/davidi2">@davidi2</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“the elve age, post:12, topic:451527”][quote]If you’re going to use someone else’s article, for god’s sake, reference it.[/quote] Ironic, but it’s just a post that will end up dying most likely.[/quote]Ahaha, good find. Though we don’t really want references to H-F here <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/wink.png?v=5" title=":wink:" class="emoji" alt=":wink:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-debate-section-rules-guidelines/451527/13">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-debate-section-rules-guidelines/451527/13</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 28 Jul 2012 02:20:45 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-451527-13</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-debate-section-rules-guidelines/451527.rss">[How To Debate] Section Rules &amp; Guidelines</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[How To Debate] Section Rules &amp; Guidelines</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@the_elve_age the elve age]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/the_elve_age">@the_elve_age</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <blockquote>If you're going to use someone else's article, for god's sake, reference it.</blockquote> Ironic, but it's just a post that will end up dying most likely.
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-debate-section-rules-guidelines/451527/12">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-debate-section-rules-guidelines/451527/12</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 28 Jul 2012 02:19:01 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-451527-12</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-debate-section-rules-guidelines/451527.rss">[How To Debate] Section Rules &amp; Guidelines</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[How To Debate] Section Rules &amp; Guidelines</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@davidi2 Davidi2]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/davidi2">@davidi2</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“Whackatre, post:10, topic:451527”][quote author=Loveandpower link=topic=554411.msg4061180#msg4061180 date=1343438602]<br>
Unless the author got actual permission from the site to copy and paste then it’s just as bad as copyright infringement. (while not legally speaking )</p>
<p>It’s sort of like when you go make rules for a rsps. It can be quite irritating when you take the time to make a nice set of rules, make them look professional, etc, etc. Only to find out a week later that two servers ran by total idiots are using the same rules without your permission. You of all people David, should realize the amount of work that goes into a topic like this.<br>
[/quote]</p>
<p>Because forum posts cannot be copyrighted, plagiarism should not be accounted for.[/quote]We still don’t support plagiarism, it’s just that under these circumstances there is nothing wrong with this post.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-debate-section-rules-guidelines/451527/11">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-debate-section-rules-guidelines/451527/11</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 28 Jul 2012 01:48:06 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-451527-11</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-debate-section-rules-guidelines/451527.rss">[How To Debate] Section Rules &amp; Guidelines</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[How To Debate] Section Rules &amp; Guidelines</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@whackatre Whackatre]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/whackatre">@whackatre</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“Loveandpower, post:8, topic:451527”]Unless the author got actual permission from the site to copy and paste then it’s just as bad as copyright infringement. (while not legally speaking )</p>
<p>It’s sort of like when you go make rules for a rsps. It can be quite irritating when you take the time to make a nice set of rules, make them look professional, etc, etc. Only to find out a week later that two servers ran by total idiots are using the same rules without your permission. You of all people David, should realize the amount of work that goes into a topic like this.[/quote]</p>
<p>Because forum posts cannot be copyrighted, plagiarism should not be accounted for.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-debate-section-rules-guidelines/451527/10">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-debate-section-rules-guidelines/451527/10</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 28 Jul 2012 01:45:28 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-451527-10</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-debate-section-rules-guidelines/451527.rss">[How To Debate] Section Rules &amp; Guidelines</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[How To Debate] Section Rules &amp; Guidelines</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@davidi2 Davidi2]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/davidi2">@davidi2</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Er, who even says the person there wrote it first anyways? Who says this isn’t the same person? And this isn’t anything like the rules for a RSPS, those are about a specific server, this is general advice for anyone. Because it’s from HF, I can’t lock this topic and link to it, but otherwise that’s probably what I would have done. Similar to when people posted the links to grammar tutorials and such, but really, there is nothing wrong with this post. He’s not even taking ‘credit’ for it, per say. While yes, it’s a bit arrogantly worded, its good tips for the section. Why should he have to rewrite it? “If it aint broke, don’t fix it” Only things I would change are some wordings making it sound like he has authority, but whatever.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-debate-section-rules-guidelines/451527/9">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-debate-section-rules-guidelines/451527/9</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 28 Jul 2012 01:27:32 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-451527-9</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-debate-section-rules-guidelines/451527.rss">[How To Debate] Section Rules &amp; Guidelines</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[How To Debate] Section Rules &amp; Guidelines</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Loveandpower Loveandpower]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/loveandpower">@Loveandpower</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Unless the author got actual permission from the site to copy and paste then it’s just as bad as copyright infringement. (while not legally speaking )</p>
<p>It’s sort of like when you go make rules for a rsps. It can be quite irritating when you take the time to make a nice set of rules, make them look professional, etc, etc. Only to find out a week later that two servers ran by total idiots are using the same rules without your permission. You of all people David, should realize the amount of work that goes into a topic like this.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-debate-section-rules-guidelines/451527/8">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-debate-section-rules-guidelines/451527/8</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 28 Jul 2012 01:23:22 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-451527-8</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-debate-section-rules-guidelines/451527.rss">[How To Debate] Section Rules &amp; Guidelines</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[How To Debate] Section Rules &amp; Guidelines</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@davidi2 Davidi2]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/davidi2">@davidi2</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“Loveandpower, post:6, topic:451527”][quote author=Davidi2 link=topic=554411.msg4061169#msg4061169 date=1343437300]</p>
<p>[quote author=Loveandpower link=topic=554411.msg4060697#msg4060697 date=1343397714]<br>
reported, this is nearly word for word from <a href="http://badsite.net">badsite.net</a><br>
[/quote]Ok…? Who cares? <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=5" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"> It’s still good stuff to look at. Not saying it’s getting a sticky, but still.<br>
[/quote]It’s  unprofessional and sets a bad  example/reputation for a  programming  board/community  board.[/quote]How… at all? Why does it matter where it came from as long as the content is fine?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-debate-section-rules-guidelines/451527/7">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-debate-section-rules-guidelines/451527/7</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 28 Jul 2012 01:18:31 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-451527-7</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-debate-section-rules-guidelines/451527.rss">[How To Debate] Section Rules &amp; Guidelines</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[How To Debate] Section Rules &amp; Guidelines</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Loveandpower Loveandpower]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/loveandpower">@Loveandpower</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“Davidi2, post:5, topic:451527”][quote author=Loveandpower link=topic=554411.msg4060697#msg4060697 date=1343397714]<br>
reported, this is nearly word for word from <a href="http://badsite.net" rel="nofollow noopener">badsite.net</a><br>
[/quote]Ok…? Who cares? <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=5" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"> It’s still good stuff to look at. Not saying it’s getting a sticky, but still.[/quote]It’s  unprofessional and sets a bad  example/reputation for a  programming  board/community  board.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-debate-section-rules-guidelines/451527/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-debate-section-rules-guidelines/451527/6</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 28 Jul 2012 01:17:33 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-451527-6</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-debate-section-rules-guidelines/451527.rss">[How To Debate] Section Rules &amp; Guidelines</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[How To Debate] Section Rules &amp; Guidelines</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@davidi2 Davidi2]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/davidi2">@davidi2</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“Loveandpower, post:4, topic:451527”]reported, this is nearly word for word from <a href="http://badsite.net">badsite.net</a>[/quote]Ok…? Who cares? <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=5" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"> It’s still good stuff to look at. Not saying it’s getting a sticky, but still.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-debate-section-rules-guidelines/451527/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-debate-section-rules-guidelines/451527/5</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 28 Jul 2012 01:01:40 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-451527-5</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-debate-section-rules-guidelines/451527.rss">[How To Debate] Section Rules &amp; Guidelines</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[How To Debate] Section Rules &amp; Guidelines</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Loveandpower Loveandpower]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/loveandpower">@Loveandpower</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>reported, this is nearly word for word from <a href="http://hackforums.net" rel="nofollow noopener">hackforums.net</a></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-debate-section-rules-guidelines/451527/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-debate-section-rules-guidelines/451527/4</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jul 2012 14:01:54 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-451527-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-debate-section-rules-guidelines/451527.rss">[How To Debate] Section Rules &amp; Guidelines</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[How To Debate] Section Rules &amp; Guidelines</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@NumberEleven NumberEleven]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/numbereleven">@NumberEleven</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote quote-modified" data-post="2" data-topic="451527">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 Soulcist:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Well, I’m not going to lie, these rules should be stickied because I like em’. Though, I’m not sure if the staff team will approve of this, not sure.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Appreciate your comments.</p>
<p>The rules could possibly be written differently.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-debate-section-rules-guidelines/451527/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-debate-section-rules-guidelines/451527/3</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jul 2012 11:26:20 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-451527-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-debate-section-rules-guidelines/451527.rss">[How To Debate] Section Rules &amp; Guidelines</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[How To Debate] Section Rules &amp; Guidelines</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Ix_Soulcist_xI Soulcist]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/ix_soulcist_xi">@Ix_Soulcist_xI</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Well, I’m not going to lie, these rules should be stickied because I like em’. Though, I’m not sure if the staff team will approve of this, not sure.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-debate-section-rules-guidelines/451527/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-debate-section-rules-guidelines/451527/2</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jul 2012 10:30:13 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-451527-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-debate-section-rules-guidelines/451527.rss">[How To Debate] Section Rules &amp; Guidelines</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[How To Debate] Section Rules &amp; Guidelines</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@NumberEleven NumberEleven]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/numbereleven">@NumberEleven</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p><span class="bbcode-u"><span class="bbcode-b">Purpose of the thread</span></span><br>
The purpose of this thread is to preserve the quality of discussion and debate in this section.  Throughout this thread, there will be material on various topics that shall enable you to post constructive, concise, and meaningful replies.  This section contains material which can be seen as offensive to some, and it’s for this reason we employ laws and regulations on what can be posted here.  You’ll learn about the various rules and associated punishments that are in place in this forum.  Moparscape Staff take the content being posted here very seriously, so it’s imperative that you don’t blunder, as the consequences may be unforeseen.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-u"><span class="bbcode-b">How to debate</span></span><br>
Believe it or not, knowing how to debate is a sure-fire way of boosting your reputation within this forum. Too many times, you’ll see people posting threads with no actual intent to provide for debate. The purpose of this section is to discuss, debate, educate, influence, persuade, or inform. As the original poster, you can ensure your thread stays alive and flourishes simply by the hypothesis you put forth. Let’s take a look at a couple of examples.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-u"><span class="bbcode-b">Thread With No Potential Or Purpose</span></span></p>
<pre><code class="lang-auto">abortion is fucking sick. all you peopol who would purposly kill your own baby are mental.</code></pre>
<p><span class="bbcode-u"><span class="bbcode-b">Thread With Meaningful Content &amp; Quality Hypothesis</span></span></p>
<p>[code]Hi,</p>
<p>I’d like to discuss the hot topic of abortion with everyone today. Personally, I don’t think abortion is right and I believe it should be made illegal. I don’t see how you can intentionally kill an alive human embryo for your own selfish needs.</p>
<p>What are your thoughts on abortion? Have you ever had any real-life experience with abortion? And why do you feel the way you do?</p>
<p>Thanks[/code]</p>
<p>You can immediately see the difference here. The second thread would be acceptable and would, most likely, stay alive for quite some time. The first thread would probably be locked by the site’s staff, as it can be deemed offensive.</p>
<p>Offensive posting in this section is a really big issue. People will often post in the Intellectual Discussions &amp; Debates forum because they’re passionate about something. Or, other times, they’ll post simply out of anger or frustration. The first example was, as I’d like to say, an angry thread. The user did not think about what they were saying and just said what they were thinking at the time. Warnings, bans, and negative reputation are the most common results from creating such ranting threads.</p>
<p>When creating a topic for debate, you should remember a few things. Don’t make your side of the argument too overpowering. If possible, start with a fairly neutral statement on the topic, and then pose your hypothesis or opinion. Use evidence, examples, and thought out material in your thread. You might like to use the following structure.</p>
<p>[code]Abortion is one of the most commonly discussed topics in today’s society. It’s so commonly discussed because the results of abortion can effect so many lives; people will spend hours tearing their hair out deciding what the best option for themselves is. <span class="bbcode-b">&lt;&lt;&gt;&gt;</span></p>
<p>Personally, I feel as though abortion is a good option for those who have mistakenly fallen pregnant and feel as though they couldn’t or shouldn’t give birth to or care for a baby. <span class="bbcode-b">&lt;&lt;&lt;This section goes over your personal opinion and doesn’t ever escalate to the point of offensiveness.&gt;&gt;&gt;</span></p>
<p>I feel this way because I’ve been through the abortion process a number of times. I’ve had tough times contemplating what option is right, but each time I’ve come out at the end thinking I did the right thing. The International Federation of Birth and Parenthood has proven that 90% of people will carry out an abortion if they have to (2010). <span class="bbcode-b">&lt;&lt;&gt;&gt;</span></p>
<p>What are your thoughts on abortion? Do you think you’d kill your own baby, or would you put up with the labour and give up your personal aspirations to parent the child? <span class="bbcode-b">&lt;&lt;&lt;In a relatively neutral statement or two, pose your question to the audience.&gt;&gt;&gt;</span>[/code]<br>
You aren’t required to post using this structure: this is simply a guideline you might like to adopt.</p>
<p>If you want to become a reputable member in this section, there’s a few things you should strive to maintain.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-u"><span class="bbcode-b">Grammatical Accuracy</span></span><br>
This is really easy to do. Proofread everything you post. If you’re unsure of something, use Google. There’s hundreds of excellent resources available on the Internet that will help you correct your spelling and grammar. Being able to post with grammatical accuracy not only saves you from lingering in the low quality area, but it also makes people take you more seriously. No one’s going to actually care about what you’re saying if you can’t even spell it correctly.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-u"><span class="bbcode-b">Remain Neutral</span></span><br>
You’re allowed to post your opinion. You’re allowed to argue your point. You’re allowed to say your point of view is better than theirs <span class="bbcode-b">but only if you are able to back up your argument</span>. Don’t expect everyone to believe you when you say, “Abortion is the only way” unless you legitimately know for a fact (and provide examples and evidence) that you’re correct.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-u"><span class="bbcode-b">Remain Calm</span></span><br>
People are always going to troll you. People are always going to get angry at you for having an opinion. Let the staff take care of these individuals. Simply report their post and it’ll be dealt with. Do not reply to these people, as you’ll derail your own thread and end up in the wrong with them.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-u"><span class="bbcode-b">Keep It On Track!</span></span><br>
You’re the boss. It’s your thread, so you need to maintain it. If someone has said something, and there’s a few replies relating to what they’d said instead of the original topic, the chances are, the thread’s going to be derailed sooner or later. Simply post telling everyone to stay on topic.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-u"><span class="bbcode-b">My unofficial rules</span></span><br>
<span class="bbcode-b">Respect other peoples’ opinions</span>. If you don’t agree with them, that’s your own prerogative, however, you must respect others’ thoughts and feelings.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Don’t mindlessly rant</span>. I’ve seen a lot of people going on about how they hate a particular religion or race. No one cares unless you’re making a valid point, which you’re not.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">If you’re going to use someone else’s article, for god’s sake, reference it</span>. Leeching is not permitted on Mopar. Also, if you’re going to do this, don’t just quote the whole thing and hit Post. Actually make a point or valid argument that will spark discussion.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Low quality posting &amp; flaming is not allowed</span>. This doesn’t just apply to this section, but perhaps it’s taken a little more seriously here. Pointless, mindless, or just plain stupid threads will be closed or moved.</p>
<p>Now I think you’re ready.</p>
<aside class="onebox whitelistedgeneric">
  <header class="source">
      <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/uploads/default/original/2X/1/1f0dc167bcf798bdbd70b03bf0fd1bc836e54e1a.png" class="site-icon" width="32" height="32">
      <a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/?action=post;board=229.0" target="_blank">moparisthebest.com</a>
  </header>
  <article class="onebox-body">
    <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/uploads/default/original/2X/4/41fecb6185fddc2758aeba68c3f8c9c78e26e4ff.png" class="thumbnail onebox-avatar" width="500" height="500">

<h3><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/?action=post;board=229.0" target="_blank">moparisthebest.com</a></h3>

<p>programming, irc, cars</p>


  </article>
  <div class="onebox-metadata">
    
    
  </div>
  <div style="clear: both"></div>
</aside>

          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-debate-section-rules-guidelines/451527/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-debate-section-rules-guidelines/451527/1</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jul 2012 10:09:30 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-451527-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-debate-section-rules-guidelines/451527.rss">[How To Debate] Section Rules &amp; Guidelines</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
