<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Protecting Your Economy</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/protecting-your-economy/551111</link>
    <description>I am just brainstorming a few ideas and thought about this:

There almost always will be dupes in private servers, there are probably still some unknown ones in RuneScape. Dupes are probably single-handedly the most game breaking and difficult bugs that exist. Even the most compotent programmers here cannot anticipate every dupe in the servers as they design, it always takes a player base to find them, due to more angles of the game mechanics being &quot;explored&quot; at a greater rate than what one developer testing their server locally can achieve.

Call it an anti dupe system if you will, but what about creating

[ul][li]Implementing a flagging system in every method that can create an item, addItem, createGroundItem, containers (bank, trade, shops) etc.[/li][/ul]


[ul]if a certain criteria is met i.e. count &gt;= 5000000 &amp;&amp; item != 995 (create a seperate system to flag coins as they will accumulate in higher numbers legitimately probably more than any other item (no one should have 5 million yew logs) or something to that effect and temporarily disable that players ability to drop items, trade and sell to shops so no potentially duped items are leaked to the public and then that account can be manually reviewed by administration... this is where a detailed logging system comes into play... maybe an abstract logging system that grabs and logs every action the player does in a single file.[/ul]


So for example, commonly valuable items such as coins, rares, end game armours and weapons, logs, ores, gems, bones, feathers should be more &quot;sensitive&quot; to the flagging system as opposed to say cabbages, raw shrimps and ashes. Group certain items to flag at different counts because 5000 coins is common and should never flag, but 5000 blue partyhats/abyssal whips should never be a thing in your server [i]if[/i] they are a rare item.

This way you stop potential items from flooding and destroying your &quot;economies&quot;, resulting in hopefully no eco resets and therefore not pissing your players off and losing your precious player count. People don&#39;t even need to know there was a dupe with something like this because hopefully your logging system will tell you how the dupe was done. Oh, and also, temporarily mute the player so they cannot tell strangers in game.

If done right, flagging accounts and temp. disabling there trading etc. (inconveniencing them) should only happen rarely, and everytime some rich player manages to accumulate 5 million yew logs because they actually bought them from players over the course of a year, they can be given exceptions in the system as you now know your game allows players to legitimately earn those items. Scale the flagging for counts of items to your economy. At the beginning of an economy no one should be getting 500m coins, so if it&#39;s the first day of the server and silab logs on a runeagents the shit out of your server, at least you will have the ability to restrict the distribution of those items which gives you plenty of time to re-create and fix the problem.

In my opinion everyone should implement a system like this. Think of a dupe as the fire, you don&#39;t assume your babies will not touch the fire, you assume they are curious and will touch and burn themselves. Put up a safety guard that will stop them from hurting themselves...</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 17 Apr 2015 17:10:07 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/protecting-your-economy/551111.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Protecting Your Economy</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Callisto Callisto]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/callisto">@Callisto</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“lare69, post:6, topic:551111”][quote author=Bowser jr link=topic=670026.msg4480344#msg4480344 date=1429189582]<br>
This is worthless without tracking the players actions to find the duplication bug.<br>
[/quote]<br>
^[/quote]</p>
<p>does anyone read, i suggested this in the first post</p>
<blockquote>then that account can be manually reviewed by administration... this is where a detailed logging system comes into play... maybe an abstract logging system that grabs and logs every action the player does in a single file.</blockquote>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/protecting-your-economy/551111/7">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/protecting-your-economy/551111/7</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 17 Apr 2015 17:10:07 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-551111-7</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/protecting-your-economy/551111.rss">Protecting Your Economy</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Protecting Your Economy</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Clawz_fury lare69]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/clawz_fury">@Clawz_fury</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote" data-post="2" data-topic="551111">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 Bowser jr:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>This is worthless without tracking the players actions to find the duplication bug.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>^</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/protecting-your-economy/551111/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/protecting-your-economy/551111/6</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 17 Apr 2015 16:42:19 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-551111-6</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/protecting-your-economy/551111.rss">Protecting Your Economy</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Protecting Your Economy</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Callisto Callisto]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/callisto">@Callisto</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>that’s the problem. it seems annoying to some people to protect their game. that’s why server’s don’t last long. also you don’t have to input every item id.</p>
<p>in the add method</p>
<pre><code class="lang-auto">if (getCount() &gt;= 5000000)
//flag system here</code></pre>
<p>then instead of being lazy, scale, amend, adapt and add to to it until you have some sort of working model that fits most scenarios relative to your server</p>
<p>it will only work if you create a base system and add to it as you gather data</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/protecting-your-economy/551111/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/protecting-your-economy/551111/5</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 16 Apr 2015 21:18:11 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-551111-5</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/protecting-your-economy/551111.rss">Protecting Your Economy</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Protecting Your Economy</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@CSharp95 CSharp95]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/csharp95">@CSharp95</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>An interesting concept.<br>
I feel like it would be rather annoying to make seeing how you’d have to manually put in each item id, although you could have it just go off of the item’s base gold value.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/protecting-your-economy/551111/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/protecting-your-economy/551111/4</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 16 Apr 2015 19:42:38 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-551111-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/protecting-your-economy/551111.rss">Protecting Your Economy</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Protecting Your Economy</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Callisto Callisto]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/callisto">@Callisto</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>yes that is why i suggested</p>
<aside class="quote">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/callisto/40/5_e05bb34c421432ee4d40de30c10af3e5.png" class="avatar"> Callisto:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>this is where a detailed logging system comes into play… maybe an abstract logging system that grabs and logs every action the player does in a single file.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>i didn’t go into detail as that would be a different topic</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/protecting-your-economy/551111/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/protecting-your-economy/551111/3</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 16 Apr 2015 13:31:24 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-551111-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/protecting-your-economy/551111.rss">Protecting Your Economy</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Protecting Your Economy</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@bowserjr2 Bowser jr]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/bowserjr2">@bowserjr2</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>This is worthless without tracking the players actions to find the duplication bug. And you should really find a dynamic way of tracking this, have static values like this is begging for problems. Either you set the limits too high or forget to set a limit.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/protecting-your-economy/551111/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/protecting-your-economy/551111/2</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 16 Apr 2015 13:06:22 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-551111-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/protecting-your-economy/551111.rss">Protecting Your Economy</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Protecting Your Economy</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Callisto Callisto]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/callisto">@Callisto</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I am just brainstorming a few ideas and thought about this:</p>
<p>There almost always will be dupes in private servers, there are probably still some unknown ones in RuneScape. Dupes are probably single-handedly the most game breaking and difficult bugs that exist. Even the most compotent programmers here cannot anticipate every dupe in the servers as they design, it always takes a player base to find them, due to more angles of the game mechanics being “explored” at a greater rate than what one developer testing their server locally can achieve.</p>
<p>Call it an anti dupe system if you will, but what about creating</p>
<p>[ul][li]Implementing a flagging system in every method that can create an item, addItem, createGroundItem, containers (bank, trade, shops) etc.[/li][/ul]</p>
<p>[ul]if a certain criteria is met i.e. count &gt;= 5000000 &amp;&amp; item != 995 (create a seperate system to flag coins as they will accumulate in higher numbers legitimately probably more than any other item (no one should have 5 million yew logs) or something to that effect and temporarily disable that players ability to drop items, trade and sell to shops so no potentially duped items are leaked to the public and then that account can be manually reviewed by administration… this is where a detailed logging system comes into play… maybe an abstract logging system that grabs and logs every action the player does in a single file.[/ul]</p>
<p>So for example, commonly valuable items such as coins, rares, end game armours and weapons, logs, ores, gems, bones, feathers should be more “sensitive” to the flagging system as opposed to say cabbages, raw shrimps and ashes. Group certain items to flag at different counts because 5000 coins is common and should never flag, but 5000 blue partyhats/abyssal whips should never be a thing in your server <span class="bbcode-i">if</span> they are a rare item.</p>
<p>This way you stop potential items from flooding and destroying your “economies”, resulting in hopefully no eco resets and therefore not pissing your players off and losing your precious player count. People don’t even need to know there was a dupe with something like this because hopefully your logging system will tell you how the dupe was done. Oh, and also, temporarily mute the player so they cannot tell strangers in game.</p>
<p>If done right, flagging accounts and temp. disabling there trading etc. (inconveniencing them) should only happen rarely, and everytime some rich player manages to accumulate 5 million yew logs because they actually bought them from players over the course of a year, they can be given exceptions in the system as you now know your game allows players to legitimately earn those items. Scale the flagging for counts of items to your economy. At the beginning of an economy no one should be getting 500m coins, so if it’s the first day of the server and silab logs on a runeagents the shit out of your server, at least you will have the ability to restrict the distribution of those items which gives you plenty of time to re-create and fix the problem.</p>
<p>In my opinion everyone should implement a system like this. Think of a dupe as the fire, you don’t assume your babies will not touch the fire, you assume they are curious and will touch and burn themselves. Put up a safety guard that will stop them from hurting themselves…</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/protecting-your-economy/551111/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/protecting-your-economy/551111/1</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 16 Apr 2015 11:13:50 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-551111-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/protecting-your-economy/551111.rss">Protecting Your Economy</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
