<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Troublesome XP and Level Box</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/troublesome-xp-and-level-box/159981</link>
    <description>Alright, I&#39;ve searched these forums far and wide. Well, alright, I looked around a little and I couldn&#39;t find my problem, so I was hoping maybe someone know off of the top of their head.

You know that magic little black box at the bottom of the stat&#39;s menu? 

WHERE on Earth does it get the variables that it puts inside of it from?! It&#39;s maddening.

In particular I would like to change, when you mouse over a skill, the XP to next level, because it&#39;s kind of frustrating not leveling up at what it says you should (Changed the getLevelPerXP and such) If anyone knows, or if it&#39;s just a part of the client that reads certain variable names or some craziness let me know.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 24 Nov 2007 00:31:20 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/troublesome-xp-and-level-box/159981.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Troublesome XP and Level Box</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Archbishop Archbishop]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/archbishop">@Archbishop</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Alright, I’ve searched these forums far and wide. Well, alright, I looked around a little and I couldn’t find my problem, so I was hoping maybe someone know off of the top of their head.</p>
<p>You know that magic little black box at the bottom of the stat’s menu?</p>
<p>WHERE on Earth does it get the variables that it puts inside of it from?! It’s maddening.</p>
<p>In particular I would like to change, when you mouse over a skill, the XP to next level, because it’s kind of frustrating not leveling up at what it says you should (Changed the getLevelPerXP and such) If anyone knows, or if it’s just a part of the client that reads certain variable names or some craziness let me know.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/troublesome-xp-and-level-box/159981/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/troublesome-xp-and-level-box/159981/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 24 Nov 2007 00:31:20 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-159981-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/troublesome-xp-and-level-box/159981.rss">Troublesome XP and Level Box</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
