<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Help or Request?</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/help-or-request/372315</link>
    <description>Hey im having troubles with my webclient because it has class files and not java files, so i used jad decompiler, but it didn&#39;t do it right so when i compiled i got a bunch of errors. I tried new clients but i didnt like them. Could someone help me make my webclient or can i requeset someone to make it for me? My client was from Yourserver modified by locksmin and made by heaven pkz... i think. Just use that client and message me. Im not being lazy cause i literally almost tried everything.

Thank you,
Lilgdog13

Edit: sorry I put it in the wrong section</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 08 Dec 2010 02:09:26 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/help-or-request/372315.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Help or Request?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@lilgdog13 lilgdog13]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/lilgdog13">@lilgdog13</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Hey im having troubles with my webclient because it has class files and not java files, so i used jad decompiler, but it didn’t do it right so when i compiled i got a bunch of errors. I tried new clients but i didnt like them. Could someone help me make my webclient or can i requeset someone to make it for me? My client was from Yourserver modified by locksmin and made by heaven pkz… i think. Just use that client and message me. Im not being lazy cause i literally almost tried everything.</p>
<p>Thank you,<br>
Lilgdog13</p>
<p>Edit: sorry I put it in the wrong section</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/help-or-request/372315/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/help-or-request/372315/1</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 08 Dec 2010 02:09:26 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-372315-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/help-or-request/372315.rss">Help or Request?</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
