<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>How to Fight</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-fight/20099</link>
    <description>My first time making a topic here i think but il try my best to make it good so here we go..Follow these rules and you&#39;ll be fine.

1.Never i repeat Never go looking for a fight, dont go looking for trouble..let trouble find you
2.Never underestimate the enemy
3.If you knock someout dont bootstomp (unless your black) jk lol
4.Never pull hair, scratch, or punch/kick in the nuts..its against the rules of being a man
5.Random people just post rules il add later.

ok so here we go..your about to get in a fight..but you dont know what the fuck to do..my recommendation would be fight like a hockey player i know its kind of lame but it works..ignore this if you know any type of martial arts/boxing..

Hockey Fighting- Watch the whole video [url=http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=A3JJMEoN8Mg]http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=A3JJMEoN8Mg[/url]
its pretty simple grab by the collar and start throwing lefts and rights..in 1:12 of the video watch what he does, if the guy is bigger/stronger then you wait for your punch keep your head low so hes just hitting your head not your face it wont hurt i promise and when hes not expecting it throw a big right.


where to hit- Red represents damage points ( If you know you can take the kid, hit these spots leave some damge on the kids face..you&#39;ll get a good rep) 
Black represents Ko points (when your punch the jaw try and use uppercuts/hooks..i might be a off for some of the ko points but if anyone would like to fix it be my guest..) [img]http://img215.imageshack.us/img215/8743/robotjaw1kc1.jpg[/img]

Elbows - A good elbow to the chin could knock someout easily (Getting the speed, and mastering the timing is another thing though)

Knees- I personally love using my knees wether its fighting or giving someone a nice charliehorse k so the black dots represent good places to knee honestly ive never seen anyone charliehorse in a fight but i think it would work nicely lol ( if you knee where the red dot is in this picture..it doesnt matter how big/tough this guy is a nice knee there could drop anyone again Anyone why? because it winds you so bad getting hit there hurt like a bitch you gasp for air when you get hit there i also heard you can kill someone by hitting to hard so its not really recomended but if your in trouble do it)
[img]http://img216.imageshack.us/img216/8889/aaaaaaaaed7.jpg[/img]

Blocking- If your in trouble keep your head low, face down..use your arms and knees to block, and when he aint expecting it..throw a nice knee to the solarplex..( i think thats what its called..not to sure though =s)


&lt;blockquote&gt;Karate is for pussies. You gotta street fight. Don&#39;t go out looking for it, but when it comes to you, take the opportunity and go fucking mental.

Footwork is the key to. Always stay on your toes and &quot;dance&quot; with the person your fighting. If your going to try and floor the person, throw a few punches first, then put all your weight in to a punch.&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;I pwn all the little fighter nubs here. No need for a tutorial. The best spot is under the nose that cartilage and uppermouth. You missed it, how could you?

Option 2. Go gorilla/beserker mode and pwn &#39;em bad. ;P 

Work out. Don&#39;t be a fat sh*t.&lt;/blockquote&gt;

Notes:

I am not responsible for any action you do that hurts yourself, your property, or another person in any way/shape or form. You do this at your own risk, and willingly. If you should hurt another person, to the point of severe injury or death, you are responsible, and you will probably be severely punished. You could obtain many years in prison for doing this, and you  accept this fact, and know that I&#39;m not responsible if you do.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 02 Aug 2007 05:34:41 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>General Discussion</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-fight/20099.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>How to Fight</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Hippie_Slay Hippie_Slay]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/hippie_slay">@Hippie_Slay</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Wow. I didn’t think this would be a serious guide but it looks like it helps…</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-fight/20099/105">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-fight/20099/105</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 02 Aug 2007 05:34:41 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-20099-105</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-fight/20099.rss">How to Fight</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>How to Fight</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@MastrChief MastrChief]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/mastrchief">@MastrChief</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>And what if you honestly don’t care if you live or die? Do I have your acceptance to go beserk then?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-fight/20099/104">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-fight/20099/104</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 31 Jul 2007 12:31:52 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-20099-104</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-fight/20099.rss">How to Fight</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>How to Fight</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@geel9 geel9]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/geel9">@geel9</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Karate is useful. If you’re getting mugged by somenoe in an allyway, berserk is NOT going to help. Rather, a few well-trained, lightning-fast kicks and punches, and you can get out. If you want to succeed in life, beat the guys that ATTACK you, and then RUN AWAY. You may think it’s weak, but if you don’t wanna be knocked out and killed in an allyway, RUN!</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-fight/20099/103">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-fight/20099/103</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 31 Jul 2007 08:57:12 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-20099-103</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-fight/20099.rss">How to Fight</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>How to Fight</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@nator123123 nator123123]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/nator123123">@nator123123</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Slapping is very effective xD</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-fight/20099/102">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-fight/20099/102</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 29 Jul 2007 11:53:37 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-20099-102</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-fight/20099.rss">How to Fight</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>How to Fight</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@MastrChief MastrChief]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/mastrchief">@MastrChief</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote no-group" data-post="100" data-topic="20099">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/nator123123/40/5_6259e4fa9dfe0dec282fb0955bb1974c.png" class="avatar"> nator123123:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Dude, this topic is useless. Just slap them in the face and run.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>No because that would just get you beat with a crowbar.</p>
<p>It actually helps to know how to fight before you get into one.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-fight/20099/101">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-fight/20099/101</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 29 Jul 2007 11:02:40 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-20099-101</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-fight/20099.rss">How to Fight</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>How to Fight</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@nator123123 nator123123]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/nator123123">@nator123123</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Dude, this topic is useless. Just slap them in the face and run.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-fight/20099/100">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-fight/20099/100</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 29 Jul 2007 10:20:22 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-20099-100</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-fight/20099.rss">How to Fight</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>How to Fight</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@ronny.m.p ronny.m.p]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/ronny.m.p">@ronny.m.p</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Martial Arts are stupid.</p>
<p>I made up this move when I was getting ready for a school fight after-school.  I’ll try to explain it as best I can.</p>
<p>The Knocker:</p>
<p>First grab the wrist (whatever one is easier to get at) and shove two fingers into the veins on the bottem.  You opponent will be stunned and in a fair bit of pain.  Now, before he snaps back flip his arm over so you are looking at his elbow.  Take your arm that you arn’t holding his wrist with and push down (very hard) on the elbow.  This causes EXTREME pain and your opponent will end up on his knees or his but almost instantly.  Now grab the back of his head and knee him right in the face.  Down in three seconds.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-fight/20099/99">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-fight/20099/99</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 29 Jul 2007 00:38:51 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-20099-99</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-fight/20099.rss">How to Fight</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>How to Fight</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@dragonus18 dragonus18]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/dragonus18">@dragonus18</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>digging is fun thats why</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-fight/20099/98">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-fight/20099/98</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 28 Jul 2007 23:51:04 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-20099-98</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-fight/20099.rss">How to Fight</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>How to Fight</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@whothe0 the fu superior]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/whothe0">@whothe0</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Who the hell dug up this thread? it was since like 2006</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-fight/20099/97">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-fight/20099/97</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 21 Jul 2007 19:13:14 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-20099-97</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-fight/20099.rss">How to Fight</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>How to Fight</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@pk3r_kyle pk3r kyle]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/pk3r_kyle">@pk3r_kyle</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p><a href="http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=3Q_NG0U-CM8" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">how not to fight</a><br>
<a href="http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=U08VPfGNkCY" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">how to fight</a></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-fight/20099/96">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-fight/20099/96</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 21 Jul 2007 01:35:12 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-20099-96</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-fight/20099.rss">How to Fight</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>How to Fight</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@xshadez xshadez]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/xshadez">@xshadez</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>lothy:<br>
Lol… there’s no such thing as a “KO point”. A knockout is achieved when the head is hit hard enough to cause the brain to hit the inside part of the skull. Yes, you can hit them in the jaw. But hitting them anywhere with enough force will cause their head to jerk back. When the head stops moving back, the brain can still hit the inside of the skull, and that’s how it happens.</p>
<p>EDIT: Better way to explain it - Think of it as inertia, one of Newton’s laws. If you’re on a bus that stops quickly, you’ll feel yourself go flying forward. If you’re in a car that hits another car head-on, you’ll either a) Get thrown out the windscreen or b) you’ll get jerked forward hard, the seatbelt will keep you there, and afterwards you’ll most likely have whiplash.</p>
<h2>Apply this to fighting. The fist (car 1) hits the head (car 2) head on. Wink The head flies back, and then stops, and the brain keeps going, until the skull (seatbelt in the car) stops it going back further. But the brain hits the skull hard and you get knocked out.</h2>
<p>i couldnt have said it better my self your brain is basically sitting in a liquid with hard walls around it so if you move very fast (ie) getting punched hard it will just go donk into the back of your skull… obviously your brain dosent cope well with being knocked around</p>
<p>ive been in alot of fights and trust me being in one fight will teach you alot more than reading about it on the internet alot of first timers<br>
get all wobbly and there arms get heavy because theyr not used to the adrenaline</p>
<p>basically the best advice i can give you is you know how you concentrate on a racing game or some sort you react very fast to keep the car under control fighting is very similar if you can watch every move they make, you can counter easily thats why all you beserk style fighters would get f****d up by a vet theyd just wait for one swing duck\dodge\block and unload on your face</p>
<p>probably the bezt way to knock someone out hook to the temple or elbow straight up the jaw idk if its actually called the temple<br>
but if you find the soft part on the sides of your skull theyr very sensitive, also ther are pressure points in your shoulder feel underneath on your armpit runnign along to your elbow is a huge unprotected nerve you can feel it but its incredibly hard to hit in a fight as you might have guessed but one good strike will overload your nervous system and guess what&gt;? your going down</p>
<p>a ddt would be effective but ive never actually tried it in a real fight only when im messin around wit my boys</p>
<p>and thats about it<br>
all i can teach you is keep your guard up and concentrate on your opponent otherwise youll most likely get the beatdown<br>
unless your bigger than them but trust me  fighting has little to do with size\strength sure its an advantage but without the experience its all for nothing</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-fight/20099/95">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-fight/20099/95</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jul 2007 23:59:59 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-20099-95</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-fight/20099.rss">How to Fight</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>How to Fight</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@_M_ose ~M°ose~]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/_m_ose">@_M_ose</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>ORRRR You could just get em down and give em a nice curbstomp =]</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-fight/20099/94">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-fight/20099/94</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 15 Jul 2007 19:58:58 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-20099-94</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-fight/20099.rss">How to Fight</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>How to Fight</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@VB6_FTW VB6 FTW]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/vb6_ftw">@VB6_FTW</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>These steps will be good if I ever join a karate class.<br>
“Kids, cut the brick in half.”<br>
“HI-YAH THIS!!!”<br>
lol</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-fight/20099/93">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-fight/20099/93</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 15 Jul 2007 18:27:09 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-20099-93</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-fight/20099.rss">How to Fight</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>How to Fight</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@jonyo jonyo]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/jonyo">@jonyo</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“MastrChief, post:91, topic:20099”]Anyone seen chicks fight? They are fucking brutal.</p>
<p>I saw one go down earlier this year, those 2 tore each other and the teachers trying to split them apart up. Our “sweep” teacher got bitch slapped.[/quote]</p>
<p>Hah, we have sweeps too, it’s annoying. And yes, they can be scary. Other times, they’ll just scream at each other. And <span class="bbcode-i">other</span> times it’s entertaining <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/smiley.png?v=6" title=":smiley:" class="emoji" alt=":smiley:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-fight/20099/92">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-fight/20099/92</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 14 Jul 2007 11:42:49 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-20099-92</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-fight/20099.rss">How to Fight</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>How to Fight</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@MastrChief MastrChief]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/mastrchief">@MastrChief</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Anyone seen chicks fight? They are fucking brutal.</p>
<p>I saw one go down earlier this year, those 2 tore each other and the teachers trying to split them apart up. Our “sweep” teacher got bitch slapped.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-fight/20099/91">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-fight/20099/91</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 05 Jul 2007 22:55:48 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-20099-91</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-fight/20099.rss">How to Fight</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>How to Fight</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@nathanmarck nathanmarck]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/nathanmarck">@nathanmarck</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“Erj, post:20, topic:20099”]This is a good method, but in most fights at<br>
my school…they throw a few puches and kicks then they go for a head lock.[/quote]<br>
init my school radcliffe has some fucking pussy fights<br>
also would u class some1 getting you down and punching you 3 times then u kicking him in the stomach getting battered</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-fight/20099/90">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-fight/20099/90</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 05 Jul 2007 22:51:44 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-20099-90</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-fight/20099.rss">How to Fight</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>How to Fight</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@MastrChief MastrChief]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/mastrchief">@MastrChief</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“Fr33sc4p3, post:88, topic:20099”]What i have noticed, if someone is starting on you, obviously wanting a fight so you hit him, in the face as hard as you can first.</p>
<p>90% of the time he will leave you alone and just walk away then, or just say “LIEK OMG WTF U FKING CUNT U HIT ME FOR?!?!?!?! WE WASNT FIGHTING”</p>
<p>I got that off my sister, when i broke her door, and she was shouting at me i was shouting back and she just ran up and punched me in the face LOL.</p>
<p>But yeah, normally if she hits me id lock her in a cupboard or sit on her until she cant breath, but i was so shocked she hit me that hard in the face i didnt bother doing anything back[/quote]</p>
<p>I hate when you’re about to go berserk on someone’s ass and they start to play it cool =\</p>
<p>Siblings can be your best friend/worst enemy. Hell, my sister knows how to piss me off better than anyone else, yet she’s there for me when I start feeling emu.</p>
<p>Lock her in the cupboard? LOL.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-fight/20099/89">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-fight/20099/89</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 05 Jul 2007 18:41:38 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-20099-89</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-fight/20099.rss">How to Fight</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>How to Fight</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@tL tL]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/tl">@tL</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>What i have noticed, if someone is starting on you, obviously wanting a fight so you hit him, in the face as hard as you can first.</p>
<p>90% of the time he will leave you alone and just walk away then, or just say “LIEK OMG WTF U FKING CUNT U HIT ME FOR?!?!?!?! WE WASNT FIGHTING”</p>
<p>I got that off my sister, when i broke her door, and she was shouting at me i was shouting back and she just ran up and punched me in the face LOL.</p>
<p>But yeah, normally if she hits me id lock her in a cupboard or sit on her until she cant breath, but i was so shocked she hit me that hard in the face i didnt bother doing anything back</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-fight/20099/88">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-fight/20099/88</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 05 Jul 2007 18:37:12 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-20099-88</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-fight/20099.rss">How to Fight</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>How to Fight</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@MastrChief MastrChief]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/mastrchief">@MastrChief</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I’m 15, I fight sophmores and juniors.</p>
<p>Just because you can’t fight without having to concentrate doesn’t mean nobody else can.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-fight/20099/87">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-fight/20099/87</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 05 Jul 2007 17:29:38 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-20099-87</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-fight/20099.rss">How to Fight</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>How to Fight</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@MybJames MybJames]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/mybjames">@MybJames</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“MastrChief, post:85, topic:20099”][quote author=MybJames link=topic=30461.msg1570828#msg1570828 date=1183655343]<br>
Don’t go  mental in a fight, keep it calm and fight the right way, going beserk is an easy way to get your ass kicked, the adrenaline will take away all your fighting talents.<br>
[/quote]</p>
<p>Never happened for me =\</p>
<p>I’m never clam in a fight, I attack until they can’t hit back and it works for me.</p>
<p>TIP: If you can’t feel the hit, neither can they. Hit HARDER![/quote]<br>
Obviously you have never fought anybody who has any talent, or you are younger.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-fight/20099/86">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-fight/20099/86</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 05 Jul 2007 17:25:46 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-20099-86</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-fight/20099.rss">How to Fight</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>How to Fight</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@MastrChief MastrChief]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/mastrchief">@MastrChief</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote no-group" data-post="84" data-topic="20099">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/mybjames/40/5_6259e4fa9dfe0dec282fb0955bb1974c.png" class="avatar"> MybJames:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Don’t go  mental in a fight, keep it calm and fight the right way, going beserk is an easy way to get your ass kicked, the adrenaline will take away all your fighting talents.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Never happened for me =\</p>
<p>I’m never clam in a fight, I attack until they can’t hit back and it works for me.</p>
<p>TIP: If you can’t feel the hit, neither can they. Hit HARDER!</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-fight/20099/85">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-fight/20099/85</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 05 Jul 2007 17:14:18 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-20099-85</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-fight/20099.rss">How to Fight</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>How to Fight</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@MybJames MybJames]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/mybjames">@MybJames</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Don’t go  mental in a fight, keep it calm and fight the right way, going beserk is an easy way to get your ass kicked, the adrenaline will take away all your fighting talents.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-fight/20099/84">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-fight/20099/84</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 05 Jul 2007 17:09:03 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-20099-84</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-fight/20099.rss">How to Fight</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>How to Fight</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@jonyo jonyo]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/jonyo">@jonyo</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote no-group" data-post="80" data-topic="20099">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 FastBawlz:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Jonyo STFU and stop gravedigging…</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Lol shut up, it doesn’t matter if the topic is old its still important</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-fight/20099/83">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-fight/20099/83</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 05 Jul 2007 11:16:08 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-20099-83</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-fight/20099.rss">How to Fight</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>How to Fight</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Cunit Cunit]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/cunit">@Cunit</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>you must’a been real bored <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/confused.png?v=6" title=":confused:" class="emoji" alt=":confused:"> :rolleyes:</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-fight/20099/82">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-fight/20099/82</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 03 Jul 2007 21:38:51 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-20099-82</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-fight/20099.rss">How to Fight</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>How to Fight</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@blah_bah7 blah bah7]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/blah_bah7">@blah_bah7</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Knees- I personally love using my knees wether its fighting or giving someone a nice charliehorse k so the black dots represent good places to knee honestly ive never seen anyone charliehorse in a fight but i think it would work nicely lol ( if you knee where the red dot is in this picture…it doesnt matter how big/tough this guy is a nice knee there could drop anyone again Anyone why? because it winds you so bad getting hit there hurt like a bitch you gasp for air when you get hit there i also heard you can kill someone by hitting to hard so its not really recomended but if your in trouble do it)</p>
<p>red dot, kick them there and it will kill them</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-fight/20099/81">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-fight/20099/81</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 26 Jun 2007 07:12:51 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-20099-81</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-fight/20099.rss">How to Fight</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
