<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>[317]Rotate NPC&#39;s in Delta[317]</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/317-rotate-npcs-in-delta-317/349055</link>
    <description>[b]Hello.[/b]

I&#39;d like to start this thread of by saying that I really want to rotate my NPC&#39;s, it looks like such a huge failiure when they&#39;re all facing the same way and some are looking into walls and what not.

I&#39;ve searched around for ways to rotate NPC´s and most threads asking how to do so were answered with a simple &quot;you can&#39;t&quot;. 
Althought one thread proved promising, it had a link to a guide on how to rotate NPC&#39;s in 317.
[b]Link to the guide: http://tiny.cc/rq0ey[/b]

[b]Picture found on that page:[/b]
[img]http://img509.imageshack.us/img509/2878/differentfacingbo7.png[/img]

However my server is running on a Delta source and apperently this does not work on Delta (Doesn&#39;t give any errors, but NPC&#39;s just wont rotate).
Some guy on the page previously linked said this:
&lt;blockquote&gt;it does works on delta, well atleast for me(you must delete the other facing codes at the update blocks in npchandler).&lt;/blockquote&gt;

Sadly, I don&#39;t know how &quot;update blocks&quot; look like or how to safely remove them without  screwing my server up.
Is there anyone who could teach me about update blocks and maybe help me out here?

You wouldn&#39;t just be helping me, a whole lot of people want to rotate NPC&#39;s...</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 14 Jul 2010 21:01:56 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/317-rotate-npcs-in-delta-317/349055.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>[317]Rotate NPC&#39;s in Delta[317]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Praktikanten Praktikanten]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/praktikanten">@Praktikanten</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p><span class="bbcode-b">Hello.</span></p>
<p>I’d like to start this thread of by saying that I really want to rotate my NPC’s, it looks like such a huge failiure when they’re all facing the same way and some are looking into walls and what not.</p>
<p>I’ve searched around for ways to rotate NPC´s and most threads asking how to do so were answered with a simple “you can’t”.<br>
Althought one thread proved promising, it had a link to a guide on how to rotate NPC’s in 317.<br>
<span class="bbcode-b">Link to the guide: <a href="http://tiny.cc/rq0ey" rel="nofollow noopener">http://tiny.cc/rq0ey</a></span></p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Picture found on that page:</span><br>
<img src="http://img509.imageshack.us/img509/2878/differentfacingbo7.png" alt width="" height=""></p>
<p>However my server is running on a Delta source and apperently this does not work on Delta (Doesn’t give any errors, but NPC’s just wont rotate).<br>
Some guy on the page previously linked said this:</p>
<blockquote>it does works on delta, well atleast for me(you must delete the other facing codes at the update blocks in npchandler).</blockquote>
<p>Sadly, I don’t know how “update blocks” look like or how to safely remove them without  screwing my server up.<br>
Is there anyone who could teach me about update blocks and maybe help me out here?</p>
<p>You wouldn’t just be helping me, a whole lot of people want to rotate NPC’s…</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/317-rotate-npcs-in-delta-317/349055/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/317-rotate-npcs-in-delta-317/349055/1</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jul 2010 21:01:56 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-349055-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/317-rotate-npcs-in-delta-317/349055.rss">[317]Rotate NPC&#39;s in Delta[317]</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
