<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Binding this fight &quot;profile&quot; to an npc id?</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/binding-this-fight-profile-to-an-npc-id/422254</link>
    <description>Well, the title may have sounded confusing, but.. I&#39;ll explain it here

Base: Flaresoft 474 (Which is Hyperion/rs2serv)

Well, basically, if you don&#39;t know how it functions, flaresoft uses individual class files for each &quot;boss&quot; monster if you will, in this case I mean a npc that uses more than one type of attack, for example, Solus (One of the bosses) summons mages, heals, rapid attacks, barrages and moves back a step, etc.

So I decided to make one myself, and it includes delrith, and he will play in one of the main storylines in my server.. so.. once I finished it up (I based it heavily off of current boss classes, making modifications to wherever it suited my needs), I realized something... what exactly binds/tells the server that Delrith should use that class file for his attacks? So I decided to look through the other class files.. I couldn&#39;t find anything like that, so I decided to do a quick skim through the source, still nothing to be found.

Basically, if anyone has any experience with this, could they help me figure out how to &quot;bind&quot; the class and the id?</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 20 Nov 2011 04:42:01 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/binding-this-fight-profile-to-an-npc-id/422254.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Binding this fight &quot;profile&quot; to an npc id?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@drubrkletern drubrkletern]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/drubrkletern">@drubrkletern</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Well, the title may have sounded confusing, but… I’ll explain it here</p>
<p>Base: Flaresoft 474 (Which is Hyperion/rs2serv)</p>
<p>Well, basically, if you don’t know how it functions, flaresoft uses individual class files for each “boss” monster if you will, in this case I mean a npc that uses more than one type of attack, for example, Solus (One of the bosses) summons mages, heals, rapid attacks, barrages and moves back a step, etc.</p>
<p>So I decided to make one myself, and it includes delrith, and he will play in one of the main storylines in my server… so… once I finished it up (I based it heavily off of current boss classes, making modifications to wherever it suited my needs), I realized something… what exactly binds/tells the server that Delrith should use that class file for his attacks? So I decided to look through the other class files… I couldn’t find anything like that, so I decided to do a quick skim through the source, still nothing to be found.</p>
<p>Basically, if anyone has any experience with this, could they help me figure out how to “bind” the class and the id?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/binding-this-fight-profile-to-an-npc-id/422254/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/binding-this-fight-profile-to-an-npc-id/422254/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 20 Nov 2011 04:42:01 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-422254-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/binding-this-fight-profile-to-an-npc-id/422254.rss">Binding this fight &quot;profile&quot; to an npc id?</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
