<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Buying bank spaces?</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/buying-bank-spaces/458912</link>
    <description>In the new Jagex money-making store thing, you can now buy like 250 more bank spaces.... I found this a bit unfair. I know it&#39;s only a minor thing to add, but still you should be able to get them via quests or something, not just for paying money.

Edit: I thought everything was supposed to be cosmetic.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 01 Oct 2012 00:05:02 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/buying-bank-spaces/458912.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Buying bank spaces?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@davidi2 Davidi2]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/davidi2">@davidi2</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Yea but Pokemon doesn’t revolve around money, and I didn’t say ‘get max cash’ for the completionist cape either. I think maxing our your XP would be like maxing out your levels in Pokemon, which would count towards ‘completing’ the game. Because you can’t lose those once you get it (unlike money)</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/buying-bank-spaces/458912/48">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/buying-bank-spaces/458912/48</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 01 Oct 2012 00:05:02 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-458912-48</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/buying-bank-spaces/458912.rss">Buying bank spaces?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Buying bank spaces?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@bowserjr2 Bowser jr]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/bowserjr2">@bowserjr2</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote" data-post="46" data-topic="458912">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/user_avatar/forum.moparisthebest.com/davidi2/40/2579_1.png" class="avatar"> Davidi2:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Actually the completionists cape doesn’t cover everything. It covers most things, yes, but there is plenty it doesnt cover. Like unlocking/getting every pet, getting max slayer points, getting a certain number of player kills for the hats/duel arena hats, getting 200m xp in stats. etc. Really it’s an infinite number of things you can add.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Getting every pet and maybe some hat stuff is something that is legitimate to add as requirement. Getting 200M XP,  2^32 / 2 gp and max slayer points isn’t real tasks. Reaching the technical limit shouldn’t be seen as a requirement for beating the game.</p>
<p>You wouldn’t say you haven’t beaten Pokèmon before you have $999.999?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/buying-bank-spaces/458912/47">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/buying-bank-spaces/458912/47</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 01 Oct 2012 00:01:46 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-458912-47</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/buying-bank-spaces/458912.rss">Buying bank spaces?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Buying bank spaces?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@davidi2 Davidi2]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/davidi2">@davidi2</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Actually the completionists cape doesn’t cover everything. It covers most things, yes, but there is plenty it doesnt cover. Like unlocking/getting every pet, getting max slayer points, getting a certain number of player kills for the hats/duel arena hats, getting 200m xp in stats. etc. Really it’s an infinite number of things you can add.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/buying-bank-spaces/458912/46">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/buying-bank-spaces/458912/46</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 30 Sep 2012 23:58:25 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-458912-46</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/buying-bank-spaces/458912.rss">Buying bank spaces?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Buying bank spaces?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@bowserjr2 Bowser jr]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/bowserjr2">@bowserjr2</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“rip4d, post:43, topic:458912”][quote author=Taharok link=topic=561819.msg4115635#msg4115635 date=1349023928]<br>
RPGs can be beaten, ones that are updated simply take a really long time to beat. That’s not to say every player must work toward beating it…that’s totally not true. Most RS players feel that achieving 138 combat is “beating” the game for some reason, which is why they work so hard on combat and little on everything else. But to truly beat the game, you really do need to do everything.<br>
[/quote]Pretty much this. The completionist cape is basically “beating the game,” but when I said you aren’t done, I meant it as Bowser put it, that there is always something to do, like in Pokemon.[/quote]<br>
I didn’t make my point clear enough. I did not compare RS to Pokèmon. I said that a credit screen isn’t a sign of beating the game. For all those who have played Pokèmon, you know that there is <span class="bbcode-b">new</span> content after that. When you have gotten the trimmed completionist cape, there isn’t anything new. You have done everything the game expect you to do.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/buying-bank-spaces/458912/45">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/buying-bank-spaces/458912/45</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 30 Sep 2012 23:49:08 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-458912-45</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/buying-bank-spaces/458912.rss">Buying bank spaces?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Buying bank spaces?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Kidpaparoach Kidpaparoach]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/kidpaparoach">@Kidpaparoach</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Urgh, please stop trying to argue with me. I don’t want to argue as you seem to have forgotten my original point and you seem to be arguing with me to prove you are ‘correct’ not to prove your point. You shouldn’t argue with someone just to try to disprove them, you should debate with someone to teach them the correct one however not taking it so far your forcing your point on them. I of course am being a hypocrite I always force facts on people (sometimes my facts are wrong, I’m only human I make mistakes).</p>
<p>Someone who experiences the full game is considered a good player, someone who only does one part of the game is considered a bad player (in most cases). Another example of pokemon (pokemon ftw) if you only trained your zapdos lets say to level 100 and completed the game with that but tried to play again your friend who has 6 pokemon that are level 80s, they are using moomoo milks etc who do you thinks gonna win? The person with one good factor or the person who is experiencing the game to the full and also spending less time possibly on it in order to be better than the first person in my example.</p>
<p>What tahorak said is correct to my knowledge.<br>
But my original point is, lets say you need to complete 5% of Rs completion to be considered good. When I say 5%  I don’t just mean xp, I mean minigames, wiseness (to know whats good and whats bad) and so on. Mr extremez is nowhere near that 5%, yes he’s probably past the 5% xp mark but i’m sure with a lot of tasks he’d do them badly hence why I said he was a bad player. It wasn’t meant as an insult, i wanted to tell him what I believe is the truth when he seem(s) to believe otherwise.<br>
Whether you achieve something small or big as long as you play it correctly your achievement is good but he’s just missing the point of the game. Theirs nothing wrong with missing the point of the game just the player needs to admit their not the best at the game i.e. I’m shiiiit at fifa who cares its a game.<br>
A games for enjoyment (and ofc profit for the people that own the game etc), he shouldn’t of taken that as an insult(I feel like he took that as an insult).</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/buying-bank-spaces/458912/44">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/buying-bank-spaces/458912/44</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 30 Sep 2012 23:40:38 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-458912-44</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/buying-bank-spaces/458912.rss">Buying bank spaces?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Buying bank spaces?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@rip4d rip4d]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/rip4d">@rip4d</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“Taharok, post:42, topic:458912”]RPGs can be beaten, ones that are updated simply take a really long time to beat. That’s not to say every player must work toward beating it…that’s totally not true. Most RS players feel that achieving 138 combat is “beating” the game for some reason, which is why they work so hard on combat and little on everything else. But to truly beat the game, you really do need to do everything.[/quote]Pretty much this. The completionist cape is basically “beating the game,” but when I said you aren’t done, I meant it as Bowser put it, that there is always something to do, like in Pokemon.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/buying-bank-spaces/458912/43">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/buying-bank-spaces/458912/43</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 30 Sep 2012 17:22:25 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-458912-43</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/buying-bank-spaces/458912.rss">Buying bank spaces?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Buying bank spaces?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@mod_taharok Taharok]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/mod_taharok">@mod_taharok</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>RPGs can be beaten, ones that are updated simply take a really long time to beat. That’s not to say every player must work toward beating it…that’s totally not true. Most RS players feel that achieving 138 combat is “beating” the game for some reason, which is why they work so hard on combat and little on everything else. But to truly beat the game, you really do need to do everything.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/buying-bank-spaces/458912/42">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/buying-bank-spaces/458912/42</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 30 Sep 2012 16:52:08 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-458912-42</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/buying-bank-spaces/458912.rss">Buying bank spaces?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Buying bank spaces?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@bowserjr2 Bowser jr]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/bowserjr2">@bowserjr2</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>rip4d: Completionist cape is what is says, you have completed the game. The Pokèmon games are perfect examples of games where the credits doesn’t mark the end of the game. You have still stuff to do.  Lots of games doesn’t end at the credit.<br>
When you have completed every piece of game content, you have beaten it. 200M exp doesn’t count.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/buying-bank-spaces/458912/41">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/buying-bank-spaces/458912/41</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 30 Sep 2012 16:41:19 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-458912-41</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/buying-bank-spaces/458912.rss">Buying bank spaces?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Buying bank spaces?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@rip4d rip4d]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/rip4d">@rip4d</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>By storyline, I meant there is no single storyline that is prominent throughout the game. There is no story mode of sorts, just quests that all have their own stories. If you own a quest cape, does that mean you’ve suddenly beaten the game? No, not at all, you’ve simply done all of the quests. And just because I said there is no single storyline, I suddenly know nothing about the game? Are you retarded? I have a veteran’s cape and probably know much more about the game than you do. There is no beating this game, as there is no point where the credits role and you get a little note next to a save file saying you’ve completed it. Yes, there is a completionist cape, but you’re not done after that. Having a quest cape doesn’t mean you’re done with the game either, nor does having a max cape. There is no right or wrong way to play the game, you just play as you like.</p>
<p>And for the record, I know there are a bunch of storylines, RotM is the only Grandmaster quest I have left and quite frankly I can’t wait for the next Myreque quest to come out.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/buying-bank-spaces/458912/40">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/buying-bank-spaces/458912/40</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 30 Sep 2012 16:24:07 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-458912-40</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/buying-bank-spaces/458912.rss">Buying bank spaces?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Buying bank spaces?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Kidpaparoach Kidpaparoach]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/kidpaparoach">@Kidpaparoach</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Since I’m replying to you on a mobile phone I can’t quote what you said so this is going to be a very simple reply and if you wish for me to re-reply with more info please do state so.</p>
<p>Their is a storyline, their are book(s), heroes(or something, basically important characters in the game like korasi, the raptor and so on). Considering you never realised this I’m going to assume you don’t know too much about the game considering most updates are heavily tied into the storyline. I don’t read the lore and I know this. What did you think the rotm quest series was about? Their is a story, and its pretty intresting(the book(s) are aweful though it sounds like its written for 5 year olds).</p>
<p>Their is a certain way of playing each activity, people consider ‘suomi’ the best player in game due to the fact he has completed the game in a sense. The completionist cape is a reward for completing the game.<br>
What I’m saying quite simply you can’t put someone who only does what he does on par with a player who plays the full game as the player who plays the game fully will have more knowledge, abilities and so forth. Its not a bad thing if your not good at the game of course, its only a game.<br>
Its not an opinion, its a fact.<br>
Let’s say you were looking for a wife, their was a girl who was amazing at cooking however their was a girl who was pretty good at cooking and other things but her cooking ability was not as good as the other girl. Who would you chose(‘love’ etc aside, just based on ability performance.<br>
Sorry if this doesn’t make much sense, I want to put too much info in so I have forgotten a lot of my original points+ some of what your question was:L.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/buying-bank-spaces/458912/39">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/buying-bank-spaces/458912/39</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 30 Sep 2012 13:51:42 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-458912-39</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/buying-bank-spaces/458912.rss">Buying bank spaces?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Buying bank spaces?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@rip4d rip4d]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/rip4d">@rip4d</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>There is no storyline, there is no goal that you accomplish and “beat the game” and suddenly access post-game content. Runescape is an MMORPG, and people can play however they’d like. If they want to grind levels, they can grind levels. If they want to socialize, they can socialize. There is no point to the game that is being missed if you play a certain way, and they are not bad at the game because of it. Runescape is such a great game because there are no restrictions, you play how YOU want.</p>
<p>Now stop forcing your opinion down other peoples’ throats, Roach.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/buying-bank-spaces/458912/38">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/buying-bank-spaces/458912/38</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 30 Sep 2012 11:58:02 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-458912-38</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/buying-bank-spaces/458912.rss">Buying bank spaces?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Buying bank spaces?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Kidpaparoach Kidpaparoach]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/kidpaparoach">@Kidpaparoach</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Sigh, thats like playing CoD and only playing the campaign and never touching anything else. You aren’t experiancing the full game so you will not be good at the game as a whole however the contrast in acitivies in Rs are far bigger so its waaaay more apart in Rs.<br>
You can play how you like but in general your just bad since you don’t fully experiance the game.</p>
<p>I used to be the same(to an extent), I only Pked and did combat. Now I can do everything in the game (exl a few things) amazingly. I’ll wrap it up their since I’ve gtg (in college atm).</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/buying-bank-spaces/458912/37">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/buying-bank-spaces/458912/37</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Sep 2012 10:00:34 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-458912-37</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/buying-bank-spaces/458912.rss">Buying bank spaces?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Buying bank spaces?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@runescape_sucks runescape sucks]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/runescape_sucks">@runescape_sucks</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p><a href="http://www.runescape.com/Jagexactuallysaidthatyouhavetoplaybythiscertaintypeofgamestyleotherwiseyouwillbebannedbecausetheyreelite/" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">http://www.runescape.com/Jagexactuallysaidthatyouhavetoplaybythiscertaintypeofgamestyleotherwiseyouwillbebannedbecausetheyreelite/</a></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/buying-bank-spaces/458912/36">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/buying-bank-spaces/458912/36</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 23 Sep 2012 08:38:15 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-458912-36</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/buying-bank-spaces/458912.rss">Buying bank spaces?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Buying bank spaces?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Pink_Phat Pink Phat]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/pink_phat">@Pink_Phat</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“Kidpaparoach, post:34, topic:458912”][quote author=mr extremez link=topic=561819.msg4108134#msg4108134 date=1348261641]</p>
<aside class="quote">
<blockquote>
<p>Extremez, you don’t play Rs properly so you wouldn’t understand how much bank space you use.<br>
[/quote]There isn’t a proper way to play runescape. If I want to play 24/7 and get a skill that I want then I can. Atleast I don’t bot and I’m not a fucking suomi…</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Their is, the way the game is intended to be played is that way. Your just no lifing certain things, not experiencing the game as a whole which is how you play the game properly.[/quote]<br>
Did Jagex say that themselves? If so, please link me to it.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/buying-bank-spaces/458912/35">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/buying-bank-spaces/458912/35</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 23 Sep 2012 08:32:47 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-458912-35</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/buying-bank-spaces/458912.rss">Buying bank spaces?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Buying bank spaces?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Kidpaparoach Kidpaparoach]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/kidpaparoach">@Kidpaparoach</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“mr extremez, post:33, topic:458912”][quote author=Kidpaparoach link=topic=561819.msg4107282#msg4107282 date=1348138552]<br>
Extremez, you don’t play Rs properly so you wouldn’t understand how much bank space you use.<br>
[/quote]There isn’t a proper way to play runescape. If I want to play 24/7 and get a skill that I want then I can. Atleast I don’t bot and I’m not a fucking suomi…[/quote]<br>
Their is, the way the game is intended to be played is that way. Your just no lifing certain things, not experiencing the game as a whole which is how you play the game properly.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/buying-bank-spaces/458912/34">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/buying-bank-spaces/458912/34</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 22 Sep 2012 21:58:47 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-458912-34</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/buying-bank-spaces/458912.rss">Buying bank spaces?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Buying bank spaces?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@mr_extremez mr extremez]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/mr_extremez">@mr_extremez</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“Kidpaparoach, post:32, topic:458912”]Extremez, you don’t play Rs properly so you wouldn’t understand how much bank space you use.[/quote]There isn’t a proper way to play runescape. If I want to play 24/7 and get a skill that I want then I can. Atleast I don’t bot and I’m not a fucking suomi…</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/buying-bank-spaces/458912/33">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/buying-bank-spaces/458912/33</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 21 Sep 2012 21:07:21 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-458912-33</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/buying-bank-spaces/458912.rss">Buying bank spaces?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Buying bank spaces?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Kidpaparoach Kidpaparoach]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/kidpaparoach">@Kidpaparoach</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Extremez, you don’t play Rs properly so you wouldn’t understand how much bank space you use.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/buying-bank-spaces/458912/32">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/buying-bank-spaces/458912/32</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 20 Sep 2012 10:55:52 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-458912-32</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/buying-bank-spaces/458912.rss">Buying bank spaces?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Buying bank spaces?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Mitko Mitko]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/mitko">@Mitko</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>It’s supposed to be available for Loyalty Points soon so this one shouldn’t be a problem.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/buying-bank-spaces/458912/31">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/buying-bank-spaces/458912/31</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 12 Sep 2012 23:33:21 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-458912-31</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/buying-bank-spaces/458912.rss">Buying bank spaces?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Buying bank spaces?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@mr_extremez mr extremez]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/mr_extremez">@mr_extremez</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Seems like a waist of cash to spend money on bank space.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/buying-bank-spaces/458912/30">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/buying-bank-spaces/458912/30</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 12 Sep 2012 23:30:01 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-458912-30</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/buying-bank-spaces/458912.rss">Buying bank spaces?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Buying bank spaces?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Jaxus Jaxus]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/jaxus">@Jaxus</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Jagex is in control, so I don’t think any actions they have taken place will be repealed. Also, since the crash of their past budget, they have needed extra money. I don’t see anything unfair about it at all; take any other company, such as Blizzard – they have tons of in-game content that you have to purchase, but they live up to their prestige due to their great support and content they provide.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/buying-bank-spaces/458912/29">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/buying-bank-spaces/458912/29</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 12 Sep 2012 00:10:30 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-458912-29</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/buying-bank-spaces/458912.rss">Buying bank spaces?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Buying bank spaces?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@the_elve_age the elve age]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/the_elve_age">@the_elve_age</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>It’s just a benefit. I don’t see people massively complaining to the bigger private servers who’s donator benefits are tremendous.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/buying-bank-spaces/458912/28">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/buying-bank-spaces/458912/28</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 11 Sep 2012 01:57:25 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-458912-28</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/buying-bank-spaces/458912.rss">Buying bank spaces?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Buying bank spaces?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@ranger_squad ranger squad]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/ranger_squad">@ranger_squad</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Alright. I might go for it <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=5" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/buying-bank-spaces/458912/27">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/buying-bank-spaces/458912/27</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 10 Sep 2012 16:39:58 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-458912-27</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/buying-bank-spaces/458912.rss">Buying bank spaces?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Buying bank spaces?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@ranger_squad ranger squad]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/ranger_squad">@ranger_squad</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Is it still possible to get questcape on a new account?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/buying-bank-spaces/458912/26">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/buying-bank-spaces/458912/26</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 10 Sep 2012 06:19:05 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-458912-26</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/buying-bank-spaces/458912.rss">Buying bank spaces?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Buying bank spaces?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@davidi2 Davidi2]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/davidi2">@davidi2</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>What? I already knew all of this, I used the tip.it quest calculator when I was going for quest cape. Everyone knows getting the cape isn’t hard, it just takes time and effort because a lot of people don’t actually like doing quests.</p>
<p>EDIT - What the hell this is completely irrelevant, this topic is about solomons not quest cape xD</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/buying-bank-spaces/458912/25">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/buying-bank-spaces/458912/25</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 10 Sep 2012 04:36:10 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-458912-25</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/buying-bank-spaces/458912.rss">Buying bank spaces?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Buying bank spaces?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@davidi2 Davidi2]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/davidi2">@davidi2</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“Loveandpower, post:7, topic:458915”][quote author=Davidi2 link=topic=561819.msg4099350#msg4099350 date=1347246186]<br>
Um. How can you disagree with massive quester if I have the quest cape? It doesn’t mean others cant be massive questers too. Lol. And no you haven’t, because I finished the most recent quest right when it came out, so technically there are very few people that have had the most recent one longer than me <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/wink.png?v=5" title=":wink:" class="emoji" alt=":wink:"></p>
<p>And no, I keep most of my quest items. Well I did at least until I most recently cleaned my bank. A rock pick isn’t a quest item though <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=5" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"><br>
[/quote]back in 04 it was considered a quest item babe <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/wink.png?v=5" title=":wink:" class="emoji" alt=":wink:"></p>
<p>(digsite came out in like 03 or something )</p>
<p>as far as everyone being a massive quester eh maybe I guess xD  but I was just pointing out there are  others who have held quest capes on here xD[/quote]Doesn’t matter if it used to be considered one, it isn’t now so there’s no reason to keep it; especially with how easy it is to get in the museum</p>
<p>And yea, to be a massive quester all you need to do is have the quest cape and continue to do new quests. The majority of people dislike questing, so that’s all I meant. I wasn’t talking about other people at all <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=5" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"> Personally I don’t really care if other people have the cape. At all.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/buying-bank-spaces/458912/24">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/buying-bank-spaces/458912/24</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 10 Sep 2012 03:17:31 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-458912-24</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/buying-bank-spaces/458912.rss">Buying bank spaces?</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
