<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>How to add shops to a 604</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-add-shops-to-a-604/417006</link>
    <description>Hey guys, I&#39;ve recently been experimenting with a 604 source (I think) I&#39;ve just been trying it out, and i&#39;ve never run a server other than a 317. I was looking at how to make custom shops. I&#39;m used to making the shops, and linking it to the NPC using wanneshop, but in this source and i think all 604&#39;s theres no wanneshop in the client.java. I&#39;ve looked around as best I can which probably wasn&#39;t good enough, and couldn&#39;t figure out where to go to link an NPC to a shop. If anyone knows how I know how to spawn the NPC, and create the shop just not link the NPC to the shop. If someone could tell me which file this is in I would be extremely grateful.

-Strafe</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 04 Oct 2011 14:16:25 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-add-shops-to-a-604/417006.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>How to add shops to a 604</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Strafe Strafe]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/strafe">@Strafe</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Hey guys, I’ve recently been experimenting with a 604 source (I think) I’ve just been trying it out, and i’ve never run a server other than a 317. I was looking at how to make custom shops. I’m used to making the shops, and linking it to the NPC using wanneshop, but in this source and i think all 604’s theres no wanneshop in the client.java. I’ve looked around as best I can which probably wasn’t good enough, and couldn’t figure out where to go to link an NPC to a shop. If anyone knows how I know how to spawn the NPC, and create the shop just not link the NPC to the shop. If someone could tell me which file this is in I would be extremely grateful.</p>
<p>-Strafe</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-add-shops-to-a-604/417006/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-add-shops-to-a-604/417006/1</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 04 Oct 2011 14:16:25 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-417006-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-add-shops-to-a-604/417006.rss">How to add shops to a 604</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
