<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>FDTD - Now with PK!</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/fdtd-now-with-pk/539916</link>
    <description>[center]
[youtube]https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=N_y6vE1RBgg[/youtube]
[hr]
[b]About:[/b]
I&#39;ve always had a lively imagination... I often listen to music or play games and find myself fantasizing about something I could put into a game; and just around that single thought, usually a whole world builds up; this affects me so much that often I miss the very game I&#39;m playing at that moment.
I started with RSPS in 2007 (holy cow, I feel weird thinking this); over the years I&#39;ve somehow learned how to code and... I think this is my prime. I&#39;m able to create anything...

And so I present to you: From Dust to Dragons... A very miniature creation of a complex, rich and deep game I dream might one day exist...
This server is my art; I&#39;ve poured my mind and soul into it... I&#39;ve worked on it for months, entire days at a time... patching almost every day.
This here, is the creation of my imagination (within the constraints of RS engine).
You will not need money, votes, friends in high places or anything of the sort to play this...
All you will need is time, open mind and that little spark that makes you want to explore something new, within a familiar world.

I truly hope you enjoy the server and I hope to see you in-game one day.
[hr]
[url=https://dl.dropboxusercontent.com/u/107478603/FDTD-v7.zip]https://dl.dropboxusercontent.com/u/107478603/FDTD-v7.zip[/url]
[url=https://dl.dropboxusercontent.com/u/107478603/FDTD-v7.rar]https://dl.dropboxusercontent.com/u/107478603/FDTD-v7.rar[/url]
[url=https://dl.dropboxusercontent.com/u/107478603/FDTD-v7.7z]https://dl.dropboxusercontent.com/u/107478603/FDTD-v7.7z[/url]
[hr]
[b]Features[/b]

[ul][li]All Skills have been re-made to be more interesting, useful, varied and exciting.[/li]
[li]Bring supplies to cities for gold.[/li]
[li]Participate in a city restoration.[/li]
[li]Attack speed stat.[/li]
[li]Counter-attack mechanic based on your defence level.[/li]
[li]Restore the wilderness gateways to get around quicker.[/li]
[li]Find out what the mysterious Abyssal relics are...[/li]
[li]Find out what happens when you activate the temple east of Varrock.[/li]
[li]Find what lurks within Karamja Volcano and Taverley...[/li]
[li]Find the mystery behind why teleport spells don&#39;t work (this is tied to the Dragonslayer subclass).[/li]
[li]Rewarding and interesting world to explore.[/li]
[li]Rewarding gameplay, yields sense of achievement and progress.[/li]
[li]Powerful weapons to discover and create.[/li]
[li]Mysteries, stories and items to find hidden in the world.[/li]
[li]Become one of the 8 subclasses to dramatically improve your playtime and support your playstyle.[/li]
[li]Find yourself playing the role of your subclass, just by accident.[/li]
[li]Meet the dedicated community members who will go out of their way to help you start out.[/li]
[li]Fight one or any amount of the custom-written 15 bosses.[/li]
[li]Discover the utility of various shields and armor in certain situations.[/li]
[li]Become a part of the item-for-item economy, where gold holds nearly no value.[/li]
[li]Speak to a developer who can truly make your ideas become reality.[/li]
[li]Discover foods that you&#39;ve never used in an RSPS before.[/li]
[li]Find yourself doing strange things like cutting mushrooms in a field for some ink or gathering honey to make your cider mature faster...[/li]
[li]Find yourself being proud of your Mithril armor, as you just point and laugh at the city guards puny attacks.[/li]
[li]Enjoy a defense system as you&#39;ve always wanted it to work in a game.[/li][/ul]

[hr]
[b]The TRUE list[/b]
[spoiler]
[ul][li]Firemaking re-written; Normal logs create a fire, Oak logs create a healing field, willow logs yield gold, maple logs yield damage boost, yew logs create a teleport field, magic logs yield runes.[/li]
[li]Smithing re-done; smelting requires logs of a certain quality to maintain the heat within the forge[/li]
[li]Bars can only craft the armor components (chest,helm, shield, legs)[/li]
[li]Dragon armor can be crafted by using a black dragonhide on a workbench (extra items required)[/li]
[li]Scripted Ice Gloves to allow players to hold Living Flame[/li]
[li]Scripted the whip to talk to the player while it is equipped[/li]
[li]Scripted the whip to awaken during battle to deal extra damage[/li]
[li]Scripted the whips equipping sequence[/li]
[li]Scripted the whip to reward the player for killing things[/li]
[li]Scripted Godswords to gain attack speed from certain stats (depending on the god)[/li]
[li]Re-wrote the entire player attack block to allow for very fast attack speeds[/li]
[li]Re-wrote creature attack block to allow for more flag-based attack/stat/counting systems[/li]
[li]Scripted dragon boots to restore Run % faster[/li]
[li]Scripted Boots of Lightness to make the Run % infinite[/li]
[li]Scripted Dragonfire Shield to release a burst of flame upon enemies at random[/li]
[li]Created a whole new creature called: crystallus; he has brutally powerful melee attacks. Shield required.[/li]
[li]Scripted Graador to take more damage, the more of his minions die[/li]
[li]Scripted Armadyl to be annoying as hell[/li]
[li]Scripted Zilyana to Reduce players resistance to holy magic[/li]
[li]Created a Subclass framework, letting players specialize in becoming better at some aspect of the game[/li]
[li]Added 8 subclasses the player can become, each dynamic and wastly different from the other[/li]
[li]Rewrote 80% of the source; naming it &#39;Katana&#39; now.[/li]
[li]Switched to re-sizeable client[/li]
[li]Slayer-level based titles[/li]
[li]Skillful endgame[/li]
[li]Interactive world[/li]
[li]Custom-created Runecrafting, now with 100% more action and murder.[/li]
[li]Custom-created way to obtain GS blades, Dragon Full helms and Dragonfire shields - Players must summon the Lava Forge from within the Wilderness volcano[/li]
[li]The whip is obtained through gathering Abyssal Relics from Dagannoths, then taking them to TzHaar-MejKat who takes the player on a journey[/li]
[li]Scripted teleport spells to depend on a server-wide effect; which can be triggered by a Dragonslayer[/li]
[li]Scripted a custom TzTok-Jad battle; involving 7 elemental tiaras, area damage abilities and explosions.[/li]
[li]Scripted a Necromancy book which summons a Skeletal Wyvern[/li]
[li]Added treasure and secret mechanic to one of the subclasses[/li]
[li]Added herblore, with a whole different approach to how it works[/li]
[li]Changed mining where the tools used will break faster/slower depending on quality of the pickaxe[/li]
[li]Added 15 different bosses, each with a special mechanic[/li]
[li]Added a way to obtain Legends cape by activating the Temple east of Varrock.[/li]
[li]Added a Bard class which can play notes and create combos and chords.[/li]
[li]Added a Quartermaster who issues slayer tasks, rewarding players with Ecto-tokens. They only have to kill 1 of said monster, but the more the better.[/li]
[li]Many different types of foods, effects and ways to obtain them[/li]
[li]Removed prayer and in its stead is &#39;Divination&#39; which is leveled by burying bones; the higher this skill the shorter the subclass cooldowns are going to be.[/li]
[li]Having higher herbalism rewards double amounts of a cut plant.[/li]
[li]100% accurate fishing (albeit adjusted levels and such, to better fit the server thematically)[/li]
[li]Bird Nests[/li]
[li]Godsword special attacks increase attack speed[/li]
[li]Players can obtain a Book of Binding from the very start by going through an elaborate writing process.[/li]
[li]Magic stones are used to upgrade iron ore and enhance various other things[/li]
[li]Dragon Square Shield now absorbs dragonbreath and releases it as healing (doesn&#39;t work against Metal dragons)[/li]
[li]EVERY. SINGLE. MONSTER. the Tracker subclass kills, is saved and with each 5 or so kills; their &#39;mastery&#39; of that monster increases which in effect increases their damage against that monster; (Bronze, Silver, Gold, Platinum, Diamond, Master)[/li]
[li]Swashbuckler subclass ignores all special type attacks (such as magic or dragonfire).[/li]
[li]Swashbucklers use Rapier as a weapon and are incredibly powerful with it. Hitting high amounts from very early on in the game.[/li]
[li]Actual plot underneath all the action within the server.[/li]
[li]Gilded armor can be made via Smithing; the player just needs to obtain &#39;perfect&#39; gold bars.[/li]
[li]Made it so that if a player buys Goldsmith Gauntlets from the shop (250k) they can halve the amount of gold bars needed for gilded.[/li]
[li]Interlinked multiple items, skills, subclasses so that they are continuously useful though-out the progression.[/li]
[li]Implemented EDS - Epic Defense System - where your Defense Level, Buffs, Food, Subclass skills and Armor all together work to reduce damage. (if with 0 defense an attack hits you for 100; at 350 defense same attack hits you for 45)[/li]
[li]Agility increases attack speed (by 0.5 at 99; 0.5 is half a second less between attacks)[/li]
[li]Armor cannot be traded, thus making the server semi-ironman[/li]
[li]Various classes have abilities that affect everyone on the server[/li]
[li]Added a feature which allows people to restore Ardougne and bring its people back to the city; which allows for multiple extra activities.[/li]
[li]Added a function to Shears to be able to cut every single growing piece of fauna found in the world, mushrooms, branches, flowers, thistles - Everything![/li]
[li]Added little mini stories and spread them through-out the world.[/li]
[li]All skillcape emotes.[/li]
[li]Added a zoo where you can feed little animals.[/li]
[li]Added little task-givers through-out the world who request things and reward you with gold or other such nonsense... like feathers.[/li]
[li]Overpowered (yet somehow balanced) weapons.[/li]
[li]0 Pay to win... In fact - 0 pay... in fact - You only win as much as you play![/li]
[li]A mostly command-free experience![/li]
[li]Added a character re-design potion.[/li]
[li]Added little mini events. Such as the battle between PKMasters and the Paladin.[/li]
[li]Truly dedicated developer/coder/creator/owner of the server (all the same person: Me)[/li]
[li]After mid-game has been reached, one can venture into Miscellania for some survival/PK action! Where you&#39;re on an island trying to maintain heat/thirst/hunger at reasonable levels while battling other players.[/li]
[li]The introductory stages shall be re-written in order to help players understand what the server really offers.[/li]
[li]Custom weapon animation system, often weapons use multiple different animations for attacks (especially godswords).[/li]
[li]Perfect mining.[/li]
[li]Basic farming, to allow for gathering of certain highly useful materials.[/li]
[li]Added teleport tablets to allow people to traverse the world a little more.[/li][/ul]
[/spoiler]
[hr]
[b]Story:[/b]
[i]This story begins, as many stories do - with a land. This land is called The Kingdom of Power, this name was placed upon it by its very own inhabitants; from their naive opinion that their kingdom cannot be taken over or otherwise disturbed.
Ages ago, before dragons were re-discovered there was an apocalyptic event... a mad scientist created a device to harvest elements of the land and create runes. These days we find these runes to be normal things, however back in that time; the machine harvested so much energy the world began shattering and unleashing demons from the very depths of the world itself. It is then, when a strange event occurred... Out of nowhere people began appearing and attacking these demons with powers before unseen by the people of the land. By the time the demons were eradicated, the heroes were gone as well... Nobody knew who these heroes were or where they came from... The only thing people knew is that they need to defend themselves.

The biggest minds of the world came together to create a plan... The plan that would become their very own undoing. They started a mission of elemental harvesting... They harvested elemental energies and placed them into Tiaras; this most of the time required torture or even death of captured elementals. 
With time, many of these tiaras were lost or destroyed, however seven of the tiaras remained. These tiaras were sent to the corners of the kingdom and deemed upon those worthy (albeit not necessarily good-spirited) to keep them. Together, the seven tiaras hold the world in balance... In theory, anyway.

And that is where my story ends... and yours begins... You have been granted a vessel of life, an adventurer although you&#39;re but mere dust in this world... Use this vessel to grow powerful, smarter, faster... Then take up arms with those beside you and destroy this kingdom, people of the land and the beasts that guard their secrets... and prevail... They do not deserve peace; they have torn the world apart, imprisoned innocent creatures and tortured the elements for millennia... After all - You are the 8th element... Defiance.

Show. Them. No. Mercy.[/i]


[url=https://dl.dropboxusercontent.com/u/107478603/FDTD-v7.zip]https://dl.dropboxusercontent.com/u/107478603/FDTD-v7.zip[/url]
[url=https://dl.dropboxusercontent.com/u/107478603/FDTD-v7.rar]https://dl.dropboxusercontent.com/u/107478603/FDTD-v7.rar[/url]
[url=https://dl.dropboxusercontent.com/u/107478603/FDTD-v7.7z]https://dl.dropboxusercontent.com/u/107478603/FDTD-v7.7z[/url]

[b]Pictures:[/b]
[img]http://i.imgur.com/XKalPaZ.png[/img]
[img]http://i.imgur.com/j6yOw82.png[/img]
[img]http://i.imgur.com/sQuwRUD.png[/img]
[img]http://i.imgur.com/VXb0bJ5.png[/img]
[img]http://i.imgur.com/H6KvI2S.png[/img]
[img]http://i.imgur.com/FqXVZ5E.png[/img]
[img]http://i.imgur.com/f2XDCf8.png[/img]
[img]http://i.imgur.com/5iCvb5u.png[/img]
[img]http://i.imgur.com/EbsIx4s.png[/img]
[img]http://i.imgur.com/Rqflx9i.png[/img]


[url=https://dl.dropboxusercontent.com/u/107478603/FDTD-v7.zip]https://dl.dropboxusercontent.com/u/107478603/FDTD-v7.zip[/url]
[url=https://dl.dropboxusercontent.com/u/107478603/FDTD-v7.rar]https://dl.dropboxusercontent.com/u/107478603/FDTD-v7.rar[/url]
[url=https://dl.dropboxusercontent.com/u/107478603/FDTD-v7.7z]https://dl.dropboxusercontent.com/u/107478603/FDTD-v7.7z[/url]
[/center]</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 03 Jun 2015 17:49:25 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/fdtd-now-with-pk/539916.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>FDTD - Now with PK!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@fuzzout fuzzout]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/fuzzout">@fuzzout</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Updated the way player actions are handled on the server <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=5" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"><br>
We now use a playerAction(action) system. It makes handling and fixing things much easier ^^</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/fdtd-now-with-pk/539916/114">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/fdtd-now-with-pk/539916/114</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 03 Jun 2015 17:49:25 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-539916-114</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/fdtd-now-with-pk/539916.rss">FDTD - Now with PK!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>FDTD - Now with PK!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Scully Scully]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/scully">@Scully</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Guys the server is great, come check it out.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/fdtd-now-with-pk/539916/113">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/fdtd-now-with-pk/539916/113</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 03 Jun 2015 07:26:47 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-539916-113</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/fdtd-now-with-pk/539916.rss">FDTD - Now with PK!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>FDTD - Now with PK!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@fuzzout fuzzout]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/fuzzout">@fuzzout</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Added the [size=12pt]<span class="bbcode-b">TRUE LIST</span>[/size]<br>
[spoiler]<br>
[ul][li]Firemaking re-written; Normal logs create a fire, Oak logs create a healing field, willow logs yield gold, maple logs yield damage boost, yew logs create a teleport field, magic logs yield runes.[/li]<br>
[li]Smithing re-done; smelting requires logs of a certain quality to maintain the heat within the forge[/li]<br>
[li]Bars can only craft the armor components (chest,helm, shield, legs)[/li]<br>
[li]Dragon armor can be crafted by using a black dragonhide on a workbench (extra items required)[/li]<br>
[li]Scripted Ice Gloves to allow players to hold Living Flame[/li]<br>
[li]Scripted the whip to talk to the player while it is equipped[/li]<br>
[li]Scripted the whip to awaken during battle to deal extra damage[/li]<br>
[li]Scripted the whips equipping sequence[/li]<br>
[li]Scripted the whip to reward the player for killing things[/li]<br>
[li]Scripted Godswords to gain attack speed from certain stats (depending on the god)[/li]<br>
[li]Re-wrote the entire player attack block to allow for very fast attack speeds[/li]<br>
[li]Re-wrote creature attack block to allow for more flag-based attack/stat/counting systems[/li]<br>
[li]Scripted dragon boots to restore Run % faster[/li]<br>
[li]Scripted Boots of Lightness to make the Run % infinite[/li]<br>
[li]Scripted Dragonfire Shield to release a burst of flame upon enemies at random[/li]<br>
[li]Created a whole new creature called: crystallus; he has brutally powerful melee attacks. Shield required.[/li]<br>
[li]Scripted Graador to take more damage, the more of his minions die[/li]<br>
[li]Scripted Armadyl to be annoying as hell[/li]<br>
[li]Scripted Zilyana to Reduce players resistance to holy magic[/li]<br>
[li]Created a Subclass framework, letting players specialize in becoming better at some aspect of the game[/li]<br>
[li]Added 8 subclasses the player can become, each dynamic and wastly different from the other[/li]<br>
[li]Rewrote 80% of the source; naming it ‘Katana’ now.[/li]<br>
[li]Switched to re-sizeable client[/li]<br>
[li]Slayer-level based titles[/li]<br>
[li]Skillful endgame[/li]<br>
[li]Interactive world[/li]<br>
[li]Custom-created Runecrafting, now with 100% more action and murder.[/li]<br>
[li]Custom-created way to obtain GS blades, Dragon Full helms and Dragonfire shields - Players must summon the Lava Forge from within the Wilderness volcano[/li]<br>
[li]The whip is obtained through gathering Abyssal Relics from Dagannoths, then taking them to TzHaar-MejKat who takes the player on a journey[/li]<br>
[li]Scripted teleport spells to depend on a server-wide effect; which can be triggered by a Dragonslayer[/li]<br>
[li]Scripted a custom TzTok-Jad battle; involving 7 elemental tiaras, area damage abilities and explosions.[/li]<br>
[li]Scripted a Necromancy book which summons a Skeletal Wyvern[/li]<br>
[li]Added treasure and secret mechanic to one of the subclasses[/li]<br>
[li]Added herblore, with a whole different approach to how it works[/li]<br>
[li]Changed mining where the tools used will break faster/slower depending on quality of the pickaxe[/li]<br>
[li]Added 15 different bosses, each with a special mechanic[/li]<br>
[li]Added a way to obtain Legends cape by activating the Temple east of Varrock.[/li]<br>
[li]Added a Bard class which can play notes and create combos and chords.[/li]<br>
[li]Added a Quartermaster who issues slayer tasks, rewarding players with Ecto-tokens. They only have to kill 1 of said monster, but the more the better.[/li]<br>
[li]Many different types of foods, effects and ways to obtain them[/li]<br>
[li]Removed prayer and in its stead is ‘Divination’ which is leveled by burying bones; the higher this skill the shorter the subclass cooldowns are going to be.[/li]<br>
[li]Having higher herbalism rewards double amounts of a cut plant.[/li]<br>
[li]100% accurate fishing (albeit adjusted levels and such, to better fit the server thematically)[/li]<br>
[li]Bird Nests[/li]<br>
[li]Godsword special attacks increase attack speed[/li]<br>
[li]Players can obtain a Book of Binding from the very start by going through an elaborate writing process.[/li]<br>
[li]Magic stones are used to upgrade iron ore and enhance various other things[/li]<br>
[li]Dragon Square Shield now absorbs dragonbreath and releases it as healing (doesn’t work against Metal dragons)[/li]<br>
[li]EVERY. SINGLE. MONSTER. the Tracker subclass kills, is saved and with each 5 or so kills; their ‘mastery’ of that monster increases which in effect increases their damage against that monster; (Bronze, Silver, Gold, Platinum, Diamond, Master)[/li]<br>
[li]Swashbuckler subclass ignores all special type attacks (such as magic or dragonfire).[/li]<br>
[li]Swashbucklers use Rapier as a weapon and are incredibly powerful with it. Hitting high amounts from very early on in the game.[/li]<br>
[li]Actual plot underneath all the action within the server.[/li]<br>
[li]Gilded armor can be made via Smithing; the player just needs to obtain ‘perfect’ gold bars.[/li]<br>
[li]Made it so that if a player buys Goldsmith Gauntlets from the shop (250k) they can halve the amount of gold bars needed for gilded.[/li]<br>
[li]Interlinked multiple items, skills, subclasses so that they are continuously useful though-out the progression.[/li]<br>
[li]Implemented EDS - Epic Defense System - where your Defense Level, Buffs, Food, Subclass skills and Armor all together work to reduce damage. (if with 0 defense an attack hits you for 100; at 350 defense same attack hits you for 45)[/li]<br>
[li]Agility increases attack speed (by 0.5 at 99; 0.5 is half a second less between attacks)[/li]<br>
[li]Armor cannot be traded, thus making the server semi-ironman[/li]<br>
[li]Various classes have abilities that affect everyone on the server[/li]<br>
[li]Added a feature which allows people to restore Ardougne and bring its people back to the city; which allows for multiple extra activities.[/li]<br>
[li]Added a function to Shears to be able to cut every single growing piece of fauna found in the world, mushrooms, branches, flowers, thistles - Everything![/li]<br>
[li]Added little mini stories and spread them through-out the world.[/li]<br>
[li]All skillcape emotes.[/li]<br>
[li]Truly dedicated developer/coder/creator/owner of the server (all the same person: Me)[/li]<br>
[li]After mid-game has been reached, one can venture into Miscellania for some survival/PK action! Where you’re on an island trying to maintain heat/thirst/hunger at reasonable levels while battling other players.[/li]<br>
[li]The introductory stages shall be re-written in order to help players understand what the server really offers.[/li]<br>
[li]Custom weapon animation system, often weapons use multiple different animations for attacks (especially godswords).[/li]<br>
[li]Perfect mining.[/li]<br>
[li]Basic farming, to allow for gathering of certain highly useful materials.[/li]<br>
[li]Added teleport tablets to allow people to traverse the world a little more.[/li][/ul]<br>
[/spoiler]</p>
<p>Also Updated the intro <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=5" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"> Now everyone can get a feel for the midgame! <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/smiley.png?v=5" title=":smiley:" class="emoji" alt=":smiley:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/fdtd-now-with-pk/539916/112">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/fdtd-now-with-pk/539916/112</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jun 2015 18:35:28 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-539916-112</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/fdtd-now-with-pk/539916.rss">FDTD - Now with PK!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>FDTD - Now with PK!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@hollynye hollynye]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/hollynye">@hollynye</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Hey very very nice server so much different than most i have ever played you really should check it out im sure ur love it and for those who like pk will love the end game</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/fdtd-now-with-pk/539916/111">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/fdtd-now-with-pk/539916/111</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jun 2015 03:40:17 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-539916-111</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/fdtd-now-with-pk/539916.rss">FDTD - Now with PK!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>FDTD - Now with PK!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@i_dd_s_k0_i i dd s k0 i]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/i_dd_s_k0_i">@i_dd_s_k0_i</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Never experienced such a <span class="bbcode-b">unique</span> server before. It’s not unique because it would have some custom items… no. It’s unique because <span class="bbcode-b">the whole concept is different</span> than any other server. There is a bit of backstory, but mostly there are classes, abilities of these classes, different world approach, more aggressive yet more rewarding. I love it. Try it out people!</p>
<p>I give this server <span class="bbcode-b">9/10.</span></p>
<p>PS: Cut all plants you see. (Yes, you can cut the plants that are there just for decoration in RS or other servers!)</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/fdtd-now-with-pk/539916/110">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/fdtd-now-with-pk/539916/110</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 30 May 2015 19:43:19 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-539916-110</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/fdtd-now-with-pk/539916.rss">FDTD - Now with PK!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>FDTD - Now with PK!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@fuzzout fuzzout]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/fuzzout">@fuzzout</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote" data-post="108" data-topic="539916">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/lil_smok3r/40/5_e05bb34c421432ee4d40de30c10af3e5.png" class="avatar"> Lil_Smok3r:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Honestly rarely play any RSPS nowadays. However this looks pretty cool so might aswell give it a bump <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=5" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"></p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>:o thank you so much! That was a very nice gesture of ya <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=5" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/fdtd-now-with-pk/539916/109">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/fdtd-now-with-pk/539916/109</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 29 May 2015 03:18:19 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-539916-109</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/fdtd-now-with-pk/539916.rss">FDTD - Now with PK!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>FDTD - Now with PK!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@system system]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/system">@system</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Honestly rarely play any RSPS nowadays. However this looks pretty cool so might aswell give it a bump <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=5" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/fdtd-now-with-pk/539916/108">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/fdtd-now-with-pk/539916/108</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 28 May 2015 23:54:56 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-539916-108</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/fdtd-now-with-pk/539916.rss">FDTD - Now with PK!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>FDTD - Now with PK!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@fuzzout fuzzout]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/fuzzout">@fuzzout</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“WarTusk-RSPS, post:106, topic:539916”][quote author=fuzzout link=topic=658767.msg4484244#msg4484244 date=1432838642]<br>
The server is completely free to play, in case anyone is wondering… there are no donations or anything… ever.<br>
[/quote]</p>
<p>My opinion:</p>
<p>Then what is your motivation to keep this online and to keep up to date with the vps? Sure I can understand " I just want players to enjoy my game and that satisfies me. " But that will only drive you so far until later in life you will figure that your time is actually worth money. And that hosting/developing a game that will never accept 1 donation is unrealistic which will lead to you shutting this down which will also waist the players time and work in your game. In these forums people always blow out of proportion “HE SHOWED A LITTLE SHOP ABOUT DONATIONS! THE NERVE! HE IS JUST MONEY HUNGRY AND WANTS A QUICK BUCK!” That is not true what so ever. I agree there is a fine line between a decent amount of advertisement for your donation system and way to much advertisement where it becomes extremely annoying.  But there is nothing wrong what so ever about having a donation system because</p>
<ol>
<li>
<p>you deserve a donation here and there <span class="bbcode-b">if</span> you produced a fun game.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>it gives players an assurance that a buck here and there will help the duration of how long your game stays online. Because if you make at least some money you are going to keep it online to see how much more you can get and it become time/cost effective.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>you might have a job and might be completely fine on funds but paying for advertisements over and over and upgrading your vps and web hosts and e.t.c does add up and purchasing all of that just to get more players who you will never get 1$ from, because you will not take even one donation just will not turn out good. You are eventually going to get sick of purchasing all of this stuff and hosting it just so people can chill on your game for no return what so ever.</p>
</li>
</ol>
<p>Just look at other top games. Find a way that you can balance the donation system so players have a desire to donate for it but at the same time where it is not a necessity for players who just cannot donate. (cosmetics is usually a really good way to go)</p>
<p>Maybe since this is your own game try adding expansions (in a sense) where you can unlock new lands and fight other types of monsters and do other quests and other fun activities for players to do that will not ruin your balance. It’s your own game you can think of some sweet stuff just use your imagination!</p>
<p>Your game looks fun continue the hard work and keep it up! I am excited to see your further development hosting your own game and see how everything turns out![/quote]</p>
<p>You know, you are amazing. Thank you so much for your comment (and I’m sorry for how little thought I had put into my last comment… that was… I don’t even know why I wrote that <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/smiley.png?v=5" title=":smiley:" class="emoji" alt=":smiley:"> it is true though).</p>
<p>I understand the concern. The thing is, I just… eh… I don’t feel something THIS simple deserves money; Yes it costs money to keep it up. The thing is… I’m a creator… I create things; I don’t want anything back… Often hobbies cost money; this is my hobby… and other than the hosting costs; the hobby is very cheap; it keeps me happy, expressed… and clear-minded.</p>
<p>It was in fact being hosted from my PC up until earlier today; I quietly switched over to a VPS and nobody noticed.<br>
This will come out cheaper than hosting it at home (because lol my PC is a monster, eats the universe in electric)… It will also make the server more stable and bring its uptime back to 100% (the pc died one morning while I was at work x,x was unable to fix until got home, dropped me to 99% uptime).</p>
<p>Anyways… I keep losing track of the topic:<br>
As stated above, its my hobby… people have expensive hobbies like stamp collecting or horse riding or mountain climbing… all of those cost way more money than my simple method of expression… I accept the little bit that this costs me.<br>
I know myself, I trust myself… The server will remain online.</p>
<p>–<br>
Last thought on the donation topic:<br>
I just… I don’t want to. I don’t want to become the very thing I despise right now… I don’t want entitled people. I want people to be the same as everyone else; all equal; playing, working together and discussing how best to beat this brutal game that’s got them trapped in Varrock.</p>
<p>That is why I removed PK from the server<br>
That is why I never added donations<br>
That is why I didn’t give everyone full bandos, 99s and 999m gp on login…</p>
<p>To keep everyone level-headed and friendly… And if you play here, that is what you will encounter… you will understand… discover… discuss and explore.</p>
<p>Thank you once again for your amazing comment, I wish you an amazing day. You deserve one.</p>
<p>-Fuzzout</p>
<p>Late edit:<br>
In one word: It’s passion that drives me. I just … I just want to create a world and watch people enjoy it, see what they do within and with it. I like being creative and my reward is seeing how others view it.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/fdtd-now-with-pk/539916/107">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/fdtd-now-with-pk/539916/107</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 28 May 2015 19:28:17 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-539916-107</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/fdtd-now-with-pk/539916.rss">FDTD - Now with PK!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>FDTD - Now with PK!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@WarTusk-RSPS WarTusk-RSPS]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/wartusk-rsps">@WarTusk-RSPS</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote" data-post="105" data-topic="539916">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/fuzzout/40/5_e05bb34c421432ee4d40de30c10af3e5.png" class="avatar"> fuzzout:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>The server is completely free to play, in case anyone is wondering… there are no donations or anything… ever.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>My opinion:</p>
<p>Then what is your motivation to keep this online and to keep up to date with the vps? Sure I can understand " I just want players to enjoy my game and that satisfies me. " But that will only drive you so far until later in life you will figure that your time is actually worth money. And that hosting/developing a game that will never accept 1 donation is unrealistic which will lead to you shutting this down which will also waist the players time and work in your game. In these forums people always blow out of proportion “HE SHOWED A LITTLE SHOP ABOUT DONATIONS! THE NERVE! HE IS JUST MONEY HUNGRY AND WANTS A QUICK BUCK!” That is not true what so ever. I agree there is a fine line between a decent amount of advertisement for your donation system and way to much advertisement where it becomes extremely annoying.  But there is nothing wrong what so ever about having a donation system because</p>
<ol>
<li>
<p>you deserve a donation here and there <span class="bbcode-b">if</span> you produced a fun game.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>it gives players an assurance that a buck here and there will help the duration of how long your game stays online. Because if you make at least some money you are going to keep it online to see how much more you can get and it become time/cost effective.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>you might have a job and might be completely fine on funds but paying for advertisements over and over and upgrading your vps and web hosts and e.t.c does add up and purchasing all of that just to get more players who you will never get 1$ from, because you will not take even one donation just will not turn out good. You are eventually going to get sick of purchasing all of this stuff and hosting it just so people can chill on your game for no return what so ever.</p>
</li>
</ol>
<p>Just look at other top games. Find a way that you can balance the donation system so players have a desire to donate for it but at the same time where it is not a necessity for players who just cannot donate. (cosmetics is usually a really good way to go)</p>
<p>Maybe since this is your own game try adding expansions (in a sense) where you can unlock new lands and fight other types of monsters and do other quests and other fun activities for players to do that will not ruin your balance. It’s your own game you can think of some sweet stuff just use your imagination!</p>
<p>Your game looks fun continue the hard work and keep it up! I am excited to see your further development hosting your own game and see how everything turns out!</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/fdtd-now-with-pk/539916/106">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/fdtd-now-with-pk/539916/106</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 28 May 2015 19:13:41 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-539916-106</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/fdtd-now-with-pk/539916.rss">FDTD - Now with PK!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>FDTD - Now with PK!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@fuzzout fuzzout]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/fuzzout">@fuzzout</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>The server is completely free to play, in case anyone is wondering… there are no donations or anything… ever.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/fdtd-now-with-pk/539916/105">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/fdtd-now-with-pk/539916/105</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 28 May 2015 18:44:02 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-539916-105</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/fdtd-now-with-pk/539916.rss">FDTD - Now with PK!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>FDTD - Now with PK!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Rs3advanced Rs3advanced]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/rs3advanced">@Rs3advanced</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Bumping! New Advertisement in the original post! Join now!</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/fdtd-now-with-pk/539916/104">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/fdtd-now-with-pk/539916/104</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 27 May 2015 23:48:44 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-539916-104</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/fdtd-now-with-pk/539916.rss">FDTD - Now with PK!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>FDTD - Now with PK!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@fuzzout fuzzout]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/fuzzout">@fuzzout</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I just updated the original post with brand new information, a new video and… stuff <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=5" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
<p>And thank you everyone for your good comments <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=5" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/fdtd-now-with-pk/539916/103">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/fdtd-now-with-pk/539916/103</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 27 May 2015 20:41:49 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-539916-103</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/fdtd-now-with-pk/539916.rss">FDTD - Now with PK!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>FDTD - Now with PK!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Ykcud Ykcud]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/ykcud">@Ykcud</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>This is a very interesting and unique server. I enjoyed what little time I spent on it, but was unable to continue as my computer is rather sensitive and this server is too intensive on it to play it for any extensive amount of time. I wish the owner(s), the server and community the best of luck.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/fdtd-now-with-pk/539916/102">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/fdtd-now-with-pk/539916/102</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 27 May 2015 19:30:35 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-539916-102</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/fdtd-now-with-pk/539916.rss">FDTD - Now with PK!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>FDTD - Now with PK!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Rs3advanced Rs3advanced]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/rs3advanced">@Rs3advanced</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Bumping this thread for interest! Everyone join for an awesome, challenging, yet rewarding experience!</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/fdtd-now-with-pk/539916/101">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/fdtd-now-with-pk/539916/101</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 27 May 2015 08:32:43 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-539916-101</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/fdtd-now-with-pk/539916.rss">FDTD - Now with PK!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>FDTD - Now with PK!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@fuzzout fuzzout]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/fuzzout">@fuzzout</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I have severely improved the tutorial <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=5" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"> Hopefully people will find it easier to get around now! <em>certainly took my time doing that x,x</em></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/fdtd-now-with-pk/539916/100">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/fdtd-now-with-pk/539916/100</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 18 May 2015 10:19:06 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-539916-100</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/fdtd-now-with-pk/539916.rss">FDTD - Now with PK!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>FDTD - Now with PK!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@YumYum YumYum]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/yumyum">@YumYum</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>looks cool</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/fdtd-now-with-pk/539916/99">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/fdtd-now-with-pk/539916/99</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 17 May 2015 16:12:06 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-539916-99</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/fdtd-now-with-pk/539916.rss">FDTD - Now with PK!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>FDTD - Now with PK!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@fuzzout fuzzout]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/fuzzout">@fuzzout</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote" data-post="97" data-topic="539916">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/cres/40/5_e05bb34c421432ee4d40de30c10af3e5.png" class="avatar"> Cres:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>can’t connect for some reason</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I’m terribly sorry to hear that… With the new client I’ve taken all the measures I could to ensure connectivity. So I’m afraid I don’t know what’s causing that <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/frowning.png?v=5" title=":frowning:" class="emoji" alt=":frowning:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/fdtd-now-with-pk/539916/98">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/fdtd-now-with-pk/539916/98</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 16 May 2015 01:12:21 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-539916-98</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/fdtd-now-with-pk/539916.rss">FDTD - Now with PK!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>FDTD - Now with PK!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Cres Cres]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/cres">@Cres</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>can’t connect for some reason</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/fdtd-now-with-pk/539916/97">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/fdtd-now-with-pk/539916/97</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 May 2015 21:00:28 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-539916-97</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/fdtd-now-with-pk/539916.rss">FDTD - Now with PK!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>FDTD - Now with PK!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Scully Scully]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/scully">@Scully</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Bamp!</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/fdtd-now-with-pk/539916/96">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/fdtd-now-with-pk/539916/96</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 May 2015 19:06:23 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-539916-96</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/fdtd-now-with-pk/539916.rss">FDTD - Now with PK!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>FDTD - Now with PK!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@fuzzout fuzzout]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/fuzzout">@fuzzout</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Dragonslayer class is amazing <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/smiley.png?v=5" title=":smiley:" class="emoji" alt=":smiley:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/fdtd-now-with-pk/539916/95">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/fdtd-now-with-pk/539916/95</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 13 May 2015 17:29:17 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-539916-95</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/fdtd-now-with-pk/539916.rss">FDTD - Now with PK!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>FDTD - Now with PK!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Kiryn Kiryn]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/kiryn">@Kiryn</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Come join and be one of the many to experience the epic and powerful class of: Dragonslayer  :eek:</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/fdtd-now-with-pk/539916/94">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/fdtd-now-with-pk/539916/94</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 12 May 2015 20:50:18 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-539916-94</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/fdtd-now-with-pk/539916.rss">FDTD - Now with PK!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>FDTD - Now with PK!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Scully Scully]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/scully">@Scully</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I’m supposed to bump this or something!</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/fdtd-now-with-pk/539916/93">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/fdtd-now-with-pk/539916/93</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 12 May 2015 20:49:34 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-539916-93</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/fdtd-now-with-pk/539916.rss">FDTD - Now with PK!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>FDTD - Now with PK!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@fuzzout fuzzout]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/fuzzout">@fuzzout</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p><span class="bbcode-i">An update has gone live:</span><br>
[size=14pt]<span class="bbcode-b">RISE OF THE DRAGONSLAYER!</span>[/size]<br>
Implemented a fever system<br>
Fixed the issue with godwars bosses bugging players out and not letting them die (‘You can die when I give you<br>
my permission to die… mwahahaaa…haa… Mr Wayne.’)<br>
Implemented a simple damage buff system with a timer<br>
Implemented a simple defense buff system with a timer<br>
Added all the necessary fire dragonslayers effects to attack functions where required<br>
Added all fire dragonslayer spells (no animations as of yet)<br>
Added all water dragonslayer spells (no animations as of yet)<br>
Added better defense calculations (now includes your defense level)<br>
Added a few extra functions for healing nearby players (to serve different purposes)<em>-will re-write later<br>
Added a cooldown to bards notes<br>
Somewhat patched the spazzy fishing animations (not great, yet…)<br>
Implemented the correct fishing animations for certain spots<br>
Completely finished up Dragonslayer class</em>-there WILL be balance updates for this<br>
Added a log-write for everyone who becomes a dragonslayer (to see who’s first)<br>
Fixed Drill Sergeants intro<br>
Went to sleep for 2 hours <em>noteworthy</em><br>
Added notifications specifically for Fuzzout of certain events taking place on the server.<br>
Engineer subclass exp requirements have been removed<br>
Reduced subclass exp requirement for highest subclass abilities to 300.<br>
Reduced other subclass ability requirements in sequence to the above adjustment (300, 200, 100).<br>
Added dragonslayers necessities to the save files<br>
Resolved a few mis-alignments and mis-counts, causing re-logging dragonslayers to lag out<br>
Re-worked the original design of the class<br>
Tweaked attack code to allow for future functionality<br>
Tweaked defense code to allow damage immunity<br>
Expanded skillname containers (used by the subclass framework) to accomodate for Dragonslayer<br>
Fixed Chronozon’s summoning function (the new client had changed the object ID of the altar)<br>
Fixed a logical error with one of the new skills<br>
Re-implemented teleport spells (with a condition that must be met)<br>
Fixed cooldown indicators on skill interfaces</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/fdtd-now-with-pk/539916/92">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/fdtd-now-with-pk/539916/92</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 12 May 2015 16:54:39 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-539916-92</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/fdtd-now-with-pk/539916.rss">FDTD - Now with PK!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>FDTD - Now with PK!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Scully Scully]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/scully">@Scully</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>The server is still fun and everything after all this time. Glad to see it back online.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/fdtd-now-with-pk/539916/91">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/fdtd-now-with-pk/539916/91</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 12 May 2015 01:16:14 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-539916-91</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/fdtd-now-with-pk/539916.rss">FDTD - Now with PK!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>FDTD - Now with PK!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@fuzzout fuzzout]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/fuzzout">@fuzzout</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>We had 6 people online :o… Shame they all kinda logged out later on XD</p>
<p>Not me though! I’m there 24/7.</p>
<p>Other than that… we have a roadmap… it has stuff… :3</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/fdtd-now-with-pk/539916/90">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/fdtd-now-with-pk/539916/90</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 11 May 2015 02:08:09 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-539916-90</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/fdtd-now-with-pk/539916.rss">FDTD - Now with PK!</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
