<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>RS PI Background Change HELP!</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rs-pi-background-change-help/520954</link>
    <description>Ok so for about 4 hours now I have been trying to change the background on my client it is a PI base and I believe it is cache packed as changing the background image in sprites doesn&#39;t work so I downloaded toms cache editor and looked on a few tutorials I changed the title.dat in Jagex archives but that didnt do anything also I cant find the background image looking through the cache so I am not sure if my background is changeable or not or if I am just being a noob and looking in the wrong place. I have been searching forums and videos all night and haven&#39;t been able to solve this problem I have little experience in coding as I just started a few days ago but I need this fixed any help is appreciated and if you need me to post anything like my cache I will because I need this fixed. I see alot of people giving rep++ to people who help them so I will give that if I can im not sure if you need a certain number of posts for that ( I am also a forum noob) all help is greatly appreciated and thank you for even reading this far I will be checking this post constantly as I am extremely desperate.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 07 Jun 2013 20:16:28 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Game Development</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rs-pi-background-change-help/520954.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>RS PI Background Change HELP!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Bhpk Bhpk]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/bhpk">@Bhpk</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I’ll help you out with your Project Insanity Source/Client.</p>
<p>What it does: Change’s your Project Insanity Client background</p>
<p>So, let’s start!<br>
Go to Client folder&gt;‘Then open’&gt;Client.java (Now we can begin)<br>
Search for</p>
<pre><code class="lang-auto"></code></pre>
<p>comment it out with ‘//’ or if you don’t really get it replace it with this</p>
<pre><code class="lang-auto"></code></pre>
<p>Now search for this again</p>
<pre><code class="lang-auto"></code></pre>
<p>and do what I said above! You have now gotten ridden of the flames!<br>
Now time to get rid of the big RuneScape logo in the background.<br>
Still in Client.java search for</p>
<pre><code class="lang-auto"></code></pre>
<p>and comment it out like so</p>
<pre><code class="lang-auto"></code></pre>
<p>or delete it!<br>
Now open up Sprite.java and search for</p>
<pre><code class="lang-auto"></code></pre>
<p>replace that with this</p>
<pre><code class="lang-auto"></code></pre>
<p>Now still in Sprite.java search for</p>
<pre><code class="lang-auto"></code></pre>
<p>and delete it! Now we need to add your background image, so go into your Sprites folder and put your background picture, also make sure that it is a .jpg or .jpeg image or it will not work!</p>
<p>Enjoy.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rs-pi-background-change-help/520954/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rs-pi-background-change-help/520954/2</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 07 Jun 2013 20:16:28 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-520954-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rs-pi-background-change-help/520954.rss">RS PI Background Change HELP!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>RS PI Background Change HELP!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Tassos Tassos]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/tassos">@Tassos</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Ok so for about 4 hours now I have been trying to change the background on my client it is a PI base and I believe it is cache packed as changing the background image in sprites doesn’t work so I downloaded toms cache editor and looked on a few tutorials I changed the title.dat in Jagex archives but that didnt do anything also I cant find the background image looking through the cache so I am not sure if my background is changeable or not or if I am just being a noob and looking in the wrong place. I have been searching forums and videos all night and haven’t been able to solve this problem I have little experience in coding as I just started a few days ago but I need this fixed any help is appreciated and if you need me to post anything like my cache I will because I need this fixed. I see alot of people giving rep++ to people who help them so I will give that if I can im not sure if you need a certain number of posts for that ( I am also a forum noob) all help is greatly appreciated and thank you for even reading this far I will be checking this post constantly as I am extremely desperate.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rs-pi-background-change-help/520954/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rs-pi-background-change-help/520954/1</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 07 Jun 2013 02:13:33 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-520954-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rs-pi-background-change-help/520954.rss">RS PI Background Change HELP!</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
