<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>.jar error right after I jar&#39;ed it</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/jar-error-right-after-i-jared-it/552618</link>
    <description>This is 667 Project Poanizer and when I jar&#39;ed it, when I try to run it, it says me this. I&#39;ve searched everywhere and nothing that can fix it. I changed everything from 127.0.0.1 to my no-ip address, I portforwarded, my source is running and canyouseeme.org says my port is open. You&#39;d be a life saver if you can help me fix it. In the comments, tell me what .java file you want to see and I&#39;ll show it or add me on skype and we could teamviewer. I&#39;m kind of tired of errors on this source; it&#39;s the 8th I fixed and I had to figure them out myself. I don&#39;t know what NullPointerException is or what the error means. So contact me on skype at sakoofortin and I&#39;ll give you my teamviewer info from there or just tell me in the comments what file you want to see :)

Thanks! :D

Error:</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 24 Jul 2015 01:46:11 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Game Development</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/jar-error-right-after-i-jared-it/552618.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>.jar error right after I jar&#39;ed it</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@sakoo99 sakoo99]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/sakoo99">@sakoo99</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>This is 667 Project Poanizer and when I jar’ed it, when I try to run it, it says me this. I’ve searched everywhere and nothing that can fix it. I changed everything from 127.0.0.1 to my no-ip address, I portforwarded, my source is running and <a href="http://canyouseeme.org" rel="nofollow noopener">canyouseeme.org</a> says my port is open. You’d be a life saver if you can help me fix it. In the comments, tell me what .java file you want to see and I’ll show it or add me on skype and we could teamviewer. I’m kind of tired of errors on this source; it’s the 8th I fixed and I had to figure them out myself. I don’t know what NullPointerException is or what the error means. So contact me on skype at sakoofortin and I’ll give you my teamviewer info from there or just tell me in the comments what file you want to see <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=5" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
<p>Thanks! <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/smiley.png?v=5" title=":smiley:" class="emoji" alt=":smiley:"></p>
<p>Error:</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/jar-error-right-after-i-jared-it/552618/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/jar-error-right-after-i-jared-it/552618/1</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 24 Jul 2015 01:46:11 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-552618-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/jar-error-right-after-i-jared-it/552618.rss">.jar error right after I jar&#39;ed it</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
