<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Justin&#39;s Official RSPS Critic Service</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/justins-official-rsps-critic-service/547774</link>
    <description>[center]Hello, have you ever played a RuneScape Private Server and thought to yourself, &quot;This is boring&quot; , &quot;There is nothing unique&quot;, or &quot;Man, I wish I could get into this server more....&quot;? I know I have, and this is how I thought of dealing with this problem. A critic service. I know that this is only my first post, that&#39;s because I usually just lurked around here and just looked for servers to play but that ends now.

Why I am doing this[spoiler]I have played many a server in my day(around 200+) and only a few have been interesting enough for me to continue playing. Now I know that I may like different types of servers than all of you. I&#39;ll tell you my ideal type of server: An Economy sever where the players make the economy(that means no weapons and armors in shops past the black/white levels), XP rate kind of low but not too low, for people to work to get 99&#39;s but not work for weeks for 99&#39;s. Full Fight caves and(if possible) Fight Kiln. Achievements with rewards. A low to medium player base(3-25+ players online, but more or less is cool also), etc. That&#39;s my ideal server and I know that some of you disagree with me but I have played all types of servers: Faction Based, Economy, PvP, PvM, Zombie Survival, name it I&#39;ve most likely played it. I have noticed tons of flaws that could make a bad server good if they were to fix.[/spoiler]

Who is this for?[spoiler]This is primarily for people who haven&#39;t released their server yet but can also be for servers that want to be improved.[/spoiler]

How It Works[spoiler]
1). Add me on Skype(JayZizzlr) And ask me to critic your server
2). Allow me to join the server you want criticized
3). I will then ask you the basics(refer to the Basic Questions below)
4). If I feel it&#39;s necessary or if I&#39;m impressed I will ask some more higher level questions
5). After all the questions have been asked and answered I will then look for some common bugs and exploits
6). After going over the bugs found if any I will then scale the server on 3 levels

Look below for the scaling system[/spoiler]

Basic Questions[spoiler]
1). What source is this base off of?
2). What are some &quot;unique&quot; features?
3). What skills are currently available/unavailable
4). What type of server is this? (Pk, Economy, etc.)
5). Why did you decide to make a Rsps? (This is big deal, and please be honest.)

When answering these questions please be honest and professional.[/spoiler]

The Scaling System[spoiler]
The servers will be on a scale of 3 categories and an overall. The three categories goes as follows: Accessibility, Continuity Factor, and Uniqueness. Along with an overall.

1). Accessibility- How easy it is to get around the server i.e where the teleports(if any are), where the shops are located, how to get around the world if its more of an actual RS thing(such as Arios).

2). Continuity Factor- Now, many people will get me when I say this, when I play a rsps I sometimes get to the point were I log off and cannot play it for a while because it&#39;s so boring. This category is based on how long I can play before I get bored and want to log off to find a more fun and played for hours server.

3). Uniqueness- I have been saying Unique a lot in this thread. That&#39;s because is is one of the most important aspects of a RSPS. When I log into a RSPS and notice it&#39;s just a complete rip off another server with just a name change I get angry. That&#39;s not why the source was released. It was released to get people a starting point in which to expand on there server, not to be an exact replica with a different name.

4). Overall- you know what this is. A simple tally on all of the above into a total points sort of thing.[/spoiler]

How Much Does This Cost?[spoiler]This is 100% COMPLETELY FREE. Why would anyone ask for money for this?[/spoiler]

Some notes on what I might need[spoiler]
1). At the moment the only thing I need is access to the ;;bank command for a certain bug/exploit[/spoiler]

Well, that&#39;s about all I can say, This is meant to help newer servers become popular not known as a one-off to players. I hope you enjoyed reading and if you want me to review your server, contact me through Skype: JayZizzlr and I&#39;ll get back to you as soon as I an able to.[/center]</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2014 01:57:52 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/justins-official-rsps-critic-service/547774.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Justin&#39;s Official RSPS Critic Service</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@dragger dragger]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/dragger">@dragger</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“Slave., post:2, topic:547774”]is this in the right spot?[/quote]I honestly couldn’t tell you. I thought that this would be the best place to put this in, if someones disagrees feel free to move this.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/justins-official-rsps-critic-service/547774/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/justins-official-rsps-critic-service/547774/3</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2014 01:57:52 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-547774-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/justins-official-rsps-critic-service/547774.rss">Justin&#39;s Official RSPS Critic Service</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Justin&#39;s Official RSPS Critic Service</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Slave2 Slave.]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/slave2">@Slave2</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>is this in the right spot?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/justins-official-rsps-critic-service/547774/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/justins-official-rsps-critic-service/547774/2</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 12 Nov 2014 11:30:34 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-547774-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/justins-official-rsps-critic-service/547774.rss">Justin&#39;s Official RSPS Critic Service</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Justin&#39;s Official RSPS Critic Service</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@dragger dragger]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/dragger">@dragger</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[center]Hello, have you ever played a RuneScape Private Server and thought to yourself, “This is boring” , “There is nothing unique”, or “Man, I wish I could get into this server more…”? I know I have, and this is how I thought of dealing with this problem. A critic service. I know that this is only my first post, that’s because I usually just lurked around here and just looked for servers to play but that ends now.</p>
<p>Why I am doing this[spoiler]I have played many a server in my day(around 200+) and only a few have been interesting enough for me to continue playing. Now I know that I may like different types of servers than all of you. I’ll tell you my ideal type of server: An Economy sever where the players make the economy(that means no weapons and armors in shops past the black/white levels), XP rate kind of low but not too low, for people to work to get 99’s but not work for weeks for 99’s. Full Fight caves and(if possible) Fight Kiln. Achievements with rewards. A low to medium player base(3-25+ players online, but more or less is cool also), etc. That’s my ideal server and I know that some of you disagree with me but I have played all types of servers: Faction Based, Economy, PvP, PvM, Zombie Survival, name it I’ve most likely played it. I have noticed tons of flaws that could make a bad server good if they were to fix.[/spoiler]</p>
<p>Who is this for?[spoiler]This is primarily for people who haven’t released their server yet but can also be for servers that want to be improved.[/spoiler]</p>
<p>How It Works[spoiler]<br>
1). Add me on Skype(JayZizzlr) And ask me to critic your server<br>
2). Allow me to join the server you want criticized<br>
3). I will then ask you the basics(refer to the Basic Questions below)<br>
4). If I feel it’s necessary or if I’m impressed I will ask some more higher level questions<br>
5). After all the questions have been asked and answered I will then look for some common bugs and exploits<br>
6). After going over the bugs found if any I will then scale the server on 3 levels</p>
<p>Look below for the scaling system[/spoiler]</p>
<p>Basic Questions[spoiler]<br>
1). What source is this base off of?<br>
2). What are some “unique” features?<br>
3). What skills are currently available/unavailable<br>
4). What type of server is this? (Pk, Economy, etc.)<br>
5). Why did you decide to make a Rsps? (This is big deal, and please be honest.)</p>
<p>When answering these questions please be honest and professional.[/spoiler]</p>
<p>The Scaling System[spoiler]<br>
The servers will be on a scale of 3 categories and an overall. The three categories goes as follows: Accessibility, Continuity Factor, and Uniqueness. Along with an overall.</p>
<p>1). Accessibility- How easy it is to get around the server i.e where the teleports(if any are), where the shops are located, how to get around the world if its more of an actual RS thing(such as Arios).</p>
<p>2). Continuity Factor- Now, many people will get me when I say this, when I play a rsps I sometimes get to the point were I log off and cannot play it for a while because it’s so boring. This category is based on how long I can play before I get bored and want to log off to find a more fun and played for hours server.</p>
<p>3). Uniqueness- I have been saying Unique a lot in this thread. That’s because is is one of the most important aspects of a RSPS. When I log into a RSPS and notice it’s just a complete rip off another server with just a name change I get angry. That’s not why the source was released. It was released to get people a starting point in which to expand on there server, not to be an exact replica with a different name.</p>
<p>4). Overall- you know what this is. A simple tally on all of the above into a total points sort of thing.[/spoiler]</p>
<p>How Much Does This Cost?[spoiler]This is 100% COMPLETELY FREE. Why would anyone ask for money for this?[/spoiler]</p>
<p>Some notes on what I might need[spoiler]<br>
1). At the moment the only thing I need is access to the ;;bank command for a certain bug/exploit[/spoiler]</p>
<p>Well, that’s about all I can say, This is meant to help newer servers become popular not known as a one-off to players. I hope you enjoyed reading and if you want me to review your server, contact me through Skype: JayZizzlr and I’ll get back to you as soon as I an able to.[/center]</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/justins-official-rsps-critic-service/547774/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/justins-official-rsps-critic-service/547774/1</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2014 20:41:16 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-547774-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/justins-official-rsps-critic-service/547774.rss">Justin&#39;s Official RSPS Critic Service</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
