<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Having Trouble</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/having-trouble/219397</link>
    <description>Hey Guys,
I wanted to try Moparscape out today, just make a local server and use console commands to achieve everything I never could in ordinary Runescape. :D  I downloaded and installed the standard install package &quot;MoparScape 3.2 w/ Aryan installer.&quot;  I got it installed fine, ran the batch file, and was able to sucessfully create and play a local game.  I encountered 2 major problems that I need help with:

1. I tried to enter the members world, but the gate wouldn&#39;t open. I used the noclip command to access it, and there were no NPCs or monsters! - How do I enable the members word, if possible?

2. Upon logging out and stopping the moparscape client, then logging back in later, my character&#39;s settings and items are gone! Isn&#39;t this supposed to be saved locally?

Thanks in advance.

EDIT: I now realize that all NPCs are nonexistent (except for shopkeepers) and that all gates, chests and other objects can not be interacted with... is this to be expected, or do I need to do something special to get it to work?</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 12 Jul 2008 00:25:21 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/having-trouble/219397.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Having Trouble</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@whiskey_pete whiskey pete]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/whiskey_pete">@whiskey_pete</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Hey Guys,<br>
I wanted to try Moparscape out today, just make a local server and use console commands to achieve everything I never could in ordinary Runescape. <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/smiley.png?v=6" title=":smiley:" class="emoji" alt=":smiley:">  I downloaded and installed the standard install package “MoparScape 3.2 w/ Aryan installer.”  I got it installed fine, ran the batch file, and was able to sucessfully create and play a local game.  I encountered 2 major problems that I need help with:</p>
<ol>
<li>
<p>I tried to enter the members world, but the gate wouldn’t open. I used the noclip command to access it, and there were no NPCs or monsters! - How do I enable the members word, if possible?</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Upon logging out and stopping the moparscape client, then logging back in later, my character’s settings and items are gone! Isn’t this supposed to be saved locally?</p>
</li>
</ol>
<p>Thanks in advance.</p>
<p>EDIT: I now realize that all NPCs are nonexistent (except for shopkeepers) and that all gates, chests and other objects can not be interacted with… is this to be expected, or do I need to do something special to get it to work?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/having-trouble/219397/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/having-trouble/219397/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 12 Jul 2008 00:25:21 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-219397-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/having-trouble/219397.rss">Having Trouble</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
