<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>72 Hours to End the War on Drugs</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/72-hours-to-end-the-war-on-drugs/397317</link>
    <description>In 72 hours, we could finally see the beginning of the end of the ‘war on drugs’. This expensive war has completely failed to curb the plague of drug addiction, while costing countless lives, devastating communities, and funneling trillions of dollars into violent organized crime networks. 

Experts all agree that the most sensible policy is to regulate, but politicians are afraid to touch the issue. In 72 hours, a global commission including former heads of state and foreign policy chiefs of the UN, EU, US, Brazil, Mexico and more will break the taboo and publicly call for new approaches including decriminalization and regulation of drugs.

This could be a once-in-a-generation tipping-point moment -- if enough of us call for an end to this madness. Politicians say they understand that the war on drugs has failed, but claim the public isn&#39;t ready for an alternative. Let&#39;s show them we not only accept a sane and humane policy -- we demand it. Sign the petition and share with everyone -- when we reach 1/2 million voices, it will be personally delivered to world leaders by the global commission.

For 50 years current drug policies have failed everyone, everywhere but public debate is stuck in the mud of fear and misinformation. Everyone, even the UN Office on Drugs and Crime which is responsible for enforcing this approach agrees -- deploying militaries and police to burn drug farms, hunting down traffickers, and imprisoning dealers and addicts – is an expensive mistake. And with massive human cost -- from Afghanistan, to Mexico, to the USA the illegal drug trade is destroying countries around the world, while addiction, overdose deaths, and HIV/AIDS infections continue to rise.

Meanwhile, countries with less-harsh enforcement -- like Switzerland, Portugal, the Netherlands, and Australia -- have not seen the explosion in drug use that proponents of the drug war have darkly predicted. Instead, they have seen significant reductions in drug-related crime, addiction and deaths, and are able to focus squarely on dismantling criminal empires. 

Powerful lobbies still stand in the way of change, including military, law enforcement, and prison departments whose budgets are at stake. And politicians fear that voters will throw them out of office if they support alternative approaches, as they will appear weak on law and order. But many former drug Ministers and Heads of State have come out in favour of reform since leaving office, and polls show that citizens across the world know the current approach is a catastrophe. Momentum is gathering towards new improved policies, particularly in regions that are ravaged by the drug trade.

If we can create a worldwide outcry in the 72 hours to support the bold calls of the Global Commission on Drug Policy, we can overpower the stale excuses for the status quo. Our voices hold the key to change -- Sign the petition and spread the word.

We have a chance to enter the closing chapter of this brutal &#39;war&#39; that has destroyed millions of lives. Global public opinion will determine if this catastrophic policy is stopped or if politicians shy away from reform. Let&#39;s rally urgently to push our hesitating leaders from doubt and fear, over the edge, and into reason.

http://www.avaaz.org/en/end_the_war_on_drugs_a/</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 01 Jun 2011 13:34:39 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>General Discussion</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/72-hours-to-end-the-war-on-drugs/397317.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>72 Hours to End the War on Drugs</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@goatee goatee]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/goatee">@goatee</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote" data-post="6" data-topic="397317">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 mutex_:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>africa probably <span class="bbcode-b">il</span>legal lol</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/72-hours-to-end-the-war-on-drugs/397317/7">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/72-hours-to-end-the-war-on-drugs/397317/7</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jun 2011 13:34:39 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-397317-7</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/72-hours-to-end-the-war-on-drugs/397317.rss">72 Hours to End the War on Drugs</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>72 Hours to End the War on Drugs</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@z z]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/z">@z</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>africa probably <span class="bbcode-b">il</span>legal lol</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/72-hours-to-end-the-war-on-drugs/397317/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/72-hours-to-end-the-war-on-drugs/397317/6</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jun 2011 09:10:45 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-397317-6</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/72-hours-to-end-the-war-on-drugs/397317.rss">72 Hours to End the War on Drugs</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>72 Hours to End the War on Drugs</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@gothic_queen casey.]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/gothic_queen">@gothic_queen</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Floridia, oh boy. Cops arrest you for .3.</p>
<p>It’s bad down here.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/72-hours-to-end-the-war-on-drugs/397317/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/72-hours-to-end-the-war-on-drugs/397317/5</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jun 2011 05:24:24 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-397317-5</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/72-hours-to-end-the-war-on-drugs/397317.rss">72 Hours to End the War on Drugs</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>72 Hours to End the War on Drugs</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@mwiebelhaus mwiebelhaus]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/mwiebelhaus">@mwiebelhaus</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Yeah omaha, nebraska is where I live! You have a have an once of weed and only receive a fine.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/72-hours-to-end-the-war-on-drugs/397317/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/72-hours-to-end-the-war-on-drugs/397317/4</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jun 2011 03:15:19 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-397317-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/72-hours-to-end-the-war-on-drugs/397317.rss">72 Hours to End the War on Drugs</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>72 Hours to End the War on Drugs</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@sppt sppt]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/sppt">@sppt</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>That chart is a bit old, since Uruguay has legalised pot up to 8 grams and like 12 plants iirc.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/72-hours-to-end-the-war-on-drugs/397317/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/72-hours-to-end-the-war-on-drugs/397317/3</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jun 2011 01:32:31 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-397317-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/72-hours-to-end-the-war-on-drugs/397317.rss">72 Hours to End the War on Drugs</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>72 Hours to End the War on Drugs</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@lothy Lothy]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/lothy">@lothy</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>It’s curious that Australia was listed. It’s no more legal here to carry drugs than it is in the US.<br>
There are a handful of tricks that you can employ to stay out of big trouble (ie, buy only half an ounce or something and you can claim personal use if caught), but it’s still illegal, except in South Australia where they have decriminalised personal use.</p>
<p>Salvia is illegal here, and drugs such as LSD and MDMA are definitely illegal. If you get caught with ‘hard’ drugs (ice, heroin) then it’s even worse.</p>
<p>EDIT: It looks like I’m a bit behind the times. If this image is accurate then most states have decriminalised it.<br>
<div class="lightbox-wrapper"><a class="lightbox" href="http://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/f/fd/World-cannabis-laws.png" title="World-cannabis-laws.png" rel="nofollow noopener"><img src="http://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/f/fd/World-cannabis-laws.png" alt width="690" height="291"><div class="meta">
<svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-far-image svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#far-image"></use></svg><span class="filename">World-cannabis-laws.png</span><span class="informations">1480×625</span><svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-discourse-expand svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#discourse-expand"></use></svg>
</div></a></div></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/72-hours-to-end-the-war-on-drugs/397317/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/72-hours-to-end-the-war-on-drugs/397317/2</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jun 2011 01:11:30 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-397317-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/72-hours-to-end-the-war-on-drugs/397317.rss">72 Hours to End the War on Drugs</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>72 Hours to End the War on Drugs</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Jython super_]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/jython">@Jython</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>In 72 hours, we could finally see the beginning of the end of the ‘war on drugs’. This expensive war has completely failed to curb the plague of drug addiction, while costing countless lives, devastating communities, and funneling trillions of dollars into violent organized crime networks.</p>
<p>Experts all agree that the most sensible policy is to regulate, but politicians are afraid to touch the issue. In 72 hours, a global commission including former heads of state and foreign policy chiefs of the UN, EU, US, Brazil, Mexico and more will break the taboo and publicly call for new approaches including decriminalization and regulation of drugs.</p>
<p>This could be a once-in-a-generation tipping-point moment – if enough of us call for an end to this madness. Politicians say they understand that the war on drugs has failed, but claim the public isn’t ready for an alternative. Let’s show them we not only accept a sane and humane policy – we demand it. Sign the petition and share with everyone – when we reach 1/2 million voices, it will be personally delivered to world leaders by the global commission.</p>
<p>For 50 years current drug policies have failed everyone, everywhere but public debate is stuck in the mud of fear and misinformation. Everyone, even the UN Office on Drugs and Crime which is responsible for enforcing this approach agrees – deploying militaries and police to burn drug farms, hunting down traffickers, and imprisoning dealers and addicts – is an expensive mistake. And with massive human cost – from Afghanistan, to Mexico, to the USA the illegal drug trade is destroying countries around the world, while addiction, overdose deaths, and HIV/AIDS infections continue to rise.</p>
<p>Meanwhile, countries with less-harsh enforcement – like Switzerland, Portugal, the Netherlands, and Australia – have not seen the explosion in drug use that proponents of the drug war have darkly predicted. Instead, they have seen significant reductions in drug-related crime, addiction and deaths, and are able to focus squarely on dismantling criminal empires.</p>
<p>Powerful lobbies still stand in the way of change, including military, law enforcement, and prison departments whose budgets are at stake. And politicians fear that voters will throw them out of office if they support alternative approaches, as they will appear weak on law and order. But many former drug Ministers and Heads of State have come out in favour of reform since leaving office, and polls show that citizens across the world know the current approach is a catastrophe. Momentum is gathering towards new improved policies, particularly in regions that are ravaged by the drug trade.</p>
<p>If we can create a worldwide outcry in the 72 hours to support the bold calls of the Global Commission on Drug Policy, we can overpower the stale excuses for the status quo. Our voices hold the key to change – Sign the petition and spread the word.</p>
<p>We have a chance to enter the closing chapter of this brutal ‘war’ that has destroyed millions of lives. Global public opinion will determine if this catastrophic policy is stopped or if politicians shy away from reform. Let’s rally urgently to push our hesitating leaders from doubt and fear, over the edge, and into reason.</p>
<p><a href="http://www.avaaz.org/en/end_the_war_on_drugs_a/" class="onebox" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">http://www.avaaz.org/en/end_the_war_on_drugs_a/</a></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/72-hours-to-end-the-war-on-drugs/397317/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/72-hours-to-end-the-war-on-drugs/397317/1</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jun 2011 01:05:38 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-397317-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/72-hours-to-end-the-war-on-drugs/397317.rss">72 Hours to End the War on Drugs</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
