<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>[Visual Basic] Mail form button click delay</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/visual-basic-mail-form-button-click-delay/345399</link>
    <description>Recently I added in a Mail Form to my Visual Basic program, and the user has to log into their google e-mail address in order to send me their message. I don&#39;t want people abusing the mail form and repeatedly sending me e-mail, or should I say, troll-mail, so I want to be able to make it so that the user can only click the &quot;Mail Form&quot; button once every day. I&#39;m not too sure where to start. I&#39;ve added the timer and set it&#39;s interval to 86,400,000. (86,400,000 are how many milliseconds are in a day FYI) I was told by someone that I&#39;d have to add in a boolean, but I haven&#39;t really worked with booleans yet, and am looking for a little help. I don&#39;t even know what I&#39;m to put in the boolean! I&#39;m not looking to be spoonfed. I just want some help with creating a boolean.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 25 Jun 2010 19:13:36 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>General Programming</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/visual-basic-mail-form-button-click-delay/345399.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>[Visual Basic] Mail form button click delay</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@davidi2 Davidi2]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/davidi2">@davidi2</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Ok the problem is this:</p>
<p>The person can just close your program and then run it again, sending you another message.</p>
<p>If you really want this to work, forget the boolean. You need to create a variable that saves even if the program is closed. (Think it’s called a resource)</p>
<p>You create it in your application properties, and then you can edit it/see it using My.Resources.variablename</p>
<p>You would want so that when you email the form, it saves the current time or something to a resource variable, and then everytime the button is clicked it checks the time and if it hasn’t been 24 hours they can’t do it.</p>
<p>Personally I would only want the person to be able to email me once, so I would make my resource a boolean, and when they email me turn it to ‘true’. Then if they ever click the button again and the resource says ‘true’, then a message box pops up saying ‘You can’t send another form!’</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/visual-basic-mail-form-button-click-delay/345399/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/visual-basic-mail-form-button-click-delay/345399/3</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jun 2010 19:13:36 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-345399-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/visual-basic-mail-form-button-click-delay/345399.rss">[Visual Basic] Mail form button click delay</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Visual Basic] Mail form button click delay</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@pure2ownage Pure_]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/pure2ownage">@pure2ownage</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <pre><code class="lang-auto">thisIsAnBoolean = true</code></pre>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/visual-basic-mail-form-button-click-delay/345399/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/visual-basic-mail-form-button-click-delay/345399/2</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jun 2010 17:41:14 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-345399-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/visual-basic-mail-form-button-click-delay/345399.rss">[Visual Basic] Mail form button click delay</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Visual Basic] Mail form button click delay</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@r0ckstar96 r0ckstar96]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/r0ckstar96">@r0ckstar96</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Recently I added in a Mail Form to my Visual Basic program, and the user has to log into their google e-mail address in order to send me their message. I don’t want people abusing the mail form and repeatedly sending me e-mail, or should I say, troll-mail, so I want to be able to make it so that the user can only click the “Mail Form” button once every day. I’m not too sure where to start. I’ve added the timer and set it’s interval to 86,400,000. (86,400,000 are how many milliseconds are in a day FYI) I was told by someone that I’d have to add in a boolean, but I haven’t really worked with booleans yet, and am looking for a little help. I don’t even know what I’m to put in the boolean! I’m not looking to be spoonfed. I just want some help with creating a boolean.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/visual-basic-mail-form-button-click-delay/345399/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/visual-basic-mail-form-button-click-delay/345399/1</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jun 2010 02:26:21 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-345399-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/visual-basic-mail-form-button-click-delay/345399.rss">[Visual Basic] Mail form button click delay</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
