<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>EcoPS || Will you get rich?</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/ecops-will-you-get-rich/551793</link>
    <description>[center][img]http://i.imgur.com/giS1oOy.png[/img][/center]

[hr]

Website: [url=http://ecops.hostzi.com]Click here![/url]
Play now: [url=http://ecops.hostzi.com/play.html]Click here![/url]

[hr]

[b][size=24pt]Salutations,[/size][/b]
Hello MoparScape. I am known as Game Master on my website, EcoPS. None of you know me, and I know none of you, so I suppose you could all recognize this as an official introduction on my behalf. EcoPS is a server that is quite dear to me, it is heavily influenced off a private server I partook in back in 2006. I&#39;ll explain all of that later, but for now, we&#39;ll get into my introduction more.

EcoPS is my very first private server, although I&#39;m not quite amateur with Java. I&#39;m confident enough in my abilities to promise all of you an economy based server that will be challenging enough (as long as there&#39;s no exploiting going on hehe...) to suit your needs. What I see lacking in the RuneScape server communities is an actual challenging economy server. Some servers which claim to be challenging and base their focus towards the economy are actually quite casual, where they tried to be a challenge for some. It irritates me to see this lack of style, so I want to bring one to the public. Which brings me here to MoparScape to put it&#39;s name out and may potentially start growing a community!

From the little I understand about MoparScape; the community is unfriendly? I hope that I am warmly welcomed here. Nonetheless, I&#39;m excited about meeting some of you!

[hr]

[b][size=24pt]So what is EcoPS?[/size][/b]
EcoPS is a server that is very dear to me personally. This server was heavily influenced off a server that was hosted in 2006 named Poor&#39;s Island. This server focused heavily on it&#39;s economy, yet was also friendly to PKers at the same time. With tough experience rates, much grinding, scarce supplies in the shops, it was obviously a home to PvMers and skillers. However, many of the important NPCs were placed in the wilderness, forcing players wanting to grind to enter the wild. Allowing PKers to feel welcomed as well. Poor&#39;s Island, unfortunately, was short-lived. However, within just a week, it grew quite nicely and had roughly 50+ players online at all times. That sort of community made the server much more fun, considering there were actual real risks to be taking now. At any moment, whilst grinding for rune armor, you could be ambushed by a few players and killed for whatever you had with you.

Unlike Poor&#39;s Island, EcoPS is using a 718 Matrix source loading a 742 cache. I chose this particular source because I don&#39;t plan on spending so much time and effort on a standard 317 source in attempts to grasp what I&#39;m attempting to capture out of this server. The current 317 servers that I&#39;ve viewed, remember that I am still very new to the RS2 emulation scene, aren&#39;t up to par with the Matrix sources, unfortunately. No worries, the revision won&#39;t effect the gameplay much!

EcoPS is designed to be challenging, yet fun at the same time. Whereas skilling is an absolute essential in the server, skillers are completely welcome. They could make some serious cash selling food, runes, or armors. Especially considering there is already reward systems placed on certain skills, such as woodcutting and firemaking. With tough experience and drop rates, we could be home to PvMers who enjoy an enduring challenge. Though, also due to the fact many of the NPCs and bosses are located in the wilderness, PKers could also come here. If you don&#39;t mind a little training and grinding, you could then get to killing players in the wilderness once you catch them.

Gold in EcoPS will also be challenging. Where we tax things such as slayer tasks and every time you yell, amongst other things, it is also just tough to get in general. Perhaps you&#39;d like to farm rune armor to sell, or maybe just cook some food to sell either to a shop or player? Either way, you will be needing some, as gold is used in a variety of things!

[hr]

[b][size=24pt]Features:[/size][/b]
[code]
-All the Godwars Dungeon bosses
-Many bosses
-Fight Caves
-Fight Kiln
-Slayer tower
-Revenants
-Slayer taxing
-Yell taxing
-Prayer &amp; magic book taxing
-Clothing taxing
-Information center for data on your account
-Scarce supplies in shops
-Many drop rates tampered with for a proper economy
-Runespan
-Grinding tab for mid-range gear
-Important NPCs located in the wilderness
-Skilling guilds
-Reset slayer tasks taxed
-Skilling rewards
-Edited some skills
[/code]

[hr]

[img]http://i.imgur.com/bQrKaTg.jpg[/img]

Thank you all for reading, and I hope you see you online!</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 03 Jun 2015 11:48:15 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/ecops-will-you-get-rich/551793.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>EcoPS || Will you get rich?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@EcoPS_GM EcoPS GM]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/ecops_gm">@EcoPS_GM</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[center]<img src="http://i.imgur.com/giS1oOy.png" alt width="" height="">[/center]</p>
<p>[hr]</p>
<p>Website: <a href="http://ecops.hostzi.com" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">Click here!</a><br>
Play now: <a href="http://ecops.hostzi.com/play.html" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">Click here!</a></p>
<p>[hr]</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">[size=24pt]Salutations,[/size]</span><br>
Hello MoparScape. I am known as Game Master on my website, EcoPS. None of you know me, and I know none of you, so I suppose you could all recognize this as an official introduction on my behalf. EcoPS is a server that is quite dear to me, it is heavily influenced off a private server I partook in back in 2006. I’ll explain all of that later, but for now, we’ll get into my introduction more.</p>
<p>EcoPS is my very first private server, although I’m not quite amateur with Java. I’m confident enough in my abilities to promise all of you an economy based server that will be challenging enough (as long as there’s no exploiting going on hehe…) to suit your needs. What I see lacking in the RuneScape server communities is an actual challenging economy server. Some servers which claim to be challenging and base their focus towards the economy are actually quite casual, where they tried to be a challenge for some. It irritates me to see this lack of style, so I want to bring one to the public. Which brings me here to MoparScape to put it’s name out and may potentially start growing a community!</p>
<p>From the little I understand about MoparScape; the community is unfriendly? I hope that I am warmly welcomed here. Nonetheless, I’m excited about meeting some of you!</p>
<p>[hr]</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">[size=24pt]So what is EcoPS?[/size]</span><br>
EcoPS is a server that is very dear to me personally. This server was heavily influenced off a server that was hosted in 2006 named Poor’s Island. This server focused heavily on it’s economy, yet was also friendly to PKers at the same time. With tough experience rates, much grinding, scarce supplies in the shops, it was obviously a home to PvMers and skillers. However, many of the important NPCs were placed in the wilderness, forcing players wanting to grind to enter the wild. Allowing PKers to feel welcomed as well. Poor’s Island, unfortunately, was short-lived. However, within just a week, it grew quite nicely and had roughly 50+ players online at all times. That sort of community made the server much more fun, considering there were actual real risks to be taking now. At any moment, whilst grinding for rune armor, you could be ambushed by a few players and killed for whatever you had with you.</p>
<p>Unlike Poor’s Island, EcoPS is using a 718 Matrix source loading a 742 cache. I chose this particular source because I don’t plan on spending so much time and effort on a standard 317 source in attempts to grasp what I’m attempting to capture out of this server. The current 317 servers that I’ve viewed, remember that I am still very new to the RS2 emulation scene, aren’t up to par with the Matrix sources, unfortunately. No worries, the revision won’t effect the gameplay much!</p>
<p>EcoPS is designed to be challenging, yet fun at the same time. Whereas skilling is an absolute essential in the server, skillers are completely welcome. They could make some serious cash selling food, runes, or armors. Especially considering there is already reward systems placed on certain skills, such as woodcutting and firemaking. With tough experience and drop rates, we could be home to PvMers who enjoy an enduring challenge. Though, also due to the fact many of the NPCs and bosses are located in the wilderness, PKers could also come here. If you don’t mind a little training and grinding, you could then get to killing players in the wilderness once you catch them.</p>
<p>Gold in EcoPS will also be challenging. Where we tax things such as slayer tasks and every time you yell, amongst other things, it is also just tough to get in general. Perhaps you’d like to farm rune armor to sell, or maybe just cook some food to sell either to a shop or player? Either way, you will be needing some, as gold is used in a variety of things!</p>
<p>[hr]</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">[size=24pt]Features:[/size]</span></p>
<pre><code class="lang-auto">-All the Godwars Dungeon bosses
-Many bosses
-Fight Caves
-Fight Kiln
-Slayer tower
-Revenants
-Slayer taxing
-Yell taxing
-Prayer &amp; magic book taxing
-Clothing taxing
-Information center for data on your account
-Scarce supplies in shops
-Many drop rates tampered with for a proper economy
-Runespan
-Grinding tab for mid-range gear
-Important NPCs located in the wilderness
-Skilling guilds
-Reset slayer tasks taxed
-Skilling rewards
-Edited some skills</code></pre>
<p>[hr]</p>
<p><img src="http://i.imgur.com/bQrKaTg.jpg" alt width="" height=""></p>
<p>Thank you all for reading, and I hope you see you online!</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/ecops-will-you-get-rich/551793/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/ecops-will-you-get-rich/551793/1</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 03 Jun 2015 11:48:15 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-551793-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/ecops-will-you-get-rich/551793.rss">EcoPS || Will you get rich?</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
