<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Looking for someone familiar with JAVA/PHP</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/looking-for-someone-familiar-with-java-php/542580</link>
    <description>Howdy all,

Over the past week or so I&#39;ve been working with different sources and finding the best and worst out of them to see which one best suited my needs! Right now I&#39;m using the FreedomX 718 source and I love it. I&#39;ve already done much of the changes from altering Dialogue, commands and various different settings to help tweak the game in my favor. Right now I&#39;m working solo on both Game and Web Aspects. 

I could use a new set of eyes to help me with a few errors I&#39;ve encountered that may see something I could have missed, I know there are folks here that are far more familiar with the way RuneScape works than I am. In addition, I&#39;d like someone to have a back and forth with. Ideas, opinions, brainstorming, problem solving, that sort of thing.

Sound like your kind of party or just have more questions? Please feel free to PM me, I&#39;m not to bad of guy and I don&#39;t bite much!
Cody</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 27 Apr 2014 08:24:42 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/looking-for-someone-familiar-with-java-php/542580.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Looking for someone familiar with JAVA/PHP</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@CodySP CodySP]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/codysp">@CodySP</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Howdy all,</p>
<p>Over the past week or so I’ve been working with different sources and finding the best and worst out of them to see which one best suited my needs! Right now I’m using the FreedomX 718 source and I love it. I’ve already done much of the changes from altering Dialogue, commands and various different settings to help tweak the game in my favor. Right now I’m working solo on both Game and Web Aspects.</p>
<p>I could use a new set of eyes to help me with a few errors I’ve encountered that may see something I could have missed, I know there are folks here that are far more familiar with the way RuneScape works than I am. In addition, I’d like someone to have a back and forth with. Ideas, opinions, brainstorming, problem solving, that sort of thing.</p>
<p>Sound like your kind of party or just have more questions? Please feel free to PM me, I’m not to bad of guy and I don’t bite much!<br>
Cody</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/looking-for-someone-familiar-with-java-php/542580/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/looking-for-someone-familiar-with-java-php/542580/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 27 Apr 2014 08:24:42 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-542580-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/looking-for-someone-familiar-with-java-php/542580.rss">Looking for someone familiar with JAVA/PHP</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
