<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Battle Of The Elites!</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/battle-of-the-elites/31836</link>
    <description>&quot;Owwwwwwwwwwww&quot;, I siad while rocovering from a shot.Ouch, That realy hurt I thought.Lucky I have Armor that regenerates when shot
&quot;Go!&quot;,I siad.&quot;Move out!&quot;,I heard somone say.While having to wait for my armour to heal I grabbed Battlerifle and headed out.
First I roled and then &quot;Boom!&quot; I got shot in the foot again. Didn&#39;t though, This armour protects getting shot in the foot.
&quot;Well, What&#39;cha waiting on Capt.?&quot;,A senior back-up soldior siad while getting out his pistol and M60.&quot;Nothing&quot;,I replied.
I put my Battlerifle in scoping position and shot at a convent and killed him. &quot;Pow&quot;,I heard a sniper go off. I seen this 
convent do a backflip and a 360!Boy was that cool.&quot;Yeaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaah!!Headshot!&quot;,siad the sniper.....
&quot;Niceeeeeeeeeeeeee&quot;,I replied.
     Here we go again wheres there sniper, Wait I turned around,I heard some foot steps, I got in proun position and searched
For the enemeys. I scoped in and I seen a Convent sniper that was skilled I Shot him 4 times in the head one time in the foot
and he did a front flip.Cool, It was amazing to be in a war, But the bad part about this is the part if you get killed.
Well Here I&#39;m in front of the mountain guarding the convent body searching for convents to come this way and they were 
fooled when they came one got sniped I killed two of them and thee other got sworded. They were fooled badly,While I was
For more convents to come I had to move out, We went around them and sneeked up on them, From behind we were at the heart 
of the base and we were in bad shape We had our sniper go on the mountain above us we had a another guy search for there
mountains and wanted to see if there are any convents over there,Well What I did was stupid, I&#39;m crazy. I went in the base
of there base, Stupid me. Well on the way out there I had to take cover to search for convents &#39;cuase I heard snipers from ever-where shooting.
then it was over I had been shot in the chest I could hardly walk.....So i was in cover then I recovered barely, I looked up.
There they were, Starring down at me &quot;Oh Crap!!!!!!!!!!&quot; I started to get my sniper and then I shot all of them without any
scope!I siad.&quot;NOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOO-SCOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOPE!!!!&quot;All 5 of them dead.Work-On-That-Back-Flip!
   Wow going into this war was risky!I thought I would be dead by now.But I was alive!I smiled, Its on. I reloaded my sniper got out my B-R
The B-r Is other wised known as Battle Rifle. Well I started to shoot so it would bring out the enemey.wow this is gonna be spooky including that we have 
snipers, I mean good snipers on us. Of course i&#39;m not the best i&#39;m just one of the very good soldiors.There was sound coming for the north
to north-east from here, I couldn&#39;t tell if it was a sniper or not. I searched the building&#39;s the mountain&#39;s no-one.That means we have to move out to another 
area to where we can find anything.Ok, we are in this area with no enemeys in sight. They might be able to see us though I thought.
Well I searched around in the building with my BR, No signs of enemey movement or no signs of sight.So I was ready to go in the 
buidling. Oh, Forgot need back so I picked up my walki-talki and said&quot;I need backup&quot; and I got about 3 Soldiors to come with me.
ok we are searching the building, and I heard something.They were talking I think they siad &quot;Ahh chikaawakaa?&quot;weird it thought.
So we are headed another way threw the building so they will not see us and we wont have a load on our shoulders,Well which
other way can we take?WAit I think I found another way in here, And it was the painful way, we had to take there sewer,ouch,
this hurts my nose. What???! I heard somthing coming I hurryed through the sewer and got out my sniper for long range,Once when 
I had seen them in sight I started to fire and killed about 15 of them and more kept on coming. I&#39;m screwed I thought while taking out my Br
Here we go again for another round, Wow this is more fun than I thought. Ok I had one in range but my Br was low on ammo. Dang I had to ask for ammo
Wow this sucks even worse then I imagined. Ok, I got some ammo from a commander, He was a 5th level commander.Well I was ready 
to go out there but needed more people on m side, So I got the 6th commander and a senior and about 3 juniors to come, We had to keep the juniors safe.
Ok, We went in, Not knowing that they already had about 100 convents in here and about 200 spartmans, Well we went in there anyways getting a barrior to hide
behind so we could take cover, I shot about 50 spartmans in the head killing all 50 I shot, I shot 50 4 headshots to the convents killing all 50 of them
and there were about 100 more left, Ok they had shot about 500 bullets killing them all while I went to go get the Huge convents not knowing they were there.
I was even more screwed now.Dang, Well I went in there and had seen about 50 Big Convents!!! Wow im in big touble if I dont have atleast 25 seniors
And 100 Juniors with about 5 commanders and 15 legends with me, well we only had one legend and that was me, We had another legend too and that was Taylor,
He had been here longer then me And im a legend and we are great buddies, well I got about 200 Juniors to come and 85 seniors and taylor had to go with the other soldiors to proctect them
And then We went in there shooting the big convents in the week spot, we had 50 snipers on board coming in here all shooting them in the weak spot killing them all and then they had alot of convents to lrage to count them.
Well theres about 500 convents 600 spartmens, how harder could it get? Well Here we go only about 185 of us and 1100 of them and we narrowed them down to 564 and we had man down dead. Nooooooooo! I got out my sniper no-scoping them.
We were narrowed down to 85, I killed about 150 of them with my sniper and killing about 15 with one bullet. And then the worst part to come the fight, They had swords we had to act fast so we all got out our sniper skilled or not skilled with snipers we killed them all amzingly.
Eagerly happy We had to move out we went threw there hall and was at section 1-65-485 And was walking and seen 15 convents we killed them all not knowing it was a trap to warn the others,
Well we had fallin&#39; in to there trap and was fooled badly, Uh-Oh I thought.&quot;We need More people!!!!&quot;, I siad while taking a M60,
I&#39;m Ready to fight. We were narrowed down to 45 seniors no juniors are left. We had about 1,508,456 seniors at base and about 16,000,000 juniors. It was enough to take down this hole building convents,Big convents,and sparkman in all.
I called to mauni base saying&quot;WE need all of our seniors and juniors to take down there army.When I got threw they replied&quot;we will send half of our juniors and seniors to come!&quot;, well I siad,&quot;Ok sounds fine to me! Thanks sir&quot;
In about a hour I had no men with me and they had been here I seen a army Of them im like holy shivertocmushroomstamushroomsbittenshiverlycrackers!!!
This was a huge army and I jumped off the first ledge not far down though. I&#39;m Down there directing them we went in there we seen about 50,000 of each convent they had and spartman
This equaled up to about 150,000 enemys no match for us though we killed them all only losing about 5 men in it. Ok we went in no more of them dang this means were gonna have to walk along ways wait im mistaken!I heard about 450000 foot-steps coming our way!
Oh boy time to have some fun!
  Uh-Oh I thought.... Am I alive? I could have known I had seen about 50,000 convents and spartmans, Man hopefully I&#39;ll make it.
&quot;Man are you gonna go or what?,&quot; said 2nd commander of the hopochi clan. &quot;Yeaaaaaaaaaas,&quot; I said while getting my B.R. out...
Pow!Boom! Shot&#39;s fired from every direction.&quot;Well come on 8,000 seniors, Juniors you stay here, Ok?&quot; I said. &quot;Ok&quot; they all said in a weird way that tracked some convents our way. sping. One of there snipers had shot and killed 5 Juniors. Boy didn&#39;t that make me mad.
I can&#39;t stand to lose men! I took out my sniper and shot them! 15 convents were there, and I killed them all.

I wrote this when I was bored.. Alot Of typos!</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 22 Jan 2007 17:59:14 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>General Discussion</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/battle-of-the-elites/31836.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Battle Of The Elites!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@wooker wooker]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/wooker">@wooker</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>You could try using paragraphs as Chris said. Also i recommend trying to put a little effort into what you write… I skimmed over it and quite frankly the content wasn’t that great <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/confused.png?v=6" title=":confused:" class="emoji" alt=":confused:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/battle-of-the-elites/31836/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/battle-of-the-elites/31836/3</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 22 Jan 2007 17:59:14 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-31836-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/battle-of-the-elites/31836.rss">Battle Of The Elites!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Battle Of The Elites!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Mr.Chris Mr.Chris]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/mr.chris">@Mr.Chris</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Ever heard of Paragraphs <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/wink.png?v=6" title=":wink:" class="emoji" alt=":wink:"></p>
<p>I’ll reads it when it’s nicely set out, and readable <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=6" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/battle-of-the-elites/31836/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/battle-of-the-elites/31836/2</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2006 00:07:15 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-31836-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/battle-of-the-elites/31836.rss">Battle Of The Elites!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Battle Of The Elites!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Trickery123 Trickery123]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/trickery123">@Trickery123</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>“Owwwwwwwwwwww”, I siad while rocovering from a shot.Ouch, That realy hurt I thought.Lucky I have Armor that regenerates when shot<br>
“Go!”,I siad.“Move out!”,I heard somone say.While having to wait for my armour to heal I grabbed Battlerifle and headed out.<br>
First I roled and then “Boom!” I got shot in the foot again. Didn’t though, This armour protects getting shot in the foot.<br>
“Well, What’cha waiting on Capt.?”,A senior back-up soldior siad while getting out his pistol and M60.“Nothing”,I replied.<br>
I put my Battlerifle in scoping position and shot at a convent and killed him. “Pow”,I heard a sniper go off. I seen this<br>
convent do a backflip and a 360!Boy was that cool.“Yeaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaah!!Headshot!”,siad the sniper…<br>
“Niceeeeeeeeeeeeee”,I replied.<br>
Here we go again wheres there sniper, Wait I turned around,I heard some foot steps, I got in proun position and searched<br>
For the enemeys. I scoped in and I seen a Convent sniper that was skilled I Shot him 4 times in the head one time in the foot<br>
and he did a front flip.Cool, It was amazing to be in a war, But the bad part about this is the part if you get killed.<br>
Well Here I’m in front of the mountain guarding the convent body searching for convents to come this way and they were<br>
fooled when they came one got sniped I killed two of them and thee other got sworded. They were fooled badly,While I was<br>
For more convents to come I had to move out, We went around them and sneeked up on them, From behind we were at the heart<br>
of the base and we were in bad shape We had our sniper go on the mountain above us we had a another guy search for there<br>
mountains and wanted to see if there are any convents over there,Well What I did was stupid, I’m crazy. I went in the base<br>
of there base, Stupid me. Well on the way out there I had to take cover to search for convents ‘cuase I heard snipers from ever-where shooting.<br>
then it was over I had been shot in the chest I could hardly walk…So i was in cover then I recovered barely, I looked up.<br>
There they were, Starring down at me “Oh Crap!!!” I started to get my sniper and then I shot all of them without any<br>
scope!I siad."NOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOO-SCOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOPE!!!“All 5 of them dead.Work-On-That-Back-Flip!<br>
Wow going into this war was risky!I thought I would be dead by now.But I was alive!I smiled, Its on. I reloaded my sniper got out my B-R<br>
The B-r Is other wised known as Battle Rifle. Well I started to shoot so it would bring out the enemey.wow this is gonna be spooky including that we have<br>
snipers, I mean good snipers on us. Of course i’m not the best i’m just one of the very good soldiors.There was sound coming for the north<br>
to north-east from here, I couldn’t tell if it was a sniper or not. I searched the building’s the mountain’s no-one.That means we have to move out to another<br>
area to where we can find anything.Ok, we are in this area with no enemeys in sight. They might be able to see us though I thought.<br>
Well I searched around in the building with my BR, No signs of enemey movement or no signs of sight.So I was ready to go in the<br>
buidling. Oh, Forgot need back so I picked up my walki-talki and said"I need backup” and I got about 3 Soldiors to come with me.<br>
ok we are searching the building, and I heard something.They were talking I think they siad "Ahh chikaawakaa?"weird it thought.<br>
So we are headed another way threw the building so they will not see us and we wont have a load on our shoulders,Well which<br>
other way can we take?WAit I think I found another way in here, And it was the painful way, we had to take there sewer,ouch,<br>
this hurts my nose. What???! I heard somthing coming I hurryed through the sewer and got out my sniper for long range,Once when<br>
I had seen them in sight I started to fire and killed about 15 of them and more kept on coming. I’m screwed I thought while taking out my Br<br>
Here we go again for another round, Wow this is more fun than I thought. Ok I had one in range but my Br was low on ammo. Dang I had to ask for ammo<br>
Wow this sucks even worse then I imagined. Ok, I got some ammo from a commander, He was a 5th level commander.Well I was ready<br>
to go out there but needed more people on m side, So I got the 6th commander and a senior and about 3 juniors to come, We had to keep the juniors safe.<br>
Ok, We went in, Not knowing that they already had about 100 convents in here and about 200 spartmans, Well we went in there anyways getting a barrior to hide<br>
behind so we could take cover, I shot about 50 spartmans in the head killing all 50 I shot, I shot 50 4 headshots to the convents killing all 50 of them<br>
and there were about 100 more left, Ok they had shot about 500 bullets killing them all while I went to go get the Huge convents not knowing they were there.<br>
I was even more screwed now.Dang, Well I went in there and had seen about 50 Big Convents!!! Wow im in big touble if I dont have atleast 25 seniors<br>
And 100 Juniors with about 5 commanders and 15 legends with me, well we only had one legend and that was me, We had another legend too and that was Taylor,<br>
He had been here longer then me And im a legend and we are great buddies, well I got about 200 Juniors to come and 85 seniors and taylor had to go with the other soldiors to proctect them<br>
And then We went in there shooting the big convents in the week spot, we had 50 snipers on board coming in here all shooting them in the weak spot killing them all and then they had alot of convents to lrage to count them.<br>
Well theres about 500 convents 600 spartmens, how harder could it get? Well Here we go only about 185 of us and 1100 of them and we narrowed them down to 564 and we had man down dead. Nooooooooo! I got out my sniper no-scoping them.<br>
We were narrowed down to 85, I killed about 150 of them with my sniper and killing about 15 with one bullet. And then the worst part to come the fight, They had swords we had to act fast so we all got out our sniper skilled or not skilled with snipers we killed them all amzingly.<br>
Eagerly happy We had to move out we went threw there hall and was at section 1-65-485 And was walking and seen 15 convents we killed them all not knowing it was a trap to warn the others,<br>
Well we had fallin’ in to there trap and was fooled badly, Uh-Oh I thought.“We need More people!!!”, I siad while taking a M60,<br>
I’m Ready to fight. We were narrowed down to 45 seniors no juniors are left. We had about 1,508,456 seniors at base and about 16,000,000 juniors. It was enough to take down this hole building convents,Big convents,and sparkman in all.<br>
I called to mauni base saying"WE need all of our seniors and juniors to take down there army.When I got threw they replied"we will send half of our juniors and seniors to come!", well I siad,“Ok sounds fine to me! Thanks sir”<br>
In about a hour I had no men with me and they had been here I seen a army Of them im like holy shivertocmushroomstamushroomsbittenshiverlycrackers!!!<br>
This was a huge army and I jumped off the first ledge not far down though. I’m Down there directing them we went in there we seen about 50,000 of each convent they had and spartman<br>
This equaled up to about 150,000 enemys no match for us though we killed them all only losing about 5 men in it. Ok we went in no more of them dang this means were gonna have to walk along ways wait im mistaken!I heard about 450000 foot-steps coming our way!<br>
Oh boy time to have some fun!<br>
Uh-Oh I thought… Am I alive? I could have known I had seen about 50,000 convents and spartmans, Man hopefully I’ll make it.<br>
“Man are you gonna go or what?,” said 2nd commander of the hopochi clan. “Yeaaaaaaaaaas,” I said while getting my B.R. out…<br>
Pow!Boom! Shot’s fired from every direction.“Well come on 8,000 seniors, Juniors you stay here, Ok?” I said. “Ok” they all said in a weird way that tracked some convents our way. sping. One of there snipers had shot and killed 5 Juniors. Boy didn’t that make me mad.<br>
I can’t stand to lose men! I took out my sniper and shot them! 15 convents were there, and I killed them all.</p>
<p>I wrote this when I was bored… Alot Of typos!</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/battle-of-the-elites/31836/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/battle-of-the-elites/31836/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 03 Dec 2006 22:34:38 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-31836-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/battle-of-the-elites/31836.rss">Battle Of The Elites!</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
