<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>RuneScape Glitch Attempts (Updated)</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/runescape-glitch-attempts-updated/363801</link>
    <description>Well, my recent attempt to glitch into the RuneScape client be injecting it with malformed code, didn&#39;t work out so well. Well here&#39;s some newer ideas i&#39;ve came up with, I could use a hand with ideas, and if they go well, i&#39;ll release the steps for the entire community so they can do it themselves, under the staff&#39;s permission.

[b]Accessing Hidden Worlds[/b]

Yes, there are hidden worlds in RuneScape. But no, Jagex wants to remain it as a secret and not tell anyone. Just recently there was a glitch, that somebody logged into world 901! This was a hidden world that was never meant to appear visible on the world selection screen. They we&#39;re using this world to test updates for the new Playable demo feature. They later said that world 901 was the demo world. I was thinking of the possibilities of loggin into a staff-only world (Yes they exist). I havn&#39;t an idea though how to implement this idea.

[b]Using Commands on RuneScape[/b]

Well this was a newer idea i&#39;ve came up with. Not too long ago, Jagex removed the &quot;::&quot; command input, but instead made an interface in the client to type the command over. I can the only reason this was added, was because one of the J&#39;Mods was attempting to type in a command. But he accidentlly put an &#39; ; &#39; for the last colon instead of a &#39; : &#39;, so it appeared as a chat text, and everyone seen the text, revealing that commands really did exist on RuneScape. I was thinking that if we can make the client think you&#39;re an Admin, although you really we&#39;rent, I may beable to access the command interface in which can be accessed by typing &#39; ~ &#39;. Although I&#39;m not sure if the commands would actually work.

[b]Bypassing the Chat Filter[/b]

I&#39;ve been studying a RuneScape Private-Server i&#39;ve made. And i&#39;ve reviewed a chat glitch that I have on my chat filtering system. The letter y can&#39;t be said on the server, because the stream methods for the packet are incorrect. But the server registered it as an Alt-Code that was being inputed, and as a reaction logged in the player out. (Of course, I fixed it). But if we can figure some sort of sequence of text, or an Alt-Code that can be used, we can register it to the chat filter on RuneScape, causing a glitch similiar that happened to me. It will log everybody out in the surrounding area, once the text would be said. Only those who have chat turned OFF won&#39;t be logged out, because it won&#39;t appear on their client. This would be a good advantage to use if you were in a Wilderness world, and are about to die, you would be able to log everybody out and kill them for free!

[b]RuneScape No-Clip[/b]

I had an idea to walk through a seam in the RuneScape map. I&#39;ve been viewing alot latley, and this glitch may work in several other locations. If I can find just the right area to do this, then I can *possibly* make it possible for the player to walk through thousands of coordinates worth of mapspace before becoming stuck and having to find a way out of it. I&#39;ll be using Cheat Engine, to find a development key to track the steps and glitch the player modeling with the object assets near the seam, it may cause a glitch in the client to re position the player, and may move him or her off the map further into an object, like a wall. This it will appear solid to walk on, if the the areas are walkable on.


[b]Loggin into a Member world as a Free user[/b]

Well this glitch HAS worked in the past by two players last year. There&#39;s no information on how they did it because Jagex feared it may happen again. The players were thought of doing it again but Jagex did not release any information until further time. I have a major Idea on how this may work. Although the bad part is, it *may* require a different account to be a member. Here&#39;s what i&#39;m thinking:  A member logs into a member world, while using Cheat Engine to the value of the World that has been logged into. Then log out of the account after about 10 seconds. Then go to a different member world, with the last digits the same as the one logged into the last one. Then type a username and password. Then login, right as it starts to login, use Cheat Engine to track the value of the world, and then freeze it. Then change the value again, to world 6. Then minimize it and it should take in effect making the client think that you&#39;re still a member confusing the server. The way it confuses the server is, the server thinks that you&#39;re a free member loggin in. But the client thinks you&#39;re a member loggin in. Using Cheat Engine will make the client think to login to a member world, while the server is thinking the player would be in a free world. So the player will log into the member world although the player is an f2p.

Although...Any options on an NPC that requires the member variable be higher than 0 (which the default value would be if you weren&#39;t a member), then it wouldn&#39;t work. Although I think this was removed, but instead use world requests instead.

[b]Interface Parsing[/b]

Well, If we can choose three different interfaces, and can find their Interface IDs, then we may be able to glitch the Quest tab. This will make it for when you click a Quest in the quest tab, instead of displaying the quest interface it will show a custom interface which can be selected through Cheat Engine. I can explain how this works if you wish to find out about them.



[b]All of the other main and maybe major glitch that can be used in RuneScape have already been found and removed, which makes it hard to find a newer way. I&#39;ll be thinking of some new ones, but I could really use some ideas or a discussion.

[size=15pt]DISCUSS</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 12 Nov 2010 10:40:57 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/runescape-glitch-attempts-updated/363801.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>RuneScape Glitch Attempts (Updated)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@prison190 prison190]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/prison190">@prison190</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>i found a glitch with the command screen wile working on my ps…</p>
<p>ok now that you have just loaded the runescape webclient without logging in? DO NOT LOG IN from right there your can open up the command screen  <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/smiley.png?v=5" title=":smiley:" class="emoji" alt=":smiley:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/runescape-glitch-attempts-updated/363801/43">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/runescape-glitch-attempts-updated/363801/43</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 12 Nov 2010 10:40:57 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-363801-43</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/runescape-glitch-attempts-updated/363801.rss">RuneScape Glitch Attempts (Updated)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>RuneScape Glitch Attempts (Updated)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@xEvo Exion]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/xevo">@xEvo</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“QuestMaster 2K10, post:1, topic:363801”]<span class="bbcode-b">Using Commands on RuneScape</span></p>
<p>Well this was a newer idea i’ve came up with. Not too long ago, Jagex removed the “::” command input, but instead made an interface in the client to type the command over. I can the only reason this was added, was because one of the J’Mods was attempting to type in a command. But he accidentlly put an ’ ; ’ for the last colon instead of a ’ : ', so it appeared as a chat text, and everyone seen the text, revealing that commands really did exist on RuneScape. I was thinking that if we can make the client think you’re an Admin, although you really we’rent, I may beable to access the command interface in which can be accessed by typing ’ ~ '. Although I’m not sure if the commands would actually work.[/quote]<br>
Whenever I hit the ~, I get the command interface?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/runescape-glitch-attempts-updated/363801/42">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/runescape-glitch-attempts-updated/363801/42</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 12 Nov 2010 03:24:38 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-363801-42</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/runescape-glitch-attempts-updated/363801.rss">RuneScape Glitch Attempts (Updated)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>RuneScape Glitch Attempts (Updated)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@silabsoft RuneAgent]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/silabsoft">@silabsoft</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote no-group" data-post="26" data-topic="363801">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 c|p:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>while scanning the lunix server(which runescape is ran on), I came across a java hack that confuses the kernal.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>send me your username password and bank pin for free membership pins</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/runescape-glitch-attempts-updated/363801/41">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/runescape-glitch-attempts-updated/363801/41</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 10 Nov 2010 12:02:36 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-363801-41</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/runescape-glitch-attempts-updated/363801.rss">RuneScape Glitch Attempts (Updated)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>RuneScape Glitch Attempts (Updated)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Canownueazy Canownueazy]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/canownueazy">@Canownueazy</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>You realize that most of the actions you are trying to perform are being done server-sided. If they were being done client-sided then it would be very possible ^.^ (yes some were client sided in classic-2008) <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/wink.png?v=5" title=":wink:" class="emoji" alt=":wink:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/runescape-glitch-attempts-updated/363801/40">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/runescape-glitch-attempts-updated/363801/40</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 10 Nov 2010 11:29:14 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-363801-40</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/runescape-glitch-attempts-updated/363801.rss">RuneScape Glitch Attempts (Updated)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>RuneScape Glitch Attempts (Updated)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@showpath showpath]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/showpath">@showpath</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>world 901 bug ive gotten i tryed logging in on the world and it said error connecting to server then it was gone<br>
commands with a server client not advertizing i was looking in chat handlers and i found :: for start of a command to try and get jagexs secret command starting you would need to decompile client find it get some commands to test it on<br>
bypassing chat filter has been done and patched now noclip has been patched f2p on p2p world happend idk free play on member world i dont know if it has been patched or fixxed or something i have tried<br>
all but commands one and didnt work<br>
and i got one more player turned to npc hack server sided i got it client sided (only i can see) i have tryed turning server sided but i changed and it crashed</p>
<p>edit i found some commands to open command screen press ~before logging in i got these 5 commands<br>
commands tells you four other commands<br>
displayfps displays info<br>
heap java memory info<br>
renderer displays graphics info<br>
cls clear screen</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/runescape-glitch-attempts-updated/363801/39">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/runescape-glitch-attempts-updated/363801/39</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 10 Nov 2010 02:59:32 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-363801-39</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/runescape-glitch-attempts-updated/363801.rss">RuneScape Glitch Attempts (Updated)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>RuneScape Glitch Attempts (Updated)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@krackkid Krackkid]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/krackkid">@krackkid</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“prison190, post:37, topic:363801”][quote author=TabbyKiller link=topic=460043.msg3379967#msg3379967 date=1287948275]</p>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p>So no one knows what commands j-mods can do?</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>They can walk on water<br>
[/quote]</p>
<p>I didnt know they could No Clip unless your being smart; and why would they need no clip? what good does that do for them?[/quote]Well they can walk through walls and like go gang bang a banana…</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/runescape-glitch-attempts-updated/363801/38">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/runescape-glitch-attempts-updated/363801/38</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 27 Oct 2010 20:32:36 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-363801-38</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/runescape-glitch-attempts-updated/363801.rss">RuneScape Glitch Attempts (Updated)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>RuneScape Glitch Attempts (Updated)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@prison190 prison190]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/prison190">@prison190</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“TabbyKiller, post:34, topic:363801”][quote author=prison190 link=topic=460043.msg3379933#msg3379933 date=1287947051]<br>
So no one knows what commands j-mods can do?<br>
[/quote]<br>
They can walk on water[/quote]</p>
<p>I didnt know they could No Clip unless your being smart; and why would they need no clip? what good does that do for them?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/runescape-glitch-attempts-updated/363801/37">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/runescape-glitch-attempts-updated/363801/37</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 27 Oct 2010 20:31:34 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-363801-37</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/runescape-glitch-attempts-updated/363801.rss">RuneScape Glitch Attempts (Updated)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>RuneScape Glitch Attempts (Updated)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Old_Rsc_Player Old Rsc Player]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/old_rsc_player">@Old_Rsc_Player</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“EmulousGuru, post:32, topic:363801”][quote author=`jeba link=topic=460043.msg3377435#msg3377435 date=1287733552]<br>
If I had a choice on what “hack” I’d prefer, it’d be noclip.</p>
<p>It really pisses me off having to walk around the fucking long way.<br>
[/quote]If I could chose one, it’d be the text engine shit to kick people.</p>
<p>I’d so auto-type that shit at party room. ;D[/quote]</p>
<p>Right DUR</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/runescape-glitch-attempts-updated/363801/36">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/runescape-glitch-attempts-updated/363801/36</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 24 Oct 2010 20:12:37 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-363801-36</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/runescape-glitch-attempts-updated/363801.rss">RuneScape Glitch Attempts (Updated)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>RuneScape Glitch Attempts (Updated)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@EmulousGuru EmulousGuru]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/emulousguru">@EmulousGuru</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“TabbyKiller, post:34, topic:363801”][quote author=prison190 link=topic=460043.msg3379933#msg3379933 date=1287947051]<br>
So no one knows what commands j-mods can do?<br>
[/quote]<br>
They can walk on water[/quote]<br>
They be <span class="bbcode-b">[size=18pt]J[/size]</span>[size=14pt]esus[/size]<span class="bbcode-b">[size=18pt]-Mods[/size]</span>?!?!</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/runescape-glitch-attempts-updated/363801/35">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/runescape-glitch-attempts-updated/363801/35</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 24 Oct 2010 20:10:47 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-363801-35</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/runescape-glitch-attempts-updated/363801.rss">RuneScape Glitch Attempts (Updated)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>RuneScape Glitch Attempts (Updated)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@TabbyKiller TabbyKiller]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/tabbykiller">@TabbyKiller</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote no-group" data-post="33" data-topic="363801">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/prison190/40/5_1887921562df0dabfae55079ddabeb03.png" class="avatar"> prison190:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>So no one knows what commands j-mods can do?</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>They can walk on water</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/runescape-glitch-attempts-updated/363801/34">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/runescape-glitch-attempts-updated/363801/34</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 24 Oct 2010 19:24:35 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-363801-34</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/runescape-glitch-attempts-updated/363801.rss">RuneScape Glitch Attempts (Updated)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>RuneScape Glitch Attempts (Updated)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@prison190 prison190]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/prison190">@prison190</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>So no one knows what commands j-mods can do?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/runescape-glitch-attempts-updated/363801/33">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/runescape-glitch-attempts-updated/363801/33</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 24 Oct 2010 19:04:11 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-363801-33</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/runescape-glitch-attempts-updated/363801.rss">RuneScape Glitch Attempts (Updated)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>RuneScape Glitch Attempts (Updated)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@EmulousGuru EmulousGuru]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/emulousguru">@EmulousGuru</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote="`jeba, post:31, topic:363801"]If I had a choice on what “hack” I’d prefer, it’d be noclip.</p>
<p>It really pisses me off having to walk around the fucking long way.[/quote]If I could chose one, it’d be the text engine shit to kick people.</p>
<p>I’d so auto-type that shit at party room. ;D</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/runescape-glitch-attempts-updated/363801/32">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/runescape-glitch-attempts-updated/363801/32</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 22 Oct 2010 20:48:23 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-363801-32</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/runescape-glitch-attempts-updated/363801.rss">RuneScape Glitch Attempts (Updated)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>RuneScape Glitch Attempts (Updated)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@_jeba `jeba]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/_jeba">@_jeba</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>If I had a choice on what “hack” I’d prefer, it’d be noclip.</p>
<p>It really pisses me off having to walk around the fucking long way.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/runescape-glitch-attempts-updated/363801/31">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/runescape-glitch-attempts-updated/363801/31</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 22 Oct 2010 07:45:52 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-363801-31</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/runescape-glitch-attempts-updated/363801.rss">RuneScape Glitch Attempts (Updated)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>RuneScape Glitch Attempts (Updated)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@marcbob marcbob]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/marcbob">@marcbob</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>if you can do this stuff, then that would be insane!!</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/runescape-glitch-attempts-updated/363801/30">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/runescape-glitch-attempts-updated/363801/30</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 22 Oct 2010 01:10:16 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-363801-30</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/runescape-glitch-attempts-updated/363801.rss">RuneScape Glitch Attempts (Updated)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>RuneScape Glitch Attempts (Updated)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@EmulousGuru EmulousGuru]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/emulousguru">@EmulousGuru</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>noez.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/runescape-glitch-attempts-updated/363801/29">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/runescape-glitch-attempts-updated/363801/29</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Oct 2010 21:16:56 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-363801-29</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/runescape-glitch-attempts-updated/363801.rss">RuneScape Glitch Attempts (Updated)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>RuneScape Glitch Attempts (Updated)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@prison190 prison190]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/prison190">@prison190</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“EmulousGuru, post:27, topic:363801”][quote author=c|p link=topic=460043.msg3376595#msg3376595 date=1287671694]<br>
while scanning the lunix server(which runescape is ran on), I came across a java hack that confuses the kernal.</p>
<p>[/quote]<br>
wat be dis ‘lunix’ serber?[/quote]</p>
<p>Are you asking what lunix is?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/runescape-glitch-attempts-updated/363801/28">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/runescape-glitch-attempts-updated/363801/28</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Oct 2010 20:52:01 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-363801-28</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/runescape-glitch-attempts-updated/363801.rss">RuneScape Glitch Attempts (Updated)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>RuneScape Glitch Attempts (Updated)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@EmulousGuru EmulousGuru]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/emulousguru">@EmulousGuru</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote no-group" data-post="26" data-topic="363801">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 c|p:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>while scanning the lunix server(which runescape is ran on), I came across a java hack that confuses the kernal.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>wat be dis ‘lunix’ serber?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/runescape-glitch-attempts-updated/363801/27">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/runescape-glitch-attempts-updated/363801/27</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Oct 2010 20:49:04 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-363801-27</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/runescape-glitch-attempts-updated/363801.rss">RuneScape Glitch Attempts (Updated)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>RuneScape Glitch Attempts (Updated)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Cheese_Police c|p]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/cheese_police">@Cheese_Police</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>while scanning the lunix server(which runescape is ran on), I came across a java hack that confuses the kernal.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/runescape-glitch-attempts-updated/363801/26">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/runescape-glitch-attempts-updated/363801/26</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Oct 2010 14:34:54 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-363801-26</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/runescape-glitch-attempts-updated/363801.rss">RuneScape Glitch Attempts (Updated)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>RuneScape Glitch Attempts (Updated)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@prison190 prison190]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/prison190">@prison190</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“EmulousGuru, post:24, topic:363801”][quote author=prison190 link=topic=460043.msg3375939#msg3375939 date=1287614330]<br>
Um no one awnserd my question, who knows any commands that j-mods can do?</p>
<p>is it the same basic’s as you can do in most rsps?<br>
[/quote]<br>
I believe JaGeX staff only use commands for debugging.<br>
If the were testing something, they would use a specific world to test it on, and it wouldn’t happen by a command.[/quote]</p>
<p>Hmm, all of this is very interesting, could you pretty please go into more detail?  <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/smiley.png?v=5" title=":smiley:" class="emoji" alt=":smiley:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/runescape-glitch-attempts-updated/363801/25">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/runescape-glitch-attempts-updated/363801/25</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 20 Oct 2010 22:45:51 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-363801-25</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/runescape-glitch-attempts-updated/363801.rss">RuneScape Glitch Attempts (Updated)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>RuneScape Glitch Attempts (Updated)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@EmulousGuru EmulousGuru]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/emulousguru">@EmulousGuru</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“prison190, post:23, topic:363801”]Um no one awnserd my question, who knows any commands that j-mods can do?</p>
<p>is it the same basic’s as you can do in most rsps?[/quote]<br>
I believe JaGeX staff only use commands for debugging.<br>
If the were testing something, they would use a specific world to test it on, and it wouldn’t happen by a command.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/runescape-glitch-attempts-updated/363801/24">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/runescape-glitch-attempts-updated/363801/24</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 20 Oct 2010 22:44:39 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-363801-24</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/runescape-glitch-attempts-updated/363801.rss">RuneScape Glitch Attempts (Updated)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>RuneScape Glitch Attempts (Updated)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@prison190 prison190]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/prison190">@prison190</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Um no one awnserd my question, who knows any commands that j-mods can do?</p>
<p>is it the same basic’s as you can do in most rsps?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/runescape-glitch-attempts-updated/363801/23">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/runescape-glitch-attempts-updated/363801/23</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 20 Oct 2010 22:38:50 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-363801-23</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/runescape-glitch-attempts-updated/363801.rss">RuneScape Glitch Attempts (Updated)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>RuneScape Glitch Attempts (Updated)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@jc22493 Jc22493]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/jc22493">@jc22493</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“Rich, post:20, topic:363801”][quote author=QuestMaster 2K10 link=topic=460043.msg3365616#msg3365616 date=1286749012]<br>
<span class="bbcode-b">Bypassing the Chat Filter</span></p>
<p>I’ve been studying a RuneScape Private-Server i’ve made. And i’ve reviewed a chat glitch that I have on my chat filtering system. The letter y can’t be said on the server, because the stream methods for the packet are incorrect. But the server registered it as an Alt-Code that was being inputed, and as a reaction logged in the player out. (Of course, I fixed it). But if we can figure some sort of sequence of text, or an Alt-Code that can be used, we can register it to the chat filter on RuneScape, causing a glitch similiar that happened to me. It will log everybody out in the surrounding area, once the text would be said. Only those who have chat turned OFF won’t be logged out, because it won’t appear on their client. This would be a good advantage to use if you were in a Wilderness world, and are about to die, you would be able to log everybody out and kill them for free!<br>
[/quote]<br>
Wasn’t this done already, and patched?[/quote]<br>
Yes, with the mu symbol.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/runescape-glitch-attempts-updated/363801/22">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/runescape-glitch-attempts-updated/363801/22</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 20 Oct 2010 19:02:24 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-363801-22</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/runescape-glitch-attempts-updated/363801.rss">RuneScape Glitch Attempts (Updated)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>RuneScape Glitch Attempts (Updated)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@_jeba `jeba]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/_jeba">@_jeba</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“QuestMaster 2K10, post:1, topic:363801”]<span class="bbcode-b">Bypassing the Chat Filter</span></p>
<p>I’ve been studying a RuneScape Private-Server i’ve made. And i’ve reviewed a chat glitch that I have on my chat filtering system. The letter y can’t be said on the server, because the stream methods for the packet are incorrect. But the server registered it as an Alt-Code that was being inputed, and as a reaction logged in the player out. (Of course, I fixed it). But if we can figure some sort of sequence of text, or an Alt-Code that can be used, we can register it to the chat filter on RuneScape, causing a glitch similiar that happened to me. It will log everybody out in the surrounding area, once the text would be said. Only those who have chat turned OFF won’t be logged out, because it won’t appear on their client. This would be a good advantage to use if you were in a Wilderness world, and are about to die, you would be able to log everybody out and kill them for free![/quote]</p>
<p>Alt code was fixed in around 492. As people were using such words as Assh(Alt255)ole and it would appear as “Asshole”.</p>
<p>As for noclipping, it’s been done multiple times, I believe it’s called “force-movement”. I may be wrong.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/runescape-glitch-attempts-updated/363801/21">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/runescape-glitch-attempts-updated/363801/21</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 20 Oct 2010 06:37:59 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-363801-21</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/runescape-glitch-attempts-updated/363801.rss">RuneScape Glitch Attempts (Updated)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>RuneScape Glitch Attempts (Updated)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@_Rich Rich]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/_rich">@_Rich</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“QuestMaster 2K10, post:1, topic:363801”]<span class="bbcode-b">Bypassing the Chat Filter</span></p>
<p>I’ve been studying a RuneScape Private-Server i’ve made. And i’ve reviewed a chat glitch that I have on my chat filtering system. The letter y can’t be said on the server, because the stream methods for the packet are incorrect. But the server registered it as an Alt-Code that was being inputed, and as a reaction logged in the player out. (Of course, I fixed it). But if we can figure some sort of sequence of text, or an Alt-Code that can be used, we can register it to the chat filter on RuneScape, causing a glitch similiar that happened to me. It will log everybody out in the surrounding area, once the text would be said. Only those who have chat turned OFF won’t be logged out, because it won’t appear on their client. This would be a good advantage to use if you were in a Wilderness world, and are about to die, you would be able to log everybody out and kill them for free![/quote]<br>
Wasn’t this done already, and patched?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/runescape-glitch-attempts-updated/363801/20">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/runescape-glitch-attempts-updated/363801/20</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 20 Oct 2010 03:20:30 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-363801-20</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/runescape-glitch-attempts-updated/363801.rss">RuneScape Glitch Attempts (Updated)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>RuneScape Glitch Attempts (Updated)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@badger41 badger41]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/badger41">@badger41</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>very intriguing. some of those descriptions sound plausible.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/runescape-glitch-attempts-updated/363801/19">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/runescape-glitch-attempts-updated/363801/19</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 20 Oct 2010 01:57:09 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-363801-19</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/runescape-glitch-attempts-updated/363801.rss">RuneScape Glitch Attempts (Updated)</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
