<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>(rs) clan tsl reqruiting</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rs-clan-tsl-reqruiting/45340</link>
    <description>hi my name is adiosk8r93 from the runescape clan the slayers lair... here are some of the things that our clan has... we are a very active clan most of us are on about 5 hours a day... 80+ combat plz... and when filling out your clan application tell them adiosk8r93 reqruited you


[IMG]http://img131.imageshack.us/img131/7692/slayerslair2pv2.gif[/img]

[align=center][b][URL=http://www.runehead.com/clans/ml.php?clan=Miner69er8]Members[/URL] - [URL=http://z11.invisionfree.com/RS_TSL/index.php?act=idx]Forums[/URL][/b]

[b]Welcome to The Slayer&#39;s Lair Recruitment Topic![/b]

[b]Introduction[/b]

[b]Thank you, for taking your time out and viewing this topic. The Slayer&#39;s Lair is a clan that has been through alot over the past couple of years. This clan was a top clan at one point in time but after going through hardships the clan crumbled down. Now The Slayer&#39;s Lair has been rebuilt and reconstructured with a new leadership team. This clan is based on a democracy, From my years of experience I have learned that it&#39;s what the members want. We will vote on any important debates to prevent questions and controversy, because quite frankly without the members a clan would be absolutely nothing.[/b]

[b]The Clan[/b]

[b]The Slayer&#39;s Lair is a great place to find new friends. We will welcome you with open arms. We have a great community and atmosphere. We have a chat room which you can find us in, #tsl. Stop in and say hi![/b]


[b]Events:[/b]

Player Killing Trips
King Black Dragon Killing
Kalphite Queen
Money Making
Combat Competitions
Friendly Wars
Full Out Wars
And Other Fun Events



New Pictures Coming Soon!!

[IMG]http://img292.imageshack.us/img292/2234/tsl5jg3.png[/img]

We Like War.

[b]Leader
Miner69er8 - 100

Advisor
All_Must_Dye - 93

Cabinent
Dragulan - 94[/b]

Position are open!!![/align]</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 07 Jan 2007 21:33:23 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rs-clan-tsl-reqruiting/45340.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>(rs) clan tsl reqruiting</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@adiosk8r93 adiosk8r93]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/adiosk8r93">@adiosk8r93</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>hi my name is adiosk8r93 from the runescape clan the slayers lair… here are some of the things that our clan has… we are a very active clan most of us are on about 5 hours a day… 80+ combat plz… and when filling out your clan application tell them adiosk8r93 reqruited you</p>
<p><img src="http://img131.imageshack.us/img131/7692/slayerslair2pv2.gif" alt width="" height=""></p>
<p>[align=center]<span class="bbcode-b"><a href="http://www.runehead.com/clans/ml.php?clan=Miner69er8" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">Members</a> - <a href="http://z11.invisionfree.com/RS_TSL/index.php?act=idx" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">Forums</a></span></p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Welcome to The Slayer’s Lair Recruitment Topic!</span></p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Introduction</span></p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Thank you, for taking your time out and viewing this topic. The Slayer’s Lair is a clan that has been through alot over the past couple of years. This clan was a top clan at one point in time but after going through hardships the clan crumbled down. Now The Slayer’s Lair has been rebuilt and reconstructured with a new leadership team. This clan is based on a democracy, From my years of experience I have learned that it’s what the members want. We will vote on any important debates to prevent questions and controversy, because quite frankly without the members a clan would be absolutely nothing.</span></p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">The Clan</span></p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">The Slayer’s Lair is a great place to find new friends. We will welcome you with open arms. We have a great community and atmosphere. We have a chat room which you can find us in, <span class="hashtag">#tsl</span>. Stop in and say hi!</span></p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Events:</span></p>
<p>Player Killing Trips<br>
King Black Dragon Killing<br>
Kalphite Queen<br>
Money Making<br>
Combat Competitions<br>
Friendly Wars<br>
Full Out Wars<br>
And Other Fun Events</p>
<p>New Pictures Coming Soon!!</p>
<p><img src="http://img292.imageshack.us/img292/2234/tsl5jg3.png" alt width="" height=""></p>
<p>We Like War.</p>
<p>[b]Leader<br>
Miner69er8 - 100</p>
<p>Advisor<br>
All_Must_Dye - 93</p>
<p>Cabinent<br>
Dragulan - 94[/b]</p>
<p>Position are open!!![/align]</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rs-clan-tsl-reqruiting/45340/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rs-clan-tsl-reqruiting/45340/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jan 2007 21:33:23 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-45340-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rs-clan-tsl-reqruiting/45340.rss">(rs) clan tsl reqruiting</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
