<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>A remix idea of SkyBlock [360]</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/a-remix-idea-of-skyblock-360/469991</link>
    <description>  Now I was making my own skyblock after wanting a skyblock for my minecraft, but would like it on the xbox 360.  While making my skyblock i covered the entire floor with lava, so when you fell off you would die, but then a idea came into my head....  I decided to add other small islands (similar to the one you start at), yet after thinking about it another idea came into my head  :P.  What about creating a story, so it makes people want to play it  :).  I decided to sorta base it off of kingdom hearts, yet the Disney characters or any kingdom hearts characters aren&#39;t their, instead I&#39;ll use custom islands based off of the characters you can chose from when you go to &quot;change skin&quot; in the menu.
  
 Heres what i got for a somewhat intro to the game

First pictures of what I&#39;m taking about as spaceship connected to the island
*front*(the tree is regular size i just did a rough making of it on the computer)
[IMG]http://i47.tinypic.com/mh7pxh.png[/img]

*back*
[IMG]http://i45.tinypic.com/2qt9udd.png[/img]
[IMG]http://i45.tinypic.com/2w56nue.png[/img]

*starting in the chest*(the items are random to set the storyline, yet also follow SkyBlocks challenges) 
[IMG]http://i46.tinypic.com/2qtdfes.png[/img]


  You where traveling with a friend(which is a high power person in the pumpkin kingdom) through a unknown planet and suddenly your ship gets hit and you get knocked out. When you wake up you find a note that tells you that your friend had to leave to go back home and help his kingdom against a unknown evil and has landed you on a small island and wants you to try and rebuild the planet.  He also goes on saying he has left you a chest to help you out on your journey and says to try and find his kingdom.  You then go on top and start your journey.

The idea is for you to explore my extending your island to other islands randomly placed on the map to lead up to the storyline that i will be placing in after I created the islands...Then ending will be known as you have gotten all the cd disk at are hidden on other islands.


Tell me what you think of my idea?  I&#39;m just trying to create something on minecraft that won&#39;t make me fall asleep with having a storyline to help push on  :)</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 26 Nov 2012 05:11:08 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Minecraft</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/a-remix-idea-of-skyblock-360/469991.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>A remix idea of SkyBlock [360]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@MrFun MrFun]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/mrfun">@MrFun</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Now I was making my own skyblock after wanting a skyblock for my minecraft, but would like it on the xbox 360.  While making my skyblock i covered the entire floor with lava, so when you fell off you would die, but then a idea came into my head…  I decided to add other small islands (similar to the one you start at), yet after thinking about it another idea came into my head  :P.  What about creating a story, so it makes people want to play it  :).  I decided to sorta base it off of kingdom hearts, yet the Disney characters or any kingdom hearts characters aren’t their, instead I’ll use custom islands based off of the characters you can chose from when you go to “change skin” in the menu.</p>
<p>Heres what i got for a somewhat intro to the game</p>
<p>First pictures of what I’m taking about as spaceship connected to the island<br>
<em>front</em>(the tree is regular size i just did a rough making of it on the computer)<br>
<img src="http://i47.tinypic.com/mh7pxh.png" alt width="309" height="292"></p>
<p><em>back</em><br>
<img src="http://i45.tinypic.com/2qt9udd.png" alt width="305" height="243"><br>
<img src="http://i45.tinypic.com/2w56nue.png" alt width="576" height="417"></p>
<p><em>starting in the chest</em>(the items are random to set the storyline, yet also follow SkyBlocks challenges)<br>
<img src="http://i46.tinypic.com/2qtdfes.png" alt width="436" height="182"></p>
<p>You where traveling with a friend(which is a high power person in the pumpkin kingdom) through a unknown planet and suddenly your ship gets hit and you get knocked out. When you wake up you find a note that tells you that your friend had to leave to go back home and help his kingdom against a unknown evil and has landed you on a small island and wants you to try and rebuild the planet.  He also goes on saying he has left you a chest to help you out on your journey and says to try and find his kingdom.  You then go on top and start your journey.</p>
<p>The idea is for you to explore my extending your island to other islands randomly placed on the map to lead up to the storyline that i will be placing in after I created the islands…Then ending will be known as you have gotten all the cd disk at are hidden on other islands.</p>
<p>Tell me what you think of my idea?  I’m just trying to create something on minecraft that won’t make me fall asleep with having a storyline to help push on  <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=5" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/a-remix-idea-of-skyblock-360/469991/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/a-remix-idea-of-skyblock-360/469991/1</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 26 Nov 2012 05:11:08 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-469991-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/a-remix-idea-of-skyblock-360/469991.rss">A remix idea of SkyBlock [360]</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
