<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Blasphemy and Treachery</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/blasphemy-and-treachery/392261</link>
    <description>My brothers, over the course of the past few weeks, Jagex has been gradually screwing us many times over. First, the issue with the servers when they showed they were offline, but were actually playable. That was ok - we could have let that by and considering it the annual mess up of Jagex. But then matters were fluctuated to the next level when they updated the ring of wealth. At first, everything seemed to be adequate - no, they seemed to be expected from Jagex updates. You could even say the update was commensurate. But behold! A nasty, hellish bug was discovered by a group of baleful, malicious players manipulated by the mentioned group of players to inaugurate scores and scores of drops and loot. News about the bug started to propagate amongst close groups of player bug abusers, and oh what wonderful abuse! The bug was abused to gather billions of gps worth of drops, and Jagex literally knew nothing about it. Some cunning minds figured they could abuse the bug to relieve the higher leveled monsters of their exquisite drops, one such monster being the corporal beast, where clans spanning huge amounts of players invaded the wild, quadruped critters stomping grounds and proceeded to eradicate the creature out of existence, earning a few hundred spirit shields as a result of the poor creatures demise. Jagex, being their natural tardy self, took over nine thousand multiplied by four seconds to finally catch on and realize there awas a bug in their so called &quot;feature&quot;. What happened following the incident was a series of horror inspiring decisions on Jagex&#39; part, leading up to them choosing to screw their player base even harder by deciding the ring still had to stay. To exacerbate matters, Jagex announced their most shocking decision: there would be no resets to players who had illegally profitted from the mentioned bug! It was an outrageous scandal! In light of these events, we are forced to conclude that Jagex in fact was compeltely aware of the bug, and they had introduced it into the game [b]on purpose[/b] to lure players to the dark side (membership) with promises of future bugs to come.

However, that was not the extent of Jagex&#39; crimes. A few weeks before, they updated one of their more useless skills, dungeoneering, and unknowingly (was it really unknowingly?) introduced another bug - the infamous null bug! Being the naturally resourceful bunch they are, Jagex&#39; faithful RuneScape players quickly found untapped potential in such unmined grounds. Adventure logs were soon filled with null kills and item drops, and made it easier to spoof accounts and sell gold. Naturally, warranted, verifiable gold sellers were saddened by such news. They held a meeting on World 81 of RuneScape at the Clan Wars lobby, and they came to a decision: gold prices had to rise - and they had to rise by such a large amount, people would think twice - no three times - before buying gold from a gold spoofer. True to their word, an aggrandizement of prices soon took hold of the black market, and trade dropped to extremely low activity. Was this a coincidence? I think not. You see, Jagex thought of new, innovative ways of how to discourage black trade, and the only way they thought of was introducing a &quot;bug&quot; into the game, then claiming it was all just an error on their part a few months later. To date, this bug has still not been fixed, and gold prices are still overblown.

And now this! They have disconnected the servers, preventing multitudes of players from continuing their lives or botting their accounts! Tell me, Jagex, have you no hearts? No feelings, no mercy, no nothing? If you can imagine the sound of a young, 16 year old teenager crying because he cannot run his bot without cringing and rushing to update your servers, then you are truly heartless, my friends and deserve no place at the top of our hierarchy.

But even that, dearest of my dearest, was clearly not enough for Jagex! They have been subtly adding new bugs into the system, and are waiting for the right moment to spring their traps upon [b]us[/b], their faithful players, dating back to the golden days of 2001!

The meaning of this, my kin, is crystal clear. There is only one logical conclusion, and that is one only a handful of people have come to recognize. My friends, my brothers, my sisters, my [i]dearest[/i].. Judgement day has arrived.

but will we stand for this? [b]no[/b], my comrades! We will revolt! We must unite under one banner, as we were before the God Wars seperated us! We must march together, hand in hand, against the common enemy. But who is this enemy, you ask? Well my friends, the enemy is none other than the RuneScape gods.

Surprised? Yes! I was surprised as well, that such [b]treachery[/b] has wormed its way into our gods minds, and has taken hold of their thoughts! At first, I was inclined to believe our enemy was Jagex, but after further investigation, Jagex appears to only be the figurehead, the plain view, call it whatever you like. The real driving force behind the company is the force of the gods. They control our destiny, and hold our lives in their hands.

But [b]we will not stand for this madness[/b]. We must turn against them. Yes my friends, you heard correct - we will turn against the gods, no matter how absurd that might sound! Guthix, Saradomin, Zamorak, Zaros, Bandos, Armadyl - what are they, if not bitter, merciless creatures of one mind, one thought and desire - the desire to eradicate us all? Even the God Wars were only a small part of the great jigsaw of the gods&#39; plans. Their only desire was to eradicate the presence of humanity on Gielinor, and they narrowly failed. It was only by a stroke of luck that humanity was saved - Guthix, being the lazy beast he is, was awakened by the combat and bloodshed, and with a mighty roar cast a sleeping spell on the combatants, causing them to slumber for decades to come. Naturally, the gods were enraged with Guthix, because he had caused the plans demise at the peak of its success, but they failed to avenge their bruised prides and egos because Guthix took to hiding and sleeping for another few decades. So now I must ask you, my dearest - who is with me?

*cheering ensues*

My friends, we must band together under the banner of a new ideal I have designed - this religion I call playerism! No longer shall our big headed friends at Jagex control our lives! We must show our strength, and combined together, that strength is indeed fearful! I shake in anticipation just imagining the extent of what we could do - we could go beyond all limits, even becoming gods ourselves! But no matter what, we must always avoid thinking like our current gods - players&#39; lives are their own to handle! We are not cattle to send to the slaughterhouse as you will, [i]gods of Gielinor![/i] We are humans - And We.. Will.. Show.. Our.. [b]Strength[/b]!</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 24 Apr 2011 00:26:51 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/blasphemy-and-treachery/392261.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Blasphemy and Treachery</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@deathschaos9 DeathsChaos9]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/deathschaos9">@deathschaos9</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Successful troll is successful.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/blasphemy-and-treachery/392261/37">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/blasphemy-and-treachery/392261/37</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 24 Apr 2011 00:26:51 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-392261-37</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/blasphemy-and-treachery/392261.rss">Blasphemy and Treachery</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Blasphemy and Treachery</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Svitkona Svitkona]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/svitkona">@Svitkona</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“reyx7, post:35, topic:392261”][quote author=ytuio9 link=topic=489428.msg3578378#msg3578378 date=1303603791]</p>
<aside class="quote">
<blockquote>
<p>No wonder my ring finger hurt when I was killing that corporeal beast with my friends. The shining started to burn.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Yes, corey! It was all a set up by Jagex, intentional bugs brought to the game with hidden motives that players haven’t comprehended yet! That is why I preach playerism, but alas, my job is a hard one…<br>
[/quote]<br>
Oh my god just shut up already…[/quote]<br>
I implore you, reyx7, search deep within your heart. All the times you have felt Jagex was toying with us, all the times you felt like someone was watching you, whispering in your brains, pushing you to the dark side, all these times you were sensing the truth! Jagex is controlling us, and if we do not fight back, we shall forever be under their thrall and domain!</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/blasphemy-and-treachery/392261/36">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/blasphemy-and-treachery/392261/36</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 24 Apr 2011 00:23:05 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-392261-36</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/blasphemy-and-treachery/392261.rss">Blasphemy and Treachery</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Blasphemy and Treachery</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@reyx7 reyx7]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/reyx7">@reyx7</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“ytuio9, post:34, topic:392261”][quote author=LilXCj link=topic=489428.msg3578373#msg3578373 date=1303603631]<br>
No wonder my ring finger hurt when I was killing that corporeal beast with my friends. The shining started to burn.<br>
[/quote]<br>
Yes, corey! It was all a set up by Jagex, intentional bugs brought to the game with hidden motives that players haven’t comprehended yet! That is why I preach playerism, but alas, my job is a hard one…[/quote]<br>
Oh my god just shut up already…</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/blasphemy-and-treachery/392261/35">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/blasphemy-and-treachery/392261/35</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 24 Apr 2011 00:16:45 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-392261-35</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/blasphemy-and-treachery/392261.rss">Blasphemy and Treachery</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Blasphemy and Treachery</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Svitkona Svitkona]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/svitkona">@Svitkona</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote" data-post="33" data-topic="392261">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/lilxcj/40/5_e05bb34c421432ee4d40de30c10af3e5.png" class="avatar"> LilXCj:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>No wonder my ring finger hurt when I was killing that corporeal beast with my friends. The shining started to burn.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Yes, corey! It was all a set up by Jagex, intentional bugs brought to the game with hidden motives that players haven’t comprehended yet! That is why I preach playerism, but alas, my job is a hard one…</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/blasphemy-and-treachery/392261/34">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/blasphemy-and-treachery/392261/34</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 24 Apr 2011 00:09:51 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-392261-34</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/blasphemy-and-treachery/392261.rss">Blasphemy and Treachery</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Blasphemy and Treachery</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@LilXCj LilXCj]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/lilxcj">@LilXCj</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>No wonder my ring finger hurt when I was killing that corporeal beast with my friends. The shining started to burn.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/blasphemy-and-treachery/392261/33">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/blasphemy-and-treachery/392261/33</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 24 Apr 2011 00:07:11 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-392261-33</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/blasphemy-and-treachery/392261.rss">Blasphemy and Treachery</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Blasphemy and Treachery</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Svitkona Svitkona]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/svitkona">@Svitkona</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“reyx7, post:30, topic:392261”][quote author=badger41 link=topic=489428.msg3578354#msg3578354 date=1303602662]<br>
i stopped reading halfway through because you are so ignorant of the matters that the level of facepalm i had was too immense to continue.<br>
[/quote]<br>
I know, when he started talking about Jagex STOPPING bots, and how that is a crime, I was pretty much ready to punch him in the face.[/quote]<br>
My friend, it is you who needs to aquire skills of reading and listening, for never in my post have I mentioned bots.</p>
<aside class="quote" data-post="29" data-topic="392261">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/badger41/40/5_e05bb34c421432ee4d40de30c10af3e5.png" class="avatar"> badger41:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>i stopped reading halfway through because you are so ignorant of the matters that the level of facepalm i had was too immense to continue.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Dear badger41, open your eyes to the world! Look around you, and notice all the crimes and atrocities that occur - and for what? For the <span class="bbcode-i">gods</span>? Tear down that shroud upon your eyes, and you shall reach your full potential as a level 138 player!</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/blasphemy-and-treachery/392261/32">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/blasphemy-and-treachery/392261/32</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 24 Apr 2011 00:02:03 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-392261-32</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/blasphemy-and-treachery/392261.rss">Blasphemy and Treachery</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Blasphemy and Treachery</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@nacional nacional]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/nacional">@nacional</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I believe everything in here blindly. Let my martyr not go in vain.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/blasphemy-and-treachery/392261/31">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/blasphemy-and-treachery/392261/31</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 23 Apr 2011 23:53:40 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-392261-31</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/blasphemy-and-treachery/392261.rss">Blasphemy and Treachery</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Blasphemy and Treachery</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@reyx7 reyx7]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/reyx7">@reyx7</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote" data-post="29" data-topic="392261">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/badger41/40/5_e05bb34c421432ee4d40de30c10af3e5.png" class="avatar"> badger41:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>i stopped reading halfway through because you are so ignorant of the matters that the level of facepalm i had was too immense to continue.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I know, when he started talking about Jagex STOPPING bots, and how that is a crime, I was pretty much ready to punch him in the face.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/blasphemy-and-treachery/392261/30">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/blasphemy-and-treachery/392261/30</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 23 Apr 2011 23:52:01 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-392261-30</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/blasphemy-and-treachery/392261.rss">Blasphemy and Treachery</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Blasphemy and Treachery</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@badger41 badger41]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/badger41">@badger41</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>i stopped reading halfway through because you are so ignorant of the matters that the level of facepalm i had was too immense to continue.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/blasphemy-and-treachery/392261/29">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/blasphemy-and-treachery/392261/29</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 23 Apr 2011 23:51:02 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-392261-29</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/blasphemy-and-treachery/392261.rss">Blasphemy and Treachery</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Blasphemy and Treachery</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@reyx7 reyx7]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/reyx7">@reyx7</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Someone’s been doing to much L.A.R.P.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/blasphemy-and-treachery/392261/28">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/blasphemy-and-treachery/392261/28</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 23 Apr 2011 23:50:01 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-392261-28</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/blasphemy-and-treachery/392261.rss">Blasphemy and Treachery</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Blasphemy and Treachery</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Svitkona Svitkona]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/svitkona">@Svitkona</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“Mack n cheese, post:25, topic:392261”]too long.</p>
<p>some one sum this up for me in a simple 4-5 sentences[/quote]<br>
In a world where atrocious gods rule, it is to be expected that people will not want to put any effort in anything. I emplore you, brother, rescind the villanious suggestions! Abolish the gods, and you shall become free of any opressors, at liberty to act as you will and wish!</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/blasphemy-and-treachery/392261/27">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/blasphemy-and-treachery/392261/27</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 23 Apr 2011 23:43:54 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-392261-27</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/blasphemy-and-treachery/392261.rss">Blasphemy and Treachery</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Blasphemy and Treachery</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@krackkid Krackkid]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/krackkid">@krackkid</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“Mack n cheese, post:25, topic:392261”]too long.</p>
<p>some one sum this up for me in a simple 4-5 sentences[/quote]Join the power of the gods, not the people! Join us brother and we will fight besides our gods!</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/blasphemy-and-treachery/392261/26">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/blasphemy-and-treachery/392261/26</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 23 Apr 2011 23:42:21 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-392261-26</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/blasphemy-and-treachery/392261.rss">Blasphemy and Treachery</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Blasphemy and Treachery</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Mack_n_cheese Mack n cheese]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/mack_n_cheese">@Mack_n_cheese</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>too long.</p>
<p>some one sum this up for me in a simple 4-5 sentences</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/blasphemy-and-treachery/392261/25">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/blasphemy-and-treachery/392261/25</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 23 Apr 2011 23:38:22 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-392261-25</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/blasphemy-and-treachery/392261.rss">Blasphemy and Treachery</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Blasphemy and Treachery</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Svitkona Svitkona]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/svitkona">@Svitkona</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“krackkid, post:23, topic:392261”][quote author=asshole_rule link=topic=489428.msg3578329#msg3578329 date=1303601165]</p>
<p>[quote author=krackkid link=topic=489428.msg3578318#msg3578318 date=1303600695]</p>
<aside class="quote">
<blockquote>
<aside class="quote">
<blockquote>
<p>I see now, the almighty gods have shown the way of this post, forever now I shall be changed.</p>
<p>I hope my brothers will follow the powers of the gods.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>My friend, the gods are our enemy! Their ultimate goal is our extinction and eradication from Gielinor!<br>
[/quote]No my brother you got this all wrong, the gods are gonna give us there powers to help them! They are on our sides them are evil clones fighting you must trust me.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>You’ve opened my eyes.</p>
<p>KILL YTUIO9<br>
[/quote]YES MY BROTHER ATTACK HIM! With the gods power we shall win![/quote]<br>
You shall not pass!</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/blasphemy-and-treachery/392261/24">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/blasphemy-and-treachery/392261/24</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 23 Apr 2011 23:27:55 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-392261-24</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/blasphemy-and-treachery/392261.rss">Blasphemy and Treachery</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Blasphemy and Treachery</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@krackkid Krackkid]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/krackkid">@krackkid</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“asshole_rule, post:22, topic:392261”][quote author=krackkid link=topic=489428.msg3578318#msg3578318 date=1303600695]</p>
<aside class="quote">
<blockquote>
<aside class="quote">
<blockquote>
<p>I see now, the almighty gods have shown the way of this post, forever now I shall be changed.</p>
<p>I hope my brothers will follow the powers of the gods.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>My friend, the gods are our enemy! Their ultimate goal is our extinction and eradication from Gielinor!<br>
[/quote]No my brother you got this all wrong, the gods are gonna give us there powers to help them! They are on our sides them are evil clones fighting you must trust me.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>You’ve opened my eyes.</p>
<p>KILL YTUIO9[/quote]YES MY BROTHER ATTACK HIM! With the gods power we shall win!</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/blasphemy-and-treachery/392261/23">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/blasphemy-and-treachery/392261/23</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 23 Apr 2011 23:27:05 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-392261-23</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/blasphemy-and-treachery/392261.rss">Blasphemy and Treachery</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Blasphemy and Treachery</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@asshole_rule asshole_rule]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/asshole_rule">@asshole_rule</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“krackkid, post:17, topic:392261”][quote author=ytuio9 link=topic=489428.msg3578314#msg3578314 date=1303600479]</p>
<aside class="quote">
<blockquote>
<p>I see now, the almighty gods have shown the way of this post, forever now I shall be changed.</p>
<p>I hope my brothers will follow the powers of the gods.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>My friend, the gods are our enemy! Their ultimate goal is our extinction and eradication from Gielinor!<br>
[/quote]No my brother you got this all wrong, the gods are gonna give us there powers to help them! They are on our sides them are evil clones fighting you must trust me.[/quote]</p>
<p>You’ve opened my eyes.</p>
<p>KILL YTUIO9</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/blasphemy-and-treachery/392261/22">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/blasphemy-and-treachery/392261/22</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 23 Apr 2011 23:26:05 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-392261-22</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/blasphemy-and-treachery/392261.rss">Blasphemy and Treachery</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Blasphemy and Treachery</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Svitkona Svitkona]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/svitkona">@Svitkona</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote quote-modified" data-post="19" data-topic="392261">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/krackkid/40/5_e05bb34c421432ee4d40de30c10af3e5.png" class="avatar"> krackkid:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Lets go raise our arms my brothers! FIGHT WITH THE GODS! NOT AGAINST!!! They are our friends.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>History has proven to us countless times how evil the gods are! They will turn us against each other, forever doomed in our blindness!</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/blasphemy-and-treachery/392261/21">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/blasphemy-and-treachery/392261/21</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 23 Apr 2011 23:25:57 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-392261-21</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/blasphemy-and-treachery/392261.rss">Blasphemy and Treachery</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Blasphemy and Treachery</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@rant rant]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/rant">@rant</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Eh fagex deserves this, i personally haven’t played runescape in years, but hell i’m gonna have some fun spreading the info about rs bugs.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/blasphemy-and-treachery/392261/20">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/blasphemy-and-treachery/392261/20</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 23 Apr 2011 23:24:50 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-392261-20</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/blasphemy-and-treachery/392261.rss">Blasphemy and Treachery</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Blasphemy and Treachery</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@krackkid Krackkid]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/krackkid">@krackkid</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Lets go raise our arms my brothers! FIGHT WITH THE GODS! NOT AGAINST!!! They are our friends.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/blasphemy-and-treachery/392261/19">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/blasphemy-and-treachery/392261/19</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 23 Apr 2011 23:23:15 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-392261-19</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/blasphemy-and-treachery/392261.rss">Blasphemy and Treachery</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Blasphemy and Treachery</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Svitkona Svitkona]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/svitkona">@Svitkona</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“krackkid, post:17, topic:392261”][quote author=ytuio9 link=topic=489428.msg3578314#msg3578314 date=1303600479]</p>
<aside class="quote">
<blockquote>
<p>I see now, the almighty gods have shown the way of this post, forever now I shall be changed.</p>
<p>I hope my brothers will follow the powers of the gods.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>My friend, the gods are our enemy! Their ultimate goal is our extinction and eradication from Gielinor!<br>
[/quote]No my brother you got this all wrong, the gods are gonna give us there powers to help them! They are on our sides them are evil clones fighting you must trust me.[/quote]<br>
No, they are the evil figures that aret he cause of Gielinors demise! If we force them off their self-imposed thrones, victory shall forever belong to us!</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/blasphemy-and-treachery/392261/18">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/blasphemy-and-treachery/392261/18</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 23 Apr 2011 23:22:22 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-392261-18</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/blasphemy-and-treachery/392261.rss">Blasphemy and Treachery</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Blasphemy and Treachery</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@krackkid Krackkid]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/krackkid">@krackkid</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“ytuio9, post:16, topic:392261”][quote author=krackkid link=topic=489428.msg3578306#msg3578306 date=1303600126]<br>
I see now, the almighty gods have shown the way of this post, forever now I shall be changed.</p>
<p>I hope my brothers will follow the powers of the gods.<br>
[/quote]<br>
My friend, the gods are our enemy! Their ultimate goal is our extinction and eradication from Gielinor![/quote]No my brother you got this all wrong, the gods are gonna give us there powers to help them! They are on our sides them are evil clones fighting you must trust me.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/blasphemy-and-treachery/392261/17">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/blasphemy-and-treachery/392261/17</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 23 Apr 2011 23:18:15 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-392261-17</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/blasphemy-and-treachery/392261.rss">Blasphemy and Treachery</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Blasphemy and Treachery</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Svitkona Svitkona]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/svitkona">@Svitkona</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“krackkid, post:15, topic:392261”]I see now, the almighty gods have shown the way of this post, forever now I shall be changed.</p>
<p>I hope my brothers will follow the powers of the gods.[/quote]<br>
My friend, the gods are our enemy! Their ultimate goal is our extinction and eradication from Gielinor!</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/blasphemy-and-treachery/392261/16">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/blasphemy-and-treachery/392261/16</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 23 Apr 2011 23:14:39 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-392261-16</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/blasphemy-and-treachery/392261.rss">Blasphemy and Treachery</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Blasphemy and Treachery</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@krackkid Krackkid]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/krackkid">@krackkid</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I see now, the almighty gods have shown the way of this post, forever now I shall be changed.</p>
<p>I hope my brothers will follow the powers of the gods.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/blasphemy-and-treachery/392261/15">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/blasphemy-and-treachery/392261/15</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 23 Apr 2011 23:08:46 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-392261-15</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/blasphemy-and-treachery/392261.rss">Blasphemy and Treachery</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Blasphemy and Treachery</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Svitkona Svitkona]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/svitkona">@Svitkona</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote" data-post="13" data-topic="392261">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/ilikearrays/40/5_e05bb34c421432ee4d40de30c10af3e5.png" class="avatar"> IlikeArrays:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Runescape died with the release of rs2. Get over it.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>If you put enough effort into it, you can revive the deadest of humans with a simple cure spell. My friend, we must band together to overthrow the vengeful gods!</p>
<p>[quote=“krackkid, post:12, topic:392261”][quote author=ytuio9 link=topic=489428.msg3578280#msg3578280 date=1303599641]</p>
<aside class="quote">
<blockquote>
<p>Someone make this smaller please D:</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>My friend, if everybody would not spend at least some of their effort in the name of advancind playerism, then our cause will surely fail, and the gods will prevail!<br>
[/quote]Then I will say this</p>
<p>tl;dr, its complete shit, not worth reading, useless, stupid, to loong, loooong cat, etc, etc[/quote]<br>
It seems you have completely missed the principles of playerism. There is not much for me to do except hope that one day you will learn to fully see past the veil of darkness the gods have placed over your eyes.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/blasphemy-and-treachery/392261/14">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/blasphemy-and-treachery/392261/14</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 23 Apr 2011 23:07:10 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-392261-14</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/blasphemy-and-treachery/392261.rss">Blasphemy and Treachery</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Blasphemy and Treachery</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@IlikeArrays IlikeArrays]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/ilikearrays">@IlikeArrays</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Runescape died with the release of rs2. Get over it.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/blasphemy-and-treachery/392261/13">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/blasphemy-and-treachery/392261/13</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 23 Apr 2011 23:03:55 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-392261-13</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/blasphemy-and-treachery/392261.rss">Blasphemy and Treachery</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
