<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>UEDcra</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/uedcra/443933</link>
    <description>Hello all, I&#39;d like to welcome you all (again for some) to play with us on the UEDcraft server. Below this, you can find all most all of the details you would want to know about the server.

The Basics:
TeamSpeak
50 slot server
Features Faction based PvP, MCMMO, Multiple worlds, such as our up coming LOTR map, and a regularly held Hunger Games Tournament.
Special ranks, and benifits to to server donators, you can check the donations section of UEDcraft.com for more information.

The Server Hierarchy:

Ranks:
Member
Apprentice
Journeyman
Traveler
Pioneer
MIT
Mod
Head-Mod
Artisan-Admin
Tech-Admin
Head-Admin
Note: Apprentice through Pioneer can be obtained by donating.


The UEDcraft staff consist&#39;s of the following members:
Admins:
UED_iRx - Server owner and Head Admin.
NexGenInsanity - Our cheif builder, and Artisan Admin.
John_Dong - Our main man for server maint. and our Tech-Admin.

Moderators:
Shanks2112 - Head Moderator in charge of the Moderation team and event planner.
raw900 - Works directly with Shanks to keep the server going.
Tunbridge - One of two Moderators In Training (MIT), who reports issues to the rest of the staff.
ZombieKittenz - Our other MIT, helping Tunbridge report any server problems.

UEDcraft Sponsors:
We are proudly sponsored by the following:



SubZeroServers
Website: www.subzeroservers.net
Profile: A global force in the server hosting business. Providing high quality servers for: Voice, Games &amp; Web Hosting.

GamerPeer
Website: www.gamerpeer.com
Profile: The latest craze in gaming for those who want to connect with players all over the world quickly and without the fuss of long registration forms. A social networking website just for gamers! Find your perfect community for all the games you love here.

Xsplit
Website: www.xsplit.com
Profile: A world leader in screen capture technology used by world professionals on live streaming websites. The advanced technology allows you to use all the high end servers needed for quality streaming and the best price.

SpadeSocial
Website: www.spadesocial.com
Profile: Poker social networking heaven. Upload, view, discuss all the videos in the world of poker and stay ahead of the game by checking out the latest and greatest from the world of poker. Have one up on your friends about what&#39;s hot and what&#39;s not quickly and without fuss. A world of poker ready for you to watch without the red tape.

NinjaCoders
Website: www.ninja-coders.com
Profile: Take the hardship out of Minecraft with the Android App developed by the technological wizards at NinjaCoders. Minecraft Canary is just one of the award winning Apps you can download for your Android device and give you the edge in the game. Tons of quick tutorials of how to make anything in the game including the secret tool &quot;Canary&quot; which keeps track of day/night times and tells you when its about to be day/night! Cool huh? You can download their app from the app store at any time.


For more information, visit www.uedcraft.com, and have a look around our forums. If you still have questions for us, contact a staff member.

Server IP: 69.64.34.39:25615</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 04 Jun 2012 02:00:41 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Minecraft</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/uedcra/443933.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>UEDcra</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@LostSilver LostSilver]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/lostsilver">@LostSilver</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Hello all, I’d like to welcome you all (again for some) to play with us on the UEDcraft server. Below this, you can find all most all of the details you would want to know about the server.</p>
<p>The Basics:<br>
TeamSpeak<br>
50 slot server<br>
Features Faction based PvP, MCMMO, Multiple worlds, such as our up coming LOTR map, and a regularly held Hunger Games Tournament.<br>
Special ranks, and benifits to to server donators, you can check the donations section of <a href="http://UEDcraft.com" rel="nofollow noopener">UEDcraft.com</a> for more information.</p>
<p>The Server Hierarchy:</p>
<p>Ranks:<br>
Member<br>
Apprentice<br>
Journeyman<br>
Traveler<br>
Pioneer<br>
MIT<br>
Mod<br>
Head-Mod<br>
Artisan-Admin<br>
Tech-Admin<br>
Head-Admin<br>
Note: Apprentice through Pioneer can be obtained by donating.</p>
<p>The UEDcraft staff consist’s of the following members:<br>
Admins:<br>
UED_iRx - Server owner and Head Admin.<br>
NexGenInsanity - Our cheif builder, and Artisan Admin.<br>
John_Dong - Our main man for server maint. and our Tech-Admin.</p>
<p>Moderators:<br>
Shanks2112 - Head Moderator in charge of the Moderation team and event planner.<br>
raw900 - Works directly with Shanks to keep the server going.<br>
Tunbridge - One of two Moderators In Training (MIT), who reports issues to the rest of the staff.<br>
ZombieKittenz - Our other MIT, helping Tunbridge report any server problems.</p>
<p>UEDcraft Sponsors:<br>
We are proudly sponsored by the following:</p>
<p>SubZeroServers<br>
Website: <a href="http://www.subzeroservers.net" rel="nofollow noopener">www.subzeroservers.net</a><br>
Profile: A global force in the server hosting business. Providing high quality servers for: Voice, Games &amp; Web Hosting.</p>
<p>GamerPeer<br>
Website: <a href="http://www.gamerpeer.com" rel="nofollow noopener">www.gamerpeer.com</a><br>
Profile: The latest craze in gaming for those who want to connect with players all over the world quickly and without the fuss of long registration forms. A social networking website just for gamers! Find your perfect community for all the games you love here.</p>
<p>Xsplit<br>
Website: <a href="http://www.xsplit.com" rel="nofollow noopener">www.xsplit.com</a><br>
Profile: A world leader in screen capture technology used by world professionals on live streaming websites. The advanced technology allows you to use all the high end servers needed for quality streaming and the best price.</p>
<p>SpadeSocial<br>
Website: <a href="http://www.spadesocial.com" rel="nofollow noopener">www.spadesocial.com</a><br>
Profile: Poker social networking heaven. Upload, view, discuss all the videos in the world of poker and stay ahead of the game by checking out the latest and greatest from the world of poker. Have one up on your friends about what’s hot and what’s not quickly and without fuss. A world of poker ready for you to watch without the red tape.</p>
<p>NinjaCoders<br>
Website: <a href="http://www.ninja-coders.com" rel="nofollow noopener">www.ninja-coders.com</a><br>
Profile: Take the hardship out of Minecraft with the Android App developed by the technological wizards at NinjaCoders. Minecraft Canary is just one of the award winning Apps you can download for your Android device and give you the edge in the game. Tons of quick tutorials of how to make anything in the game including the secret tool “Canary” which keeps track of day/night times and tells you when its about to be day/night! Cool huh? You can download their app from the app store at any time.</p>
<p>For more information, visit <a href="http://www.uedcraft.com" rel="nofollow noopener">www.uedcraft.com</a>, and have a look around our forums. If you still have questions for us, contact a staff member.</p>
<p>Server IP: 69.64.34.39:25615</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/uedcra/443933/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/uedcra/443933/1</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 04 Jun 2012 02:00:41 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-443933-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/uedcra/443933.rss">UEDcra</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
