<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>EFF launches campaign to free phones from software locks</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/eff-launches-campaign-to-free-phones-from-software-locks/259147</link>
    <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;The Electronic Frontier Foundation (EFF) is asking for the public&#39;s help in its new campaign to free cell phones from the software locks.

The Digital Millenium Copyright Act (DMCA) is a U.S copyright law that prohibits circumventing anti-piracy measures that are built into commercial software. Many cell phone manufacturers and service providers build software locks to protect their business models instead of copyrighted material.

Often users come up with ways to connect to a new service provider or run the software of their choice. But the threat of litigation under the DMCA has made them adopt the options provided by the manufacturer without further questions.

Consumers need a DMCA exemption in cases where the DMCA aids the cell phone manufacturers reduce business competition and consumer choice. Every 3 years, the U.S. Copyright Office convenes a rulemaking to consider granting exemptions to the DMCA&#39;s ban to ease the consumer harm. EFF has already filed exemption requests with the Copyright Office addressing the issues in which public is also allowed to participate in the rulemaking proceeding.

You can sign the EFF&#39;s Petition to the Copyright Office and share your stories about cell phone frustrations before the February 2 deadline.&lt;/blockquote&gt;
sauce: http://www.neowin.net/news/main/09/01/28/eff-launches-campaign-to-free-phones-from-software-locks

IMO, they don&#39;t have a right to produce threats like that against us. Our phone, gtfo.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2009 18:26:42 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>General Discussion</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/eff-launches-campaign-to-free-phones-from-software-locks/259147.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>EFF launches campaign to free phones from software locks</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Uriko Uriko]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/uriko">@Uriko</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <blockquote>The Electronic Frontier Foundation (EFF) is asking for the public's help in its new campaign to free cell phones from the software locks.
<p>The Digital Millenium Copyright Act (DMCA) is a U.S copyright law that prohibits circumventing anti-piracy measures that are built into commercial software. Many cell phone manufacturers and service providers build software locks to protect their business models instead of copyrighted material.</p>
<p>Often users come up with ways to connect to a new service provider or run the software of their choice. But the threat of litigation under the DMCA has made them adopt the options provided by the manufacturer without further questions.</p>
<p>Consumers need a DMCA exemption in cases where the DMCA aids the cell phone manufacturers reduce business competition and consumer choice. Every 3 years, the U.S. Copyright Office convenes a rulemaking to consider granting exemptions to the DMCA’s ban to ease the consumer harm. EFF has already filed exemption requests with the Copyright Office addressing the issues in which public is also allowed to participate in the rulemaking proceeding.</p>
<p>You can sign the EFF’s Petition to the Copyright Office and share your stories about cell phone frustrations before the February 2 deadline.</p>
</blockquote><br>
sauce: <a href="http://www.neowin.net/news/main/09/01/28/eff-launches-campaign-to-free-phones-from-software-locks" rel="nofollow noopener">http://www.neowin.net/news/main/09/01/28/eff-launches-campaign-to-free-phones-from-software-locks</a>
<p>IMO, they don’t have a right to produce threats like that against us. Our phone, gtfo.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/eff-launches-campaign-to-free-phones-from-software-locks/259147/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/eff-launches-campaign-to-free-phones-from-software-locks/259147/1</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2009 18:26:42 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-259147-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/eff-launches-campaign-to-free-phones-from-software-locks/259147.rss">EFF launches campaign to free phones from software locks</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
