<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>How to resolve most common portforwarding errors!</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-resolve-most-common-portforwarding-errors/448346</link>
    <description>A lot of people have troubles portforwarding for many different reasons.

Most people have the problems due to an annoying wireless router that&#39;s a pain in the butt to portforward on.   :mad: :mad:

I&#39;m going to tell you how to RESOLVE most of those problems.  
:eek:
^Yeah, I know right!

Note: This is teaching you to resolve the most common portforwarding problems, not telling you specifically how to portfoward, but I do explain that a little bit. It&#39;s pointless to go into details about that because not everyone has the same wifi router.


You&#39;re going to need this: http://www.yougetsignal.com/tools/open-ports/
It comes in handy, bookmark it and shortcut it on your desktop. It&#39;s the best open port checker, it&#39;s convenient and lets you choose the IP to check instead of just the port. 

Turn off your windows firewall before you start this.

Firstly, you need to at least try to find a portforwarding guide for your router and try it out. You&#39;ve most likely already done this and came across problems, considering you are viewing this page.

The most common problem is that people portforward on their router wrong. Try messing around with your portforwarding page for a while until you know for a fact you&#39;re doing this part right.

Another common error, one I came across A LOT when I was a newbie, I always happened to put my port/server into my client wrong. Almost all bases where coded onto by many different coders 

so they&#39;re not always easy to find out where to put your ip. So what I do, is search for keywords such as, &quot;server, IP, .no-ip,&quot; etc... in your client.java or gui.java or egui.java file.
If you aren&#39;t sure if it&#39;s your router or if it&#39;s just your client messing up, then you need to set your client to an ip that you know works, such as one for another server that uses a similar client/base 

source. It will most likely reject you for using the wrong client but if it does something aside from saying error connecting and you know for a fact that there server is online, then that means that nothing is wrong with your client.

Another common mistake is that sometimes people use the wrong port when portforwarding. One time I tried 43954 and got soo mad because I couldn&#39;t get port 43594 to work. Lol. I later realized my typo. So check your server, client, and routers port.

If you&#39;re kinda looking for a last resort google this. &quot;How to open all ports on [YOUR ROUTER NAME AND MODEL HERE]&quot; Open all your ports and then guess what? Your port will for sure be open.

I&#39;m not sure if you can do that on all routers, but you can on a lot.

This doesn&#39;t always work for anyone but if you&#39;re still having portforwarding errors give PFConfig a try. It didn&#39;t work for me but it works for a lot of people, that&#39;s why I&#39;m recommending it. 

If you did that and you&#39;re still having errors, it&#39;s most likely not a portforwarding error.



Conclusion:

Portforwarding isn&#39;t easy for everyone. If you are still having problems even after trying everything on this post, I recommend buying a NETGEAR router, those are SOO easy to portforward with, 

especially the NETGEAR N600 router. If you&#39;re money tight, you should just suck it up and shamefully resort to Hamachi, let&#39;s face it, it saves you time and stress. I&#39;ll be honest with you right now, Hamachi won&#39;t get you nearly as many players, but if you&#39;re server is worthly of having players, you will get them. 

I&#39;m working on a guide on how to get you&#39;re server really popular. BEFORE YOU FLAME, &quot;They already have that n00b! Blah blah *Troll face here*,&quot; keep reading! I&#39;m almost positive that they will already have other guides for this, but not all guides and tips are the same. Learn from more than just one person&#39;s experiences and you&#39;ll learn even more.

Thanks for reading! Hope the guide helped you, if you dislike this guide, I don&#39;t mind CONSTRUCTIVE criticism. If you liked it or it helped you, please leave some feedback and appreciation.  :) ;) :D :cool: :rolleyes: :P :o ;D

Credits-
100% - Me (Cloudnine)</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 05 Jul 2012 07:03:29 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-resolve-most-common-portforwarding-errors/448346.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>How to resolve most common portforwarding errors!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@belhelmiel belhelmiel]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/belhelmiel">@belhelmiel</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote" data-post="2" data-topic="448346">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 Level 120 Dungeoneering:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Awesome guide. Although, they could just use PFConfig Free or SimplePortForwarder. <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/wink.png?v=5" title=":wink:" class="emoji" alt=":wink:"></p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Thanks for feedback, I forgot to add that. But that doesn’t always work. Never worked for me. <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=5" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-resolve-most-common-portforwarding-errors/448346/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-resolve-most-common-portforwarding-errors/448346/3</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 05 Jul 2012 07:03:29 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-448346-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-resolve-most-common-portforwarding-errors/448346.rss">How to resolve most common portforwarding errors!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>How to resolve most common portforwarding errors!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Level_120_Dungeoneer Level 120 Dungeoneering]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/level_120_dungeoneer">@Level_120_Dungeoneer</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Awesome guide. Although, they could just use PFConfig Free or SimplePortForwarder. <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/wink.png?v=5" title=":wink:" class="emoji" alt=":wink:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-resolve-most-common-portforwarding-errors/448346/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-resolve-most-common-portforwarding-errors/448346/2</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 05 Jul 2012 06:35:40 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-448346-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-resolve-most-common-portforwarding-errors/448346.rss">How to resolve most common portforwarding errors!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>How to resolve most common portforwarding errors!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@belhelmiel belhelmiel]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/belhelmiel">@belhelmiel</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>A lot of people have troubles portforwarding for many different reasons.</p>
<p>Most people have the problems due to an annoying wireless router that’s a pain in the butt to portforward on.   :mad: :mad:</p>
<p>I’m going to tell you how to RESOLVE most of those problems.<br>
:eek:<br>
^Yeah, I know right!</p>
<p>Note: This is teaching you to resolve the most common portforwarding problems, not telling you specifically how to portfoward, but I do explain that a little bit. It’s pointless to go into details about that because not everyone has the same wifi router.</p>
<p>You’re going to need this: <a href="http://www.yougetsignal.com/tools/open-ports/" rel="nofollow noopener">http://www.yougetsignal.com/tools/open-ports/</a><br>
It comes in handy, bookmark it and shortcut it on your desktop. It’s the best open port checker, it’s convenient and lets you choose the IP to check instead of just the port.</p>
<p>Turn off your windows firewall before you start this.</p>
<p>Firstly, you need to at least try to find a portforwarding guide for your router and try it out. You’ve most likely already done this and came across problems, considering you are viewing this page.</p>
<p>The most common problem is that people portforward on their router wrong. Try messing around with your portforwarding page for a while until you know for a fact you’re doing this part right.</p>
<p>Another common error, one I came across A LOT when I was a newbie, I always happened to put my port/server into my client wrong. Almost all bases where coded onto by many different coders</p>
<p>so they’re not always easy to find out where to put your ip. So what I do, is search for keywords such as, “server, IP, .no-ip,” etc… in your client.java or gui.java or egui.java file.<br>
If you aren’t sure if it’s your router or if it’s just your client messing up, then you need to set your client to an ip that you know works, such as one for another server that uses a similar client/base</p>
<p>source. It will most likely reject you for using the wrong client but if it does something aside from saying error connecting and you know for a fact that there server is online, then that means that nothing is wrong with your client.</p>
<p>Another common mistake is that sometimes people use the wrong port when portforwarding. One time I tried 43954 and got soo mad because I couldn’t get port 43594 to work. Lol. I later realized my typo. So check your server, client, and routers port.</p>
<p>If you’re kinda looking for a last resort google this. “How to open all ports on [YOUR ROUTER NAME AND MODEL HERE]” Open all your ports and then guess what? Your port will for sure be open.</p>
<p>I’m not sure if you can do that on all routers, but you can on a lot.</p>
<p>This doesn’t always work for anyone but if you’re still having portforwarding errors give PFConfig a try. It didn’t work for me but it works for a lot of people, that’s why I’m recommending it.</p>
<p>If you did that and you’re still having errors, it’s most likely not a portforwarding error.</p>
<p>Conclusion:</p>
<p>Portforwarding isn’t easy for everyone. If you are still having problems even after trying everything on this post, I recommend buying a NETGEAR router, those are SOO easy to portforward with,</p>
<p>especially the NETGEAR N600 router. If you’re money tight, you should just suck it up and shamefully resort to Hamachi, let’s face it, it saves you time and stress. I’ll be honest with you right now, Hamachi won’t get you nearly as many players, but if you’re server is worthly of having players, you will get them.</p>
<p>I’m working on a guide on how to get you’re server really popular. BEFORE YOU FLAME, “They already have that n00b! Blah blah <em>Troll face here</em>,” keep reading! I’m almost positive that they will already have other guides for this, but not all guides and tips are the same. Learn from more than just one person’s experiences and you’ll learn even more.</p>
<p>Thanks for reading! Hope the guide helped you, if you dislike this guide, I don’t mind CONSTRUCTIVE criticism. If you liked it or it helped you, please leave some feedback and appreciation.  <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=5" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"> <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/wink.png?v=5" title=":wink:" class="emoji" alt=":wink:"> <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/smiley.png?v=5" title=":smiley:" class="emoji" alt=":smiley:"> <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/cool.png?v=5" title=":cool:" class="emoji" alt=":cool:"> :rolleyes: <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=5" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"> :o ;D</p>
<p>Credits-<br>
100% - Me (Cloudnine)</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-resolve-most-common-portforwarding-errors/448346/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-resolve-most-common-portforwarding-errors/448346/1</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 05 Jul 2012 04:31:25 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-448346-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-resolve-most-common-portforwarding-errors/448346.rss">How to resolve most common portforwarding errors!</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
