<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>317# [OldSchool]</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/317-oldschool/364110</link>
    <description>[b][center]Hello, welcome to my Server thread, I have decided to make a 317 server which I am sure will blow Everyone&#39;s mind.[/b][/center]

[center]I plan to have an Economy like no other server, which I hope will make the game more enjoyable. ;D

The exp rate is either going to be between 10X-30X Runescape (40-120 Per hit). This is undecided and I may end up running a poll.

This server will take anyone who plays back to the Mage Bank Era of RuneScape, which I believe is when RuneScape was at its best.[/center]

[center]There will only be Old school items but I assure you if the Community would like New-Era items added, they will be added.

There will be no Customs.

Every Mini-game will be coded to perfection.

Every NPC in the Server will serve a purpose.

Every Skill will be coded to perfection. [/center]

You will not find Items in the shops such as Abyssal Whips/Rune Armour Etc. These will be received as drops from monsters to provide a steady economy, Potions will be bought into the game by the Herblore skill and Ingredients to make Potions will be dropped by NPC&#39;s, I believe this is how a server should be and this is how my server will be.

This thread will be Updated Weekly if not daily with EVERYTHING I deem important enough to post here.

It is undecided which Source/Client I am going to use yet but it will most likely be a Blank 317 and coded by me and no-one else.



FAQ!
Q: Why such slow Exp Rates?
A: I believe with fast Exp Rates people will get bored of the server eventually, with these exp rates the training will be fast enough to achieve 99 in a skill and I guarantee you once you have reached that 99, it will be an achievement.

Q: Will there be Rares/Discontinued items?
A: Yes, there will be, Once the server is up and running a Drop party will be held which I will be dropping Rare items.

Q: When will this server Be released?
A: There may be a wait but the wait will be worth it.

Q: Why no new age items (God swords etc.)
A: I believe that God swords are overpowered and make PKing too easy, a Hybrid with an AGS takes little to no skill at all, God swords may be bought into the game but the attack bonuses will be considerably lowered.

If you would like to know something about the server, Please don&#39;t Hesitate to post.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 13 Oct 2010 02:10:14 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/317-oldschool/364110.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>317# [OldSchool]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Kielan Kielan]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/kielan">@Kielan</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Good question, Here’s an example using one of the most common weapons, The abyssal whip, it will be received from killing a abyssal demon which requires 85 Slayer, the EXP rate for slayer will be fast enough and I believe one of the best Money-Makers in-Game. the drop rate will be considerably low but not too low that people will have to kill hundreds to kill a whip, the drop rate will have to be considered and tested by me and a few others.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/317-oldschool/364110/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/317-oldschool/364110/3</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 13 Oct 2010 02:10:14 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-364110-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/317-oldschool/364110.rss">317# [OldSchool]</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>317# [OldSchool]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Ix_Soulcist_xI Soulcist]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/ix_soulcist_xi">@Ix_Soulcist_xI</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>This seems to be something nice and neat under development. Though I have a question regarding the economy; how are you going to make it unique unlike any other server? That is quite hard to understand since a economy can go from like; Horrible, Bad, Medium, Good, Perfectioned Economy.</p>
<p>Besides all that, I hope the project goes well and successful.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/317-oldschool/364110/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/317-oldschool/364110/2</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 13 Oct 2010 01:48:25 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-364110-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/317-oldschool/364110.rss">317# [OldSchool]</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>317# [OldSchool]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Kielan Kielan]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/kielan">@Kielan</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p><span class="bbcode-b">[center]Hello, welcome to my Server thread, I have decided to make a 317 server which I am sure will blow Everyone’s mind.</span>[/center]</p>
<p>[center]I plan to have an Economy like no other server, which I hope will make the game more enjoyable. ;D</p>
<p>The exp rate is either going to be between 10X-30X Runescape (40-120 Per hit). This is undecided and I may end up running a poll.</p>
<p>This server will take anyone who plays back to the Mage Bank Era of RuneScape, which I believe is when RuneScape was at its best.[/center]</p>
<p>[center]There will only be Old school items but I assure you if the Community would like New-Era items added, they will be added.</p>
<p>There will be no Customs.</p>
<p>Every Mini-game will be coded to perfection.</p>
<p>Every NPC in the Server will serve a purpose.</p>
<p>Every Skill will be coded to perfection. [/center]</p>
<p>You will not find Items in the shops such as Abyssal Whips/Rune Armour Etc. These will be received as drops from monsters to provide a steady economy, Potions will be bought into the game by the Herblore skill and Ingredients to make Potions will be dropped by NPC’s, I believe this is how a server should be and this is how my server will be.</p>
<p>This thread will be Updated Weekly if not daily with EVERYTHING I deem important enough to post here.</p>
<p>It is undecided which Source/Client I am going to use yet but it will most likely be a Blank 317 and coded by me and no-one else.</p>
<p>FAQ!<br>
Q: Why such slow Exp Rates?<br>
A: I believe with fast Exp Rates people will get bored of the server eventually, with these exp rates the training will be fast enough to achieve 99 in a skill and I guarantee you once you have reached that 99, it will be an achievement.</p>
<p>Q: Will there be Rares/Discontinued items?<br>
A: Yes, there will be, Once the server is up and running a Drop party will be held which I will be dropping Rare items.</p>
<p>Q: When will this server Be released?<br>
A: There may be a wait but the wait will be worth it.</p>
<p>Q: Why no new age items (God swords etc.)<br>
A: I believe that God swords are overpowered and make PKing too easy, a Hybrid with an AGS takes little to no skill at all, God swords may be bought into the game but the attack bonuses will be considerably lowered.</p>
<p>If you would like to know something about the server, Please don’t Hesitate to post.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/317-oldschool/364110/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/317-oldschool/364110/1</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 13 Oct 2010 00:33:42 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-364110-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/317-oldschool/364110.rss">317# [OldSchool]</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
