<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Model Making, adding, and using them in-game</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/model-making-adding-and-using-them-in-game/279477</link>
    <description>Hey guys, I hope this is the right section, considering models are mostly client sided.  Anyways, the point is..

 I&#39;ve just begun my first model. I want to know how to add them in game.
As in, making it a certain type of file. For example: .mdl

I am complete my model and I want to add it into my game. So can someone please tell me how to get &quot;Ints&quot; for the item, how to add it into ITEM.CFG, and use them in-game. I don&#39;t know what I can offer in return really :s Probably admin in my server.. that&#39;s all I can think of. Well My msn is camz2004@hotmail.com if you feel you can&#39;t help me in a single response. But I would greatly appreciate any help whatsoever.
Rise Against is online now   	Reply With Quote</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 20 May 2009 22:58:31 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Game Development</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/model-making-adding-and-using-them-in-game/279477.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Model Making, adding, and using them in-game</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@S_I_N_N_E_R S I N N E R]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/s_i_n_n_e_r">@S_I_N_N_E_R</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Hey guys, I hope this is the right section, considering models are mostly client sided.  Anyways, the point is…</p>
<p>I’ve just begun my first model. I want to know how to add them in game.<br>
As in, making it a certain type of file. For example: .mdl</p>
<p>I am complete my model and I want to add it into my game. So can someone please tell me how to get “Ints” for the item, how to add it into ITEM.CFG, and use them in-game. I don’t know what I can offer in return really :s Probably admin in my server… that’s all I can think of. Well My msn is <a href="mailto:camz2004@hotmail.com">camz2004@hotmail.com</a> if you feel you can’t help me in a single response. But I would greatly appreciate any help whatsoever.<br>
Rise Against is online now   	Reply With Quote</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/model-making-adding-and-using-them-in-game/279477/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/model-making-adding-and-using-them-in-game/279477/1</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 20 May 2009 22:58:31 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-279477-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/model-making-adding-and-using-them-in-game/279477.rss">Model Making, adding, and using them in-game</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
