<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Lock</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/lock/31525</link>
    <description>i saw [url=http://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php/topic,45906.0.html/]this[/url] and wanted to count down who wanted to un-ban, him
[hr]
[quote=&quot;Mrquarter&quot;]Do you idiots want to know the real reason. This is Mrquarter, the person he framed. It all began here:
Me, Flamed Fury1, and Guthan38 are talking on MSN. Me and Guthan38 De-obbed the Runescape Client and were cleaning it up and making it work. We got it all done and we sent it to Flamed Fury1. He said I will fix all that needs to be fixed. The next day, he says to me &quot;here is the client, release it on Moparscape.org but take all credit for you, don&#39;t mention my name. I am sick of everybody thinking I know everything and I want you to have credit.&quot; If you thought somebody would do that, you are mistaken. I thought it was suspicious but to get to the bottom of it, I decided to post it. I did and a day later, Moparisthebest pmed me saying that I better talk or I am IP Baned. I talked to Mopar and Flamed Fury1 was caught red-handed. He got IP Baned for it and he sort of deserves it. He keylogged everybody and deserves what he got.

That is the real story since I was involved highly. Thank you.

-Mrquarter[/quote]
nvm i lock it and w8 for it to get deleted</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 03 Dec 2006 02:52:14 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/lock/31525.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Lock</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@phse phse]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/phse">@phse</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>i saw <a href="http://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php/topic,45906.0.html/" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">this</a> and wanted to count down who wanted to un-ban, him<br>
[hr]</p>
<p>[quote=“Mrquarter”]Do you idiots want to know the real reason. This is Mrquarter, the person he framed. It all began here:<br>
Me, Flamed Fury1, and Guthan38 are talking on MSN. Me and Guthan38 De-obbed the Runescape Client and were cleaning it up and making it work. We got it all done and we sent it to Flamed Fury1. He said I will fix all that needs to be fixed. The next day, he says to me “here is the client, release it on <a href="http://Moparscape.org" rel="nofollow noopener">Moparscape.org</a> but take all credit for you, don’t mention my name. I am sick of everybody thinking I know everything and I want you to have credit.” If you thought somebody would do that, you are mistaken. I thought it was suspicious but to get to the bottom of it, I decided to post it. I did and a day later, Moparisthebest pmed me saying that I better talk or I am IP Baned. I talked to Mopar and Flamed Fury1 was caught red-handed. He got IP Baned for it and he sort of deserves it. He keylogged everybody and deserves what he got.</p>
<p>That is the real story since I was involved highly. Thank you.</p>
<p>-Mrquarter[/quote]<br>
nvm i lock it and w8 for it to get deleted</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/lock/31525/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/lock/31525/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 03 Dec 2006 02:52:14 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-31525-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/lock/31525.rss">Lock</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
