<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Agervita, From Agriculture to Industry!</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/agervita-from-agriculture-to-industry/507379</link>
    <description>[b]What&#39;s it about?[/b]

You start with a field, some seeds, and the intention to build an entire kingdom! As you progress through the game you will progress from a small family run farm, to an agricultural village, to a full blown industrial metropolis! You&#39;ll make new tools, methods of farming, and gain NPC followers throughout your journey. Your decisions will determine how far you will venture, will you build a kingdom and gain vast riches, or will you die desperate and alone in an unforgiving wilderness?


[b]Progress?[/b]

As I&#39;m making this game from scratch in C#, and I have little to know artistic skills, there isn&#39;t much to show, although I&#39;ve already finished tons of back end systems that will drive the game through to completion!

Below I&#39;ll keep track of the progress, as well as some nice screenshots to gaze at 

GUI Implementation - 60% / Still need to make a few behind the scenes improvements.
Rendering Implementation - 100% / We&#39;re good to go here!
Player Storage - 90% / Just need to setup the online database!
Audio - 100% / We&#39;re all good here, just need to build an audio library!
World Storage - 10% / I haven&#39;t worked on this much, although I know exactly how I&#39;ll complete this!
Scripting - 30% / The backend implementation is there, I just need to bring in &quot;hook-points&quot;, which will be editable through scripting!
Game Art - 0% / Using borrowed sprites at the moment, going to have to find an artist!

[img]http://www.freemmorpgmaker.com/files/imagehost/pics/d41272aa4fee023b778869e1796ec21c.png[/img]
[img]http://www.freemmorpgmaker.com/files/imagehost/pics/8a63a38d074a2475668e040e708661a3.png[/img]


[b]The Team:[/b]

Project Owner / Lead Programmer - General Pony / John.
Artist - NA .
Web Developer - Aaron.

* PM me if you&#39;re interesting in joining the team, work reference will be required!

Regards,
GA</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 12 Mar 2013 03:36:55 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Game Development</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/agervita-from-agriculture-to-industry/507379.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Agervita, From Agriculture to Industry!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@General_Pony General Pony]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/general_pony">@General_Pony</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p><span class="bbcode-b">What’s it about?</span></p>
<p>You start with a field, some seeds, and the intention to build an entire kingdom! As you progress through the game you will progress from a small family run farm, to an agricultural village, to a full blown industrial metropolis! You’ll make new tools, methods of farming, and gain NPC followers throughout your journey. Your decisions will determine how far you will venture, will you build a kingdom and gain vast riches, or will you die desperate and alone in an unforgiving wilderness?</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Progress?</span></p>
<p>As I’m making this game from scratch in C#, and I have little to know artistic skills, there isn’t much to show, although I’ve already finished tons of back end systems that will drive the game through to completion!</p>
<p>Below I’ll keep track of the progress, as well as some nice screenshots to gaze at</p>
<p>GUI Implementation - 60% / Still need to make a few behind the scenes improvements.<br>
Rendering Implementation - 100% / We’re good to go here!<br>
Player Storage - 90% / Just need to setup the online database!<br>
Audio - 100% / We’re all good here, just need to build an audio library!<br>
World Storage - 10% / I haven’t worked on this much, although I know exactly how I’ll complete this!<br>
Scripting - 30% / The backend implementation is there, I just need to bring in “hook-points”, which will be editable through scripting!<br>
Game Art - 0% / Using borrowed sprites at the moment, going to have to find an artist!</p>
<p><img src="http://www.freemmorpgmaker.com/files/imagehost/pics/d41272aa4fee023b778869e1796ec21c.png" alt width="" height=""><br>
<img src="http://www.freemmorpgmaker.com/files/imagehost/pics/8a63a38d074a2475668e040e708661a3.png" alt width="" height=""></p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">The Team:</span></p>
<p>Project Owner / Lead Programmer - General Pony / John.<br>
Artist - NA .<br>
Web Developer - Aaron.</p>
<ul>
<li>PM me if you’re interesting in joining the team, work reference will be required!</li>
</ul>
<p>Regards,<br>
GA</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/agervita-from-agriculture-to-industry/507379/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/agervita-from-agriculture-to-industry/507379/1</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 12 Mar 2013 03:36:55 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-507379-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/agervita-from-agriculture-to-industry/507379.rss">Agervita, From Agriculture to Industry!</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
