<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>SCAR questions</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/scar-questions/23556</link>
    <description>Hey, I haven&#39;t been around RuneScape at all the past year.

I might want to run SCAR just for the hell of it. Give my computer something to do while it&#39;s on overnight. Maybe even get lucky and make a nice character which might interst me in playing a bit. But I have some questions. I didn&#39;t know where else to put it, but if it&#39;s in the wrong place, just let a mod move it.

1. Does SCAR use a fake mouse?
2. Can I run multiple characters on SCAR? If so, how much computer resource does one character take? (Don&#39;t even know why I&#39;m asking the second question as I&#39;ve got a high end PC but I&#39;d like to estimate how I could run if I could run multiples)
3. How reliable is SCAR? Can I get a good overnight 8-10 hours straight like Aryan once did?
4. Will virus scans and disk defragments mess SCAR up? (These are schedules overnight on certain days of the week).</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 10 Nov 2006 03:41:26 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/scar-questions/23556.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>SCAR questions</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Starblaster100 Starblaster100]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/starblaster100">@Starblaster100</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>no, it uses your actual mouse<br>
not unless you have a virtual PC<br>
Depends on the script, i have seen 22 hour autoing before.<br>
It will lag your PC, which may muck up some scripts, but it shouldn’t be too bad</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/scar-questions/23556/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/scar-questions/23556/2</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 Nov 2006 03:41:26 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-23556-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/scar-questions/23556.rss">SCAR questions</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>SCAR questions</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@blade5x blade5x]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/blade5x">@blade5x</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Hey, I haven’t been around RuneScape at all the past year.</p>
<p>I might want to run SCAR just for the hell of it. Give my computer something to do while it’s on overnight. Maybe even get lucky and make a nice character which might interst me in playing a bit. But I have some questions. I didn’t know where else to put it, but if it’s in the wrong place, just let a mod move it.</p>
<ol>
<li>Does SCAR use a fake mouse?</li>
<li>Can I run multiple characters on SCAR? If so, how much computer resource does one character take? (Don’t even know why I’m asking the second question as I’ve got a high end PC but I’d like to estimate how I could run if I could run multiples)</li>
<li>How reliable is SCAR? Can I get a good overnight 8-10 hours straight like Aryan once did?</li>
<li>Will virus scans and disk defragments mess SCAR up? (These are schedules overnight on certain days of the week).</li>
</ol>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/scar-questions/23556/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/scar-questions/23556/1</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 Nov 2006 02:59:53 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-23556-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/scar-questions/23556.rss">SCAR questions</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
