<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Sharing Creativity</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/sharing-creativity/553446</link>
    <description>I&#39;ve been curious for a while now... is creativity a skill? a talent? is it really that hard to come up with something new or interesting?
If the above turns out to be a rare thing, well... I will spitball a few ideas here. Maybe others will join in too in the comments!
[b]So here goes:[/b]
[b]1. Missions[/b] - This is almost like slayer tasks. You&#39;re given a task to go there and kill that. THAT should preferably be difficult. Anyone with this same task, fighting the same thing as you should be rewarded for a successful kill. If you want to spice things up, scale up the monsters stats based on the amount of attackers present.
[hr]
[b]2. Expeditions[/b] - This is something that I&#39;m coding on my server right now; you speak to a fellow in town and he tells you about a currently available expedition (this can be randomized every 30 minutes or something). 
[b]The expeditions can vary in the following fields: [/b]
-Treasure (means there will be a loot chest or whatever), 
-Boss, 
-Gathering (mine nodes/trees/herbs/farmables spawned), 
-Power (server context-specific thing, i.e. a temple for say, enchanting bones to get triple pray exp or whatever).
[hr]
[b]3. Combat skills[/b] - Improve the already existing system; for example: Why shouldn&#39;t higher attack level have extra abilities that it yields? Like, say parrying an attack, or being able to cut incoming spells in half when wielding 2-handers... stuff like that. Or having high defence would allow for counter-attacking a creature.
[hr]
[b]4. Monster AI [/b]- Besides just making a thing hit hard and have a lot of health, why don&#39;t you make the monster do something cool? Why not make the monster summon a thing that kidnaps one of your teammates and takes them to a different dimension where they have to suffer until you cut the main boss&#39; head off?
Why not make a monster eat someone and suck the life out of them until you break its teeth and pull your friend out? Why not make a monster run away when it&#39;s weak?
[hr]
[b]5. 20++ skills[/b] - that number is really high; so why is it that you cannot come up with anything creative in all of those areas? What is so exciting about woodcutting on RS that you cannot give it a better purpose other than clicking on a tree every couple of seconds? Why not make firemaking useful? Why not make the prayer a combat skill? Why not make agility a factor in combat?
[hr]
[b]6. The world[/b] - RS has an amazing world, full of objects and things that are seemingly useless; why don&#39;t you create some lore and get the entire world involved? Why not let people cut flowers with a knife? Why not let people gather mushrooms from the ground? Why not let people cut branches, bushes or Ferns?
[hr]
[b]7. Here, let me give you a REAL idea:[/b]
Magic books (held in shield-slot) - Why not add a special effect to each book? For example you could have a book that adds a freeze-effect to your water/air/earth spells; or you could have a book that drains the opponents magic level, restoring your life. Or why not have a book that makes you build up magic essence, eventually reaching 5 charges and letting you choose an effect (be it, healing or increased damage or perhaps a big magical shield)?

There are absolutely no limits to what you can do... I know it&#39;s possible to create everything I just said, you know why? Because I did :)
So I&#39;m sure you can too! So get out there, create something awesome and creative. Be the creator you (didn&#39;t) want to be!

I&#39;ll probably scribble down more ideas if people don&#39;t hate me for posting this haha.

Have a glorious evening/morning!
 -Fuzzout.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 30 Sep 2015 02:32:01 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/sharing-creativity/553446.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Sharing Creativity</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Welliton_inc Welliton_inc]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/welliton_inc">@Welliton_inc</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Some of those features are pretty nice. But when I talk about a unique server I’m talking about making a unique concept of actually playing a RSPS emulation, e.g a zombie apocalypse server.</p>
<p>But to answer your original question. I do believe not everybody is born with a creative mind. I’m not just talking about RSPS related, I’m talking about it in general. Every one of us is capable of creative thinking but some people are just better at it than others. Being able to think of bright ideas on the spot is not something one can just pick up on.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/sharing-creativity/553446/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/sharing-creativity/553446/2</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 30 Sep 2015 02:32:01 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-553446-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/sharing-creativity/553446.rss">Sharing Creativity</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Sharing Creativity</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@fuzzout fuzzout]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/fuzzout">@fuzzout</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I’ve been curious for a while now… is creativity a skill? a talent? is it really that hard to come up with something new or interesting?<br>
If the above turns out to be a rare thing, well… I will spitball a few ideas here. Maybe others will join in too in the comments!<br>
<span class="bbcode-b">So here goes:</span><br>
<span class="bbcode-b">1. Missions</span> - This is almost like slayer tasks. You’re given a task to go there and kill that. THAT should preferably be difficult. Anyone with this same task, fighting the same thing as you should be rewarded for a successful kill. If you want to spice things up, scale up the monsters stats based on the amount of attackers present.<br>
[hr]<br>
<span class="bbcode-b">2. Expeditions</span> - This is something that I’m coding on my server right now; you speak to a fellow in town and he tells you about a currently available expedition (this can be randomized every 30 minutes or something).<br>
<span class="bbcode-b">The expeditions can vary in the following fields: </span><br>
-Treasure (means there will be a loot chest or whatever),<br>
-Boss,<br>
-Gathering (mine nodes/trees/herbs/farmables spawned),<br>
-Power (server context-specific thing, i.e. a temple for say, enchanting bones to get triple pray exp or whatever).<br>
[hr]<br>
<span class="bbcode-b">3. Combat skills</span> - Improve the already existing system; for example: Why shouldn’t higher attack level have extra abilities that it yields? Like, say parrying an attack, or being able to cut incoming spells in half when wielding 2-handers… stuff like that. Or having high defence would allow for counter-attacking a creature.<br>
[hr]<br>
<span class="bbcode-b">4. Monster AI </span>- Besides just making a thing hit hard and have a lot of health, why don’t you make the monster do something cool? Why not make the monster summon a thing that kidnaps one of your teammates and takes them to a different dimension where they have to suffer until you cut the main boss’ head off?<br>
Why not make a monster eat someone and suck the life out of them until you break its teeth and pull your friend out? Why not make a monster run away when it’s weak?<br>
[hr]<br>
<span class="bbcode-b">5. 20++ skills</span> - that number is really high; so why is it that you cannot come up with anything creative in all of those areas? What is so exciting about woodcutting on RS that you cannot give it a better purpose other than clicking on a tree every couple of seconds? Why not make firemaking useful? Why not make the prayer a combat skill? Why not make agility a factor in combat?<br>
[hr]<br>
<span class="bbcode-b">6. The world</span> - RS has an amazing world, full of objects and things that are seemingly useless; why don’t you create some lore and get the entire world involved? Why not let people cut flowers with a knife? Why not let people gather mushrooms from the ground? Why not let people cut branches, bushes or Ferns?<br>
[hr]<br>
<span class="bbcode-b">7. Here, let me give you a REAL idea:</span><br>
Magic books (held in shield-slot) - Why not add a special effect to each book? For example you could have a book that adds a freeze-effect to your water/air/earth spells; or you could have a book that drains the opponents magic level, restoring your life. Or why not have a book that makes you build up magic essence, eventually reaching 5 charges and letting you choose an effect (be it, healing or increased damage or perhaps a big magical shield)?</p>
<p>There are absolutely no limits to what you can do… I know it’s possible to create everything I just said, you know why? Because I did <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=5" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"><br>
So I’m sure you can too! So get out there, create something awesome and creative. Be the creator you (didn’t) want to be!</p>
<p>I’ll probably scribble down more ideas if people don’t hate me for posting this haha.</p>
<p>Have a glorious evening/morning!<br>
-Fuzzout.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/sharing-creativity/553446/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/sharing-creativity/553446/1</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 29 Sep 2015 19:03:44 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-553446-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/sharing-creativity/553446.rss">Sharing Creativity</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
