<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>HolyPkerz V2 - Allstar Edited</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/holypkerz-v2-allstar-edited/389740</link>
    <description>This is an Edited AllstarScape Source

Now, before you start about how much Allstar sucks, please hear me out as many of the complaints about Allstar have been fixed such as easy to dupe and crash

[size=24pt]Updates:[/size]
&lt;blockquote&gt;- Anti Syi
- Full Anti Null (Tested on 5 different nullers both Offline and Online) The nuller doesn&#39;t have to be banned or anything
- Ogre bow glitch fixed
- Fully working clan chat that shows up in music interface
     - I also added a button you can click so when you&#39;re talking regular it will send clan messages instead of regular chat
- Fixed it so you can cook mantas and sharks
- Barrows Glitch Fixed (Before you Needed Range as well as Defense to Wear)
- New Players List (says the ranks of players and the pk points)
- High Scores Board
- Xpmini Game
- Ticket System (Only place to buy phats masks and santas as well as a few other great items)
     - You buy a ticket with max money
- Edited thieving so you don&#39;t receive as much money as before
- All Godsword specs (armadyl give 25% more damage, sara hits heals your hp by half the damage and heals prayer by a quarter of the damage, bandos hits gives 10% more damage, and zammy freezes the opponent [currently only works in PvP])
- Attack Option only appears in wild
- Anti high alch, trade, telegrab, and cheat client dupes
- Dfs Making (90 smith needed)
- Gs Making, get hilt and blade from gsmini (80 smith needed)
- New Stats Tab
    - Inside stats tab a updating player count was added and tells you the xp till next level until you reach max level
    - Farmin xp now shows instead of being just -1
- Reduced strength bonus of weapons and armor
- Phats have strength bonus so people pk with them
- No blood rune lag
- Anti trade scam
- A timer that says when server restarts (uses grahams event manager)
- A server panel
- Added all the missing requirements
- Fixed it so you can eat without a weapon
- Fixed it so if you have 0 prayer you can still wear weapons and armor
- Fixed the :chalreq: disconnect glitch
- No Rollback
- Real Slayer with good drops
- Skillcape Trimming
- Armor Trimming (Good money)

Newest Updates:
- Attack style saves when you logout instead of going back to accurate every time.
- Made it so you can&#39;t mage the slayer monsters if you don&#39;t have the right slayer level
- New home with a portal room
- orb at home that replaces the high scores board and newspaper crate.  You click it and it sends a frame that gives you 3 options: updates, news, or high scores
- Fixed the prayer glitch where you can&#39;t attack someone if they have any of the 3 protect prayers on
- Deleted the prayer icons that show above your head because silabsoft client can&#39;t see them and it messes up the text
- Made it so while you&#39;re using the prayer, your prayer skill will update constantly, slowly going down until 0 (before you&#39;d have to log out to see how much prayer you have left.
- Made some items unspawnable to anyone except main owner in pickup command
- Removed the teleother spells
- Fixed the dupe where two people log onto the same account and just trade their stuff over
- Changed protect from melee prayer to block 40% of the damage 100% of the time
- You need 43 prayer to use protect from melee
- Added the Guthans Effect(Works against players and npcs)
- Made it so Veracs hits through protect from melee 100% of the time
- Made both Veracs and Guthans harder to get
- Added a Safe Timer, you have 10 seconds when you login where you can&#39;t be attacked and you can&#39;t attack others
- One click pickup
- Added a ticket shop where the currency needed is tickets instead of coins
- Made it so if you high alch items bought with tickets then you will get tickets back
- Made it so you can&#39;t alch tickets or sell them to a store allowing players to buy them at discount prices
- Added in trading sticks and buy sell and alch for 1b, used for currency
- Took jad out of kqueen and made kqueen&#39;s max hit 55
- Working Easter Quest
- New home
- New shops
- Modified the pk ranks so it takes up less lines of code
- Legends cape can only be worn by people with all 99s
- Dark Bow gives range xp
- Dark Bow hits 2x each time and 2 arrows are removed each time as well
- Removed GS mini and Icon mini
- Removed arrows from shops and firemaking chest
- Deleted huge amounts of unneeded code and I can already see that the server is loading and running much faster
- Fixed the player updating where you&#39;d have to relog to recognize that a player is online
- Custom Mining
- Auto Cooking (like cook all option)
- Added in my code for 2h weapons
- Legends Cape gives best strength bonus out of all other capes
- Fixed the glitch where if you teleport inside of the same area the server doesn&#39;t update the image for the other players
- Deleted all the unused npcs as well as their drops (if they had any)
- Organized and cleaned autospawn.cfg so the npcs are easier to manage (add/remove)
- Fixed the items kept on death code so you keep the most expensive items
     - This includes the items you are wearing as well
- Modified the weapon timers for player v player and player v npc so it&#39;s more realistic
- Made it so Kalphite Queen attacks multiple targets
- Changed Kalphite Queen Drops
- Changed Slayer Drops
- Added Full Void Melee effect
- Added Ultimate Strength prayer
- Modified the drain rate of protect from melee prayer
- Modified the shops so the good items need to be obtained from npc drops
- Lowered the stats of armor and weapons to make for better pking
- Fixed a critical error that would randomly kick all the players off the server then not let anyone on
- Fixed the trade code so it saves better to prevent duping
- Protect from melee works against npcs
- Fixed npc health where it would be divided by number of players in the area
- 100% npc retaliation when attacked
- Fixed poison code
     - When poisoned, every hit was green instead of red
     - When poison wore off, the message was spammed infinitely
- Adjusted mage lvl required to attack Npcs
- Fixed magic vs npcs
     - Used RS formula for xp but with better xp rates
     - Modified damage to RS damage
     - Made it so you can&#39;t attack dead npcs
     - Fixed ancients blood spells to heal 25% of damage dealt
- Custom Clan Wars (100%)
     1. Working Timers(Show on the interface I used for it)
          a. Two minute start timer
          b. 10 minute in-game timer     
     2. Using an interface that tells you how many people are left on each team and how many kills each team has and how much time is                    left in the game
          a. The interface only shows once you are in the game
     3. Middle barriers that completely disappear when the starting timer ends
          a. The sever sends a message to all players in Clan Wars three seconds before the barriers drop
     4. ::challenge playerName to challenge a person
          a. It won&#39;t send it if the person is not in a clan or in the same clan as the person sending the clan chat
          b. It also won&#39;t send it if the person is challenging themselves or if the person was already challenged
          c. A message is sent to the person challenged telling them to ::accept or ::decline
          d. If one minute passes after the challenge is sent and the person doesn&#39;t reply with ::accept or ::decline the challenge expires and the person can challenge another person.  If the person is challenged they are unable to challenge others until they answer their challenge making it so they have an incentive to answer the challenge.
     5. When a person is challenged they can ::accept or ::decline
          a. If the person accepts then the server will look through all of the players currently online and sort them in respect to which clan they are on(won&#39;t do anything for the people who aren&#39;t in a clan or in one of the unchallenged clans).
          b.  The server will start the pre game timer of two minutes and send a message to all the people involved to enter the portal.
     6. When the time reaches zero, if both of the teams have the same amount of kills, it goes to one minute overtime.  If a winner is still not decided then it declares the match a draw.  Otherwise, it announces who won to the whole server and teleports you back to the waiting room.
     7. Added 8 custom death messages that are sent to the person who is killed and the killer 
- Added prayer pots
- Added anti poison pots
- Added 3 custom bosses
     - 1. Gwd Boss (Troll) Drops bandos + armadyl.
     - 2. Gwd Boss (Demon) Drops zammy + sara.  Multi hit type attack
     - 3. Three Stage Boss that drops best one-handed weapon and shield in the game.&lt;/blockquote&gt;

[size=24pt]Skilling:[/size]
[size=10pt][color=teal]
     - Mining
          - You are able to mine the basic ores: tin, copper, iron, coal, gold, mith, addy, and rune
          - The animation continues throughout the mining process
          - Added custom timers to each rock with random times between certain lengths (since I don&#39;t know the correct timers)
     - Cooking
          - Auto cooks the fish
          - Added a timer in, but I don&#39;t know the correct timer
     - Woodcutting
          - Changed the timers for the trees
          - Redid most of the woodcutting code to work better
     - Slayer
          - Kill npcs for xp
     - Thieving
          - Stalls give gems instead of money
     - Crafting
          - Use gems from thieving.
          - You cut gems for xp
          - Added amulet making with use of mould and furnace
          - Added ability to string amulets
     - Smithing
          - Created a new process for determining the amount of xp given for smithing items due to the fact that old one only took into account the bars needed multiplied by a set number for each different bar type.
          - There was already a code for smelting but I deleted it and made a much better one.  The one I made uses the  smelting interface and checks for and deletes the ores needed to make the bars.  For iron I also included the rate of success for the different levels.

     - Fletching (90%)
          - Created a new code for fletching.
          - Ability to fletch arrow shafts
          - Uses interface
          - Ability to fletch both long and shortbow
          - Ability to fletch arrows with feathers + arrow shafts + arrow tips (in progress)

     - Agility
          - Uses agility course in wild
          - Xp halved for each repeated use of one of the obstacles before completing the course
          - Bonus xp awarded upon completion of the course

     - Firemaking
         - Fire timers
         - Forced movement (this is still an allstar so clipping obviously doesn&#39;t work)

Clan Wars
[IMG]http://i863.photobucket.com/albums/ab200/HolyPkerz/HolyPkerz1.jpg[/img]

Darkbow
[IMG]http://i863.photobucket.com/albums/ab200/HolyPkerz/HolyPkerz2.jpg[/img]

Guthans
[IMG]http://i863.photobucket.com/albums/ab200/HolyPkerz/HolyPkerz3.jpg[/img]

Ticket Shop
[IMG]http://i863.photobucket.com/albums/ab200/HolyPkerz/HolyPkerz4.jpg[/img]

Npc Reset
[IMG]http://i863.photobucket.com/albums/ab200/HolyPkerz/HolyPkerz5.jpg[/img]

Stats Tab
[IMG]http://i863.photobucket.com/albums/ab200/HolyPkerz/statstab1.jpg[/img]
[IMG]http://i863.photobucket.com/albums/ab200/HolyPkerz/statstab2.jpg[/img]

Clan Chat
[IMG]http://i863.photobucket.com/albums/ab200/HolyPkerz/clanchat.jpg[/img]

Woodcutting
[IMG]http://i863.photobucket.com/albums/ab200/HolyPkerz/woodcutting.jpg[/img]

Mining
[IMG]http://i863.photobucket.com/albums/ab200/HolyPkerz/mining.jpg[/img]

Smithing
[IMG]http://i863.photobucket.com/albums/ab200/HolyPkerz/smithing.jpg[/img]

Fishing
[IMG]http://i863.photobucket.com/albums/ab200/HolyPkerz/fishing.jpg[/img]

Credits: 
- Me
- Matzie (music interface, anti blood rune lag, anti high alch dupe, anti trade scam)
- Mod Allstar (base)
- KickingJamie (ipanel, 1 connection per ip) &lt;--- not his but got from his source
- Owner of Futurescape (1 click item pickup code)
- MoparScape Tut (Server-Sided Clan Chat)</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 01 Jun 2012 02:16:19 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/holypkerz-v2-allstar-edited/389740.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>HolyPkerz V2 - Allstar Edited</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@weeddamn weeddamn]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/weeddamn">@weeddamn</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>You’re making good progress xd</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/holypkerz-v2-allstar-edited/389740/80">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/holypkerz-v2-allstar-edited/389740/80</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jun 2012 02:16:19 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-389740-80</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/holypkerz-v2-allstar-edited/389740.rss">HolyPkerz V2 - Allstar Edited</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>HolyPkerz V2 - Allstar Edited</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@aliff118118 aliff118118]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/aliff118118">@aliff118118</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Looks good bro good luck man  <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/cool.png?v=5" title=":cool:" class="emoji" alt=":cool:"></p>
<p>-pksomething2</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/holypkerz-v2-allstar-edited/389740/79">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/holypkerz-v2-allstar-edited/389740/79</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 17 May 2012 19:46:16 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-389740-79</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/holypkerz-v2-allstar-edited/389740.rss">HolyPkerz V2 - Allstar Edited</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>HolyPkerz V2 - Allstar Edited</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@kingman002 kingman002]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/kingman002">@kingman002</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Sweet dude when you’re ready I’ll play it.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/holypkerz-v2-allstar-edited/389740/78">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/holypkerz-v2-allstar-edited/389740/78</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 22 Apr 2012 23:06:55 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-389740-78</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/holypkerz-v2-allstar-edited/389740.rss">HolyPkerz V2 - Allstar Edited</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>HolyPkerz V2 - Allstar Edited</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@mr_dope mr dope]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/mr_dope">@mr_dope</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote" data-post="76" data-topic="389740">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/kronixz/40/5_e05bb34c421432ee4d40de30c10af3e5.png" class="avatar"> kronixz:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Good luck</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Thanks.  I’ll probably be finishing most of the updates before summer break starts so I can test it online.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/holypkerz-v2-allstar-edited/389740/77">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/holypkerz-v2-allstar-edited/389740/77</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 22 Apr 2012 21:16:21 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-389740-77</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/holypkerz-v2-allstar-edited/389740.rss">HolyPkerz V2 - Allstar Edited</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>HolyPkerz V2 - Allstar Edited</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@kronixz kronikz]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/kronixz">@kronixz</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Good luck</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/holypkerz-v2-allstar-edited/389740/76">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/holypkerz-v2-allstar-edited/389740/76</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 22 Apr 2012 21:03:18 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-389740-76</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/holypkerz-v2-allstar-edited/389740.rss">HolyPkerz V2 - Allstar Edited</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>HolyPkerz V2 - Allstar Edited</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@mr_dope mr dope]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/mr_dope">@mr_dope</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Haha, that’s a relief.  If you ever have time, I would love to have you back helping with the server.  I know you’re busy though.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/holypkerz-v2-allstar-edited/389740/75">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/holypkerz-v2-allstar-edited/389740/75</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 22 Apr 2012 20:59:29 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-389740-75</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/holypkerz-v2-allstar-edited/389740.rss">HolyPkerz V2 - Allstar Edited</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>HolyPkerz V2 - Allstar Edited</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@matzie matzie]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/matzie">@matzie</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote" data-post="73" data-topic="389740">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 Dj_:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Well remember the good old days of whip/dds pking? And yeah me too. My account got keylogged so i quit.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Getting keylogged, is your fault. obviously you downloaded something you should not have :o and since they knew it was your RS user/pass i would assume you tried downloading something for RS. and serves you right for getting owned <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/wink.png?v=5" title=":wink:" class="emoji" alt=":wink:"> Botters go fuck yourself, hackers unite! rage, I’m not dead <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=5" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"> just been hibernating.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/holypkerz-v2-allstar-edited/389740/74">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/holypkerz-v2-allstar-edited/389740/74</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 17 Apr 2012 16:58:47 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-389740-74</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/holypkerz-v2-allstar-edited/389740.rss">HolyPkerz V2 - Allstar Edited</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>HolyPkerz V2 - Allstar Edited</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Djayboi6 Dj_]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/djayboi6">@Djayboi6</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Well remember the good old days of whip/dds pking? And yeah me too. My account got keylogged so i quit.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/holypkerz-v2-allstar-edited/389740/73">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/holypkerz-v2-allstar-edited/389740/73</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 02 Mar 2012 21:08:58 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-389740-73</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/holypkerz-v2-allstar-edited/389740.rss">HolyPkerz V2 - Allstar Edited</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>HolyPkerz V2 - Allstar Edited</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Skyru Skyru]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/skyru">@Skyru</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I didn’t think godswords were a big deal, I kind of enjoyed having one. <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/wink.png?v=5" title=":wink:" class="emoji" alt=":wink:"><br>
But my RS days are long behind me. &lt;/3</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/holypkerz-v2-allstar-edited/389740/72">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/holypkerz-v2-allstar-edited/389740/72</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 02 Mar 2012 21:05:55 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-389740-72</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/holypkerz-v2-allstar-edited/389740.rss">HolyPkerz V2 - Allstar Edited</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>HolyPkerz V2 - Allstar Edited</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Djayboi6 Dj_]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/djayboi6">@Djayboi6</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I loved rs at the point of 377 - 464. And then godswords were released <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/confused.png?v=5" title=":confused:" class="emoji" alt=":confused:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/holypkerz-v2-allstar-edited/389740/71">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/holypkerz-v2-allstar-edited/389740/71</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 02 Mar 2012 21:04:35 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-389740-71</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/holypkerz-v2-allstar-edited/389740.rss">HolyPkerz V2 - Allstar Edited</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>HolyPkerz V2 - Allstar Edited</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Skyru Skyru]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/skyru">@Skyru</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“Dj_, post:69, topic:389740”]You should rock a 377 gameframe. <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/smiley.png?v=5" title=":smiley:" class="emoji" alt=":smiley:"> would look amazing for this.[/quote]I suggested a 317 loading 377 also. He is not big on programming clients. Although, he did promised me he would read up on them. <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/wink.png?v=5" title=":wink:" class="emoji" alt=":wink:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/holypkerz-v2-allstar-edited/389740/70">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/holypkerz-v2-allstar-edited/389740/70</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 02 Mar 2012 21:01:34 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-389740-70</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/holypkerz-v2-allstar-edited/389740.rss">HolyPkerz V2 - Allstar Edited</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>HolyPkerz V2 - Allstar Edited</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Djayboi6 Dj_]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/djayboi6">@Djayboi6</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>You should rock a 377 gameframe. <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/smiley.png?v=5" title=":smiley:" class="emoji" alt=":smiley:"> would look amazing for this.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/holypkerz-v2-allstar-edited/389740/69">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/holypkerz-v2-allstar-edited/389740/69</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 02 Mar 2012 20:59:43 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-389740-69</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/holypkerz-v2-allstar-edited/389740.rss">HolyPkerz V2 - Allstar Edited</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>HolyPkerz V2 - Allstar Edited</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Skyru Skyru]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/skyru">@Skyru</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Looks good Dope. Now you client looks much ‘cleaner’ in a sense.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/holypkerz-v2-allstar-edited/389740/68">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/holypkerz-v2-allstar-edited/389740/68</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 02 Mar 2012 20:47:24 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-389740-68</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/holypkerz-v2-allstar-edited/389740.rss">HolyPkerz V2 - Allstar Edited</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>HolyPkerz V2 - Allstar Edited</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Djayboi6 Dj_]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/djayboi6">@Djayboi6</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“Skyru, post:57, topic:389740”][quote author=Dj_ link=topic=485651.msg3930590#msg3930590 date=1330640378]<br>
Well good news. Your client doesnt make me want to throw up. <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/smiley.png?v=5" title=":smiley:" class="emoji" alt=":smiley:"> hope you keep up with this. Allstar was one of my favorites.<br>
[/quote]<br>
The inventory background is discusting.[/quote]<br>
This is true but at least its not all colorful and gay looking frame with gross icons.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/holypkerz-v2-allstar-edited/389740/67">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/holypkerz-v2-allstar-edited/389740/67</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 02 Mar 2012 19:43:36 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-389740-67</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/holypkerz-v2-allstar-edited/389740.rss">HolyPkerz V2 - Allstar Edited</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>HolyPkerz V2 - Allstar Edited</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@mr_dope mr dope]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/mr_dope">@mr_dope</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“Skyru, post:65, topic:389740”]Anytime. Just remember, don’t use a tutorial for eveything.<br>
Anyways, I’m sure you will get the hang of it fast. Goodluck.[/quote]</p>
<p>Thanks.</p>
<p><img src="http://i863.photobucket.com/albums/ab200/HolyPkerz/Untitled-1.jpg" alt width="254" height="252"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/holypkerz-v2-allstar-edited/389740/66">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/holypkerz-v2-allstar-edited/389740/66</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 02 Mar 2012 04:04:10 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-389740-66</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/holypkerz-v2-allstar-edited/389740.rss">HolyPkerz V2 - Allstar Edited</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>HolyPkerz V2 - Allstar Edited</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Skyru Skyru]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/skyru">@Skyru</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Anytime. Just remember, don’t use a tutorial for eveything.<br>
Anyways, I’m sure you will get the hang of it fast. Goodluck.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/holypkerz-v2-allstar-edited/389740/65">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/holypkerz-v2-allstar-edited/389740/65</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 02 Mar 2012 03:33:05 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-389740-65</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/holypkerz-v2-allstar-edited/389740.rss">HolyPkerz V2 - Allstar Edited</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>HolyPkerz V2 - Allstar Edited</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@mr_dope mr dope]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/mr_dope">@mr_dope</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Ok, I’ll look into it and start reading some tuts.  Thanks for the suggestions.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/holypkerz-v2-allstar-edited/389740/64">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/holypkerz-v2-allstar-edited/389740/64</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 02 Mar 2012 03:24:48 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-389740-64</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/holypkerz-v2-allstar-edited/389740.rss">HolyPkerz V2 - Allstar Edited</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>HolyPkerz V2 - Allstar Edited</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Skyru Skyru]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/skyru">@Skyru</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Well, if I were you, i’d get into client programming.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/holypkerz-v2-allstar-edited/389740/63">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/holypkerz-v2-allstar-edited/389740/63</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 02 Mar 2012 03:18:59 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-389740-63</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/holypkerz-v2-allstar-edited/389740.rss">HolyPkerz V2 - Allstar Edited</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>HolyPkerz V2 - Allstar Edited</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@mr_dope mr dope]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/mr_dope">@mr_dope</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>To be honest, I don’t know anything about clients, so I’d have to look some stuff up to make any changes.  I had a friend who was going to make the client that I would be releasing my source with, but I haven’t heard from him in a while.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/holypkerz-v2-allstar-edited/389740/62">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/holypkerz-v2-allstar-edited/389740/62</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 02 Mar 2012 03:12:29 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-389740-62</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/holypkerz-v2-allstar-edited/389740.rss">HolyPkerz V2 - Allstar Edited</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>HolyPkerz V2 - Allstar Edited</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Skyru Skyru]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/skyru">@Skyru</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“mr dope, post:60, topic:389740”]No, it’s a good point.  I’m not the creator of this client and I don’t much like the extra details either.  Plain and simple is usually the best.[/quote]Maybe 317 loading 377? <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/wink.png?v=5" title=":wink:" class="emoji" alt=":wink:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/holypkerz-v2-allstar-edited/389740/61">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/holypkerz-v2-allstar-edited/389740/61</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 02 Mar 2012 02:54:23 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-389740-61</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/holypkerz-v2-allstar-edited/389740.rss">HolyPkerz V2 - Allstar Edited</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>HolyPkerz V2 - Allstar Edited</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@mr_dope mr dope]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/mr_dope">@mr_dope</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>No, it’s a good point.  I’m not the creator of this client and I don’t much like the extra details either.  Plain and simple is usually the best.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/holypkerz-v2-allstar-edited/389740/60">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/holypkerz-v2-allstar-edited/389740/60</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 02 Mar 2012 02:35:56 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-389740-60</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/holypkerz-v2-allstar-edited/389740.rss">HolyPkerz V2 - Allstar Edited</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>HolyPkerz V2 - Allstar Edited</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Skyru Skyru]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/skyru">@Skyru</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“mr dope, post:58, topic:389740”]Thanks for the input.  I’ll get the inventory background fixed.[/quote]I wasn’t trying to be rude, sorry if I came off as mean.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/holypkerz-v2-allstar-edited/389740/59">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/holypkerz-v2-allstar-edited/389740/59</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 02 Mar 2012 02:25:35 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-389740-59</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/holypkerz-v2-allstar-edited/389740.rss">HolyPkerz V2 - Allstar Edited</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>HolyPkerz V2 - Allstar Edited</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@mr_dope mr dope]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/mr_dope">@mr_dope</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Thanks for the input.  I’ll get the inventory background fixed.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/holypkerz-v2-allstar-edited/389740/58">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/holypkerz-v2-allstar-edited/389740/58</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 02 Mar 2012 02:22:36 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-389740-58</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/holypkerz-v2-allstar-edited/389740.rss">HolyPkerz V2 - Allstar Edited</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>HolyPkerz V2 - Allstar Edited</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Skyru Skyru]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/skyru">@Skyru</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote" data-post="56" data-topic="389740">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 Dj_:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Well good news. Your client doesnt make me want to throw up. <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/smiley.png?v=5" title=":smiley:" class="emoji" alt=":smiley:"> hope you keep up with this. Allstar was one of my favorites.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>The inventory background is discusting.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/holypkerz-v2-allstar-edited/389740/57">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/holypkerz-v2-allstar-edited/389740/57</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 01 Mar 2012 22:28:22 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-389740-57</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/holypkerz-v2-allstar-edited/389740.rss">HolyPkerz V2 - Allstar Edited</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>HolyPkerz V2 - Allstar Edited</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Djayboi6 Dj_]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/djayboi6">@Djayboi6</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Well good news. Your client doesnt make me want to throw up. <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/smiley.png?v=5" title=":smiley:" class="emoji" alt=":smiley:"> hope you keep up with this. Allstar was one of my favorites.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/holypkerz-v2-allstar-edited/389740/56">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/holypkerz-v2-allstar-edited/389740/56</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 01 Mar 2012 22:19:38 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-389740-56</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/holypkerz-v2-allstar-edited/389740.rss">HolyPkerz V2 - Allstar Edited</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
