<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Help pl0x</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/help-pl0x/257194</link>
    <description>hello i need help with a few things, if you know how to help me with ANY of these things PLEASE post!!

1. following doesnt work, whenever you try to follow someone it says &quot;you are now following playername&quot; and it just moves your character beside the one you tried to follow and then your character sits there.

2. range in my server is messed up, first, the mage bow has no special attack, second the dark bow only shoots one arrow lol... and third when you try to range someone your character moves from where you are to like 3 steps away from the person you are attacking.

3. i would like skillcape emotes added, i know this is possible because i found in client.java where it said something like:  &quot;a magic skillcape emote&quot; and it had one for most of the skills, i just want to know if i can make a command like ::cape so that if you type ::cape and your wearing a skilcape, it will do that cape&#39;s emote.


If you can help please help me!!!

   Thanks -  Maxim!</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2009 20:30:09 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/help-pl0x/257194.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Help pl0x</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Maxim706 Maxim706]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/maxim706">@Maxim706</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>hello i need help with a few things, if you know how to help me with ANY of these things PLEASE post!!</p>
<ol>
<li>
<p>following doesnt work, whenever you try to follow someone it says “you are now following playername” and it just moves your character beside the one you tried to follow and then your character sits there.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>range in my server is messed up, first, the mage bow has no special attack, second the dark bow only shoots one arrow lol… and third when you try to range someone your character moves from where you are to like 3 steps away from the person you are attacking.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>i would like skillcape emotes added, i know this is possible because i found in client.java where it said something like:  “a magic skillcape emote” and it had one for most of the skills, i just want to know if i can make a command like ::cape so that if you type ::cape and your wearing a skilcape, it will do that cape’s emote.</p>
</li>
</ol>
<p>If you can help please help me!!!</p>
<p>Thanks -  Maxim!</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/help-pl0x/257194/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/help-pl0x/257194/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2009 20:30:09 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-257194-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/help-pl0x/257194.rss">Help pl0x</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
