<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Best language to make games?</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/best-language-to-make-games/88713</link>
    <description>ok, so i was just wondering, what your thoughts are? im going to start out small and am aiming towards 3D games, so what is your thoughts?

also programs and such to make worlds/levels and graphics (eg guns, characters etc.)</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 06 May 2007 01:30:29 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>General Programming</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/best-language-to-make-games/88713.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Best language to make games?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@zstars zstars]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/zstars">@zstars</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“pplsuqbawlz, post:35, topic:88713”]<span class="mention">@zstars-Learn</span>: Diminishing returns, what you’re talking about, and how the client works.</p>
<p>Then comment, the more you speak, the more you need to just be quiet.</p>
<p>They don’t waste their time “making the game efficient” if they did that, they’d make their own (complete) obfuscater with minimal overhead; And a not randomly changing(rotating) protocol that can (and for the most part does) slip up packet bot attempts.[/quote]</p>
<p>I don’t mean to be rude or anything, as my own english isn’t good, but I honestly don’t think that I understand your post. The only thing that I understand is that you seem to think they don’t mind whether the game is efficient or not. That’s an opinion I suppose, so I’m not gonna argue about something so pointless. If you want to think that, then fine. You might be a bit lost though, because the program that is obfuscated is not the server, which is the one we are talking about, but the client. As I am sure you are aware, the client is the java applet through which you play. That java applet connects to a server, which is probably either made in Java or in C++. Also, protocol changes have nothing to do with code efficiency. The computer cycles it takes to parse a packet will be the same, whether the opcode is 0x5555 or 0x7777. Same for packet structure changes.</p>
<p>Also, maybe in your ambience telling someone that “the more you speak the more you need to just be quiet” is considered perfectly acceptable, but to normal people it sounds like a not-so polite way to start a post. If it was constructive criticism then it wouldn’t really matter, but you don’t seem to be providing any argument nor contributing with anything.</p>
<p>Anyway, enjoy <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=6" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/best-language-to-make-games/88713/36">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/best-language-to-make-games/88713/36</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 06 May 2007 01:30:29 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-88713-36</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/best-language-to-make-games/88713.rss">Best language to make games?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Best language to make games?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@pplsuqbawlz pplsuqbawlz]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/pplsuqbawlz">@pplsuqbawlz</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p><span class="mention">@zstars-Learn</span>: Diminishing returns, what you’re talking about, and how the client works.</p>
<p>Then comment, the more you speak, the more you need to just be quiet.</p>
<p>They don’t waste their time “making the game efficient” if they did that, they’d make their own (complete) obfuscater with minimal overhead; And a not randomly changing(rotating) protocol that can (and for the most part does) slip up packet bot attempts.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/best-language-to-make-games/88713/35">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/best-language-to-make-games/88713/35</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 06 May 2007 00:32:17 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-88713-35</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/best-language-to-make-games/88713.rss">Best language to make games?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Best language to make games?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@zstars zstars]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/zstars">@zstars</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote no-group quote-modified" data-post="33" data-topic="88713">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/rln/40/5_6259e4fa9dfe0dec282fb0955bb1974c.png" class="avatar"> RLN:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>[quote=zstars]Also, in reality, the higher level a language is, the slower it is. Assembler (if you’re good enough) is faster than C, C is faster than C++</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>What do you think C and C++ get turned into? What do you think ASM gets turned into? Everything becomes machine code. It is possible for C code to be faster than ASM, or C++ code to be faster than C code. It depends on the compiler/assembler and the coder.[/quote]</p>
<p>100% true. Hence my parenthesis</p>
<blockquote>...Assembler ***(if you're good enough)*** is faster than C...</blockquote>
<p>The java and c++ optimizers (at least of MSVC++) are very good, so if the lower level language programmer doesn’t really know about efficiency or optimization, often the higher level language optimizer can do a better job.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/best-language-to-make-games/88713/34">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/best-language-to-make-games/88713/34</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 05 May 2007 21:57:55 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-88713-34</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/best-language-to-make-games/88713.rss">Best language to make games?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Best language to make games?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@RLN RLN]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/rln">@RLN</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <blockquote>Also, in reality, the higher level a language is, the slower it is. Assembler (if you're good enough) is faster than C, C is faster than C++</blockquote>
What do you think C and C++ get turned into? What do you think ASM gets turned into? Everything becomes machine code. It is possible for C code to be faster than ASM, or C++ code to be faster than C code. It depends on the compiler/assembler and the coder.
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/best-language-to-make-games/88713/33">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/best-language-to-make-games/88713/33</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 05 May 2007 21:48:02 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-88713-33</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/best-language-to-make-games/88713.rss">Best language to make games?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Best language to make games?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@zstars zstars]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/zstars">@zstars</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p><a class="mention" href="/u/mopar">@mopar</a></p>
<p>I know you weren’t, but pplsuqbawlz seems to. Anyway, I limit personal insults to a minimum and try to use information instead, which is what most people who read forums are looking for. And I expect intelligent people to do the same.</p>
<p>Now, about pathfinding, you are right, the runescape NPCs AI is especially crappy, and that would sure reduce the algorithm complexity a lot. Still I think the NPCs movement isn’t entirely random, but the truth is that I can’t really remember.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/best-language-to-make-games/88713/32">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/best-language-to-make-games/88713/32</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 05 May 2007 20:20:36 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-88713-32</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/best-language-to-make-games/88713.rss">Best language to make games?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Best language to make games?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Mopman Mopman]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/mopman">@Mopman</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Chill dude, nobody was attacking anyone, discussions on language wars get heated, you should harden your defenses against personal insults before embarking on them <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/wink.png?v=6" title=":wink:" class="emoji" alt=":wink:"> IRC is a great medium for this.</p>
<p>Anyways, I was not contesting the idea that a MMORPG server is a complex task at all, and nor do I believe was pplsuqbawls. I was contesting the idea that Java cannot handle that complex task. I’m not sure why you suddenly decided that we are saying if you use Java you can run the server on smaller hardware either… that made no sense.</p>
<p>There are plenty of companies using Java for efficiency-critical applications, I’m not allowed to mention web applications apparently, but since that’s all I know I can’t give you any decent examples. <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=6" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"></p>
<p>(PS. The player paths are generated client side afaik, and I’m not so sure about the NPCs, but I don’t think I’ve ever seen an NPC walk a path, only one square at a time, which means their pathfinding DOES pretty much just involve “can I walk here or not”)</p>
<p>EDIT: Except of course, when they walk to you (when you attack them). However, this pathfinding algorithm is very very very simple, which is why it sucks so much balls and they get stuck all the time.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/best-language-to-make-games/88713/31">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/best-language-to-make-games/88713/31</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 05 May 2007 20:02:41 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-88713-31</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/best-language-to-make-games/88713.rss">Best language to make games?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Best language to make games?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@zstars zstars]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/zstars">@zstars</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Excuse me, but you keep insulting me, and you don’t even seem to try to make sense, so I will suggest that you start using your brain. First, you should try to get on topic. If you aren’t able to follow our conversation, you can also refer to the topic title. In two words. VIDEO GAMES. It couldn’t matter less if C++ was only used for games. Because THAT IS WHAT WE ARE TALKING ABOUT. It doesn’t matter if the Runescape industry (video games) is a 1%, BECAUSE WHAT WE ARE TALKING ABOUT IS ABOUT THAT ONE PERCENT.</p>
<p>Also, either you aren’t understanding my posts, or you are blatantly ignoring my points in order to defend Java against some imaginary enemies. I have stated MYSELF that ASM is faster than C, and that C is faster than C++. As I’ve already said, in this same topic, lower level languages have a tendency to be, when used properly, more efficient. For the same reason, Java, which is clearly higher level, tends to be less eficient than Java. If you don’t agree, which should be strange, seeing how you say yourself that, efficiency wise, ASM &gt; C &gt; C++, please provide FACTS instead of unrelated claims and personal offenses. For example, a COMPANY that uses Java for efficiency-critical applications.</p>
<p>And about pathfinding, first, it is not only 2000 people, but the thousands NPCs that are constantly moving. If it was as easy as you seem to think (actually I doubt you think about it, you seem to be attacking my words without making any real sense) you wouldn’t even need to look up an algorithm. And second, it is not only checking if you can move to a tile or not. The character has to choose the shortest path and has to evade obstacles in the way.<br>
Anyway… What point are you supposed to be trying to make? I am saying that a MMORPG server is a complex task, which does indeed require a lot of processor power and resources. You don’t agree? Then fine, you can ignore reality, anyone who is foolish enough to be tricked into believing that won’t change opinion by my words anyway. Maybe Blizzard or Sony Online Entertainment are crazy and they are using server clusters to host their servers when they could instead use the motorola of their TI-89 titanium calculator.</p>
<p>And about that final attack against the video game industry in general, is it even directed at me, or at the creator of the thread? Why should I care if there is a 99.9% failure rate (BTW something makes me think you are making that number up), I am not even a professional game developer. Go tell the game companies. I am sure you could help them, specially the MMORPG developers. You could go and tell em “hey dudes you should really resell your server clusters and host your MMORPG on a second hand pentium one, dun wry, it will be able to handle five thousand entities no problem, no complex maths need to be used anyway”.</p>
<p>Anyway, who cares.</p>
<p>Edit: BTW, I don’t really think you care about knowledge, as you only seem to want to attack me or something, but for whom it may concern:<br>
<a href="http://www.policyalmanac.org/games/aStarTutorial.htm" class="onebox" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">http://www.policyalmanac.org/games/aStarTutorial.htm</a></p>
<p>That’s a very detailed description of the A* Pathfinding algorithm. It is probably the most used one, it is tile based, and probably Runescape uses it or a variation as well.<br>
Note that the author of the pathfinding article seems to agree with my view:</p>
<blockquote>6. Some Speed Tips:   As you develop your own A* program, or adapt the one I wrote, you will eventually find that pathfinding is using a hefty chunk of your CPU time, particularly if you have a decent number of pathfinding units on the board and a reasonably large map. If you read the stuff on the net, you will find that this is true even for the professionals who design games like Starcraft or Age of Empires. If you see things start to slow down due to pathfinding, here are some ideas that may speed things up:</blockquote>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/best-language-to-make-games/88713/30">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/best-language-to-make-games/88713/30</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 05 May 2007 19:36:49 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-88713-30</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/best-language-to-make-games/88713.rss">Best language to make games?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Best language to make games?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@pplsuqbawlz pplsuqbawlz]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/pplsuqbawlz">@pplsuqbawlz</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p><a class="mention" href="/u/zstars">@zstars</a>- You clearly have no experience in the work field. Let’s begin with your statement:</p>
<blockquote>"It gets turned into native code, yes. But that means nothing."</blockquote>
Way to go, either you miss the blatantly obvious in its entirety; or you consider "oxymoron" a religion.
<p>Now, you need to get your facts straight, the gaming industry (in which ALL of your examples come from) accounts for less than a meager 1% of all programing applications worldwide. As if that doesn’t state enough about the relevance of your quotes, you claim “C++” is more efficient, when clearly it’s not; I could straight up destroy you with code written to do the same things in C. Or even better ASM, or even better, use the processor documentation and code it SPECIFIC to each computer’s implementation. Or even better, get a degree in micro technologies, and build from the ground up a computer, 1 million times more efficient to execute the same chunk of code.</p>
<p>You appear to be naive, which is the only reason I even brought up education level.</p>
<p>You assume that pathfinding for 2000 people on a tile based game is actually in any form or way “a joke?” do you even know how the games’ pathfinding works? You generate a path, you keep the path client side, the path is WALKED/RAN 1 TILE by 1 TILE, all that the server need’s do is check if the tile is a valid one to move to, which is INCREDIBLY easy to do with a halving algorithm in say a lookup table? (BTW it’s also more efficient too [gasp]). It’s not a collision engine where complex maths decide when/if an object hits another object in the environment, it’s actually THAT basic, checkers on a checker board… Can you draw inside the lines?</p>
<p>Try, getting some programming experience in the real world market, then-&gt;come back? Maybe a 99.9% failure rate for game creators doesn’t stave you off, that’s fine <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=6" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"> I have no doubt the next big game company hasn’t even been founded, but forgive my skepticism. Life is not all fun and games;</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/best-language-to-make-games/88713/29">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/best-language-to-make-games/88713/29</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 05 May 2007 10:58:20 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-88713-29</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/best-language-to-make-games/88713.rss">Best language to make games?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Best language to make games?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@zstars zstars]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/zstars">@zstars</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p><a class="mention" href="/u/mopman">@mopman</a></p>
<p>Yes you are right, I wasn’t understanding what you meant by saying that websites were written in Java. Indeed, Java is a good language for more things than making applets.</p>
<p>Anyway, about runescape’s server language, there are reasons for both possibilities, and we will never know for sure unless they said it themselves, so I suppose there is no much point in arguing about it.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/best-language-to-make-games/88713/28">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/best-language-to-make-games/88713/28</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 05 May 2007 05:23:18 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-88713-28</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/best-language-to-make-games/88713.rss">Best language to make games?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Best language to make games?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@1337h4x 1337h4x]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/1337h4x">@1337h4x</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I always program my games in html, and very rarely use mySql if I want to make a graphic intense game.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/best-language-to-make-games/88713/27">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/best-language-to-make-games/88713/27</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 05 May 2007 02:41:14 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-88713-27</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/best-language-to-make-games/88713.rss">Best language to make games?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Best language to make games?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Mopman Mopman]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/mopman">@Mopman</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I quite understand you, and agree with many of your points. I wasn’t talking about webservers in relation to this argument, that was in response to you saying that a website could not be written in Java. We seem to just be using different terms here - you are basically saying that only what gets sent to the client is the website, whereas the application serving those pages, written in Java, is the server. I disagree. Take the World of Warcraft website again as an example - they are running Apache to serve pages, and Tomcat-powered Java code to generate XML, which is sent to the client and rendered. In my eyes, that website is written in Java, not XML, as the logic is all Java and the XML is purely the output. You saying that the website is written in HTML/XML and the Java code is simply a server sounds as silly to me as saying that a console app is written in <a href="http://command.com" rel="nofollow noopener">command.com</a> and the application is simply the provider. (I realise this analogy dosen’t quite fit, as a console is hardly a client-server model, I’m just trying to get you to see where the Java code fits in and understand what I mean when i say “the website is written in Java” and how that differs from “the server is written in Java”).</p>
<p>As for the MMORPG servers, if I was writing a MMORPG, the server would most certainly be in C++. I never said anywhere that Java was <span class="bbcode-i">better</span> than C++ for the job, but that it would hold up, or dare I say it would even be equal. This argument is the staple of the Java fan-boy wars and will never be settled until you write a game server in C++ and I write one in Java and we compare speeds, however I am confident in saying the Java one would perform. Java has come a long way since being ‘the language you write applets in’.</p>
<p>As a sidenote, of course Blizzard dosen’t ask for Java programmers for their network code - the client and server are both written in C++. With Runescape, however, the client is already written in Java, and they are after all called “Java Gaming Experts”. You may be right, the server may be in C++, however an explanation for the fact they are accepting C++ programmers where “no real company would do so” could be that in the online gaming world, Java is not a widely accepted language and there will be many C++ programmers applying for this job who would be perfectly capable, even if they may not have officially recognised Java qualifications or even a hell of a lot of experience. As I always say, a programmer is a programmer, they are not tied to one language.</p>
<p>Basically what I’m saying is, don’t rule out the idea that the server is Java, it is not as absurd as you think it is.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/best-language-to-make-games/88713/26">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/best-language-to-make-games/88713/26</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 05 May 2007 00:39:23 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-88713-26</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/best-language-to-make-games/88713.rss">Best language to make games?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Best language to make games?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@zstars zstars]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/zstars">@zstars</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p><a class="mention" href="/u/mopman">@mopman</a></p>
<p>I am sorry if I sounded like that, but I don’t think I have glaring errors. Websites and web servers are a different thing. A web servers, <em>serves</em> websites but a web server is <em>not</em> a website. Technologies such as the JavaServer Technologies aren’t websites, but, again, webservers. Also, in any case, as I already said, we are not talking about websites, but about MMORPGs. Also, none of the things I listed is database work. You are right that the benchmarks aren’t of servers though, so the situation might be different. However, if java was better for making mmorpg servers, we can assume that some mmorpg developer would have realised already. And the fact is that, except Runescape, and we aren’t even sure of that, as, no matter what you want to think, no serious gaming company would ask for C++ knowledge if Java is what they need, no company seems to have made a mmporg server in java. In fact, in most game studios they don’t even seem to need people with java knowledge, but C++'s instead, so we can assume they are writting their games and servers in that language.</p>
<p>Blizzard for example, which is the developer of WoW, the most successful MMORPG atm, doesn’t require java for any of their “programmer” jobs. For the job of “network programmer”, for example:</p>
<pre><code class="lang-auto"> Network Programmer

Blizzard Entertainment is looking for a talented and smart Software Engineer who has a passion for games and programming. This position is in the Core Technology department, which creates tools and libraries for games such as World of Warcraft, as well as continues the development of our legacy titles such as Warcraft 3, Starcraft and Diablo 2.

Blizzard offers a fun, creative, and technically challenging environment with excellent compensation and a full range of benefits.

Requirements

    * 2 years minimum industry or hobby programming C++.
    * BS degree or equivalent in experience.
    * Experience in writing tools
    * Comfortable with the fast pace of game technology; can learn and apply new knowledge quickly
    * A passion for video games!
    * SQL or other database experience a big plus.
    * Mac and cross-platform programming experience also a bonus. 

Please send code samples in text files as well as a cover letter, resume and salary history in separate Word format documents to resumes@blizzard.com. Please list this job and your name in the subject line.

Basic Tips for Resume/Demo Submission

No calls or follow-up emails, please. This is a full-time position in Irvine, California. </code></pre>
<p>Also, I never said that a high number of connections was a problem. The problem is that each one of these connections represent a player, who is constantly acting and sending packets to the server. Pathfinding for 1 player is fast. Pathfinding for 2000 isn’t a joke. And there is much more than pathfinding in a mmorpg. I’m just talking about pathfinding because it is basically pure maths. But even what is not pure maths takes processor time and resources.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/best-language-to-make-games/88713/25">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/best-language-to-make-games/88713/25</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 04 May 2007 23:56:03 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-88713-25</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/best-language-to-make-games/88713.rss">Best language to make games?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Best language to make games?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@frank frank_]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/frank">@frank</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[me=frank_]points at google, as someone else already has[/me]</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/best-language-to-make-games/88713/24">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/best-language-to-make-games/88713/24</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 04 May 2007 23:34:37 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-88713-24</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/best-language-to-make-games/88713.rss">Best language to make games?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Best language to make games?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Mopman Mopman]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/mopman">@Mopman</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Pretending efficiency dosen’t matter would indeed be unrealistic - but that is nothing close to what I said.</p>
<p>What I actually said was, most of what they are doing is not highly mathmatical, whereas the benchmarks you read where Java was x milliseconds slower than C are based on highly math-intensive tasks. Of course there is AI and pathfinding etc. - but most of what you listed is just enumeration and database work, not major math.</p>
<p>You did in fact say that websites don’t use Java - you said that anyone who says that is mistaking java for javascript. There is no such thing as a “website language” - websites can be and are written in exactly the same languages any other application is written in and Java is a very very big player.</p>
<p>A single example of a MMORPG server that is written in Java? Runescape, to the best of my knowledge. Before you say that I don’t know that for sure, you don’t know for sure what those other propietary (having a brain fart, can’t spell that word right this second) systems are written in either.</p>
<p>I wasn’t trying to disrespect anyone, discussion is a good thing - however your post came across with a tone that suggested you knew everything and we didn’t. People that do this while having glaring errors in their posts gets up my ass. Peace.</p>
<p>EDIT: “Having to handle lots of connections” is no reason at all not to use Java, by the way. As has been said, some of the hugest websites are written purely in Java. Just because the WoW website is a slow piece of shit, dosen’t mean Java Server Technologies are not scalable <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/wink.png?v=6" title=":wink:" class="emoji" alt=":wink:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/best-language-to-make-games/88713/23">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/best-language-to-make-games/88713/23</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 04 May 2007 23:19:46 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-88713-23</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/best-language-to-make-games/88713.rss">Best language to make games?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Best language to make games?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@zstars zstars]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/zstars">@zstars</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“Mopman, post:21, topic:88713”][quote]There are webpages with java applets, of course, after all that’s what java excels with. But what does that have to do with anything? Also, why do you say google is written in java? or other sites? For what I know, google, the search engine, doesn’t even have a java applet. Seeing how you are saying that top sites are written with Java, I suppose you are mistaking Java with JavaScript, which is a complete different thing and isn’t even a programming, but an scripting language.<br>
[/quote]</p>
<p>Your knowledge of server-side Java technologies is severely lacking. Maybe you should read up a bit on them before trying to argue that other people don’t know what they are talking about.</p>
<p>EDIT: The guy was referring to servlets etc., not Java applets or Javascript.</p>
<p>EDIT2: Actually, you mentioned World of Warcraft. Guess what language their website is written in? :)[/quote]</p>
<p>And maybe if you feel like being disrespectful you could at least try to make some sense.</p>
<p>Saying that a website is made in java is a wrong statement, because java is a programming language, not html, nor any other website language. Saying that a website uses java might be right, but even if google does, that has nothing to do with this topic. I am not talking about websites, we all know java is used in websites, and I’ve never said otherwise. I am talking about MMORPG servers.</p>
<p>If you don’t agree that most of them, if not all, are written in C++, provide A SINGLE EXAMPLE of one that is in java. Otherwise, stop insulting me with nothing but empty words.</p>
<p>By the way, talking about not knowing what talking about. We are talking about MMORPG servers. And your knowledge at that respect seems to be limited.</p>
<blockquote>If you read, they say that experience in C, C++ OR Java is required. Any competent C or C++ programmer can pick up Java with a snap of the fingers, so this doesn't necessarily mean the server is written in C++.
<p>The “Desirable” skills generally aren’t skills that are needed for the job, they just make you look better. Anyone who can efficiently solve a problem in assembler has a very organised and logical mind and in Jagex’s eyes would make a valuable addition to the team. You can’t use job requirements as proof.</p>
<p>That said, obviously nobody here works for Jagex (except Sema of course! Wink) and can’t know for sure, but personally I’d be inclined to say it’s Java. I see no reason to write the server in C/C++, there isn’t any HEAVY mathematical processing to do (well OK, there is a fair amount when you look at the big picture, but it’s not the main tasks), I hear that with Hotspot and such Java can be fairly efficient and it would just make a lot more sense businesswise to be using the same language.</p>
</blockquote>
<p>So there isn’t heavy mathematical processing? MMORPG servers are one of the most complex kind of servers, and their load IS heavy. In fact, most MMORPG’s servers can’t even be handled by a single computer. SWG, WOW, and EQ2 servers use a system of clusters.<br>
If you are wondering why a single PC can’t handle a server, lets think about it for a moment.<br>
Of course, a MMORPG server is way too complex, so let’s focus on the mathematical aspects.</p>
<p>A full runescape server has 2000 players. The same server, has to keep hold of <em>thousand</em> of npcs. From the varrock banker to a rat in lumbridge. Seeing how these NPCS have an AI, the servers has to be <em>constantly</em> going through their AI loops. Also, quite often, the AI will decide that it’s time for the NPC to move around. Then, and that can happens to npcs about once every 20 seconds, random numbers will have to be generated, in order to move to a random place. Also, a pathfinding algorith has to be run, because otherwise the rat could walk through a wall. Of course, while all this happens, the server has also to parse the thousand mbs in packets coming from the two thousand clients. Once parsed, it has to carry out these actions, which most often will also involve generating random numbers, making calculations (such as damage, or success chance) and pathfinding (any walking requires pathfinding). The server, of course, also has to keep track of every item each player has in its inventory, and the anti cheating measure has to check that every client is legit and is not sending wrong packets, such as “go through wall” or “attack banker” packets. Of course, I could go on, but I hope you get the idea. MMORPGS require hundreds of computers, often in clusters, running the server. Pretending efficiency doesn’t matter, or that servers don’t need to be efficient, can hardly be more unrealistic.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/best-language-to-make-games/88713/22">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/best-language-to-make-games/88713/22</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 04 May 2007 22:55:20 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-88713-22</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/best-language-to-make-games/88713.rss">Best language to make games?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Best language to make games?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Mopman Mopman]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/mopman">@Mopman</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <blockquote>There are webpages with java applets, of course, after all that's what java excels with. But what does that have to do with anything? Also, why do you say google is written in java? or other sites? For what I know, google, the search engine, doesn't even have a java applet. Seeing how you are saying that top sites are written with Java, I suppose you are mistaking Java with JavaScript, which is a complete different thing and isn't even a programming, but an scripting language.</blockquote>
<p>Your knowledge of server-side Java technologies is severely lacking. Maybe you should read up a bit on them before trying to argue that other people don’t know what they are talking about.</p>
<p>EDIT: The guy was referring to servlets etc., not Java applets or Javascript.</p>
<p>EDIT2: Actually, you mentioned World of Warcraft. Guess what language their website is written in? <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=6" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/best-language-to-make-games/88713/21">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/best-language-to-make-games/88713/21</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 04 May 2007 22:12:53 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-88713-21</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/best-language-to-make-games/88713.rss">Best language to make games?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Best language to make games?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@zstars zstars]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/zstars">@zstars</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“jagex_fagex, post:15, topic:88713”][quote author=ruler link=topic=129809.msg1262628#msg1262628 date=1178303644]<br>
I suggest using PHP to write games.<br>
[/quote]<br>
so wtf are you smoking?</p>
<p>ima start with c++ i think, any more suggestions for graphics, like texturing, mapping, that kiinda stuff?[/quote]</p>
<p>There are free engines which you can use. You could use directx straight away but it’s not worth it. Personally, I like Irrlicht the most (3d engine) but Ogre3d is very good too, maybe even better. If you don’t feel confident enough to use 3d straight away, or if you aren’t too fluent with C++ yet, you can try a 2D engine first, such as Allegro. One thing though, before starting with anything it is important to know C++ well enough. Also, some useful advice would be to start low. Personally, I always started with a Pong game.</p>
<p>Now, about my lovers… First I would like to say that Java is a great language, but idealizing it does no good. Let’s face reality.</p>
<p>[quote=“k00dr, post:16, topic:88713”][quote author=zstars link=topic=129809.msg1262132#msg1262132 date=1178290340]<br>
Don’t kill me please. Joking, what’s up with you though, no need to get aggressive. Bytecode languages are less efficient than C++, and that’s a fact. If in any aspect a byte code language is more efficient, it is only because the C++ programmer didn’t make a good job. Otherwise most programs would be made in java, as it is platform independant and easier to debug, but reality shows that most are made in C++. And that’s because it’s more efficient. Proof?<br>
[/quote]</p>
<p>If you actually knew about JIT compilation and Java HotSpot, then maybe you would stop pulling these “facts” out of your ass :P[/quote]</p>
<p>The facts are just where your quote ends. And you know that. If you search in google, there are hundreds of benchmarks that prove that C++ is more efficient. And if in one it isn’t, it is because the C++ programmer doesn’t know how to manage memory.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group quote-modified" data-post="17" data-topic="88713">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/newbiehacker/40/5_6259e4fa9dfe0dec282fb0955bb1974c.png" class="avatar"> newbiehacker:</div>
<blockquote>
<p><a class="mention" href="/u/zstars">@zstars</a>: perhaps if you had read pplsuqbawlz’s post correctly you would have noticed him talking about the hotspost VM.  Now I’m sure you don’t understand what JIT compiling is, but if you could go read the definition, then you would probably evenetually come to the conclusion that it stands for “Just In Time” compiler and has something to do about converting bytecode.  The thing is, that this simple task turns the java bytecode contained in the class files into native code.  Now I’m no expert, but I’d say that java bytecode turned programatically into native code instead of being typed by a human would be MORE efficient than anything most people could code.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I know about the JIT debugger. It gets turned into native code, yes. But that means nothing. Even if your statement about humans being unable to write code more efficiently than machines was true (and it isn’t) it wouldn’t be relevant, because java code is optimized, but so is C++'s.<br>
Also, in reality, the higher level a language is, the slower it is. Assembler (if you’re good enough) is faster than C, C is faster than C++, C++ is faster than Java. For proof, refer to the links I posted earlier or look for any unbiased benchmark table. You are right, however, that many people using a lower level language wouldn’t write faster code, because they don’t understand that language properly or because they don’t know how to optimize.</p>
<p>[quote=“pplsuqbawlz, post:18, topic:88713”][quote author=k00dr link=topic=129809.msg1262745#msg1262745 date=1178308025]</p>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p>Don’t kill me please. Joking, what’s up with you though, no need to get aggressive. Bytecode languages are less efficient than C++, and that’s a fact. If in any aspect a byte code language is more efficient, it is only because the C++ programmer didn’t make a good job. Otherwise most programs would be made in java, as it is platform independant and easier to debug, but reality shows that most are made in C++. And that’s because it’s more efficient. Proof?</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>If you actually knew about JIT compilation and Java HotSpot, then maybe you would stop pulling these “facts” out of your ass <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=6" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"><br>
[/quote]</p>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p><a class="mention" href="/u/zstars">@zstars</a>: perhaps if you had read pplsuqbawlz’s post correctly you would have noticed him talking about the hotspost VM.  Now I’m sure you don’t understand what JIT compiling is, but if you could go read the definition, then you would probably evenetually come to the conclusion that it stands for “Just In Time” compiler and has something to do about converting bytecode.  The thing is, that this simple task turns the java bytecode contained in the class files into native code.  Now I’m no expert, but I’d say that java bytecode turned programatically into native code instead of being typed by a human would be MORE efficient than anything most people could code.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Precisely. And Javacisnotrecognized, the post was not directed towards you, I simply agreed with you and then went on to discuss other things.</p>
<p>PHP, eww, it’s not even a compiled language more like script “pre-hyper-text-processing” language. EWWW. Naw php has its usages, a game, isn’t highly suggested.</p>
<p><a class="mention" href="/u/zstars">@zstars</a>: Like semaphore stated previously, it’s easy as hell for even the noobiest programmer to make a rock solid secure server infrastructure in java, with little to no effort. Plus, if you want to quote examples to me, look at google, and all the other top sites in the world… They’re written in java. Especially google. Please get your facts straight, go to college (it’s not pointless school, some of the crap you learn there does have a point).[/quote]</p>
<p>Yeah, it’s true that it is easy to make a server in java. And in Visual Basic too, for that matter. Also, you shouldn’t worry about my education, you should worry more about yours. I don’t even see what you are trying to tell me when you say that top sites are written in java. A site is, for me, a webpage. There are webpages with java applets, of course, after all that’s what java excels with. But what does that have to do with anything? Also, why do you say google is written in java? or other sites? For what I know, google, the search engine, doesn’t even have a java applet. Seeing how you are saying that top sites are written with Java, I suppose you are mistaking Java with JavaScript, which is a complete different thing and isn’t even a programming, but an scripting language.</p>
<p>Finally, some facts, if you don’t believe them, check them yourself.<br>
-Apache, the most popular web server, is written in ANSI C for compatibility and efficiency.<br>
-World of Warcraft server is written in C++.<br>
-StarWars Galaxies server is written in C++.<br>
-Everquest server is written in C++.<br>
-Everquest 2 server is written in C++.<br>
-Half Life / Counter strike dedicated servers are written in C++.<br>
-Quake 4 dedicated servers are written in C++.<br>
-Diablo 2 servers are written in C++.<br>
(…)</p>
<p>In fact, I don’t know of any single professional server for any game that is programmed in java. You can argue and say that that JIT is god, but in that fact is the reality. No professional company writes game servers in java, and much less MMORPG servers, because it would be a waste of money. Also, if anyone is curious as to how I know these servers are written in java, in the case of dedicated servers, they are available for download. In the case for MMORPG servers, you can check that the only jobs they offer for java programmers, is as a web designer. You can also check that any game or systems related job requires C++.</p>
<p>Edit: I don’t even know why I am wasting time about this…</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/best-language-to-make-games/88713/20">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/best-language-to-make-games/88713/20</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 04 May 2007 22:07:40 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-88713-20</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/best-language-to-make-games/88713.rss">Best language to make games?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Best language to make games?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@pplsuqbawlz pplsuqbawlz]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/pplsuqbawlz">@pplsuqbawlz</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote no-group quote-modified" data-post="2" data-topic="89137">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/lawl/40/5_6259e4fa9dfe0dec282fb0955bb1974c.png" class="avatar"><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/89137/2">On another topic</a>
</div>
<blockquote>
<p>[quote]* Assembler programming experience;</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>why does jagex want assembly experience?</p>
<p>why do i always make new pages[/quote]<br>
RS-Demon need’s to be cracked by jagex. Lol they wanna know what makes it tick.</p>
<p>And you make new pages because, you always chime in 10 seconds too late.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/best-language-to-make-games/88713/19">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/best-language-to-make-games/88713/19</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 04 May 2007 20:58:35 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-88713-19</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/best-language-to-make-games/88713.rss">Best language to make games?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Best language to make games?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@pplsuqbawlz pplsuqbawlz]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/pplsuqbawlz">@pplsuqbawlz</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“k00dr, post:16, topic:88713”][quote author=zstars link=topic=129809.msg1262132#msg1262132 date=1178290340]<br>
Don’t kill me please. Joking, what’s up with you though, no need to get aggressive. Bytecode languages are less efficient than C++, and that’s a fact. If in any aspect a byte code language is more efficient, it is only because the C++ programmer didn’t make a good job. Otherwise most programs would be made in java, as it is platform independant and easier to debug, but reality shows that most are made in C++. And that’s because it’s more efficient. Proof?<br>
[/quote]</p>
<p>If you actually knew about JIT compilation and Java HotSpot, then maybe you would stop pulling these “facts” out of your ass :P[/quote]</p>
<aside class="quote no-group quote-modified" data-post="17" data-topic="88713">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/newbiehacker/40/5_6259e4fa9dfe0dec282fb0955bb1974c.png" class="avatar"> newbiehacker:</div>
<blockquote>
<p><a class="mention" href="/u/zstars">@zstars</a>: perhaps if you had read pplsuqbawlz’s post correctly you would have noticed him talking about the hotspost VM.  Now I’m sure you don’t understand what JIT compiling is, but if you could go read the definition, then you would probably evenetually come to the conclusion that it stands for “Just In Time” compiler and has something to do about converting bytecode.  The thing is, that this simple task turns the java bytecode contained in the class files into native code.  Now I’m no expert, but I’d say that java bytecode turned programatically into native code instead of being typed by a human would be MORE efficient than anything most people could code.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Precisely. And Javacisnotrecognized, the post was not directed towards you, I simply agreed with you and then went on to discuss other things.</p>
<p>PHP, eww, it’s not even a compiled language more like script “pre-hyper-text-processing” language. EWWW. Naw php has its usages, a game, isn’t highly suggested.</p>
<p><a class="mention" href="/u/zstars">@zstars</a>: Like semaphore stated previously, it’s easy as hell for even the noobiest programmer to make a rock solid secure server infrastructure in java, with little to no effort. Plus, if you want to quote examples to me, look at google, and all the other top sites in the world… They’re written in java. Especially google. Please get your facts straight, go to college (it’s not pointless school, some of the crap you learn there does have a point).</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/best-language-to-make-games/88713/18">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/best-language-to-make-games/88713/18</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 04 May 2007 20:36:40 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-88713-18</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/best-language-to-make-games/88713.rss">Best language to make games?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Best language to make games?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@newbiehacker newbiehacker]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/newbiehacker">@newbiehacker</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p><a class="mention" href="/u/zstars">@zstars</a>: perhaps if you had read pplsuqbawlz’s post correctly you would have noticed him talking about the hotspost VM.  Now I’m sure you don’t understand what JIT compiling is, but if you could go read the definition, then you would probably evenetually come to the conclusion that it stands for “Just In Time” compiler and has something to do about converting bytecode.  The thing is, that this simple task turns the java bytecode contained in the class files into native code.  Now I’m no expert, but I’d say that java bytecode turned programatically into native code instead of being typed by a human would be MORE efficient than anything most people could code.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/best-language-to-make-games/88713/17">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/best-language-to-make-games/88713/17</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 04 May 2007 20:05:26 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-88713-17</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/best-language-to-make-games/88713.rss">Best language to make games?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Best language to make games?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@k00dr k00dr]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/k00dr">@k00dr</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote no-group quote-modified" data-post="11" data-topic="88713">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/user_avatar/forum.moparisthebest.com/zstars/40/166_2.png" class="avatar"> zstars:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Don’t kill me please. Joking, what’s up with you though, no need to get aggressive. Bytecode languages are less efficient than C++, and that’s a fact. If in any aspect a byte code language is more efficient, it is only because the C++ programmer didn’t make a good job. Otherwise most programs would be made in java, as it is platform independant and easier to debug, but reality shows that most are made in C++. And that’s because it’s more efficient. Proof?</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>If you actually knew about JIT compilation and Java HotSpot, then maybe you would stop pulling these “facts” out of your ass <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=6" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/best-language-to-make-games/88713/16">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/best-language-to-make-games/88713/16</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 04 May 2007 19:47:05 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-88713-16</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/best-language-to-make-games/88713.rss">Best language to make games?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Best language to make games?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@jagex_fagex jagex_fagex]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/jagex_fagex">@jagex_fagex</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote no-group" data-post="13" data-topic="88713">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/ruler/40/5_6259e4fa9dfe0dec282fb0955bb1974c.png" class="avatar"> ruler:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>I suggest using PHP to write games.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>so wtf are you smoking?</p>
<p>ima start with c++ i think, any more suggestions for graphics, like texturing, mapping, that kiinda stuff?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/best-language-to-make-games/88713/15">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/best-language-to-make-games/88713/15</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 04 May 2007 18:59:07 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-88713-15</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/best-language-to-make-games/88713.rss">Best language to make games?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Best language to make games?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@frank frank_]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/frank">@frank</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“pplsuqbawlz, post:6, topic:88713”]And just for clarification, the runescape server is written in java.</p>
<p>FOR PROOF: Java is not low end enough to provide responses to ping requests, try pinging the server.</p>
<p>The server Name is “JaGeX 3.1”… Also standard for java to rename the server… Not to mention all the file types are “ws” webservlet (java)… lol. There’s plenty more reasons for those whom look.[/quote]</p>
<p>the servers run debian, afaik you are allowed to run different services on it &gt;_&gt;</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/best-language-to-make-games/88713/14">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/best-language-to-make-games/88713/14</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 04 May 2007 18:38:26 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-88713-14</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/best-language-to-make-games/88713.rss">Best language to make games?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Best language to make games?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@ruler ruler]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/ruler">@ruler</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I suggest using PHP to write games.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/best-language-to-make-games/88713/13">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/best-language-to-make-games/88713/13</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 04 May 2007 18:34:04 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-88713-13</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/best-language-to-make-games/88713.rss">Best language to make games?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Best language to make games?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Mopman Mopman]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/mopman">@Mopman</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>If you read, they say that experience in C, C++ OR Java is required. Any competent C or C++ programmer can pick up Java with a snap of the fingers, so this doesn’t necessarily mean the server is written in C++.</p>
<p>The “Desirable” skills generally aren’t skills that are needed for the job, they just make you look better. Anyone who can efficiently solve a problem in assembler has a very organised and logical mind and in Jagex’s eyes would make a valuable addition to the team. You can’t use job requirements as proof.</p>
<p>That said, obviously nobody here works for Jagex (except Sema of course! ;)) and can’t know for sure, but personally I’d be inclined to say it’s Java. I see no reason to write the server in C/C++, there isn’t any HEAVY mathematical processing to do (well OK, there is a fair amount when you look at the big picture, but it’s not the main tasks), I hear that with Hotspot and such Java can be fairly efficient and it would just make a lot more sense businesswise to be using the same language.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/best-language-to-make-games/88713/12">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/best-language-to-make-games/88713/12</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 04 May 2007 16:47:06 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-88713-12</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/best-language-to-make-games/88713.rss">Best language to make games?</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
