<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Qq</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/qq/416994</link>
    <description>Well, today I have finally reached my goal, which was to get full bandos, dragonfire shield, fury, whip etc etc.. So then when I finally got my bandos chestplate today, (I spent all day at blue dragons.) I decided to go to the clan wars and test the gear out.. I was there for about 3 hours, then I started to get a bit tired (it was 4:00am) but still continued to play.. So I kept going back and fourth in the white portal.. Then I mistakenly clicked the red portal.. I ran in, then got barraged and dragon claw rushed in seconds. I didn&#39;t think anything of it at the time because I thought I was in the white portal.. So after I died I realized my guy had nothing on him and lost everything.. So yeah Gf bank.. QQ

Dejavu I guess? 3 years ago the same thing happened, but I only lost rune (G). :P

[s]But yeah, just wanted to tell you guys, even though I&#39;ll probably get flamed in seconds.. :|[/s]

lol I don&#39;t know why I told you guys this last night.. I guess a mod should delete it or lock it, seeing how this is topic is pretty much useless...</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 04 Oct 2011 09:02:56 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/qq/416994.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Qq</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@EMINEM_BEAST EMINEM BEAST™]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/eminem_beast">@EMINEM_BEAST</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Well, today I have finally reached my goal, which was to get full bandos, dragonfire shield, fury, whip etc etc… So then when I finally got my bandos chestplate today, (I spent all day at blue dragons.) I decided to go to the clan wars and test the gear out… I was there for about 3 hours, then I started to get a bit tired (it was 4:00am) but still continued to play… So I kept going back and fourth in the white portal… Then I mistakenly clicked the red portal… I ran in, then got barraged and dragon claw rushed in seconds. I didn’t think anything of it at the time because I thought I was in the white portal… So after I died I realized my guy had nothing on him and lost everything… So yeah Gf bank… QQ</p>
<p>Dejavu I guess? 3 years ago the same thing happened, but I only lost rune (G). <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=5" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"></p>
<p><span class="bbcode-s">But yeah, just wanted to tell you guys, even though I’ll probably get flamed in seconds… <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/expressionless.png?v=5" title=":expressionless:" class="emoji" alt=":expressionless:"></span></p>
<p>lol I don’t know why I told you guys this last night… I guess a mod should delete it or lock it, seeing how this is topic is pretty much useless…</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/qq/416994/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/qq/416994/1</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 04 Oct 2011 09:02:56 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-416994-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/qq/416994.rss">Qq</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
