<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Marijuana Legalization!</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/marijuana-legalization/272186</link>
    <description>Well i&#39;ve been doin some research today and I told myself lets compare, weed, alcohol, cigarettes... You will be amazed at what I found out!!!  :D  ;)  :eek: LEGALIZE IT!!!  ;D


Death Ratio Of The U.S.:
1. Heart disease: 652,091
2. Cancer: 559,312 
3. Stroke (cerebrovascular diseases): 143,579 
4. Chronic lower respiratory diseases: 130,933 
5. Accidents (unintentional injuries): 117,809 
6. Diabetes: 75,119 
7. Alzheimer&#39;s disease: 71,599 
8. Influenza/Pneumonia: 63,001 
9. Nephritis, nephrotic syndrome, and nephrosis: 43,901 
10. Septicemia: 34,136 


Chemicals in Marijuana:
THC (delta-9-tetrahydrocannabinol)
400 other known Chemicals (But other plants contain 400 chemicals as well)


Cigarettes: (These Chemicals Can Kill You) Over 4,000 Chemicals, 43 Cause Cancer
Benzene: Petrol Additive  (carcinogen and is associated with leukaemia, used as a solvent in fuel)
Formaldehyd: Embalming Fluid (causes cancer, highly poisonous, used to preserve dead bodies)
Ammonia: Cleaner (Ammonia is used for cleaning utensils such as... Floor Cleaner, Toilet Cleaner etc.)
Acetone: Nail Polish Remover (This chemical is used in Nail Polish Remover)
Tar: (Can get drawn into the lungs and fill your lungs up thus causing cancer, and respritory issues)
Nicotine: Insecticide (One of the most addictive substances)
Carbon Monoxide: Car Exhaust Fumes (Odorless, tasteless, poisionous gas, can cause Carbon Monoxide Poisioning when taken in large quanities)
Arsenic: Rat Poison (Used daily to kill your household rodents)
Hydrogen Cyanide: Gas Chamber
DDT: Banned Insecticide
Lead: (Lead can be fatal when taken in large quanities, thus causing lead poisioning)
Napthalene: MothBalls (Ingredient in mothballs, mothballs are used to keep snakes, beetles and other insects off your lawn)
Cadmium: Batteries (Cadmium is used in most batteries, like the Nickle Cadmium battery in your computer!)
Butane: Lighter Fluid (Gas thats used in lighter fluid)


Alcohol:
Drinking Alcohol leads to loss of coordination, judgement, slower reflexes, distorted vision, memory lapse, blackouts
Alcohol can damage every organ in your body
Can cause cancer
Drinking large quanities of alcohol can lead to comas, or death
Even if your not drinking if your around people drinking you have a higher chance of getting hurt
You can&#39;t drive after one drink
Mixing alcohol with medications can cause death
Bad Breath
Addictive
Depresses your central nervous system

Makes you do things you normally wouldn&#39;t do, such as driving while under the influence of alcohol
ALCOHOL IS A DRUG
Extensive alcohol intake is likely to produce withdrawal symptoms, including severe anxiety, tremors, hallucinations, and convulsions
More than 100,000 U.S. deaths are caused by excessive alcohol consumption each year. Direct and indirect causes of death include drunk driving, cirrhosis of the liver, falls, cancer, and stroke.
Youth who drink alcohol are 50 times more likely to use cocaine than those who never drink alcohol.
Traffic crashes are the greatest single cause of death for persons aged 6–33. About 45% of these fatalities are in alcohol-related crashes.
Underage drinking costs the United States more than $58 billion every year — enough to buy every public school student a state-of-the-art computer.
Alcohol kills 6½ times more youth than all other illicit drugs combined.


Short Term / Long Term Effects Marijuana:
Bad Short Term Memory
Lowered Learning Abilities
Difficulty Thinking &amp; Problem Solving
Inability To Drive: (Lower than drinking alcohol)
Distorted Senses, Sight, Hearing, Touch, Time, and Depth
Reduced Athletic Ability
Elevated Heart Rate
Anxiety, Panic Attacks
Cancer: (Smoke it moderately lessens the risk of getting cancer, moderately means a joint every few days!)
Dry Mouth: Kotton Mouth (Easy fix just drink liquids)


Long Term Effects Of Cigarettes:
Cancer: Cancer is an alternation in cells causing your cells to grow and spread rapidly.
Heart &amp; Blood Vessel Disease: Carbon Monoxide gets into the blood and decreases oxygen going to the heart. The more you smoke the greater risk you have of having a heart attack.
Lung Disease: Bronchitis, Emphysema, higher risk of getting colds, pneumonia, and other lung infections
Gastrointestinal disease: Increases the acid in your stomache, can cause peptic ulcer
Gastroesophageal reflux: Stomache acid comes up into your esophagus.
Higher risk of bone fractures
Men have problems getting erections
Insomnia
Reduced Athletic Ability


Good Effects Of Marijuana:
Munchies: (Makes you eat a lot)
Sexual Stimulant: (Makes you wanna have sex)
Increase Mental Abilities: (May be different for others but some it will increase your thinking)
Safer to smoke marijuana than drinking alcohol
Reduce problems with glaucoma: (glaucoma causes you to lose your vision)
Relaxes
Improves Creativity / Imagination
Reduces Anger Issues
Reduces nausea from chemotherapy
Helps you eat and hold food down
Fantastic Antidepressant: (Less side effects than many prescription antidepressants)
Reduces stress


Facts and Info of Marijuana:
Marijuana may help ease symptoms of AIDS, Cancer, Multiple Sclerosis, Depression.
People really can&#39;t overdoes on marijuana (Small animals yes because they are smaller, but people NO)

Facts About Cigarettes:
Nicotine is more of a gateway drug, because kids get hold of cigarettes then they get addicted to them and there is the introduction of smoking.
Cigarettes cost the nation over $100 Billion per year in health costs!
Tobacco companies spend over $4 billion a year promoting their deadly product
1.3 Million people quit smoking each year, but about 48 Million continue to smoke
Tobacco is often the first drug used by young people, who then go on and use alcohol, marijuana, and other drugs!!


How The Economy Can Benefit Off Of Marijuana Being Legal:
	The United States will flourish if marijuana is legal, even though there are many different strands of marijuana
there can be a flat tax for all of them just like how there is with onions, apples, carrots, lettuce etc... Just look at
any food produce that can be grown, thats the same for marijuana, we can sell marijuana in stores, such as gas stations,
medical facilities, drug stores, almost any local store. Marijuana is just like any produce you can grow it you can sell it
there shouldn&#39;t be a law against growing it or using it, it can benefit the whole country by it being legal, more than half
of the United States does marijuana illegally. If marijuana was legal we wouldn&#39;t have to spend money on housing inmates in jail
the average inmate costs $94.87, when you could just keep them out of jail. Just think how much money the whole country would save
if marijuana was legal, lets say 1500000 people go to jail for marijuana a year, for them to stay just one day thats $142,305,000!
Now if we didn&#39;t put them in jail for marijuana thats $142,305,000 more to spend on education, roads, medical etc. The government is
wasting money on putting people in jail for having marijuana, people who do marijuana just wanna do marijuana they
don&#39;t wanna bother anyone else. If marijuana was legal there would be less crimes over drugs, because people could just go to the store
and buy it instead of having to hide from the law to deal their drugs to get money under the table. When the government can just sell it
by gram, ounces, pounds etc. Anyways marijuana is less lethal than any other drugs out there like cigarettes, alcohol if you compare all the
data I collected you will find that marijuana is less dangerous than all of the others. If the U.S. is afraid of losing money they could just tax
it like how I said, and more money will come in, because if you think about it marijuana is just like apples, apples you can grow legally then you can
eat them without paying tax to the government, so marijuana you can grow and use it without getting taxed by the government so if marijuana isn&#39;t legal because
of that reason then what makes apples legal?


Websites:
http://www.drugs.com/cg/cigarette-smoking-and-its-health-risks.html
http://www.well.com/user/woa/fspot.htm
http://serendip.brynmawr.edu/exchange/node/1808
http://www.quitsmokingsupport.com/whatsinit.htm
http://www.quit-smoking-stop.com/harmful-chemicals-in-cigarettes.html
http://www.cdc.gov/nchs/FASTATS/lcod.htm
http://www.allpotseeds.com/bad-effects-of-pot.html
http://www.alaw.org/tobacco_control/quit_smoking_today/quit_kit/facts_about_cigarette_smoking.html
http://www.freevibe.com/Drug_Facts/alcohol.asp
http://ncadi.samhsa.gov/govpubs/ph323/
http://www.gdcada.org/statistics/alcohol.htm
http://www.dc.state.fl.us/pub/statsbrief/cost.html</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 10 Apr 2009 12:47:33 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>General Discussion</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/marijuana-legalization/272186.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Marijuana Legalization!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@The_Un-Named The Un-Named]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/the_un-named">@The_Un-Named</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Feel free to repost this when it’s a bit more structured, but try to keep such facts as alcohol leads to cocaine, and tobaco to drugs out of it please.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/marijuana-legalization/272186/18">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/marijuana-legalization/272186/18</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 Apr 2009 12:47:33 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-272186-18</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/marijuana-legalization/272186.rss">Marijuana Legalization!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Marijuana Legalization!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@bowserjr2 Bowser jr]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/bowserjr2">@bowserjr2</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“zammyking111, post:4, topic:272186”]You can’t ban em all because if you ban em all, more people will go to jail and as i found out it costs $94.87 a day to house an inmate, well in the state of Florida that is.</p>
<p>And seriously if your gonna post useless comments and being a dick about it, just go /cut wrist and don’t post on this thread.[/quote]<br>
Don’t put them into jail but give them a fine, and disallow sale and import of it.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/marijuana-legalization/272186/17">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/marijuana-legalization/272186/17</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 Apr 2009 10:44:52 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-272186-17</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/marijuana-legalization/272186.rss">Marijuana Legalization!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Marijuana Legalization!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@zammyking111 zammyking111]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/zammyking111">@zammyking111</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I forgot to add the cost of a probation officer in that cost <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=6" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"> man our government, spends, spends, spends and is spending money it doesn’t even have.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/marijuana-legalization/272186/16">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/marijuana-legalization/272186/16</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 Apr 2009 06:23:21 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-272186-16</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/marijuana-legalization/272186.rss">Marijuana Legalization!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Marijuana Legalization!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Cheese_Police c|p]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/cheese_police">@Cheese_Police</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote no-group" data-post="3" data-topic="272186">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/bowserjr2/40/5_6bca9977b612b7aeef77ba1ec1cd67b3.png" class="avatar"> bowserjr2:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Why not just ban Cigarettes, alcohol and Marijuana.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>because prohibition doesn’t work.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/marijuana-legalization/272186/15">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/marijuana-legalization/272186/15</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 Apr 2009 03:17:07 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-272186-15</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/marijuana-legalization/272186.rss">Marijuana Legalization!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Marijuana Legalization!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@SomethingToHide STH]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/somethingtohide">@SomethingToHide</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote no-group" data-post="12" data-topic="272186">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/zammyking111/40/5_6bca9977b612b7aeef77ba1ec1cd67b3.png" class="avatar"> zammyking111:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>exactly legalize it <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=6" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"></p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I was talking about the idea of banning cigarettes/alcohol. Honestly we NEED them. Population control, let the fuckers die.</p>
<p>But I’m all for legalizing.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/marijuana-legalization/272186/14">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/marijuana-legalization/272186/14</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 Apr 2009 02:29:22 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-272186-14</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/marijuana-legalization/272186.rss">Marijuana Legalization!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Marijuana Legalization!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@cooper cooper]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/cooper">@cooper</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“SomethingToHide, post:11, topic:272186”]Didn’t anyone learn anything from the prohibition act?</p>
<p>Making it illegal makes MORE people do it and causes MORE problems.[/quote]<br>
Not if the government uses lethal force… <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=6" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/marijuana-legalization/272186/13">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/marijuana-legalization/272186/13</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 Apr 2009 02:28:31 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-272186-13</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/marijuana-legalization/272186.rss">Marijuana Legalization!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Marijuana Legalization!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@zammyking111 zammyking111]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/zammyking111">@zammyking111</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>exactly legalize it <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=6" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/marijuana-legalization/272186/12">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/marijuana-legalization/272186/12</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 Apr 2009 02:27:52 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-272186-12</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/marijuana-legalization/272186.rss">Marijuana Legalization!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Marijuana Legalization!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@SomethingToHide STH]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/somethingtohide">@SomethingToHide</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Didn’t anyone learn anything from the prohibition act?</p>
<p>Making it illegal makes MORE people do it and causes MORE problems.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/marijuana-legalization/272186/11">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/marijuana-legalization/272186/11</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 Apr 2009 02:25:12 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-272186-11</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/marijuana-legalization/272186.rss">Marijuana Legalization!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Marijuana Legalization!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@zammyking111 zammyking111]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/zammyking111">@zammyking111</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“Frell, post:9, topic:272186”][quote author=zammyking111 link=topic=359127.msg2740604#msg2740604 date=1239329307]<br>
not true, there still will be people that do not do it, like there are people that do not smoke cigarettes. You respect those peoples wishes and don’t make them do something that they don’t want, I don’t smoke marijuana. I just started growing it, for some of my friends <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/smiley.png?v=6" title=":smiley:" class="emoji" alt=":smiley:"><br>
[/quote]<br>
That is why you bug me on msn with links to music videos about gettin high.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p>If it was legal everyone would be mindless high zombies doing nothing</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>most of the united states is already in that state.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Good point but why have more? If you get caught into weed you will realize that it is more fun and enjoyable than alot of things, but you waste so much doing it.[/quote]<br>
Thats only kottonmouth kings <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/expressionless.png?v=6" title=":expressionless:" class="emoji" alt=":expressionless:"> doesn’t mean you do it…</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/marijuana-legalization/272186/10">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/marijuana-legalization/272186/10</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 Apr 2009 02:18:33 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-272186-10</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/marijuana-legalization/272186.rss">Marijuana Legalization!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Marijuana Legalization!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Frell Frell]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/frell">@Frell</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote no-group quote-modified" data-post="6" data-topic="272186">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/zammyking111/40/5_6bca9977b612b7aeef77ba1ec1cd67b3.png" class="avatar"> zammyking111:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>not true, there still will be people that do not do it, like there are people that do not smoke cigarettes. You respect those peoples wishes and don’t make them do something that they don’t want, I don’t smoke marijuana. I just started growing it, for some of my friends <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/smiley.png?v=6" title=":smiley:" class="emoji" alt=":smiley:"></p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>That is why you bug me on msn with links to music videos about gettin high.</p>
<p>[quote=“Miss Silabsoft, post:7, topic:272186”][quote author=Frell link=topic=359127.msg2740600#msg2740600 date=1239329211]<br>
If it was legal everyone would be mindless high zombies doing nothing<br>
[/quote]<br>
most of the united states is already in that state.[/quote]<br>
Good point but why have more? If you get caught into weed you will realize that it is more fun and enjoyable than alot of things, but you waste so much doing it.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/marijuana-legalization/272186/9">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/marijuana-legalization/272186/9</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 Apr 2009 02:11:38 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-272186-9</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/marijuana-legalization/272186.rss">Marijuana Legalization!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Marijuana Legalization!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@lawl lawl]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/lawl">@lawl</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>thanks for pointing out the obvious</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/marijuana-legalization/272186/8">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/marijuana-legalization/272186/8</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 Apr 2009 02:11:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-272186-8</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/marijuana-legalization/272186.rss">Marijuana Legalization!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Marijuana Legalization!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@silabsoft RuneAgent]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/silabsoft">@silabsoft</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote no-group" data-post="5" data-topic="272186">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/frell/40/5_6bca9977b612b7aeef77ba1ec1cd67b3.png" class="avatar"> Frell:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>If it was legal everyone would be mindless high zombies doing nothing</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>most of the united states is already in that state.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/marijuana-legalization/272186/7">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/marijuana-legalization/272186/7</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 Apr 2009 02:09:49 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-272186-7</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/marijuana-legalization/272186.rss">Marijuana Legalization!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Marijuana Legalization!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@zammyking111 zammyking111]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/zammyking111">@zammyking111</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>not true, there still will be people that do not do it, like there are people that do not smoke cigarettes. You respect those peoples wishes and don’t make them do something that they don’t want, I don’t smoke marijuana. I just started growing it, for some of my friends <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/smiley.png?v=6" title=":smiley:" class="emoji" alt=":smiley:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/marijuana-legalization/272186/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/marijuana-legalization/272186/6</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 Apr 2009 02:08:27 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-272186-6</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/marijuana-legalization/272186.rss">Marijuana Legalization!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Marijuana Legalization!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Frell Frell]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/frell">@Frell</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>If it was legal everyone would be mindless high zombies doing nothing</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/marijuana-legalization/272186/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/marijuana-legalization/272186/5</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 Apr 2009 02:06:51 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-272186-5</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/marijuana-legalization/272186.rss">Marijuana Legalization!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Marijuana Legalization!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@zammyking111 zammyking111]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/zammyking111">@zammyking111</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>You can’t ban em all because if you ban em all, more people will go to jail and as i found out it costs $94.87 a day to house an inmate, well in the state of Florida that is.</p>
<p>And seriously if your gonna post useless comments and being a dick about it, just go /cut wrist and don’t post on this thread.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/marijuana-legalization/272186/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/marijuana-legalization/272186/4</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 Apr 2009 02:04:51 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-272186-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/marijuana-legalization/272186.rss">Marijuana Legalization!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Marijuana Legalization!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@bowserjr2 Bowser jr]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/bowserjr2">@bowserjr2</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Why not just ban Cigarettes, alcohol and Marijuana.<br>
Its all cost the community much money, but I’am against punish people with prison by using Marijuana, only they who make lots of money of it should get in prison.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/marijuana-legalization/272186/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/marijuana-legalization/272186/3</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 Apr 2009 02:02:23 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-272186-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/marijuana-legalization/272186.rss">Marijuana Legalization!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Marijuana Legalization!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@ilyaostr9 io9]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/ilyaostr9">@ilyaostr9</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>gg nobody gives a shit.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/marijuana-legalization/272186/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/marijuana-legalization/272186/2</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 Apr 2009 02:00:53 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-272186-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/marijuana-legalization/272186.rss">Marijuana Legalization!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Marijuana Legalization!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@zammyking111 zammyking111]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/zammyking111">@zammyking111</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Well i’ve been doin some research today and I told myself lets compare, weed, alcohol, cigarettes… You will be amazed at what I found out!!!  <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/smiley.png?v=6" title=":smiley:" class="emoji" alt=":smiley:">  <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/wink.png?v=6" title=":wink:" class="emoji" alt=":wink:">  :eek: LEGALIZE IT!!!  ;D</p>
<p>Death Ratio Of The U.S.:</p>
<ol>
<li>Heart disease: 652,091</li>
<li>Cancer: 559,312</li>
<li>Stroke (cerebrovascular diseases): 143,579</li>
<li>Chronic lower respiratory diseases: 130,933</li>
<li>Accidents (unintentional injuries): 117,809</li>
<li>Diabetes: 75,119</li>
<li>Alzheimer’s disease: 71,599</li>
<li>Influenza/Pneumonia: 63,001</li>
<li>Nephritis, nephrotic syndrome, and nephrosis: 43,901</li>
<li>Septicemia: 34,136</li>
</ol>
<p>Chemicals in Marijuana:<br>
THC (delta-9-tetrahydrocannabinol)<br>
400 other known Chemicals (But other plants contain 400 chemicals as well)</p>
<p>Cigarettes: (These Chemicals Can Kill You) Over 4,000 Chemicals, 43 Cause Cancer<br>
Benzene: Petrol Additive  (carcinogen and is associated with leukaemia, used as a solvent in fuel)<br>
Formaldehyd: Embalming Fluid (causes cancer, highly poisonous, used to preserve dead bodies)<br>
Ammonia: Cleaner (Ammonia is used for cleaning utensils such as… Floor Cleaner, Toilet Cleaner etc.)<br>
Acetone: Nail Polish Remover (This chemical is used in Nail Polish Remover)<br>
Tar: (Can get drawn into the lungs and fill your lungs up thus causing cancer, and respritory issues)<br>
Nicotine: Insecticide (One of the most addictive substances)<br>
Carbon Monoxide: Car Exhaust Fumes (Odorless, tasteless, poisionous gas, can cause Carbon Monoxide Poisioning when taken in large quanities)<br>
Arsenic: Rat Poison (Used daily to kill your household rodents)<br>
Hydrogen Cyanide: Gas Chamber<br>
DDT: Banned Insecticide<br>
Lead: (Lead can be fatal when taken in large quanities, thus causing lead poisioning)<br>
Napthalene: MothBalls (Ingredient in mothballs, mothballs are used to keep snakes, beetles and other insects off your lawn)<br>
Cadmium: Batteries (Cadmium is used in most batteries, like the Nickle Cadmium battery in your computer!)<br>
Butane: Lighter Fluid (Gas thats used in lighter fluid)</p>
<p>Alcohol:<br>
Drinking Alcohol leads to loss of coordination, judgement, slower reflexes, distorted vision, memory lapse, blackouts<br>
Alcohol can damage every organ in your body<br>
Can cause cancer<br>
Drinking large quanities of alcohol can lead to comas, or death<br>
Even if your not drinking if your around people drinking you have a higher chance of getting hurt<br>
You can’t drive after one drink<br>
Mixing alcohol with medications can cause death<br>
Bad Breath<br>
Addictive<br>
Depresses your central nervous system</p>
<p>Makes you do things you normally wouldn’t do, such as driving while under the influence of alcohol<br>
ALCOHOL IS A DRUG<br>
Extensive alcohol intake is likely to produce withdrawal symptoms, including severe anxiety, tremors, hallucinations, and convulsions<br>
More than 100,000 U.S. deaths are caused by excessive alcohol consumption each year. Direct and indirect causes of death include drunk driving, cirrhosis of the liver, falls, cancer, and stroke.<br>
Youth who drink alcohol are 50 times more likely to use cocaine than those who never drink alcohol.<br>
Traffic crashes are the greatest single cause of death for persons aged 6–33. About 45% of these fatalities are in alcohol-related crashes.<br>
Underage drinking costs the United States more than $58 billion every year — enough to buy every public school student a state-of-the-art computer.<br>
Alcohol kills 6½ times more youth than all other illicit drugs combined.</p>
<p>Short Term / Long Term Effects Marijuana:<br>
Bad Short Term Memory<br>
Lowered Learning Abilities<br>
Difficulty Thinking &amp; Problem Solving<br>
Inability To Drive: (Lower than drinking alcohol)<br>
Distorted Senses, Sight, Hearing, Touch, Time, and Depth<br>
Reduced Athletic Ability<br>
Elevated Heart Rate<br>
Anxiety, Panic Attacks<br>
Cancer: (Smoke it moderately lessens the risk of getting cancer, moderately means a joint every few days!)<br>
Dry Mouth: Kotton Mouth (Easy fix just drink liquids)</p>
<p>Long Term Effects Of Cigarettes:<br>
Cancer: Cancer is an alternation in cells causing your cells to grow and spread rapidly.<br>
Heart &amp; Blood Vessel Disease: Carbon Monoxide gets into the blood and decreases oxygen going to the heart. The more you smoke the greater risk you have of having a heart attack.<br>
Lung Disease: Bronchitis, Emphysema, higher risk of getting colds, pneumonia, and other lung infections<br>
Gastrointestinal disease: Increases the acid in your stomache, can cause peptic ulcer<br>
Gastroesophageal reflux: Stomache acid comes up into your esophagus.<br>
Higher risk of bone fractures<br>
Men have problems getting erections<br>
Insomnia<br>
Reduced Athletic Ability</p>
<p>Good Effects Of Marijuana:<br>
Munchies: (Makes you eat a lot)<br>
Sexual Stimulant: (Makes you wanna have sex)<br>
Increase Mental Abilities: (May be different for others but some it will increase your thinking)<br>
Safer to smoke marijuana than drinking alcohol<br>
Reduce problems with glaucoma: (glaucoma causes you to lose your vision)<br>
Relaxes<br>
Improves Creativity / Imagination<br>
Reduces Anger Issues<br>
Reduces nausea from chemotherapy<br>
Helps you eat and hold food down<br>
Fantastic Antidepressant: (Less side effects than many prescription antidepressants)<br>
Reduces stress</p>
<p>Facts and Info of Marijuana:<br>
Marijuana may help ease symptoms of AIDS, Cancer, Multiple Sclerosis, Depression.<br>
People really can’t overdoes on marijuana (Small animals yes because they are smaller, but people NO)</p>
<p>Facts About Cigarettes:<br>
Nicotine is more of a gateway drug, because kids get hold of cigarettes then they get addicted to them and there is the introduction of smoking.<br>
Cigarettes cost the nation over $100 Billion per year in health costs!<br>
Tobacco companies spend over $4 billion a year promoting their deadly product<br>
1.3 Million people quit smoking each year, but about 48 Million continue to smoke<br>
Tobacco is often the first drug used by young people, who then go on and use alcohol, marijuana, and other drugs!!</p>
<p>How The Economy Can Benefit Off Of Marijuana Being Legal:<br>
The United States will flourish if marijuana is legal, even though there are many different strands of marijuana<br>
there can be a flat tax for all of them just like how there is with onions, apples, carrots, lettuce etc… Just look at<br>
any food produce that can be grown, thats the same for marijuana, we can sell marijuana in stores, such as gas stations,<br>
medical facilities, drug stores, almost any local store. Marijuana is just like any produce you can grow it you can sell it<br>
there shouldn’t be a law against growing it or using it, it can benefit the whole country by it being legal, more than half<br>
of the United States does marijuana illegally. If marijuana was legal we wouldn’t have to spend money on housing inmates in jail<br>
the average inmate costs $94.87, when you could just keep them out of jail. Just think how much money the whole country would save<br>
if marijuana was legal, lets say 1500000 people go to jail for marijuana a year, for them to stay just one day thats $142,305,000!<br>
Now if we didn’t put them in jail for marijuana thats $142,305,000 more to spend on education, roads, medical etc. The government is<br>
wasting money on putting people in jail for having marijuana, people who do marijuana just wanna do marijuana they<br>
don’t wanna bother anyone else. If marijuana was legal there would be less crimes over drugs, because people could just go to the store<br>
and buy it instead of having to hide from the law to deal their drugs to get money under the table. When the government can just sell it<br>
by gram, ounces, pounds etc. Anyways marijuana is less lethal than any other drugs out there like cigarettes, alcohol if you compare all the<br>
data I collected you will find that marijuana is less dangerous than all of the others. If the U.S. is afraid of losing money they could just tax<br>
it like how I said, and more money will come in, because if you think about it marijuana is just like apples, apples you can grow legally then you can<br>
eat them without paying tax to the government, so marijuana you can grow and use it without getting taxed by the government so if marijuana isn’t legal because<br>
of that reason then what makes apples legal?</p>
<p>Websites:<br>
<aside class="onebox whitelistedgeneric">
  <header class="source">
      <img src="https://www.drugs.com/img/favicon/ddc-icon-32x32.png" class="site-icon" width="32" height="32">
      <a href="https://www.drugs.com/cg/cigarette-smoking-and-your-health.html" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Drugs.com</a>
  </header>
  <article class="onebox-body">
    <img src="https://www.drugs.com/img/social/ddc-facebook-icon.png" class="thumbnail onebox-avatar" width="200" height="200">

<h3><a href="https://www.drugs.com/cg/cigarette-smoking-and-your-health.html" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Cigarette Smoking and your Health - What You Need to Know</a></h3>

<p>Care guide for Cigarette Smoking and your Health. Includes: possible causes, signs and symptoms, standard treatment options and means of care and support.</p>


  </article>
  <div class="onebox-metadata">
    
    
  </div>
  <div style="clear: both"></div>
</aside>
<br>
<a href="http://www.well.com/user/woa/fspot.htm" class="onebox" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">http://www.well.com/user/woa/fspot.htm</a><br>
<a href="http://serendip.brynmawr.edu/exchange/node/1808" class="onebox" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">http://serendip.brynmawr.edu/exchange/node/1808</a><br>
<a href="http://www.quitsmokingsupport.com/whatsinit.htm" class="onebox" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">http://www.quitsmokingsupport.com/whatsinit.htm</a><br>
<a href="http://www.quit-smoking-stop.com/harmful-chemicals-in-cigarettes.html" class="onebox" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">http://www.quit-smoking-stop.com/harmful-chemicals-in-cigarettes.html</a><br>
<a href="http://www.cdc.gov/nchs/FASTATS/lcod.htm" class="onebox" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">http://www.cdc.gov/nchs/FASTATS/lcod.htm</a><br>
<a href="http://www.allpotseeds.com/bad-effects-of-pot.html" class="onebox" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">http://www.allpotseeds.com/bad-effects-of-pot.html</a><br>
<a href="http://www.alaw.org/tobacco_control/quit_smoking_today/quit_kit/facts_about_cigarette_smoking.html" class="onebox" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">http://www.alaw.org/tobacco_control/quit_smoking_today/quit_kit/facts_about_cigarette_smoking.html</a><br>
<a href="http://www.freevibe.com/Drug_Facts/alcohol.asp" class="onebox" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">http://www.freevibe.com/Drug_Facts/alcohol.asp</a><br>
<a href="http://ncadi.samhsa.gov/govpubs/ph323/" class="onebox" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">http://ncadi.samhsa.gov/govpubs/ph323/</a><br>
<a href="http://www.gdcada.org/statistics/alcohol.htm" class="onebox" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">http://www.gdcada.org/statistics/alcohol.htm</a><br>
<a href="http://www.dc.state.fl.us/pub/statsbrief/cost.html" class="onebox" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">http://www.dc.state.fl.us/pub/statsbrief/cost.html</a></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/marijuana-legalization/272186/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/marijuana-legalization/272186/1</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 Apr 2009 01:55:10 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-272186-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/marijuana-legalization/272186.rss">Marijuana Legalization!</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
