<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Cispa</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/cispa/438837</link>
    <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;An onrush of condemnation and criticism kept the SOPA and PIPA acts from passing earlier this year, but US lawmakers have already authored another authoritarian bill that could give them free reign to creep the Web in the name of cybersecurity.

As congressmen in Washington consider how to handle the ongoing issue of cyberattacks, some legislators have lent their support to a new act that, if passed, would let the government pry into the personal correspondence of anyone of their choosing.

H.R. 3523, a piece of legislation dubbed the Cyber Intelligence Sharing and Protection Act (or CISPA for short), has been created under the guise of being a necessary implement in America’s war against cyberattacks. But the vague verbiage contained within the pages of the paper could allow Congress to circumvent existing exemptions to online privacy laws and essentially monitor, censor and stop any online communication that it considers disruptive to the government or private parties. Critics have already come after CISPA for the capabilities that it will give to seemingly any federal entity that claims it is threatened by online interactions, but unlike the Stop Online Privacy Act and the Protect IP Acts that were discarded on the Capitol Building floor after incredibly successful online campaigns to crush them, widespread recognition of what the latest would-be law will do has yet to surface to the same degree.
Kendall Burman of the Center for Democracy and Technology tells RT that Congress is currently considering a number of cybersecurity bills that could eventually be voted into law, but for the group that largely advocates an open Internet, she warns that provisions within CISPA are reason to worry over what the realities could be if it ends up on the desk of President Barack Obama. So far CISPA has been introduced, referred and reported by the House Permanent Select Committee on Intelligence and expects to go before a vote in the first half of Congress within the coming weeks.

“We have a number of concerns with something like this bill that creates sort of a vast hole in the privacy law to allow government to receive these kinds of information,” explains Burman, who acknowledges that the bill, as written, allows the US government to involve itself into any online correspondence, current exemptions notwithstanding, if it believes there is reason to suspect cyber crime. As with other authoritarian attempts at censorship that have come through Congress in recent times, of course, the wording within the CISPA allows for the government to interpret the law in such a number of degrees that any online communication or interaction could be suspect and thus unknowingly monitored.

In a press release penned last month by the CDT, the group warned then that CISPA allows Internet Service Providers to “funnel private communications and related information back to the government without adequate privacy protections and controls.

The bill does not specify which agencies ISPs could disclose customer data to, but the structure and incentives in the bill raise a very real possibility that the National Security Agency or the DOD’s Cybercommand would be the primary recipient,” reads the warning.

The Electronic Frontier Foundation, another online advocacy group, has also sharply condemned CISPA for what it means for the future of the Internet. “It effectively creates a ‘cybersecurity&#39;’ exemption to all existing laws,” explains the EFF, who add in a statement of their own that “There are almost no restrictions on what can be collected and how it can be used, provided a company can claim it was motivated by ‘cybersecurity purposes.’”

What does that mean? Both the EFF and CDT say an awfully lot. Some of the biggest corporations in the country, including service providers such as Google, Facebook, Twitter or AT&amp;T, could copy confidential information and send them off to the Pentagon if pressured, as long as the government believes they have reason to suspect wrongdoing. In a summation of their own, the Congressional Research Service, a nonpartisan arm of the Library of Congress, explains that “efforts to degrade, disrupt or destroy” either “a system or network of a government or private entity” is reason enough for Washington to reach in and read any online communiqué of their choice.
The authors of CISPA say the bill has been made “To provide for the sharing of certain cyber threat intelligence and cyber threat information between the intelligence community and cybersecurity entities,” but not before noting that the legislation could be used “and for other purposes,” as well — which, of course, are not defined.

“Cyber security, when done right and done narrowly, could benefit everyone,” Burman tells RT. “But it needs to be done in an incremental way with an arrow approach, and the heavy hand that lawmakers are taking with these current bills . . . it brings real serious concerns.”

So far CISPA has garnered support from over 100 representatives in the House who are favoring this cybersecurity legislation without taking into considerations what it could do to the everyday user of the Internet. And while the backlash created by opponents of SOPA and PIPA has not materialized to the same degree yet, Burman warns Congress that it could be only a matter of time before concerned Americans step up to have their say.

“One of the lessons we learned in the reaction to SOPA and PIPA is that when Congress tries to legislate on things that are going to affect Internet users’ experience, the Internet users are going to pay attention,” says Burman. H.R. 3523, she cautions, “Definitely could affect in a very serious way the internet experience.” Luckily, adds Burman, “People are starting to notice.” Given the speed that the latest censorship bill could sneak through Congress, however, anyone concerned over the future of the Internet should be on the lookout for CISPA as it continues to be considered on Capitol Hill.&lt;/blockquote&gt;
src: http://rt.com/usa/news/cispa-bill-sopa-internet-175/</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 10 Apr 2012 17:56:44 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>General Discussion</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/cispa/438837.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Cispa</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@T41 t4]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/t41">@T41</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“eczema3, post:24, topic:438837”][quote author=t4 link=topic=541545.msg3970174#msg3970174 date=1334078737]</p>
<aside class="quote">
<blockquote>
<aside class="quote">
<blockquote>
<p>if you own them, then why wouldn’t you digitize them yourself?</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I can answer that from my own perspective.  I own all 9 seasons of Star Trek: The Next Generation, and 3 seasons of Sliders.  It would take me hours upon hours swapping out DVDs and manually doing other things to rip them all to a digital format, when I can just go own a torrent site, find a good rip, and click ‘download’.  It’s also much easier to play them with XBMC than swapping out disks manually and going through the awful menus.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>eh, i’d rather rip it myself honestly. you’ll only find, for the most part, proper quality rips on private sites. at that point you’d have to maintain a decent ration/be active/etc.<br>
[/quote]<br>
Do you use thepiratebay much? It’s very much a public torrent site, and there’s a loot of good quality shit there.[/quote]<br>
i don’t find public trackers to be reliable when it comes to flac rips, or even mp3 for that matter. some idiot could transcode youtube videos into 256kbps mp3 and upload it tagged as being a proper 256kbps rip.</p>
<p>the same goes for videos, sort of. i’d much rather watch a video from source encoded using the H264 codec.</p>
<p>edit: i mean sure, if you want to have something and could care less about archiving/perfection in the quality department, i guess it works out pretty well</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/cispa/438837/26">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/cispa/438837/26</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 10 Apr 2012 17:56:44 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-438837-26</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/cispa/438837.rss">Cispa</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Cispa</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@moparisthebest Moparisthebest]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/moparisthebest">@moparisthebest</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“eczema3, post:24, topic:438837”][quote author=t4 link=topic=541545.msg3970174#msg3970174 date=1334078737]</p>
<aside class="quote">
<blockquote>
<aside class="quote">
<blockquote>
<p>if you own them, then why wouldn’t you digitize them yourself?</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I can answer that from my own perspective.  I own all 9 seasons of Star Trek: The Next Generation, and 3 seasons of Sliders.  It would take me hours upon hours swapping out DVDs and manually doing other things to rip them all to a digital format, when I can just go own a torrent site, find a good rip, and click ‘download’.  It’s also much easier to play them with XBMC than swapping out disks manually and going through the awful menus.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>eh, i’d rather rip it myself honestly. you’ll only find, for the most part, proper quality rips on private sites. at that point you’d have to maintain a decent ration/be active/etc.<br>
[/quote]<br>
Do you use thepiratebay much? It’s very much a public torrent site, and there’s a loot of good quality shit there.[/quote]<br>
That’s where I end up getting most of everything I need from.  For the most part, I think ‘private torrent sites’ are a joke, with very few exceptions.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/cispa/438837/25">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/cispa/438837/25</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 10 Apr 2012 17:53:11 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-438837-25</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/cispa/438837.rss">Cispa</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Cispa</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@eczema3 eczema3]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/eczema3">@eczema3</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“t4, post:23, topic:438837”][quote author=Moparisthebest link=topic=541545.msg3970170#msg3970170 date=1334078232]</p>
<aside class="quote">
<blockquote>
<p>if you own them, then why wouldn’t you digitize them yourself?</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I can answer that from my own perspective.  I own all 9 seasons of Star Trek: The Next Generation, and 3 seasons of Sliders.  It would take me hours upon hours swapping out DVDs and manually doing other things to rip them all to a digital format, when I can just go own a torrent site, find a good rip, and click ‘download’.  It’s also much easier to play them with XBMC than swapping out disks manually and going through the awful menus.<br>
[/quote]<br>
eh, i’d rather rip it myself honestly. you’ll only find, for the most part, proper quality rips on private sites. at that point you’d have to maintain a decent ration/be active/etc.[/quote]<br>
Do you use thepiratebay much? It’s very much a public torrent site, and there’s a loot of good quality shit there.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/cispa/438837/24">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/cispa/438837/24</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 10 Apr 2012 17:48:06 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-438837-24</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/cispa/438837.rss">Cispa</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Cispa</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@T41 t4]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/t41">@T41</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“Moparisthebest, post:22, topic:438837”][quote author=t4 link=topic=541545.msg3970023#msg3970023 date=1334064895]<br>
if you own them, then why wouldn’t you digitize them yourself?<br>
[/quote]</p>
<p>I can answer that from my own perspective.  I own all 9 seasons of Star Trek: The Next Generation, and 3 seasons of Sliders.  It would take me hours upon hours swapping out DVDs and manually doing other things to rip them all to a digital format, when I can just go own a torrent site, find a good rip, and click ‘download’.  It’s also much easier to play them with XBMC than swapping out disks manually and going through the awful menus.[/quote]<br>
eh, i’d rather rip it myself honestly. you’ll only find, for the most part, proper quality rips on private sites. at that point you’d have to maintain a decent ration/be active/etc.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/cispa/438837/23">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/cispa/438837/23</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 10 Apr 2012 17:25:37 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-438837-23</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/cispa/438837.rss">Cispa</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Cispa</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@moparisthebest Moparisthebest]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/moparisthebest">@moparisthebest</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote quote-modified" data-post="20" data-topic="438837">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 t4:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>if you own them, then why wouldn’t you digitize them yourself?</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I can answer that from my own perspective.  I own all 9 seasons of Star Trek: The Next Generation, and 3 seasons of Sliders.  It would take me hours upon hours swapping out DVDs and manually doing other things to rip them all to a digital format, when I can just go own a torrent site, find a good rip, and click ‘download’.  It’s also much easier to play them with XBMC than swapping out disks manually and going through the awful menus.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/cispa/438837/22">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/cispa/438837/22</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 10 Apr 2012 17:17:12 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-438837-22</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/cispa/438837.rss">Cispa</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Cispa</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@vortex vortex]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/vortex">@vortex</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>What Speljohan is saying is, you should download only legal shit. I for one download all my shit (even the TS/TC/CAM movies that just got into theaters) from this place: <a href="http://store.mtv3.fi/mtv3/" rel="nofollow noopener">http://store.mtv3.fi/mtv3/</a></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/cispa/438837/21">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/cispa/438837/21</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 10 Apr 2012 13:57:10 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-438837-21</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/cispa/438837.rss">Cispa</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Cispa</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@T41 t4]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/t41">@T41</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>if you own them, then why wouldn’t you digitize them yourself?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/cispa/438837/20">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/cispa/438837/20</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 10 Apr 2012 13:34:55 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-438837-20</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/cispa/438837.rss">Cispa</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Cispa</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Speljohan Speljohan]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/speljohan">@Speljohan</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“mwiebelhaus, post:18, topic:438837”][quote author=Speljohan link=topic=541545.msg3968797#msg3968797 date=1333980323]</p>
<aside class="quote">
<blockquote>
<p>What is honestly the future of things like usenet, if a bill like this gets passed? Should I be investing in a couple terabytes of hard-space and be stocking up on all the movies and TV shows I haven’t watched yet so in the future I have something to watch when I don’t want to pay $60 dollars for a blu-ray movie and I can no longer easily get new movies on the internet?<br>
[/quote]You shouldn’t watch movies/tv-series then, douchebag.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Ah man I am such a bad guy how unethical of me to download a copy of something that I didn’t pay for even though you obviously use usenet for the exact same shit and have no respect for copyright laws either. I had a nice response to your fucking idiotic comment that didn’t answer my question at all, but I realized that would result in me listening to some more fucking stupid comments attacking my viewpoints and that Americans are greedy blah blah blah</p>
<p>[quote author=Speljohan link=topic=516332.msg3747990#msg3747990 date=1315804812]<br>
You are correct, usenet is da bomb.<br>
[/quote][/quote]And what makes you think i am using usenet to download things i do not legally own?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/cispa/438837/19">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/cispa/438837/19</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 10 Apr 2012 06:26:53 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-438837-19</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/cispa/438837.rss">Cispa</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Cispa</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@mwiebelhaus mwiebelhaus]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/mwiebelhaus">@mwiebelhaus</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“Speljohan, post:15, topic:438837”][quote author=mwiebelhaus link=topic=541545.msg3968444#msg3968444 date=1333940671]<br>
What is honestly the future of things like usenet, if a bill like this gets passed? Should I be investing in a couple terabytes of hard-space and be stocking up on all the movies and TV shows I haven’t watched yet so in the future I have something to watch when I don’t want to pay $60 dollars for a blu-ray movie and I can no longer easily get new movies on the internet?<br>
[/quote]You shouldn’t watch movies/tv-series then, douchebag.[/quote]</p>
<p>Ah man I am such a bad guy how unethical of me to download a copy of something that I didn’t pay for even though you obviously use usenet for the exact same shit and have no respect for copyright laws either. I had a nice response to your fucking idiotic comment that didn’t answer my question at all, but I realized that would result in me listening to some more fucking stupid comments attacking my viewpoints and that Americans are greedy blah blah blah</p>
<aside class="quote" data-post="9" data-topic="414371">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/speljohan/40/5_e05bb34c421432ee4d40de30c10af3e5.png" class="avatar"><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/usenet-ftw/414371/9">USENET ftw</a>
</div>
<blockquote>
<p>You are correct, usenet is da bomb.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/cispa/438837/18">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/cispa/438837/18</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 10 Apr 2012 02:49:37 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-438837-18</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/cispa/438837.rss">Cispa</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Cispa</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Pwnd Pwnd]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/pwnd">@Pwnd</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>WHAT WILL I EVER DO WITHOUT MY MOVIES AND TV SHOWS???</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/cispa/438837/17">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/cispa/438837/17</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 09 Apr 2012 16:05:50 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-438837-17</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/cispa/438837.rss">Cispa</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Cispa</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@bowserjr2 Bowser jr]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/bowserjr2">@bowserjr2</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“Speljohan, post:15, topic:438837”][quote author=mwiebelhaus link=topic=541545.msg3968444#msg3968444 date=1333940671]<br>
What is honestly the future of things like usenet, if a bill like this gets passed? Should I be investing in a couple terabytes of hard-space and be stocking up on all the movies and TV shows I haven’t watched yet so in the future I have something to watch when I don’t want to pay $60 dollars for a blu-ray movie and I can no longer easily get new movies on the internet?<br>
[/quote]You shouldn’t watch movies/tv-series then, douchebag.[/quote]<br>
Taking his ideology into account, I will agree with you.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/cispa/438837/16">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/cispa/438837/16</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 09 Apr 2012 14:41:32 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-438837-16</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/cispa/438837.rss">Cispa</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Cispa</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Speljohan Speljohan]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/speljohan">@Speljohan</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“mwiebelhaus, post:12, topic:438837”]What is honestly the future of things like usenet, if a bill like this gets passed? Should I be investing in a couple terabytes of hard-space and be stocking up on all the movies and TV shows I haven’t watched yet so in the future I have something to watch when I don’t want to pay $60 dollars for a blu-ray movie and I can no longer easily get new movies on the internet?[/quote]You shouldn’t watch movies/tv-series then, douchebag.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/cispa/438837/15">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/cispa/438837/15</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 09 Apr 2012 14:05:23 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-438837-15</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/cispa/438837.rss">Cispa</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Cispa</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@T41 t4]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/t41">@T41</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote quote-modified" data-post="12" data-topic="438837">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/mwiebelhaus/40/5_e05bb34c421432ee4d40de30c10af3e5.png" class="avatar"> mwiebelhaus:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>What is honestly the future of things like usenet, if a bill like this gets passed? Should I be investing in a couple terabytes of hard-space and be stocking up on all the movies and TV shows I haven’t watched yet so in the future I have something to watch when I don’t want to pay $60 dollars for a blu-ray movie and I can no longer easily get new movies on the internet?</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>invest in a non-US/UK VPN or VPS/dedicated - try NL</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/cispa/438837/14">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/cispa/438837/14</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 09 Apr 2012 13:41:37 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-438837-14</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/cispa/438837.rss">Cispa</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Cispa</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@sinisoul sini]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/sinisoul">@sinisoul</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Internet privacy is a lie.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/cispa/438837/13">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/cispa/438837/13</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 09 Apr 2012 03:50:19 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-438837-13</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/cispa/438837.rss">Cispa</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Cispa</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@mwiebelhaus mwiebelhaus]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/mwiebelhaus">@mwiebelhaus</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>What is honestly the future of things like usenet, if a bill like this gets passed? Should I be investing in a couple terabytes of hard-space and be stocking up on all the movies and TV shows I haven’t watched yet so in the future I have something to watch when I don’t want to pay $60 dollars for a blu-ray movie and I can no longer easily get new movies on the internet?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/cispa/438837/12">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/cispa/438837/12</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 09 Apr 2012 03:04:31 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-438837-12</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/cispa/438837.rss">Cispa</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Cispa</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@T41 t4]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/t41">@T41</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“Bowser jr, post:10, topic:438837”][quote author=Miss Silabsoft link=topic=541545.msg3967470#msg3967470 date=1333850517]<br>
I would try to care but my internet censorship is worse.<br>
[/quote]<br>
We know, luckily the censorship in China doesn’t affect the whole word. Look at it from the bright side, they didn’t catch you complaining about censorship.[/quote]<br>
or did they!?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/cispa/438837/11">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/cispa/438837/11</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 08 Apr 2012 02:36:44 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-438837-11</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/cispa/438837.rss">Cispa</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Cispa</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@bowserjr2 Bowser jr]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/bowserjr2">@bowserjr2</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote" data-post="9" data-topic="438837">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 Miss Silabsoft:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>I would try to care but my internet censorship is worse.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>We know, luckily the censorship in China doesn’t affect the whole word. Look at it from the bright side, they didn’t catch you complaining about censorship.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/cispa/438837/10">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/cispa/438837/10</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 08 Apr 2012 02:07:54 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-438837-10</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/cispa/438837.rss">Cispa</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Cispa</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@silabsoft RuneAgent]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/silabsoft">@silabsoft</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I would try to care but my internet censorship is worse.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/cispa/438837/9">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/cispa/438837/9</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 08 Apr 2012 02:01:57 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-438837-9</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/cispa/438837.rss">Cispa</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Cispa</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@bowserjr2 Bowser jr]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/bowserjr2">@bowserjr2</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote" data-post="7" data-topic="438837">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/frell/40/5_e05bb34c421432ee4d40de30c10af3e5.png" class="avatar"> Frell:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>BEND OVER AND CISPA MY ASS</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>That make no sense, should I bend over while cisping your ass? But that doesn’t make any less sense than this bill. I feel bad for you Americans, the only non-fascist candidate is an old crazy libertarian.</p>
<p>PS: Do you have a nice ass?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/cispa/438837/8">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/cispa/438837/8</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 08 Apr 2012 01:38:36 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-438837-8</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/cispa/438837.rss">Cispa</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Cispa</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Frell Frell]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/frell">@Frell</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>BEND OVER AND CISPA MY ASS</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/cispa/438837/7">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/cispa/438837/7</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 08 Apr 2012 01:16:18 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-438837-7</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/cispa/438837.rss">Cispa</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Cispa</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Speljohan Speljohan]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/speljohan">@Speljohan</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“Bowser jr, post:5, topic:438837”][quote author=sppt link=topic=541545.msg3967413#msg3967413 date=1333846775]</p>
<aside class="quote">
<blockquote>
<p>Sounds great, finally nail those damn pirates down.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Yeah, they really are sucking the life out of all businesses, it’s good to finally see something being done about this <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=5" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"><br>
[/quote]<br>
Do you know any copyrighted materials that is own by the US federal government?<br>
I want to suck out their life by downloading a couple of thousand copies.[/quote]No man, it’s illegal, don’t do that! Respect the laws man</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/cispa/438837/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/cispa/438837/6</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 08 Apr 2012 01:09:20 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-438837-6</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/cispa/438837.rss">Cispa</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Cispa</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@bowserjr2 Bowser jr]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/bowserjr2">@bowserjr2</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“sppt, post:3, topic:438837”][quote author=Speljohan link=topic=541545.msg3967409#msg3967409 date=1333846706]<br>
Sounds great, finally nail those damn pirates down.<br>
[/quote]<br>
Yeah, they really are sucking the life out of all businesses, it’s good to finally see something being done about this :)[/quote]<br>
Good idea, I will get a pirate-ship and suck out the life of John Fredriksen’s businesses, that filthy tax-evader.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/cispa/438837/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/cispa/438837/5</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 08 Apr 2012 01:08:25 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-438837-5</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/cispa/438837.rss">Cispa</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Cispa</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@The_Un-Named The Un-Named]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/the_un-named">@The_Un-Named</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>What a great bill. It’s great that they’re cracking down on internet paedophiles, finally someone is thinking of the children.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/cispa/438837/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/cispa/438837/4</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 08 Apr 2012 01:02:11 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-438837-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/cispa/438837.rss">Cispa</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Cispa</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@sppt sppt]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/sppt">@sppt</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote" data-post="2" data-topic="438837">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/speljohan/40/5_e05bb34c421432ee4d40de30c10af3e5.png" class="avatar"> Speljohan:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Sounds great, finally nail those damn pirates down.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Yeah, they really are sucking the life out of all businesses, it’s good to finally see something being done about this <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=5" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/cispa/438837/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/cispa/438837/3</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 08 Apr 2012 00:59:35 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-438837-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/cispa/438837.rss">Cispa</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Cispa</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Speljohan Speljohan]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/speljohan">@Speljohan</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Sounds great, finally nail those damn pirates down.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/cispa/438837/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/cispa/438837/2</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 08 Apr 2012 00:58:26 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-438837-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/cispa/438837.rss">Cispa</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
