<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>The Rules [10/31/2012]</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-rules-10-31-2012/268469</link>
    <description>[b]Foreword:[/b]

The staff reserve the right to interpret these rules any way they see fit. The following rules are more like guidelines. You shouldn&#39;t be looking for loopholes in them, rather, you should just get along with them. We&#39;re looking for users that use common sense. For example, we would prefer a user that knows just because something isn&#39;t on the rules, that it isn&#39;t necessarily allowed.
 
[size=10pt][b][u]Ideals:[/u][/b][/size]

[ul][li]We are not anti-leech. If you respect our community and our ideas, feel free to ask questions and they will be kindly answered if you follow the rules. Answer to questions that others ask if you know the answer or offer useful content, [b]otherwise remain silent[/b].[/li]
[li]We don&#39;t talk about things we don&#39;t know. This is an informative community.[/li]
[li] We do not care about post count alone. If someone has high post count but most of it is spam, we hate them. If someone has a high post count with informative posts, we love them. The higher count, the more we hate/love them.[/li]
[li]We do [b]not[/b] make spelling mistakes on purpose. We use &quot;you&quot; not &quot;u&quot;, we use &quot;why&quot; not &quot;y&quot; etc.[/li][/ul]


[size=10pt][b][u]Rules:[/u][/b][/size]
[b]Rule 1:[/b]
Moderators lock topics/remove posts and topics/hand infractions to users at their own discretion as required to foster a positive community. Any disagreement with a staff member&#39;s decision is to be resolved through the use of the PM system. Any public disputes are [b]unacceptable[/b] and punishable. A moderators decision is final, if you have a problem with it, pm an administrator. Trying to resolve it through a thread will result in a heavier punishment.

[b] Rule 2:[/b]
Everybody is equal, don&#39;t treat people worse than you do others(E.G., don&#39;t isolate someone and flame them).

[b]Rule 3:[/b]
Posts should be knowledgeable, try to put some effort into them, it&#39;ll save hassle and stop you from looking like an idiot.

[b]Rule 4:[/b]
We only have [b]one[/b] forum account per person, you can use the same account for [url=http://moparisthebest.com/smf]MoparScape[/url], [url=http://moparisthebest.com/smf]Moparisthebest[/url] and [url=http://gamedev.moparisthebest.com/smf]Mopar Game Dev[/url].

[b]Rule 5:[/b]
Advertising is to be kept strictly to the designated boards ([url=http://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php/board,221.0.html]RS2[/url] | [url=http://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php/board,119.0.html]RS Classic[/url]), or the [url=http://moparisthebest.com/serverstatus.php]Server Status Page[/url] (RS2 only).

[b]Rule 6:[/b]
We don&#39;t post misleading links, do not try to trick people into visiting things they don&#39;t want to.

[b]Rule 7:[/b]
bad picsographic content is not allowed under any circumstances. This includes images, links, or deep-rooted discussions regarding watching, sharing, creating, or otherwise being involved with bad picsographic media. bad picsography may be referenced and discussed up to the point where it does not violate the above statement.

Explicit content or otherwise questionable content may be allowed, but we expect users to use the &#39;NSFW&#39; rule when posting ([b]N[/b]ot [b]S[/b]afe [b]F[/b]or [b]W[/b]ork). Users are expected to use this tag in the title to inform other users the topic may contain explicit content. Please use your discretion when posting such content.

[b]Rule 8:[/b]
We do not sell anything on this site, period.  This includes offering &#39;rewards&#39; for donations or anything like that. [b]Selling via signature is not an exception.[/b] Furthermore, all requests of price or value for any property related to the game RuneScape is disallowed on these boards.  This rule exists to prevent scamming, dishonest trading, and legal liability regarding the exchange of Jagex property.  We do not encourage people to buy or sell anything related to RuneScape, Jagex, or any of their games.

[b]Rule 9:[/b]
Do not post or upload any copyrighted material.

[b]Rule 10:[/b]
We never advertise via the PM system whether the site is approved or not. If your site is approved than you must advertise through appropriate means.

[b]Rule 11:[/b]
We respect each other and other communities. We do [b]not[/b] flame. There is to be no fighting on the forums.

All of the rules stated in this post apply to [url=http://moparisthebest.com/smf]Moparscape[/url] and [url=http://moparisthebest.com/smf]Moparisthebest[/url], they apply to all topics and all messages, failure to comply to these rules with result in punishment handed out at the staff members&#39; digression.

[b]Section specific rules:[/b]

[b]    [u]RS2 Boards [/u][/b]

[ul][li] [url=https://moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php/topic,284809.0.html]RS2 Server Tutorials[/url] [/li]
[li] [url=https://moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php/topic,313422.0.html]RS2 Server Development[/url] [/li]
[li] [url=https://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php/topic,640022.0.html]RS2 Server Advertisement[/url] [/li]
[li] [url=https://moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php/topic,331370.0.html]RS2 Server Help[/url] [/li]
[li] [url=https://moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php/topic,319141.0.html]RS2 Client Hacking[/url] [/li][/ul]


[ul][li][url=https://moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php/topic,322496.0.html]RS2 Models[/url] [/li][/ul]


[b]    [u]RSC Boards [/u][/b]

[ul][li] [url=http://moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php/topic,234212.0.html]RSC Development[/url] [/li]
[li] [url=http://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php/topic,350113.0.html]RSC Advertisement[/url] [/li][/ul]</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 20 Mar 2009 12:21:28 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Community Suggestions</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-rules-10-31-2012/268469.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>The Rules [10/31/2012]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Bebemycat2 Bebe]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/bebemycat2">@Bebemycat2</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p><span class="bbcode-b">Foreword:</span></p>
<p>The staff reserve the right to interpret these rules any way they see fit. The following rules are more like guidelines. You shouldn’t be looking for loopholes in them, rather, you should just get along with them. We’re looking for users that use common sense. For example, we would prefer a user that knows just because something isn’t on the rules, that it isn’t necessarily allowed.</p>
<p>[size=10pt]<span class="bbcode-b"><span class="bbcode-u">Ideals:</span></span>[/size]</p>
<p>[ul][li]We are not anti-leech. If you respect our community and our ideas, feel free to ask questions and they will be kindly answered if you follow the rules. Answer to questions that others ask if you know the answer or offer useful content, <span class="bbcode-b">otherwise remain silent</span>.[/li]<br>
[li]We don’t talk about things we don’t know. This is an informative community.[/li]<br>
[li] We do not care about post count alone. If someone has high post count but most of it is spam, we hate them. If someone has a high post count with informative posts, we love them. The higher count, the more we hate/love them.[/li]<br>
[li]We do <span class="bbcode-b">not</span> make spelling mistakes on purpose. We use “you” not “u”, we use “why” not “y” etc.[/li][/ul]</p>
<p>[size=10pt]<span class="bbcode-b"><span class="bbcode-u">Rules:</span></span>[/size]<br>
<span class="bbcode-b">Rule 1:</span><br>
Moderators lock topics/remove posts and topics/hand infractions to users at their own discretion as required to foster a positive community. Any disagreement with a staff member’s decision is to be resolved through the use of the PM system. Any public disputes are <span class="bbcode-b">unacceptable</span> and punishable. A moderators decision is final, if you have a problem with it, pm an administrator. Trying to resolve it through a thread will result in a heavier punishment.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b"> Rule 2:</span><br>
Everybody is equal, don’t treat people worse than you do others(E.G., don’t isolate someone and flame them).</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Rule 3:</span><br>
Posts should be knowledgeable, try to put some effort into them, it’ll save hassle and stop you from looking like an idiot.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Rule 4:</span><br>
We only have <span class="bbcode-b">one</span> forum account per person, you can use the same account for <a href="http://moparisthebest.com/smf" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">MoparScape</a>, <a href="http://moparisthebest.com/smf" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">Moparisthebest</a> and <a href="http://gamedev.moparisthebest.com/smf" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">Mopar Game Dev</a>.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Rule 5:</span><br>
Advertising is to be kept strictly to the designated boards (<a href="http://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php/board,221.0.html" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">RS2</a> | <a href="http://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php/board,119.0.html" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">RS Classic</a>), or the <a href="http://moparisthebest.com/serverstatus.php" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">Server Status Page</a> (RS2 only).</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Rule 6:</span><br>
We don’t post misleading links, do not try to trick people into visiting things they don’t want to.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Rule 7:</span><br>
bad picsographic content is not allowed under any circumstances. This includes images, links, or deep-rooted discussions regarding watching, sharing, creating, or otherwise being involved with bad picsographic media. bad picsography may be referenced and discussed up to the point where it does not violate the above statement.</p>
<p>Explicit content or otherwise questionable content may be allowed, but we expect users to use the ‘NSFW’ rule when posting (<span class="bbcode-b">N</span>ot <span class="bbcode-b">S</span>afe <span class="bbcode-b">F</span>or <span class="bbcode-b">W</span>ork). Users are expected to use this tag in the title to inform other users the topic may contain explicit content. Please use your discretion when posting such content.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Rule 8:</span><br>
We do not sell anything on this site, period.  This includes offering ‘rewards’ for donations or anything like that. <span class="bbcode-b">Selling via signature is not an exception.</span> Furthermore, all requests of price or value for any property related to the game RuneScape is disallowed on these boards.  This rule exists to prevent scamming, dishonest trading, and legal liability regarding the exchange of Jagex property.  We do not encourage people to buy or sell anything related to RuneScape, Jagex, or any of their games.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Rule 9:</span><br>
Do not post or upload any copyrighted material.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Rule 10:</span><br>
We never advertise via the PM system whether the site is approved or not. If your site is approved than you must advertise through appropriate means.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Rule 11:</span><br>
We respect each other and other communities. We do <span class="bbcode-b">not</span> flame. There is to be no fighting on the forums.</p>
<p>All of the rules stated in this post apply to <a href="http://moparisthebest.com/smf" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">Moparscape</a> and <a href="http://moparisthebest.com/smf" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">Moparisthebest</a>, they apply to all topics and all messages, failure to comply to these rules with result in punishment handed out at the staff members’ digression.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Section specific rules:</span></p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">    <span class="bbcode-u">RS2 Boards </span></span></p>
<p>[ul][li] <a href="https://moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php/topic,284809.0.html" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">RS2 Server Tutorials</a> [/li]<br>
[li] <a href="https://moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php/topic,313422.0.html" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">RS2 Server Development</a> [/li]<br>
[li] <a href="https://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php/topic,640022.0.html" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">RS2 Server Advertisement</a> [/li]<br>
[li] <a href="https://moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php/topic,331370.0.html" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">RS2 Server Help</a> [/li]<br>
[li] <a href="https://moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php/topic,319141.0.html" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">RS2 Client Hacking</a> [/li][/ul]</p>
<p>[ul][li]<a href="https://moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php/topic,322496.0.html" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">RS2 Models</a> [/li][/ul]</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">    <span class="bbcode-u">RSC Boards </span></span></p>
<p>[ul][li] <a href="http://moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php/topic,234212.0.html" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">RSC Development</a> [/li]<br>
[li] <a href="http://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php/topic,350113.0.html" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">RSC Advertisement</a> [/li][/ul]</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-rules-10-31-2012/268469/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-rules-10-31-2012/268469/1</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 20 Mar 2009 12:21:28 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-268469-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-rules-10-31-2012/268469.rss">The Rules [10/31/2012]</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
