<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Can someone TeamView me? Source problems</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/can-someone-teamview-me-source-problems/453478</link>
    <description>Im having problems with my source, and the run.bat is saying that i am missing my javac file, which im sure i have. I have tried to edit the code, but none of my attempts have been successful. I apologize, as I&#39;m sure its something obvious but I am new to this, so please be patient as I would really like to learn the in&#39;s and out&#39;s of running a server, java, etc. If someone could use teamviewer and help me out i would really appreciate it, because like i said, I want to learn and I would like to see exactly how you all approach problems like this so I dont have to ask again, thanks.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 09 Aug 2012 01:52:19 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/can-someone-teamview-me-source-problems/453478.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Can someone TeamView me? Source problems</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@rynds1 rynds1]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/rynds1">@rynds1</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Im having problems with my source, and the run.bat is saying that i am missing my javac file, which im sure i have. I have tried to edit the code, but none of my attempts have been successful. I apologize, as I’m sure its something obvious but I am new to this, so please be patient as I would really like to learn the in’s and out’s of running a server, java, etc. If someone could use teamviewer and help me out i would really appreciate it, because like i said, I want to learn and I would like to see exactly how you all approach problems like this so I dont have to ask again, thanks.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/can-someone-teamview-me-source-problems/453478/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/can-someone-teamview-me-source-problems/453478/1</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 09 Aug 2012 01:52:19 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-453478-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/can-someone-teamview-me-source-problems/453478.rss">Can someone TeamView me? Source problems</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
