<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>I get disconnected from my server when I teleport</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/i-get-disconnected-from-my-server-when-i-teleport/252066</link>
    <description>I get disconnected when I try to teleport to barrows, Jad and stuff.. I tried using Silab and mopar client but still just disconnects me. I&#39;m using a server source by the way so I didn&#39;t make. Sorry I&#39;m new but does anyone know how to fix this?[br][br][size=1]Posted on: December 22, 2008, 06:48:31 pm[/size][hr]anyone help please? I seem to be freezing when I trade NPC&#39;s and sometimes equipping items..some things won&#39;t freeze If I go on mopar client and some won&#39;t freeze when I go on silab. Anyone know how to fix this please? some teleport locations will only work for mopar client</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2008 20:34:43 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/i-get-disconnected-from-my-server-when-i-teleport/252066.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>I get disconnected from my server when I teleport</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@steelrends steelrends]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/steelrends">@steelrends</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I get disconnected when I try to teleport to barrows, Jad and stuff… I tried using Silab and mopar client but still just disconnects me. I’m using a server source by the way so I didn’t make. Sorry I’m new but does anyone know how to fix this?[br][br][size=1]Posted on: December 22, 2008, 06:48:31 pm[/size][hr]anyone help please? I seem to be freezing when I trade NPC’s and sometimes equipping items…some things won’t freeze If I go on mopar client and some won’t freeze when I go on silab. Anyone know how to fix this please? some teleport locations will only work for mopar client</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/i-get-disconnected-from-my-server-when-i-teleport/252066/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/i-get-disconnected-from-my-server-when-i-teleport/252066/1</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2008 20:34:43 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-252066-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/i-get-disconnected-from-my-server-when-i-teleport/252066.rss">I get disconnected from my server when I teleport</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
