<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Account Creation</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/account-creation/545269</link>
    <description>Hello,

I started a project of my own recently and am curious about account creation.  I am using noobscape source which is derived from easy rsc and one great feature is automatic account creation upon login if that account does not exist.  I don&#39;t see this project being especially popular for the time being so utilizing text documents for players is sufficient.  I am curious though if there is a &#39;simple&#39; way to disable the auto account creation and instead interface with a forum.  Getting the forum to write out to a text document would be simple but I&#39;m not sure how to stop auto character creation at the login screen.

Also, as an aside, how &#39;difficult&#39; might it be to revert back to an sql database if the server did pick up?  Should I stop now and start fresh with another source with these capabilities if that is a future possibility or might it be within reason to do it later?

Any advice is welcome, thank you!</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2014 11:37:45 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/account-creation/545269.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Account Creation</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Artemis_Wp Artemis Wp]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/artemis_wp">@Artemis_Wp</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Playerlogin.java it is</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/account-creation/545269/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/account-creation/545269/3</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2014 11:37:45 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-545269-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/account-creation/545269.rss">Account Creation</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Account Creation</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@stEps stEps]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/steps">@stEps</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>for easyrsc i believe it is in the playerlogin, or i think xent moved it into the player class.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/account-creation/545269/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/account-creation/545269/2</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2014 15:26:11 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-545269-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/account-creation/545269.rss">Account Creation</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Account Creation</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@mdttheory mdttheory]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/mdttheory">@mdttheory</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Hello,</p>
<p>I started a project of my own recently and am curious about account creation.  I am using noobscape source which is derived from easy rsc and one great feature is automatic account creation upon login if that account does not exist.  I don’t see this project being especially popular for the time being so utilizing text documents for players is sufficient.  I am curious though if there is a ‘simple’ way to disable the auto account creation and instead interface with a forum.  Getting the forum to write out to a text document would be simple but I’m not sure how to stop auto character creation at the login screen.</p>
<p>Also, as an aside, how ‘difficult’ might it be to revert back to an sql database if the server did pick up?  Should I stop now and start fresh with another source with these capabilities if that is a future possibility or might it be within reason to do it later?</p>
<p>Any advice is welcome, thank you!</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/account-creation/545269/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/account-creation/545269/1</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2014 05:33:29 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-545269-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/account-creation/545269.rss">Account Creation</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
