<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>[Flash Game] Jacksmith</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/flash-game-jacksmith/541907</link>
    <description>Came across a fun game for those of you who like to play flash games, it&#39;s very addicting and fun to play. 

Basic concept of the game:
You&#39;re a jacksmith and you have to make weapons for soldiers to use in war. Throughout your adventure you unlock new weapons, new weapon parts, etc. The enemies have powers of the elements (water, fire, earth, air) certain weapon parts are better for killing certain enemies, if you make it to the end of the enemies for that day (after making the weapons), you&#39;ll get a bonus chest with a new weapon plan in it. You can use copper, steel, gold, crystal, and a few other ore types to make weapons, you get these different ores from battling different enemies. You&#39;re also graded on how well the forging of the weapon is, the construction, and the handle, the closer to 100% the strong/better the weapons will be. This isn&#39;t just click a sword and you make a sword, you literally have to forge, construct, and put together the weapon in a certain timeframe.

Check it out, and let me know if you guys like it to.
(For anyone who was confused: I didn&#39;t make this game, not even sure who the original developer(s) are, it&#39;s just a fun game and I figured I would share it with you guys.) 

Link (AddictingGames): [url=http://www.addictinggames.com/strategy-games/jacksmith-game.jsp]Play Jacksmith on AddictingGames[/url]</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 05 Apr 2014 19:24:54 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Games</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/flash-game-jacksmith/541907.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>[Flash Game] Jacksmith</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@The_Web_Guy The Web Guy]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/the_web_guy">@The_Web_Guy</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote" data-post="2" data-topic="541907">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/docent/40/5_e05bb34c421432ee4d40de30c10af3e5.png" class="avatar"> Docent:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Since when was addicting games owned by Nickelodeon??</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I don’t know the in-depth details on it but I noticed the change maybe three/four years ago.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/flash-game-jacksmith/541907/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/flash-game-jacksmith/541907/3</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 05 Apr 2014 19:24:54 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-541907-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/flash-game-jacksmith/541907.rss">[Flash Game] Jacksmith</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Flash Game] Jacksmith</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Docent Limits]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/docent">@Docent</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Since when was addicting games owned by Nickelodeon??</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/flash-game-jacksmith/541907/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/flash-game-jacksmith/541907/2</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 05 Apr 2014 18:10:13 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-541907-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/flash-game-jacksmith/541907.rss">[Flash Game] Jacksmith</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Flash Game] Jacksmith</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@The_Web_Guy The Web Guy]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/the_web_guy">@The_Web_Guy</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Came across a fun game for those of you who like to play flash games, it’s very addicting and fun to play.</p>
<p>Basic concept of the game:<br>
You’re a jacksmith and you have to make weapons for soldiers to use in war. Throughout your adventure you unlock new weapons, new weapon parts, etc. The enemies have powers of the elements (water, fire, earth, air) certain weapon parts are better for killing certain enemies, if you make it to the end of the enemies for that day (after making the weapons), you’ll get a bonus chest with a new weapon plan in it. You can use copper, steel, gold, crystal, and a few other ore types to make weapons, you get these different ores from battling different enemies. You’re also graded on how well the forging of the weapon is, the construction, and the handle, the closer to 100% the strong/better the weapons will be. This isn’t just click a sword and you make a sword, you literally have to forge, construct, and put together the weapon in a certain timeframe.</p>
<p>Check it out, and let me know if you guys like it to.<br>
(For anyone who was confused: I didn’t make this game, not even sure who the original developer(s) are, it’s just a fun game and I figured I would share it with you guys.)</p>
<p>Link (AddictingGames): <a href="http://www.addictinggames.com/strategy-games/jacksmith-game.jsp" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">Play Jacksmith on AddictingGames</a></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/flash-game-jacksmith/541907/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/flash-game-jacksmith/541907/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 05 Apr 2014 15:27:45 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-541907-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/flash-game-jacksmith/541907.rss">[Flash Game] Jacksmith</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
