<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>A really good read:</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/a-really-good-read/31497</link>
    <description>I read this entire article, it&#39;s really good. It has opened some sort of insight, but all in all was even an entertaining read.

It&#39;s how some guy defines god and why he doesn&#39;t believe. It&#39;s a long read, but easy to follow and understand. 

http://www.update.uu.se/~fbendz/nogod/no_god.htm</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 03 Dec 2006 02:27:04 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>General Discussion</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/a-really-good-read/31497.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>A really good read:</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@xxlegitxx xxlegitxx]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/xxlegitxx">@xxlegitxx</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>It’s a good read, I’ll give it that.  But that’s all ill give it.  But there are serious holes in his logic.</p>
<p>If God doesn’t respond to your prayers, that just means (a) hes not the prayer type of God, or (b) he doesn’t give a shit about you, which is extremely likely given the skizzles of God and the crappiness of humans.  If you have a cat, you expect him to be obedient even if you couldn’t give a crap about him, right?  You will give him food no matter what though.  If he screws up, you give him a kick.  If he doesn’t you give him a reward</p>
<p>About Occam’s razor, of course we can’t understand him…  If we could understand our God, then we would BE God.  But we can’t.<br>
Some things are impossible to do for humans.  Not for God.  He can cover that 2-d surface with circles, but humans cannot understand how or why.</p>
<p>Again, omnipotence due to paradoxes isn’t valid.  He could build a wall he can’t tear down.  But then if he wanted to tear it down he can.  He knows what will happen in the future as a result of his actions.  It’s similar to how humans predict events (weather, etc), but infinitely more accurate.  His knowledge of the future does not control him, rather, he controls the future.  There are free wills, even if he is almighty.  Even though he knows what you will do, you still choose to do it.</p>
<p>Time and space is created by God.  These are four dimensions in a theoretical infinite amount.  God is.  He was not created.<br>
Void creator.  We can’t understand him.  Can someone go up and ask Him though?  If he created the laws of physics and everything, he is certainly above it all.</p>
<p>And the rest just fall under a statement said above.</p>
<p>Think about the Bible.  It gives us a set of laws that seem meaningless and seem to serve just to restrict us.  But look at our society today.  Open premarital sex and access to porn.  Yet the divorce rate is at an all-time high and happiness is at an all time low.  Hmm…  Plus think about it.  The way marriage worked back in Biblical times, how often do you think people got divorced?  My guess would be little to none.  Because if you don’t know what you’re missing, you don’t know what you are missing.  After dating 100’s of girls and finally settling down, you will always think, “Man, Jessie was a better kisser” or “Melissa had a nicer ass”, etc.  But if you had no clue what a girl even looked like before you married, you would be happy with that you have, because you don’t know anything better.  And that is why God created the 7th and 10th commandments, You shall not commit adultery and You shall not covet your neighbors ___.  Instead of viewing religion as a hindrance, view it as a door to happiness.  Look at each commandment and see the truth and reasoning behind it.  If you don’t believe in God, at least know that those commandments will make you much happier.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/a-really-good-read/31497/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/a-really-good-read/31497/4</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 03 Dec 2006 02:27:04 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-31497-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/a-really-good-read/31497.rss">A really good read:</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>A really good read:</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@bullzeye95 bullzeye]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/bullzeye95">@bullzeye95</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Wow, he has tons of good facts in there.  And good grammar too &lt;3</p>
<p>It is a good read.  He proves everything he says.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/a-really-good-read/31497/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/a-really-good-read/31497/3</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 03 Dec 2006 01:50:42 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-31497-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/a-really-good-read/31497.rss">A really good read:</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>A really good read:</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Akriam Akriam]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/akriam">@Akriam</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Hmmm…I’m not even gunna read it, it <span class="bbcode-i">is</span> probably a good read, but I see no point because I don’t even read articles about how there is God…to boring…<img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=6" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/a-really-good-read/31497/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/a-really-good-read/31497/2</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 03 Dec 2006 01:30:19 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-31497-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/a-really-good-read/31497.rss">A really good read:</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>A really good read:</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@jme jme]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/jme">@jme</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I read this entire article, it’s really good. It has opened some sort of insight, but all in all was even an entertaining read.</p>
<p>It’s how some guy defines god and why he doesn’t believe. It’s a long read, but easy to follow and understand.</p>
<p><a href="http://www.update.uu.se/~fbendz/nogod/no_god.htm" class="onebox" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">http://www.update.uu.se/~fbendz/nogod/no_god.htm</a></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/a-really-good-read/31497/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/a-really-good-read/31497/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 03 Dec 2006 01:28:25 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-31497-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/a-really-good-read/31497.rss">A really good read:</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
