<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>JayPix Studios - Programmer, Sound Engineer, Graphics Designer etc</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/jaypix-studios-programmer-sound-engineer-graphics-designer-etc/453213</link>
    <description>[center]
   [IMG]http://i50.tinypic.com/35lahxx.png[/img]
[/center]

[center][size=24pt]Who are we?[/size][/center]
[center]We are a small, free Java game development studios based in NZ. However, we have a network of Programmers, Graphic Designers, Sound Engineers etc. We are dedicated to make fun, addictive and free Java games and accepts kind donations of players. Of course, each member would be paid with players&#39; donation money for the amount their contribution.[/center]


[center]Currently our studios consists of 3 members:  Quirq, Tahooey and DeathJockey[/center]

[center][size=24pt]Our Focus[/size][/center]
[center]We are currently focusing on releasing 1 fully featured customisable RPG/Simulation game called DigiLife, you can check it out here: [url=http://digilifegame.com]http://digilifegame.com[/url]. Our team members are working hard on getting a proper release, but we need YOUR help! READ ON![/center]

[center][size=24pt]We need YOU![/size][/center]

[b]If you&#39;re a player (or subscriber for now)[/b], we would greatly appreciate your help supporting this game (not necessarily donation). We wish all players to have a fun time, you may have your say at our game forums and help shape the game!

[b]If you&#39;re a programmer [/b] who is able to work independently and is able to implement whatever you wish in a game using Slick2D game library, we&#39;ll definitely need [b]your help[/b] with the game. (You&#39;ll be paid for your amount of contribution with donation money).

At the moment, only 1 programmer / web designer, is in the studios with 1 graphics designer and 1 sound engineer

[b]If you&#39;re a great graphics designer [/b] who is able to complete graphics requests on time and with ease, we&#39;d love to have one of you guys right in our team! Of course you&#39;ll be paid from donation money (by the amount of contribution to game).

Lastly and most importantly [b]if you are a talented SOUND/MUSIC engineer [/b] you&#39;re [b]Just the people we need![/b] Yes, we need 1 more music/sound engineer, of course, like all above,  a paid job based on donation money and amount of contribution.

[center][size=24pt]Are you interested?[/size][/center]
We&#39;re offering you this opportunity to work on the fun, upcoming simulation sandbox, your contribution can drop the day count numbers on the release date! Your contribution will be listed onto our credits and you will be part of us!

If you have [b]ANY[/b] questions, please do not hesitate to ask right here. Or else, email: mrdeathjockey@gmail.com to apply (You can apply with the below form or apply yourself)!

&lt;blockquote&gt;[size=14pt]Application Form[/size]

Name: 
Age: 
Contact Email: 
Applying for (Put X on ones you&#39;re applying for)
    [ ] Programming (Java)
    [ ] Graphics Design
    [ ] Sound Engineer / Music Composing
    [ ] Web Maintenance
    [ ] Other, Please Specify: 

Your experiences with your specialised field:

Reason(s) you&#39;re interested:&lt;/blockquote&gt;</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 07 Aug 2012 06:04:38 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Game Development</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/jaypix-studios-programmer-sound-engineer-graphics-designer-etc/453213.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>JayPix Studios - Programmer, Sound Engineer, Graphics Designer etc</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@DeathJockey DeathJockey]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/deathjockey">@DeathJockey</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[center]<br>
<div class="lightbox-wrapper"><a class="lightbox" href="http://i50.tinypic.com/35lahxx.png" title="35lahxx.png" rel="nofollow noopener"><img src="http://i50.tinypic.com/35lahxx.png" alt width="690" height="258"><div class="meta">
<svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-far-image svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#far-image"></use></svg><span class="filename">35lahxx.png</span><span class="informations">800×300</span><svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-discourse-expand svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#discourse-expand"></use></svg>
</div></a></div><br>
[/center]</p>
<p>[center][size=24pt]Who are we?[/size][/center]<br>
[center]We are a small, free Java game development studios based in NZ. However, we have a network of Programmers, Graphic Designers, Sound Engineers etc. We are dedicated to make fun, addictive and free Java games and accepts kind donations of players. Of course, each member would be paid with players’ donation money for the amount their contribution.[/center]</p>
<p>[center]Currently our studios consists of 3 members:  Quirq, Tahooey and DeathJockey[/center]</p>
<p>[center][size=24pt]Our Focus[/size][/center]<br>
[center]We are currently focusing on releasing 1 fully featured customisable RPG/Simulation game called DigiLife, you can check it out here: <a href="http://digilifegame.com" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">http://digilifegame.com</a>. Our team members are working hard on getting a proper release, but we need YOUR help! READ ON![/center]</p>
<p>[center][size=24pt]We need YOU![/size][/center]</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">If you’re a player (or subscriber for now)</span>, we would greatly appreciate your help supporting this game (not necessarily donation). We wish all players to have a fun time, you may have your say at our game forums and help shape the game!</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">If you’re a programmer </span> who is able to work independently and is able to implement whatever you wish in a game using Slick2D game library, we’ll definitely need <span class="bbcode-b">your help</span> with the game. (You’ll be paid for your amount of contribution with donation money).</p>
<p>At the moment, only 1 programmer / web designer, is in the studios with 1 graphics designer and 1 sound engineer</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">If you’re a great graphics designer </span> who is able to complete graphics requests on time and with ease, we’d love to have one of you guys right in our team! Of course you’ll be paid from donation money (by the amount of contribution to game).</p>
<p>Lastly and most importantly <span class="bbcode-b">if you are a talented SOUND/MUSIC engineer </span> you’re <span class="bbcode-b">Just the people we need!</span> Yes, we need 1 more music/sound engineer, of course, like all above,  a paid job based on donation money and amount of contribution.</p>
<p>[center][size=24pt]Are you interested?[/size][/center]<br>
We’re offering you this opportunity to work on the fun, upcoming simulation sandbox, your contribution can drop the day count numbers on the release date! Your contribution will be listed onto our credits and you will be part of us!</p>
<p>If you have <span class="bbcode-b">ANY</span> questions, please do not hesitate to ask right here. Or else, email: <a href="mailto:mrdeathjockey@gmail.com">mrdeathjockey@gmail.com</a> to apply (You can apply with the below form or apply yourself)!</p>
<blockquote>[size=14pt]Application Form[/size]
<p>Name:<br>
Age:<br>
Contact Email:<br>
Applying for (Put X on ones you’re applying for)<br>
[ ] Programming (Java)<br>
[ ] Graphics Design<br>
[ ] Sound Engineer / Music Composing<br>
[ ] Web Maintenance<br>
[ ] Other, Please Specify:</p>
<p>Your experiences with your specialised field:</p>
<p>Reason(s) you’re interested:</p>
</blockquote>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/jaypix-studios-programmer-sound-engineer-graphics-designer-etc/453213/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/jaypix-studios-programmer-sound-engineer-graphics-designer-etc/453213/1</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 07 Aug 2012 06:04:38 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-453213-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/jaypix-studios-programmer-sound-engineer-graphics-designer-etc/453213.rss">JayPix Studios - Programmer, Sound Engineer, Graphics Designer etc</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
