<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Some ideas you can use in your server</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/some-ideas-you-can-use-in-your-server/551656</link>
    <description>Just some ideas I&#39;ve had throughout the years but never bothered to develop because of a lack of excuses to avoid saying that I&#39;m a lazy fuck.

[b]MOBA server in Castle Wars[/b]

People get to pick their class and then join a queue to start a 5v5 Castle Wars match. Available roles are: tank, archer, warrior, mage, support. The role you pick affects which stats you get and which items you can buy from the store. The roles of each class is very
straightforward: tank has to absorb physical damage and get the enemy flag. Archer has to shoot down enemy squishes with high dps. Warrior does pretty much the same as archer but doesn&#39;t have access to high grade tank armor. Mage is more of a utility role with weakens/stuns. Support has access to lunar spellbook and is the only role which can use barricades, cannon, etc, etc, ...
You get points to spend in the shop every minute, for every kill, for every assist and the entire team gets points for every captured flag.

[b]Special Duel Arena mode: Gladiator[/b]

You get thrown into a duel arena with a random target. You can only fight your target. You can&#39;t bring any healing items into the arena. Upon a successfull kill, your stats are restored and you get a new target. Once your killstreak starts to increase, you&#39;ll have to fight 2 targets at once and you will receive the red skull which will buff your stats slightly.

[b]Ritual of Rejuvenation (hunger games spin-off)[/b]

You start with a group of people in a central area and you are all soon released into the world with the only task to kill eachother. Every 30 minutes, a Reaping Event is hosted, summoning all participants to a battle arena untill 1 person has died. Once the Reaping Event is over, all participants, excluding the victim, will be returned to their original locations with increased combat experience and an amount of combat runes. Extra content must be added to allow the players to gain experience without having to grind to make certain &quot;paths&quot;. For example; clearing the Mage Arena should reward the player with the chosen god staff and cape with enough runes to cast the spell 100 times along with a decent magic xp boost. Killing someone outside of the Reaping Event will grant you all the experience of that player.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 31 May 2015 02:21:11 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/some-ideas-you-can-use-in-your-server/551656.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Some ideas you can use in your server</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@FoHammer FoHammer]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/fohammer">@FoHammer</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Get ahold of me Cres</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/some-ideas-you-can-use-in-your-server/551656/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/some-ideas-you-can-use-in-your-server/551656/3</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 31 May 2015 02:21:11 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-551656-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/some-ideas-you-can-use-in-your-server/551656.rss">Some ideas you can use in your server</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Some ideas you can use in your server</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Welliton_inc Welliton_inc]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/welliton_inc">@Welliton_inc</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>As a mini-game it sounds good. Although if I was to implement a unique concept into a server, I prefer it to be more permanent.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/some-ideas-you-can-use-in-your-server/551656/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/some-ideas-you-can-use-in-your-server/551656/2</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 25 May 2015 22:08:45 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-551656-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/some-ideas-you-can-use-in-your-server/551656.rss">Some ideas you can use in your server</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Some ideas you can use in your server</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Cres Cres]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/cres">@Cres</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Just some ideas I’ve had throughout the years but never bothered to develop because of a lack of excuses to avoid saying that I’m a lazy fuck.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">MOBA server in Castle Wars</span></p>
<p>People get to pick their class and then join a queue to start a 5v5 Castle Wars match. Available roles are: tank, archer, warrior, mage, support. The role you pick affects which stats you get and which items you can buy from the store. The roles of each class is very<br>
straightforward: tank has to absorb physical damage and get the enemy flag. Archer has to shoot down enemy squishes with high dps. Warrior does pretty much the same as archer but doesn’t have access to high grade tank armor. Mage is more of a utility role with weakens/stuns. Support has access to lunar spellbook and is the only role which can use barricades, cannon, etc, etc, …<br>
You get points to spend in the shop every minute, for every kill, for every assist and the entire team gets points for every captured flag.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Special Duel Arena mode: Gladiator</span></p>
<p>You get thrown into a duel arena with a random target. You can only fight your target. You can’t bring any healing items into the arena. Upon a successfull kill, your stats are restored and you get a new target. Once your killstreak starts to increase, you’ll have to fight 2 targets at once and you will receive the red skull which will buff your stats slightly.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Ritual of Rejuvenation (hunger games spin-off)</span></p>
<p>You start with a group of people in a central area and you are all soon released into the world with the only task to kill eachother. Every 30 minutes, a Reaping Event is hosted, summoning all participants to a battle arena untill 1 person has died. Once the Reaping Event is over, all participants, excluding the victim, will be returned to their original locations with increased combat experience and an amount of combat runes. Extra content must be added to allow the players to gain experience without having to grind to make certain “paths”. For example; clearing the Mage Arena should reward the player with the chosen god staff and cape with enough runes to cast the spell 100 times along with a decent magic xp boost. Killing someone outside of the Reaping Event will grant you all the experience of that player.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/some-ideas-you-can-use-in-your-server/551656/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/some-ideas-you-can-use-in-your-server/551656/1</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 25 May 2015 13:58:16 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-551656-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/some-ideas-you-can-use-in-your-server/551656.rss">Some ideas you can use in your server</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
