<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Problem jarring please help!</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/problem-jarring-please-help/549283</link>
    <description>Hello, I was just having a problem with jar making. I have always had other friends do it for me because I could never get it down. I have watched youtube videos and other tutorials on how how to jar but it never works. I have no idea if it&#39;s my client or just me messing up, I have changed all IP&#39;s in the client side of the server but not the source because I&#39;m not sure if you have to or not. I was just guessing not because I couldn&#39;t find any files with any IP&#39;s in them. But I watched a youtube video, got to the end, everything worked out fine, and when I click on the jar client nothing happens. Yes, I double clicked and the blue circle next to my cursor was spinning for a second, then nothing. I change the IP in my files to my VPS ip and jarred the client on my PC, I&#39;m sure that&#39;s fine. Somebody help please, I would really appreciate it. Thanks in advance!</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2015 09:38:50 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/problem-jarring-please-help/549283.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Problem jarring please help!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Project_Runescape Project Runescape]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/project_runescape">@Project_Runescape</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p><a href="http://prntscr.com/5uqj4u" class="onebox" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">http://prntscr.com/5uqj4u</a></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/problem-jarring-please-help/549283/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/problem-jarring-please-help/549283/2</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2015 09:38:50 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-549283-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/problem-jarring-please-help/549283.rss">Problem jarring please help!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Problem jarring please help!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Primitive317 Primitive317]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/primitive317">@Primitive317</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Hello, I was just having a problem with jar making. I have always had other friends do it for me because I could never get it down. I have watched youtube videos and other tutorials on how how to jar but it never works. I have no idea if it’s my client or just me messing up, I have changed all IP’s in the client side of the server but not the source because I’m not sure if you have to or not. I was just guessing not because I couldn’t find any files with any IP’s in them. But I watched a youtube video, got to the end, everything worked out fine, and when I click on the jar client nothing happens. Yes, I double clicked and the blue circle next to my cursor was spinning for a second, then nothing. I change the IP in my files to my VPS ip and jarred the client on my PC, I’m sure that’s fine. Somebody help please, I would really appreciate it. Thanks in advance!</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/problem-jarring-please-help/549283/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/problem-jarring-please-help/549283/1</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2015 03:25:22 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-549283-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/problem-jarring-please-help/549283.rss">Problem jarring please help!</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
