<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>A new skill I&#39;ve been thinking of</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/a-new-skill-ive-been-thinking-of/481714</link>
    <description>So while I was doing reading physics, I came up with, what i think, a great idea for a skill. It&#39;s called Observation.

This skills add&#39;s a new option in the right click menu, &quot;Observe&quot;. And basically you can observe objects/items/monsters and find out more useful ways to obtain items, earn experience, craft items, do damage, etc. It kind of has back story too, in a sense this goes against the gods of RuneScape since you go against them by obtaining forbidden knowledge that only the gods know of. Basically here&#39;s a couple of idea&#39;s that I have in mind. To start out you obtain a journal and you go around the map observing items, objects, npc&#39;s, etc. and you write down what you learn from observing them. As your knowledge increases (i.e level) you&#39;ll be able to observe more complex objects, items, etc. and learn how they work and how to use those items/objects more efficiently. Like for example, when you go around observing high level monsters you learn there strengths and weaknesses so your better prepared to kill them by exploiting their weaknesses and be better off to defend from them. And when you observe weapons you essentially learn how to use the weapon more effectively and cause greater damage. Everything you learn will be in your journal and to use what you learned you must equip your journal (like a god book).

But there are tradeoffs, seeing as the gods are outraged by you obtaining knowledge only they know of there&#39;s a chance when your observing an item or an object or an npc, that they send one of their followers to attack you. And if your weilding that journal for too long, the gods might smite you, poison you, etc. This also effects prayer. All equipment that offers a prayer bonus is neglected if you are wielding your journal. If you are using prayer while wielding your journal your prayer drains much quicker and it increases the chance of the gods smiting you. You also can&#39;t bury bones,use prayer alters, use prayer/restore pots while you are wielding the journal.

For non combat, for example you might learn how to more effectively chop down a tree or obtain an ore, you will be better at refining the ore and increase your chances of getting an ingot back. More to be added...

At higher levels, roughly 80-99 you might personally get summoned by either Sara or Zammy to appear before them. At that time they will offer you a proposition, forget all you know (your observation skill will be set to 0 and no longer trainable) and in exchange some sort of reward. Or you can choose to defy them and have an all out brawl with Sara or Zammy using your Journal and obtain A god weapon or money if you win. If you are successful, it increases your chances of being summoned by the other god but if you are not, your observation skill will be reset to 1 (and it still will be trainable but you&#39;ll have a harder time training it) which essentially is your memory being wiped and your journal taken away from you.

Mechanics of observing, you basically have to sit down next to the object/item/npc your observing for roughly 2-5 minutes and &quot;think&quot; lol. It will be a tough skill to train but oh so worth it.

To obtain the &quot;journal&quot; I was thinking of that null void in the map with a bookshelf there, but to go to the null void you need to have roughly 75 theiving and high combat level because your essentially stealing the journal from Sara and you have to get past his followers, make it to his temple and go through a portal to get to the null void. Once you steal the journal, you die(losing all your items that you have except the journal) and essentially become &quot;reborn&quot; and see the world with a whole new perspective. And when you wield the Journal, the Observe option becomes available :P

Thoughts? I&#39;m going to come back and change things around with the feed back I get.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 07 Feb 2013 04:11:03 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/a-new-skill-ive-been-thinking-of/481714.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>A new skill I&#39;ve been thinking of</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@xxx123xxx xxx123xxx]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/xxx123xxx">@xxx123xxx</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote" data-post="9" data-topic="481714">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 Newty:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>ahem <em>inb4 Lin</em></p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/a-new-skill-ive-been-thinking-of/481714/10">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/a-new-skill-ive-been-thinking-of/481714/10</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 07 Feb 2013 04:11:03 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-481714-10</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/a-new-skill-ive-been-thinking-of/481714.rss">A new skill I&#39;ve been thinking of</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>A new skill I&#39;ve been thinking of</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@NewbieNewty Newty]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/newbienewty">@NewbieNewty</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>ahem <em>inb4 Lin</em></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/a-new-skill-ive-been-thinking-of/481714/9">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/a-new-skill-ive-been-thinking-of/481714/9</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 07 Feb 2013 03:38:29 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-481714-9</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/a-new-skill-ive-been-thinking-of/481714.rss">A new skill I&#39;ve been thinking of</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>A new skill I&#39;ve been thinking of</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@xxx123xxx xxx123xxx]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/xxx123xxx">@xxx123xxx</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote quote-modified" data-post="7" data-topic="481714">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/strucker/40/5_e05bb34c421432ee4d40de30c10af3e5.png" class="avatar"> strucker:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>i would call your skill… “Stalker skill”</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>One aspect of it, observing monsters <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/confused.png?v=5" title=":confused:" class="emoji" alt=":confused:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/a-new-skill-ive-been-thinking-of/481714/8">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/a-new-skill-ive-been-thinking-of/481714/8</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 07 Feb 2013 01:58:35 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-481714-8</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/a-new-skill-ive-been-thinking-of/481714.rss">A new skill I&#39;ve been thinking of</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>A new skill I&#39;ve been thinking of</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@strucker Strucker]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/strucker">@strucker</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>i would call your skill… “Stalker skill”</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/a-new-skill-ive-been-thinking-of/481714/7">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/a-new-skill-ive-been-thinking-of/481714/7</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 07 Feb 2013 01:49:42 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-481714-7</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/a-new-skill-ive-been-thinking-of/481714.rss">A new skill I&#39;ve been thinking of</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>A new skill I&#39;ve been thinking of</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@xxx123xxx xxx123xxx]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/xxx123xxx">@xxx123xxx</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Feel free to use any of the content posted above to your hearts content. I’ve been working on this to the side and will post a much in depth version and I will be taking into consideration Flame’s idea’s especially the quest part and work on lore a bit more lol</p>
<p>Note this was just a sporadic idea that just popped in my head, only worked on this for 30 minutes so expect a more well thought out example soon <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=5" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"></p>
<p>“Examples of this would be having to observe items before picking them up, thus causing actions such as PvM and PK’ing to be less fluent”</p>
<p>Not exactly, this more of an addition then a renovation and the changes will take place only if you have the journal wielded</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/a-new-skill-ive-been-thinking-of/481714/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/a-new-skill-ive-been-thinking-of/481714/6</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 06 Feb 2013 23:54:46 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-481714-6</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/a-new-skill-ive-been-thinking-of/481714.rss">A new skill I&#39;ve been thinking of</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>A new skill I&#39;ve been thinking of</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Clawz_fury lare69]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/clawz_fury">@Clawz_fury</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>that’s actually a great idea ^^ you could even create a custom packet sent to the server whenever something is examined <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=5" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/a-new-skill-ive-been-thinking-of/481714/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/a-new-skill-ive-been-thinking-of/481714/5</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 06 Feb 2013 21:51:35 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-481714-5</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/a-new-skill-ive-been-thinking-of/481714.rss">A new skill I&#39;ve been thinking of</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>A new skill I&#39;ve been thinking of</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Flame3 John]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/flame3">@Flame3</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote" data-post="3" data-topic="481714">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 runescape sucks:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>This sounds more like a minigame idea, or a d&amp;d thing.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Also, a lot of information has been put into this skill, but I can tell not too much thought.<br>
There is a lot of stuff that isn’t so clear, such as </p><blockquote>It kind of has back story too, in a sense this goes against the gods of RuneScape since you go against them by obtaining forbidden knowledge that only the gods know of</blockquote><br>
There should definitely be a quest that you need to be able to gain some backdoor knowledge of this concept.<br>
After that quest, you should only have access to this ability through a minigame, as to have it as a skill would involve a lot of unnecessary changes to the gameplay itself. Examples of this would be having to observe items before picking them up, thus causing actions such as PvM and PK’ing to be less fluent.<br>
Here is something that I just came up with to help you with this idea. It’s sketchy, so edit it to how you like should you use it.
<blockquote>[b][u]Type: Minigame[/u][/b]
The examine tool becomes your new best friend in this minigame. This is the sister event to the Digsite minigame, where you make new use of the "Examine" option. You are given a few tools to help you with this minigame as you travel around an alternate world, encased in a farm from 300 years back. You can examine your finds; but with new features. Each successfully examined item grants you 5 points to spend on rewards after time has ended.</blockquote>
Again, I put nearly no consideration into the plot of the minigame, and you will definitely need to elaborate more on this event should you use it.
Kudos for having thought of a semi-unique idea and contributing your thoughts.
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/a-new-skill-ive-been-thinking-of/481714/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/a-new-skill-ive-been-thinking-of/481714/4</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 06 Feb 2013 21:40:37 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-481714-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/a-new-skill-ive-been-thinking-of/481714.rss">A new skill I&#39;ve been thinking of</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>A new skill I&#39;ve been thinking of</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@runescape_sucks runescape sucks]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/runescape_sucks">@runescape_sucks</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>This sounds more like a minigame idea, or a d&amp;d thing.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/a-new-skill-ive-been-thinking-of/481714/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/a-new-skill-ive-been-thinking-of/481714/3</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 06 Feb 2013 21:31:13 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-481714-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/a-new-skill-ive-been-thinking-of/481714.rss">A new skill I&#39;ve been thinking of</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>A new skill I&#39;ve been thinking of</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Clawz_fury lare69]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/clawz_fury">@Clawz_fury</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>sounds a bit boring and unnecessary tbh, I wouldn’t bother training it</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/a-new-skill-ive-been-thinking-of/481714/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/a-new-skill-ive-been-thinking-of/481714/2</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 06 Feb 2013 21:29:26 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-481714-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/a-new-skill-ive-been-thinking-of/481714.rss">A new skill I&#39;ve been thinking of</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>A new skill I&#39;ve been thinking of</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@xxx123xxx xxx123xxx]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/xxx123xxx">@xxx123xxx</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>So while I was doing reading physics, I came up with, what i think, a great idea for a skill. It’s called Observation.</p>
<p>This skills add’s a new option in the right click menu, “Observe”. And basically you can observe objects/items/monsters and find out more useful ways to obtain items, earn experience, craft items, do damage, etc. It kind of has back story too, in a sense this goes against the gods of RuneScape since you go against them by obtaining forbidden knowledge that only the gods know of. Basically here’s a couple of idea’s that I have in mind. To start out you obtain a journal and you go around the map observing items, objects, npc’s, etc. and you write down what you learn from observing them. As your knowledge increases (i.e level) you’ll be able to observe more complex objects, items, etc. and learn how they work and how to use those items/objects more efficiently. Like for example, when you go around observing high level monsters you learn there strengths and weaknesses so your better prepared to kill them by exploiting their weaknesses and be better off to defend from them. And when you observe weapons you essentially learn how to use the weapon more effectively and cause greater damage. Everything you learn will be in your journal and to use what you learned you must equip your journal (like a god book).</p>
<p>But there are tradeoffs, seeing as the gods are outraged by you obtaining knowledge only they know of there’s a chance when your observing an item or an object or an npc, that they send one of their followers to attack you. And if your weilding that journal for too long, the gods might smite you, poison you, etc. This also effects prayer. All equipment that offers a prayer bonus is neglected if you are wielding your journal. If you are using prayer while wielding your journal your prayer drains much quicker and it increases the chance of the gods smiting you. You also can’t bury bones,use prayer alters, use prayer/restore pots while you are wielding the journal.</p>
<p>For non combat, for example you might learn how to more effectively chop down a tree or obtain an ore, you will be better at refining the ore and increase your chances of getting an ingot back. More to be added…</p>
<p>At higher levels, roughly 80-99 you might personally get summoned by either Sara or Zammy to appear before them. At that time they will offer you a proposition, forget all you know (your observation skill will be set to 0 and no longer trainable) and in exchange some sort of reward. Or you can choose to defy them and have an all out brawl with Sara or Zammy using your Journal and obtain A god weapon or money if you win. If you are successful, it increases your chances of being summoned by the other god but if you are not, your observation skill will be reset to 1 (and it still will be trainable but you’ll have a harder time training it) which essentially is your memory being wiped and your journal taken away from you.</p>
<p>Mechanics of observing, you basically have to sit down next to the object/item/npc your observing for roughly 2-5 minutes and “think” lol. It will be a tough skill to train but oh so worth it.</p>
<p>To obtain the “journal” I was thinking of that null void in the map with a bookshelf there, but to go to the null void you need to have roughly 75 theiving and high combat level because your essentially stealing the journal from Sara and you have to get past his followers, make it to his temple and go through a portal to get to the null void. Once you steal the journal, you die(losing all your items that you have except the journal) and essentially become “reborn” and see the world with a whole new perspective. And when you wield the Journal, the Observe option becomes available <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=5" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"></p>
<p>Thoughts? I’m going to come back and change things around with the feed back I get.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/a-new-skill-ive-been-thinking-of/481714/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/a-new-skill-ive-been-thinking-of/481714/1</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 06 Feb 2013 04:58:53 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-481714-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/a-new-skill-ive-been-thinking-of/481714.rss">A new skill I&#39;ve been thinking of</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
