<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Mine vs. Mine [1.4.6] {Towny}.{mcMMO}.[PvP].[Mature].[Teamspeak].[Website]</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/mine-vs-mine-1-4-6-towny-mcmmo-pvp-mature-teamspeak-website/477731</link>
    <description>[b]Server Name:[/b] Mine Vs. Mine
[b]Website:[/b] [url=http://www.minevsmine.com/]www.minevsmine.com/[/url]
[b]Server Address/IP:[/b] minevsmine.com
[b]Game Play Type/s:[/b] Survival, PVP
[b]Description[/b]

[hr]


[b]What To Expect?[/b]



[ul][li]An immensely friendly community[/li][/ul]


[ul][li]Dedicated staff whom have expert knowledge in programming.[/li][/ul]


[ul][li]Very player-base orientated, with constant evolving due to feedback[/li][/ul]


[ul][li]This server is for mature players only, as such, topics discussed will reflect this.[/li][/ul]


[ul][li]Common sense is key when it comes to rules, moderators are on hand to ensure there is as little disruption as possible.[/li][/ul]


Upon joining the server first time, you will be given guest status, however, guests can not use the servers full functionality. Go to our website, minevsmine.com, and register to receive access to the /sethome, /tpa commands, and much much more! It&#39;s free and easy!

[b]Towny[/b]

The only way to protect your land, anything not in a town is susceptible to griefing.
Start a town, become a mayor, lead your residents into a prosperous time of peace, or indeed send them to arms in an effort to secure more land.
Go power hungry and control a nation (group of towns) with your actions leading to it&#39;s success or downfall.
Build something epic to be revered server wide knowing it will be there as long as your town still stands.

&quot;I&#39;m a simple guy, I don&#39;t have time for all this responsibility, I just wanna mine&quot;

Don&#39;t worry Steve, we have something for everyone. Just join one of our already existing towns, and don&#39;t forget to invite your friends!

[b]Economy[/b]
We pride ourselves on our well balanced economy featuring a server market and bazaar where players can open their own shops to buy and sell whatever they like. We even have our own custom shop plugin that uses item frames for display and has some advanced features you won&#39;t find on any other server.

[b]PvP[/b]
Gear up! The wilderness is a scary place, who knows when someones going to take a shot.

Feeling brave? check out the mob arena, choose a class, and prepare for complete chaos as you battle wave after wave of monsters like an unrelenting storm. Go in with friends, work as a team, see who can survive the longest competing for bragging rights, whilst picking up prizes along the way.

Feeling creative? Several of our Mob Arena&#39;s were designed and built by the players, if you think you&#39;ve got the talent, talk to an admin to make arrangements.

Feeling even more adventurous? Test your skills in the spleef and team death-match arenas. Winner takes all!

[b]Survival[/b]

It&#39;s survival of the fittest out there! Take advantage of towny in order to protect yourself and property.

[b]Website[/b]

Our website: [url=http://www.minevsmine.com]www.minevsmine.com[/url] boasts some unique features such as the stats tracker, want to know how long you have played? How many creepers you&#39;ve killed? Well now you can!
It&#39;s simplistic clear format makes for great functionality and is very user-friendly. Use our new suggestions area and try push your ideas, need help with anything? Head on over to our FAQ page.

[b]Rules:[/b]


[ul][li]Use common sense, this is a mature server, those entering it should therefore have at least an ounce of the stuff[/li][/ul]


[ul][li]No x-ray![/li][/ul]


[ul][li]No Cheats/Hacked clients[/li][/ul]


[ul][li]No Racist, sexist, or derogatory comments[/li][/ul]


[ul][li]No advertising other servers[/li][/ul]


[ul][li]No begging for ANYTHING.[/li][/ul]


[b]Plugins:[/b]

MCMMO-Get rewarded for what you do best!
Essentials-For all those commands you&#39;ve grown to depend on.
FrameShops-our own custom shops plugin!
PotatoBombs-Another custom plugin that&#39;s loads of fun, finally giving a use to those poisonous potatoes.
Plus many more!

[b]Owner/Admins/Moderators:[/b]

ulchm (owner)
metalhedd (admin)
nortrack (admin)
Relira (mod)
BigBossCasey (mod)
EselleM (mod)
Ryan95 (mod)
117jamie117 (mod)
xX_Kramer_Xx (mod)

[b]Pictures/Videos URL:[/b]

Check out some of the fantastic work done by our players [url=http://imgur.com/a/3eLqt#0]http://imgur.com/a/3eLqt#0[/url]

Still not convinced? Below is a player-made video giving a short insight into the server.

http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=3A-XyZ2LQ7E</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 06 Jan 2013 17:47:27 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Minecraft</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/mine-vs-mine-1-4-6-towny-mcmmo-pvp-mature-teamspeak-website/477731.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Mine vs. Mine [1.4.6] {Towny}.{mcMMO}.[PvP].[Mature].[Teamspeak].[Website]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@117jamie117 117jamie117]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/117jamie117">@117jamie117</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p><span class="bbcode-b">Server Name:</span> Mine Vs. Mine<br>
<span class="bbcode-b">Website:</span> <a href="http://www.minevsmine.com/" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">www.minevsmine.com/</a><br>
<span class="bbcode-b">Server Address/IP:</span> <a href="http://minevsmine.com" rel="nofollow noopener">minevsmine.com</a><br>
<span class="bbcode-b">Game Play Type/s:</span> Survival, PVP<br>
<span class="bbcode-b">Description</span></p>
<p>[hr]</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">What To Expect?</span></p>
<p>[ul][li]An immensely friendly community[/li][/ul]</p>
<p>[ul][li]Dedicated staff whom have expert knowledge in programming.[/li][/ul]</p>
<p>[ul][li]Very player-base orientated, with constant evolving due to feedback[/li][/ul]</p>
<p>[ul][li]This server is for mature players only, as such, topics discussed will reflect this.[/li][/ul]</p>
<p>[ul][li]Common sense is key when it comes to rules, moderators are on hand to ensure there is as little disruption as possible.[/li][/ul]</p>
<p>Upon joining the server first time, you will be given guest status, however, guests can not use the servers full functionality. Go to our website, <a href="http://minevsmine.com" rel="nofollow noopener">minevsmine.com</a>, and register to receive access to the /sethome, /tpa commands, and much much more! It’s free and easy!</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Towny</span></p>
<p>The only way to protect your land, anything not in a town is susceptible to griefing.<br>
Start a town, become a mayor, lead your residents into a prosperous time of peace, or indeed send them to arms in an effort to secure more land.<br>
Go power hungry and control a nation (group of towns) with your actions leading to it’s success or downfall.<br>
Build something epic to be revered server wide knowing it will be there as long as your town still stands.</p>
<p>“I’m a simple guy, I don’t have time for all this responsibility, I just wanna mine”</p>
<p>Don’t worry Steve, we have something for everyone. Just join one of our already existing towns, and don’t forget to invite your friends!</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Economy</span><br>
We pride ourselves on our well balanced economy featuring a server market and bazaar where players can open their own shops to buy and sell whatever they like. We even have our own custom shop plugin that uses item frames for display and has some advanced features you won’t find on any other server.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">PvP</span><br>
Gear up! The wilderness is a scary place, who knows when someones going to take a shot.</p>
<p>Feeling brave? check out the mob arena, choose a class, and prepare for complete chaos as you battle wave after wave of monsters like an unrelenting storm. Go in with friends, work as a team, see who can survive the longest competing for bragging rights, whilst picking up prizes along the way.</p>
<p>Feeling creative? Several of our Mob Arena’s were designed and built by the players, if you think you’ve got the talent, talk to an admin to make arrangements.</p>
<p>Feeling even more adventurous? Test your skills in the spleef and team death-match arenas. Winner takes all!</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Survival</span></p>
<p>It’s survival of the fittest out there! Take advantage of towny in order to protect yourself and property.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Website</span></p>
<p>Our website: <a href="http://www.minevsmine.com" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">www.minevsmine.com</a> boasts some unique features such as the stats tracker, want to know how long you have played? How many creepers you’ve killed? Well now you can!<br>
It’s simplistic clear format makes for great functionality and is very user-friendly. Use our new suggestions area and try push your ideas, need help with anything? Head on over to our FAQ page.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Rules:</span></p>
<p>[ul][li]Use common sense, this is a mature server, those entering it should therefore have at least an ounce of the stuff[/li][/ul]</p>
<p>[ul][li]No x-ray![/li][/ul]</p>
<p>[ul][li]No Cheats/Hacked clients[/li][/ul]</p>
<p>[ul][li]No Racist, sexist, or derogatory comments[/li][/ul]</p>
<p>[ul][li]No advertising other servers[/li][/ul]</p>
<p>[ul][li]No begging for ANYTHING.[/li][/ul]</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Plugins:</span></p>
<p>MCMMO-Get rewarded for what you do best!<br>
Essentials-For all those commands you’ve grown to depend on.<br>
FrameShops-our own custom shops plugin!<br>
PotatoBombs-Another custom plugin that’s loads of fun, finally giving a use to those poisonous potatoes.<br>
Plus many more!</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Owner/Admins/Moderators:</span></p>
<p>ulchm (owner)<br>
metalhedd (admin)<br>
nortrack (admin)<br>
Relira (mod)<br>
BigBossCasey (mod)<br>
EselleM (mod)<br>
Ryan95 (mod)<br>
117jamie117 (mod)<br>
xX_Kramer_Xx (mod)</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Pictures/Videos URL:</span></p>
<p>Check out some of the fantastic work done by our players <a href="http://imgur.com/a/3eLqt#0" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">http://imgur.com/a/3eLqt#0</a></p>
<p>Still not convinced? Below is a player-made video giving a short insight into the server.</p>
<div class="lazyYT" data-youtube-id="3A-XyZ2LQ7E" data-youtube-title="Minecraft Server: Mine Vs Mine Quick Insight" data-width="480" data-height="270" data-parameters="feature=oembed&amp;wmode=opaque"></div>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/mine-vs-mine-1-4-6-towny-mcmmo-pvp-mature-teamspeak-website/477731/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/mine-vs-mine-1-4-6-towny-mcmmo-pvp-mature-teamspeak-website/477731/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 06 Jan 2013 17:47:27 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-477731-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/mine-vs-mine-1-4-6-towny-mcmmo-pvp-mature-teamspeak-website/477731.rss">Mine vs. Mine [1.4.6] {Towny}.{mcMMO}.[PvP].[Mature].[Teamspeak].[Website]</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
