<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Freeware Copyright</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/freeware-copyright/155268</link>
    <description>I&#39;ve posted this here, and on srl.

&lt;blockquote&gt;Using Software: A Guide to the Ethical and Legal Use of Software 
for Members of the Academic Community

Software enables us to accomplish many different tasks with 
computers.  Unfortunately, in order to get our work done quickly 
and conveniently, some people make and use unauthorized software 
copies.  The purpose of this brochure is to provide a brief 
outline of what you legally can and cannot do with software.  
Hopefully it will help you better understand the implications and 
restrictions of the U.S. Copyright Law.


Here Are Some Relevant Facts:
----------------------------
UNAUTHORIZED copying of software is illegal.  Copyright law 
protects software authors and publishers, just as patent law 
protects inventors.

UNAUTHORIZED copying of software by individuals can harm the 
entire academic community.  If unauthorized copying proliferates 
on a campus, the institution may incur legal liability.  Also, the 
institution may find it more difficult to negotiate agreements 
that would make software more widely and less expensively 
available to members of the academic community.

UNAUTHORIZED copying and use of software deprives publishers and 
developers of a fair return for their work, increases prices, 
reduces the level of future support and enhancements, and can 
inhibit the development of new software products.

RESPECT for the intellectual work of others has traditionally been 
essential to the mission of colleges and universities.  As members 
of the academic community, we value the free exchange of ideas.  
Just as we do not tolerate plagiarism, we do not condone the 
unauthorized copying of software, including programs, 
applications, data bases and code.

THEREFORE, we offer the following statement of principle about 
intellectual property and the legal and ethical use of software.


THE EDUCOM CODE

Software and Intellectual Rights
================================
Respect for intellectual labor and creativity is vital to academic 
discourse and enterprise.  This principle applies to works of all 
authors and publishers in all media.  It encompasses respect for 
the right to acknowledgment, right to privacy, and right to 
determine the form, manner, and terms of publication and 
distribution.

Because electronic information is volatile and easily reproduced, 
respect for the work and personal expression of others is 
especially critical in computer environments.  Violations of 
authorial integrity, including plagiarism, invasion of privacy, 
unauthorized access, and trade secret and copyright violations, 
may be grounds for sanctions against members of the academic 
community.

EDUCOM&#39;s Educational Uses of Information Technology (EUIT) Program 
encourages the broadest possible adoption of this statement of 
principle.  The EDUCOM Code is intended for adaptation and use by 
individuals, and educational institutions at all levels.

Classification of Software
==========================
In terms of copyright, there are four broad classifications of 
software:

Commercial
Shareware
Freeware
Public Domain

The restrictions and limitations regarding each classification are 
different.

COMMERCIAL
----------
COMMERCIAL software represents the majority of software purchased 
from software publishers, commercial computer stores, etc.  When 
you buy software, you are actually acquiring a license to use it, 
not own it.  You acquire the license from the company that owns 
the copyright.  The conditions and restrictions of the license 
agreement vary from program to program and should be read 
carefully.  In general, commercial software licenses stipulate 
that ( 1 ) the software is covered by copyright, (2) although one 
archival copy of the software can be made, the backup copy cannot 
be used except when the original package fails or is destroyed, 
(3) modifications to the software are not allowed, (4) decompiling 
(i.e. reverse engineering) of the program code is not allowed 
without the permission of the copyright holder, and (5) 
development of new works built upon the package (derivative works) 
is not allowed without the permission of the copyright holder.

 
SHAREWARE
---------
SHAREWARE software is covered by copyright, as well.  When you 
acquire software under a shareware arrangement, you are actually 
acquiring a license to use it, not own it.  You acquire the 
license, from the individual or company that owns the copyright.  
The conditions and restrictions of the license agreement vary from 
program to program and should be read carefully.  The copyright 
holders for SHAREWARE allow purchasers to make and distribute 
copies of the software, but demand that if, after testing the 
software, you adopt it for use, you must pay for it.  In general, 
shareware, software licenses stipulate that (1) the software is 
covered by copyright, (2) although one archival copy of the 
software can be made, the backup copy cannot be used except when 
the original package fails or is destroyed, (3) modifications to 
the software are not allowed, (4) decompiling (i.e. reverse 
engineering) of the program code is not allowed without the 
permission of the copyright holder, and (5) development of new 
works built upon the package (derivative works) is not allowed 
without the permission of the copyright holder.  Selling software 
as SHAREWARE is a marketing decision, it does not change the legal 
requirements with respect to copyright.  That means that you can 
make a single archival copy, but you are obliged to pay for all 
copies adopted for use.


FREEWARE
--------
FREEWARE also is covered by copyright and subject to the 
conditions defined by the holder of the copyright.  The conditions 
for FREEWARE are in direct opposition to normal copyright 
restrictions.  In general, FREEWARE software licenses stipulate 
that (1) the software is covered by copyright, (2) copies of the 
software can be made for both archival and distribution purposes 
but that distribution cannot be for profit, (3) modifications to 
the software is allowed and encouraged, (4) decompiling (i.e. 
reverse engineering) of the program code is allowed without the 
explicit permission of the copyright holder, and (6) development 
of new works built upon the package (derivative works) is allowed 
and encouraged with the condition that derivative works must also 
be designated as FREEWARE.  That means that you cannot take 
FREEWARE, modify or extend it, and then sell it as COMMERCIAL or 
SHAREWARE software.
PUBLIC DOMAIN
-------------
PUBLIC DOMAIN software comes into being when the original 
copyright holder explicitly relinquishes all rights to the 
software.  Since under current copyright law, all intellectual 
works (including software) are protected as soon as they are 
committed to a medium, for something to be PUBLIC DOMAIN it must 
be clearly marked as such.  Before March 1, 1989, it was assumed 
that intellectual works were NOT covered by copyright unless the 
copyright symbol and declaration appeared on the work.  With the 
U.S. adherence to the Berne Convention this presumption has been 
reversed.  Now all works assume copyright protection unless the 
PUBLIC DOMAIN notification is stated.  This means that for PUBLIC 
DOMAIN software (1) copyright rights have been relinquished, (2) 
software copies can be made for both archival and distribution 
purposes with no restrictions as to distribution, (3) 
modifications to the software are allowed, (4) decompiling (i.e. 
reverse engineering) of the program code is allowed, and (5) 
development of new works built upon the package (derivative works) 
is allowed without conditions on the distribution or use of the 
derivative work.

Questions You May Have About Using Software
===========================================

What do I need to know about software and the U.S. Copyright Act?

It&#39;s really very simple.  The Copyright Law recognizes that all 
intellectual works (programs, data, pictures, articles, books, 
etc.) are automatically covered by copyright unless it is 
explicitly noted to the contrary.  That means that the owner of a 
copyright holds the exclusive right to reproduce and distribute 
his or her work.  For software this means it is illegal to copy or 
distribute software, or its documentation, without the permission 
of the copyright holder.

If you have a legal copy of software you are allowed to make a 
single archival copy of the software for backup purposes.  
However, the copy can only be used if the original software is 
destroyed or fails to work.  When the original is given away, the 
backup copy must also be given with the original or destroyed.


If software is not copy-protected, do I have the right to copy it?

Lack of copy-protection does NOT constitute permission to copy 
software without authorization of the software copyright owner.  
&quot;Non-copy-protected&quot; software enables you to make a backup copy.  
In offering non-copy-protected software to you, the developer or 
publisher has demonstrated significant trust in your integrity.


May I copy software that is available through facilities on my 
campus, so that I can use it more conveniently in my own office or 
room?

Software acquired by colleges and universities is usually covered 
by licenses.  The licenses should clearly state how and where the 
software may be legally used by members of the relevant campus 
communities (faculty, staff, and students).  Such licenses cover 
software whether installed on stand-alone or networked systems, 
whether in private offices and rooms, or in public clusters and 
laboratories.  Some institutional licenses permit copying for 
certain purposes.  The license may limit copying, as well.  
Consult your campus authorities to be sure if you are unsure about 
the permissible use of a particular software product.


May I loan software?

The 1990 modification to the Copyright Law makes it illegal to 
&quot;loan, lease or rent software&quot; for purposes of direct or indirect 
commercial advantage without the specific permission of the 
copyright holder.  Non-profit educational institutions are 
exempted from the 1990 modification, so institutional software may 
be loaned.

Some licenses may even restrict the use of a copy to a specific 
machine, even if you own more than one system.  In general, 
licenses usually do NOT allow the software to be installed or 
resident on more than a single machine, or to run the software 
simultaneously on two or more machines.


Isn&#39;t it legally &quot;fair use&quot; to copy software if the purpose in 
sharing it is purely educational?

Historically, the Copyright Law was modified to permit certain 
educational uses of copyrighted materials without the usual 
copyright restrictions.  However, &quot;fair use&quot; of computer software 
is still a cloudy issue.  The &quot;fair use&quot; amendments to the 
copyright law are intended to allow educational use of legally 
protected products, but it is limited (for paper-based products) 
to small portions of full works.  For most software it is clearly 
illegal to make and distribute unauthorized, fully-functional 
copies to class members for their individual use.  Making copies 
of a small section of code from a program in order to illustrate a 
programming technique might not be a violation.  The best 
alternative is to clear any such use with the copyright owner or 
consult the appropriate authorities at your institution.

Alternatives To Explore
=======================
Software can be expensive.  You may think that you cannot afford 
to purchase certain programs that you need.  Site-licensed and 
bulk purchased software are legal alternatives that make multiple 
copies of software more affordable.  Many educational institutions 
negotiate special prices for software used and purchased by 
faculty, staff and students.  Consult your campus computing office 
for information.  As with other software, site-licensed or bulk 
purchased software is still covered by copyright, although the 
price per copy may be significantly lower than the normal 
commercial price.  A usual condition of site-licensing or bulk-
purchasing is that copying and distribution of the software is 
limited to a central office which must maintain inventories of who 
received it.  When you leave the academic community by graduation, 
retirement, or resignation you may no longer be covered by the 
institutional agreement and may be required to return or destroy 
your copies of the software licensed to the institution.

Many colleges sell software through a campus store at &quot;educational 
discounts.&quot;  If you purchase software for yourself through such an 
outlet, the software is yours and need not be destroyed or 
surrendered when you leave the institution.  It is, however, still             
covered by normal copyright protection and covered by the specific 
conditions of the licensing agreement.

A Final Note
============
Restrictions on the use of software are far from uniform.  You 
should check carefully each piece of software and the accompanying 
documentation yourself.  In general, you do not have the right to:

Receive and use unauthorized copies of software, or

Make unauthorized copies of software for others.

If you have questions not answered by this brochure about the 
proper use and distribution of a software product, seek help from 
your computing office, the software developer or publisher, or 
other appropriate authorities at your institution.


This brochure has been produced as a service to the academic 
community by the Educational Uses of Information Technology 
Program (EUIT) of EDUCOM and the Information Technology 
Association of America (ITAA).  EDUCOM is a non-profit consortium 
of colleges and universities committed to the use and management 
of information technology in higher education.  ITAA is an 
industry association providing issues management and advocacy, 
public affairs, business-to-business networking, education and 
other member services to companies which create and market 
products and services associated with computers, communications 
and data.

Although this brochure is copyrighted, you are authorized and 
encouraged to make and distribute copies of it, in whole or in 
part, providing the source is acknowledged.  Additional copies of 
this brochure may be purchased by contacting one of the 
organizations listed below.

EDUCOM
1112 16th Street, NW
Suite 600
Washington, DC 20036
(202)872-4200

ITAA
1616 N. Fort Myer Drive, Suite 1300
Arlington, VA 22204
(703)284-5355

January, 1992
EDUCOM and ITAA


.&lt;/blockquote&gt;

This means, I can convert scar into an exe, and redistribute (as freeware) without his permission?</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 29 Oct 2007 09:13:31 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>General Discussion</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/freeware-copyright/155268.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Freeware Copyright</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@SomethingToHide STH]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/somethingtohide">@SomethingToHide</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote no-group" data-post="13" data-topic="155268">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 io9:</div>
<blockquote>
<p><span class="mention">@Seatch</span>: Oh, Congratulations! You have successfully used UPX [or other EXE packer]. How does this make you feel?</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Exactly what I was thinking.<br>
Some noob trying to bust his way into the scene by using a packer to make SCAR (already portable) into an extra portable version.</p>
<p>Nothing big.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/freeware-copyright/155268/15">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/freeware-copyright/155268/15</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 29 Oct 2007 09:13:31 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-155268-15</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/freeware-copyright/155268.rss">Freeware Copyright</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Freeware Copyright</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@PaulT PaulT]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/pault">@PaulT</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <blockquote>UNAUTHORIZED copying of software is illegal.  Copyright law
protects software authors and publishers, just as patent law
protects inventors.</blockquote>
<p>But not unethical, luckily.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/freeware-copyright/155268/14">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/freeware-copyright/155268/14</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 29 Oct 2007 07:03:40 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-155268-14</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/freeware-copyright/155268.rss">Freeware Copyright</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Freeware Copyright</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@ilyaostr9 io9]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/ilyaostr9">@ilyaostr9</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p><span class="mention">@Seatch</span>: Oh, Congratulations! You have successfully used UPX [or other EXE packer]. How does this make you feel?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/freeware-copyright/155268/13">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/freeware-copyright/155268/13</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 29 Oct 2007 06:31:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-155268-13</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/freeware-copyright/155268.rss">Freeware Copyright</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Freeware Copyright</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Search Search]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/search">@Search</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <blockquote>Redistribution and use in source and binary forms, with or without modification, are forbidden.</blockquote>
<p>^^ Even with all the legal mumojumbo I’m not going to redistribute scar without freddy1990’s permission. I doubt I’m going to get permission from him, but he may permit it, but not support downloading it.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/freeware-copyright/155268/12">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/freeware-copyright/155268/12</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 29 Oct 2007 06:06:27 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-155268-12</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/freeware-copyright/155268.rss">Freeware Copyright</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Freeware Copyright</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@xxlegitxx xxlegitxx]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/xxlegitxx">@xxlegitxx</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Oh nice.  Yea, definitely ask Freddy about it; I can’t imagine him flat-out denying permission.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/freeware-copyright/155268/11">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/freeware-copyright/155268/11</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 29 Oct 2007 06:05:48 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-155268-11</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/freeware-copyright/155268.rss">Freeware Copyright</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Freeware Copyright</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Search Search]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/search">@Search</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Yes, it’s very buggy, but I got it to work to some extent. (finding tree colors, clickpath, etc; basic stuff such as that).</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/freeware-copyright/155268/10">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/freeware-copyright/155268/10</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 29 Oct 2007 06:01:47 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-155268-10</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/freeware-copyright/155268.rss">Freeware Copyright</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Freeware Copyright</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@xxlegitxx xxlegitxx]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/xxlegitxx">@xxlegitxx</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote no-group" data-post="8" data-topic="155268">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/search/40/5_6bca9977b612b7aeef77ba1ec1cd67b3.png" class="avatar"> Search:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>It is 1 exe file.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>So all the includes, plugins, etc, are all self-contained in one exe file?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/freeware-copyright/155268/9">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/freeware-copyright/155268/9</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 29 Oct 2007 05:59:45 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-155268-9</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/freeware-copyright/155268.rss">Freeware Copyright</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Freeware Copyright</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Search Search]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/search">@Search</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I don’t know what that means, since it is freeware, not software. I need a lawyer <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/frowning.png?v=6" title=":frowning:" class="emoji" alt=":frowning:"></p>
<p>It is 1 exe file.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/freeware-copyright/155268/8">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/freeware-copyright/155268/8</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 29 Oct 2007 05:58:36 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-155268-8</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/freeware-copyright/155268.rss">Freeware Copyright</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Freeware Copyright</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@xxlegitxx xxlegitxx]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/xxlegitxx">@xxlegitxx</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote no-group quote-modified" data-post="6" data-topic="155268">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/search/40/5_6bca9977b612b7aeef77ba1ec1cd67b3.png" class="avatar"> Search:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>No, it’s an exe file. Clicking the exe opens scar without the need to install it. It’s a portable version that you can take anywhere, work school, usb, etc.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Is it one exe file or are there dlls and other files along with it?  What exactly did you do to create this mobile version?</p>
<p>Tell me exactly what this means to you:</p>
<blockquote>Redistribution and use in source and binary forms, with or without modification, are forbidden.</blockquote>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/freeware-copyright/155268/7">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/freeware-copyright/155268/7</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 29 Oct 2007 05:57:02 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-155268-7</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/freeware-copyright/155268.rss">Freeware Copyright</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Freeware Copyright</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Search Search]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/search">@Search</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“xxlegitxx, post:5, topic:155268”][quote author=Search link=topic=211978.msg1853219#msg1853219 date=1193637044]<br>
Without installation. Mobile scar still requires installation.<br>
[/quote]</p>
<p>So instead of installation, its a zip file?  Did you make any other changes?[/quote]</p>
<p>No, it’s an exe file. Clicking the exe opens scar without the need to install it. It’s a portable version that you can take anywhere, work school, usb, etc.</p>
<blockquote>Copyright (c) 2003-2007, Aivars Irmejs
All rights reserved.
<p>Redistribution and use in source and binary forms, with or without modification, are forbidden.</p>
<p>THIS SOFTWARE IS PROVIDED BY THE COPYRIGHT HOLDERS AND CONTRIBUTORS “AS IS” AND ANY EXPRESS OR IMPLIED WARRANTIES, INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, THE IMPLIED WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY AND FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE ARE DISCLAIMED. IN NO EVENT SHALL THE REGENTS OR CONTRIBUTORS BE LIABLE FOR ANY DIRECT, INDIRECT, INCIDENTAL, SPECIAL, EXEMPLARY, OR CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES (INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, PROCUREMENT OF SUBSTITUTE GOODS OR SERVICES; LOSS OF USE, DATA, OR PROFITS; OR BUSINESS INTERRUPTION) HOWEVER CAUSED AND ON ANY THEORY OF LIABILITY, WHETHER IN CONTRACT, STRICT LIABILITY, OR TORT (INCLUDING NEGLIGENCE OR OTHERWISE)</p>
</blockquote><br>
This is freeware though?
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/freeware-copyright/155268/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/freeware-copyright/155268/6</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 29 Oct 2007 05:55:06 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-155268-6</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/freeware-copyright/155268.rss">Freeware Copyright</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Freeware Copyright</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@xxlegitxx xxlegitxx]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/xxlegitxx">@xxlegitxx</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>So instead of installation, its a zip file?  Did you make any other changes?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/freeware-copyright/155268/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/freeware-copyright/155268/5</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 29 Oct 2007 05:51:38 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-155268-5</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/freeware-copyright/155268.rss">Freeware Copyright</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Freeware Copyright</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Search Search]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/search">@Search</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Without installation. Mobile scar still requires installation.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/freeware-copyright/155268/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/freeware-copyright/155268/4</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 29 Oct 2007 05:50:44 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-155268-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/freeware-copyright/155268.rss">Freeware Copyright</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Freeware Copyright</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@ilyaostr9 io9]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/ilyaostr9">@ilyaostr9</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>SCAR is already a compiled executable? %HomeDir%\Program Files\SCAR \SCAR.exe == an executabel binary (exe)</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/freeware-copyright/155268/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/freeware-copyright/155268/3</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 29 Oct 2007 05:49:46 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-155268-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/freeware-copyright/155268.rss">Freeware Copyright</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Freeware Copyright</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@xxlegitxx xxlegitxx]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/xxlegitxx">@xxlegitxx</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“Search, post:1, topic:155268”]I’ve posted this here, and on srl.</p>
<p>[…]</p>
<p>This means, I can convert scar into an exe, and redistribute (as freeware) without his permission?[/quote]</p>
<p>Technically you could I suppose.  But just ask for his permission for courtesy.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/freeware-copyright/155268/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/freeware-copyright/155268/2</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 29 Oct 2007 05:46:11 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-155268-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/freeware-copyright/155268.rss">Freeware Copyright</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Freeware Copyright</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Search Search]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/search">@Search</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I’ve posted this here, and on srl.</p>
<blockquote>Using Software: A Guide to the Ethical and Legal Use of Software 
for Members of the Academic Community
<p>Software enables us to accomplish many different tasks with<br>
computers.  Unfortunately, in order to get our work done quickly<br>
and conveniently, some people make and use unauthorized software<br>
copies.  The purpose of this brochure is to provide a brief<br>
outline of what you legally can and cannot do with software.<br>
Hopefully it will help you better understand the implications and<br>
restrictions of the U.S. Copyright Law.</p>
<h2>Here Are Some Relevant Facts:</h2>
<p>UNAUTHORIZED copying of software is illegal.  Copyright law<br>
protects software authors and publishers, just as patent law<br>
protects inventors.</p>
<p>UNAUTHORIZED copying of software by individuals can harm the<br>
entire academic community.  If unauthorized copying proliferates<br>
on a campus, the institution may incur legal liability.  Also, the<br>
institution may find it more difficult to negotiate agreements<br>
that would make software more widely and less expensively<br>
available to members of the academic community.</p>
<p>UNAUTHORIZED copying and use of software deprives publishers and<br>
developers of a fair return for their work, increases prices,<br>
reduces the level of future support and enhancements, and can<br>
inhibit the development of new software products.</p>
<p>RESPECT for the intellectual work of others has traditionally been<br>
essential to the mission of colleges and universities.  As members<br>
of the academic community, we value the free exchange of ideas.<br>
Just as we do not tolerate plagiarism, we do not condone the<br>
unauthorized copying of software, including programs,<br>
applications, data bases and code.</p>
<p>THEREFORE, we offer the following statement of principle about<br>
intellectual property and the legal and ethical use of software.</p>
<p>THE EDUCOM CODE</p>
<h1>Software and Intellectual Rights</h1>
<p>Respect for intellectual labor and creativity is vital to academic<br>
discourse and enterprise.  This principle applies to works of all<br>
authors and publishers in all media.  It encompasses respect for<br>
the right to acknowledgment, right to privacy, and right to<br>
determine the form, manner, and terms of publication and<br>
distribution.</p>
<p>Because electronic information is volatile and easily reproduced,<br>
respect for the work and personal expression of others is<br>
especially critical in computer environments.  Violations of<br>
authorial integrity, including plagiarism, invasion of privacy,<br>
unauthorized access, and trade secret and copyright violations,<br>
may be grounds for sanctions against members of the academic<br>
community.</p>
<p>EDUCOM’s Educational Uses of Information Technology (EUIT) Program<br>
encourages the broadest possible adoption of this statement of<br>
principle.  The EDUCOM Code is intended for adaptation and use by<br>
individuals, and educational institutions at all levels.</p>
<h1>Classification of Software</h1>
<p>In terms of copyright, there are four broad classifications of<br>
software:</p>
<p>Commercial<br>
Shareware<br>
Freeware<br>
Public Domain</p>
<p>The restrictions and limitations regarding each classification are<br>
different.</p>
<h2>COMMERCIAL</h2>
<p>COMMERCIAL software represents the majority of software purchased<br>
from software publishers, commercial computer stores, etc.  When<br>
you buy software, you are actually acquiring a license to use it,<br>
not own it.  You acquire the license from the company that owns<br>
the copyright.  The conditions and restrictions of the license<br>
agreement vary from program to program and should be read<br>
carefully.  In general, commercial software licenses stipulate<br>
that ( 1 ) the software is covered by copyright, (2) although one<br>
archival copy of the software can be made, the backup copy cannot<br>
be used except when the original package fails or is destroyed,<br>
(3) modifications to the software are not allowed, (4) decompiling<br>
(i.e. reverse engineering) of the program code is not allowed<br>
without the permission of the copyright holder, and (5)<br>
development of new works built upon the package (derivative works)<br>
is not allowed without the permission of the copyright holder.</p>
<h2>SHAREWARE</h2>
<p>SHAREWARE software is covered by copyright, as well.  When you<br>
acquire software under a shareware arrangement, you are actually<br>
acquiring a license to use it, not own it.  You acquire the<br>
license, from the individual or company that owns the copyright.<br>
The conditions and restrictions of the license agreement vary from<br>
program to program and should be read carefully.  The copyright<br>
holders for SHAREWARE allow purchasers to make and distribute<br>
copies of the software, but demand that if, after testing the<br>
software, you adopt it for use, you must pay for it.  In general,<br>
shareware, software licenses stipulate that (1) the software is<br>
covered by copyright, (2) although one archival copy of the<br>
software can be made, the backup copy cannot be used except when<br>
the original package fails or is destroyed, (3) modifications to<br>
the software are not allowed, (4) decompiling (i.e. reverse<br>
engineering) of the program code is not allowed without the<br>
permission of the copyright holder, and (5) development of new<br>
works built upon the package (derivative works) is not allowed<br>
without the permission of the copyright holder.  Selling software<br>
as SHAREWARE is a marketing decision, it does not change the legal<br>
requirements with respect to copyright.  That means that you can<br>
make a single archival copy, but you are obliged to pay for all<br>
copies adopted for use.</p>
<h2>FREEWARE</h2>
<h2>FREEWARE also is covered by copyright and subject to the<br>
conditions defined by the holder of the copyright.  The conditions<br>
for FREEWARE are in direct opposition to normal copyright<br>
restrictions.  In general, FREEWARE software licenses stipulate<br>
that (1) the software is covered by copyright, (2) copies of the<br>
software can be made for both archival and distribution purposes<br>
but that distribution cannot be for profit, (3) modifications to<br>
the software is allowed and encouraged, (4) decompiling (i.e.<br>
reverse engineering) of the program code is allowed without the<br>
explicit permission of the copyright holder, and (6) development<br>
of new works built upon the package (derivative works) is allowed<br>
and encouraged with the condition that derivative works must also<br>
be designated as FREEWARE.  That means that you cannot take<br>
FREEWARE, modify or extend it, and then sell it as COMMERCIAL or<br>
SHAREWARE software.<br>
PUBLIC DOMAIN</h2>
<p>PUBLIC DOMAIN software comes into being when the original<br>
copyright holder explicitly relinquishes all rights to the<br>
software.  Since under current copyright law, all intellectual<br>
works (including software) are protected as soon as they are<br>
committed to a medium, for something to be PUBLIC DOMAIN it must<br>
be clearly marked as such.  Before March 1, 1989, it was assumed<br>
that intellectual works were NOT covered by copyright unless the<br>
copyright symbol and declaration appeared on the work.  With the<br>
U.S. adherence to the Berne Convention this presumption has been<br>
reversed.  Now all works assume copyright protection unless the<br>
PUBLIC DOMAIN notification is stated.  This means that for PUBLIC<br>
DOMAIN software (1) copyright rights have been relinquished, (2)<br>
software copies can be made for both archival and distribution<br>
purposes with no restrictions as to distribution, (3)<br>
modifications to the software are allowed, (4) decompiling (i.e.<br>
reverse engineering) of the program code is allowed, and (5)<br>
development of new works built upon the package (derivative works)<br>
is allowed without conditions on the distribution or use of the<br>
derivative work.</p>
<h1>Questions You May Have About Using Software</h1>
<p>What do I need to know about software and the U.S. Copyright Act?</p>
<p>It’s really very simple.  The Copyright Law recognizes that all<br>
intellectual works (programs, data, pictures, articles, books,<br>
etc.) are automatically covered by copyright unless it is<br>
explicitly noted to the contrary.  That means that the owner of a<br>
copyright holds the exclusive right to reproduce and distribute<br>
his or her work.  For software this means it is illegal to copy or<br>
distribute software, or its documentation, without the permission<br>
of the copyright holder.</p>
<p>If you have a legal copy of software you are allowed to make a<br>
single archival copy of the software for backup purposes.<br>
However, the copy can only be used if the original software is<br>
destroyed or fails to work.  When the original is given away, the<br>
backup copy must also be given with the original or destroyed.</p>
<p>If software is not copy-protected, do I have the right to copy it?</p>
<p>Lack of copy-protection does NOT constitute permission to copy<br>
software without authorization of the software copyright owner.<br>
“Non-copy-protected” software enables you to make a backup copy.<br>
In offering non-copy-protected software to you, the developer or<br>
publisher has demonstrated significant trust in your integrity.</p>
<p>May I copy software that is available through facilities on my<br>
campus, so that I can use it more conveniently in my own office or<br>
room?</p>
<p>Software acquired by colleges and universities is usually covered<br>
by licenses.  The licenses should clearly state how and where the<br>
software may be legally used by members of the relevant campus<br>
communities (faculty, staff, and students).  Such licenses cover<br>
software whether installed on stand-alone or networked systems,<br>
whether in private offices and rooms, or in public clusters and<br>
laboratories.  Some institutional licenses permit copying for<br>
certain purposes.  The license may limit copying, as well.<br>
Consult your campus authorities to be sure if you are unsure about<br>
the permissible use of a particular software product.</p>
<p>May I loan software?</p>
<p>The 1990 modification to the Copyright Law makes it illegal to<br>
“loan, lease or rent software” for purposes of direct or indirect<br>
commercial advantage without the specific permission of the<br>
copyright holder.  Non-profit educational institutions are<br>
exempted from the 1990 modification, so institutional software may<br>
be loaned.</p>
<p>Some licenses may even restrict the use of a copy to a specific<br>
machine, even if you own more than one system.  In general,<br>
licenses usually do NOT allow the software to be installed or<br>
resident on more than a single machine, or to run the software<br>
simultaneously on two or more machines.</p>
<p>Isn’t it legally “fair use” to copy software if the purpose in<br>
sharing it is purely educational?</p>
<p>Historically, the Copyright Law was modified to permit certain<br>
educational uses of copyrighted materials without the usual<br>
copyright restrictions.  However, “fair use” of computer software<br>
is still a cloudy issue.  The “fair use” amendments to the<br>
copyright law are intended to allow educational use of legally<br>
protected products, but it is limited (for paper-based products)<br>
to small portions of full works.  For most software it is clearly<br>
illegal to make and distribute unauthorized, fully-functional<br>
copies to class members for their individual use.  Making copies<br>
of a small section of code from a program in order to illustrate a<br>
programming technique might not be a violation.  The best<br>
alternative is to clear any such use with the copyright owner or<br>
consult the appropriate authorities at your institution.</p>
<h1>Alternatives To Explore</h1>
<p>Software can be expensive.  You may think that you cannot afford<br>
to purchase certain programs that you need.  Site-licensed and<br>
bulk purchased software are legal alternatives that make multiple<br>
copies of software more affordable.  Many educational institutions<br>
negotiate special prices for software used and purchased by<br>
faculty, staff and students.  Consult your campus computing office<br>
for information.  As with other software, site-licensed or bulk<br>
purchased software is still covered by copyright, although the<br>
price per copy may be significantly lower than the normal<br>
commercial price.  A usual condition of site-licensing or bulk-<br>
purchasing is that copying and distribution of the software is<br>
limited to a central office which must maintain inventories of who<br>
received it.  When you leave the academic community by graduation,<br>
retirement, or resignation you may no longer be covered by the<br>
institutional agreement and may be required to return or destroy<br>
your copies of the software licensed to the institution.</p>
<p>Many colleges sell software through a campus store at “educational<br>
discounts.”  If you purchase software for yourself through such an<br>
outlet, the software is yours and need not be destroyed or<br>
surrendered when you leave the institution.  It is, however, still<br>
covered by normal copyright protection and covered by the specific<br>
conditions of the licensing agreement.</p>
<h1>A Final Note</h1>
<p>Restrictions on the use of software are far from uniform.  You<br>
should check carefully each piece of software and the accompanying<br>
documentation yourself.  In general, you do not have the right to:</p>
<p>Receive and use unauthorized copies of software, or</p>
<p>Make unauthorized copies of software for others.</p>
<p>If you have questions not answered by this brochure about the<br>
proper use and distribution of a software product, seek help from<br>
your computing office, the software developer or publisher, or<br>
other appropriate authorities at your institution.</p>
<p>This brochure has been produced as a service to the academic<br>
community by the Educational Uses of Information Technology<br>
Program (EUIT) of EDUCOM and the Information Technology<br>
Association of America (ITAA).  EDUCOM is a non-profit consortium<br>
of colleges and universities committed to the use and management<br>
of information technology in higher education.  ITAA is an<br>
industry association providing issues management and advocacy,<br>
public affairs, business-to-business networking, education and<br>
other member services to companies which create and market<br>
products and services associated with computers, communications<br>
and data.</p>
<p>Although this brochure is copyrighted, you are authorized and<br>
encouraged to make and distribute copies of it, in whole or in<br>
part, providing the source is acknowledged.  Additional copies of<br>
this brochure may be purchased by contacting one of the<br>
organizations listed below.</p>
<p>EDUCOM<br>
1112 16th Street, NW<br>
Suite 600<br>
Washington, DC 20036<br>
(202)872-4200</p>
<p>ITAA<br>
1616 N. Fort Myer Drive, Suite 1300<br>
Arlington, VA 22204<br>
(703)284-5355</p>
<p>January, 1992<br>
EDUCOM and ITAA</p>
<p>.</p>
</blockquote>
<p>This means, I can convert scar into an exe, and redistribute (as freeware) without his permission?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/freeware-copyright/155268/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/freeware-copyright/155268/1</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 29 Oct 2007 05:41:54 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-155268-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/freeware-copyright/155268.rss">Freeware Copyright</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
