<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>[Urgent] (NDE) NPC Definitions? [Dementhium][639]</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/urgent-nde-npc-definitions-dementhium-639/438375</link>
    <description>Hello, I have ... Not necissarily an issue but a question i would like to address..
I&#39;ve Modified some NPC definitions and saved them but when i restarted my server, nothing changed in them. Am i suppose to compile with NetBeans? If so... Is there a tutorial on how/what i should implement in the sources and etc... If not what do i have to do? Which file would i have to move, what would i have to compile, or basically anything else i would have to do, after modifying, saving and closing the program, i am very lost and i&#39;ve been trying to figure this out for about 3 days now... So i have resorted to the Server Help section... I guess i cannot do everything on my own... If somebody can help me or walk me through it etc... That would be wonderful. I really, really, need this.

Thank you for your attention, have a great day.
- M.I.A.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 03 Apr 2012 19:43:34 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/urgent-nde-npc-definitions-dementhium-639/438375.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>[Urgent] (NDE) NPC Definitions? [Dementhium][639]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@M.I.A M.I.A.]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/m.i.a">@M.I.A</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Hello, I have … Not necissarily an issue but a question i would like to address…<br>
I’ve Modified some NPC definitions and saved them but when i restarted my server, nothing changed in them. Am i suppose to compile with NetBeans? If so… Is there a tutorial on how/what i should implement in the sources and etc… If not what do i have to do? Which file would i have to move, what would i have to compile, or basically anything else i would have to do, after modifying, saving and closing the program, i am very lost and i’ve been trying to figure this out for about 3 days now… So i have resorted to the Server Help section… I guess i cannot do everything on my own… If somebody can help me or walk me through it etc… That would be wonderful. I really, really, need this.</p>
<p>Thank you for your attention, have a great day.</p>
<ul>
<li>M.I.A.</li>
</ul>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/urgent-nde-npc-definitions-dementhium-639/438375/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/urgent-nde-npc-definitions-dementhium-639/438375/1</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 03 Apr 2012 19:43:34 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-438375-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/urgent-nde-npc-definitions-dementhium-639/438375.rss">[Urgent] (NDE) NPC Definitions? [Dementhium][639]</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
