<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Coders needed! - PHP / Java / XHTML, inquire within</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/coders-needed-php-java-xhtml-inquire-within/71968</link>
    <description>[center][b]JaGOS - Java Gameserver Operating System[/b][/center]

[b]Background / Information:[/b] JaGOS&#39; aim is to be a database-driven server, the database being mySQL. &quot;Back in the day&quot;, servers were often backended by such mySQL, but this has been diminishing due to &quot;lag&quot; problems. The benefit of mySQL, however, is easily manageable data in a stable environment. You don&#39;t need to toil through a page and a half of gibberish in a data file, when you can open up one of any number of mySQL editors, search for the row you need and be able to edit it quickly and painlessly!

The problem often lied not in the minute lag the backend produced, but in having to install mySQL to run it. JaGOS plans to integrate the mySQL server with the database files readily installed into it. Start it up and away you go, right out of the box!

[u]But why mySQL?[/u] The answer is quite simple: efficiency.  What logical sense is there in a million lines at the bottom of a file generating text when a function can be used to steamline the process?  Any good programmer will tell you: there is no sense in it.  All it takes - all it really needs to take - is one function to load a speech window.  Another to load a character.  Another to load an NPC.  Instead of defining, stating, scripting, and writing everything in one file, you can write a few functions to grab and process to it from a database. A quickly shortened and more organized script is the result.

[u]Open Source.[/u] We will be asking users of the software to actively contribute in bug reporting and testing while they use the software.  Testing is simple - just use the program, and in your using it you will be testing it!  Documentation will (eventually) be provided so everyone may edit at whim and customize the server base to be truely theirs.

[u]What is in a name (JaGOS)?[/u] The approach behind JaGOS is a new, fresh look at the server world.  It avoids any copyright infringements ([i]Ja[/i]va [i]G[/i]ameserver [i]O[/i]perating [i]S[/i]ystem - it&#39;s designed as a Java game server, but it just [i]happens[/i] to work with Runescape, so so be it!).  It will be built with stability and performance in mind.

[u]The goal?[/u] Simply put - to build a fully-functioning, easily modified, official-like server. And learn along the way.

[b]What I am looking for:[/b]

[ul][li][b]Java Programmers (5(ish) people):[/b] Java programmers will be necessary for the actual building of the server. Primary focus will be core functions and processes, not spawning or creating NPCs / text or any other additionals like those. _IMPORTANT_: by &quot;Java programmers&quot;, I [u]mean[/u] Java programmers, people who can readily code in the language.  People who look at a tutorial in the Tutorials section, flip around code and combine it with four other tuts, change the wording and release isn&#39;t what I am looking for.[/li]
[li][b]Web / MySQL Developers (2 people):[/b] These folks will be in charge of developing the Website included with the software.  XHTML / CSSknowledge is a MUST, PHP is a definite plus, and graphics are another big boost.[/li][/ul]


[b]Information / Clarification:[/b]
In about a week I will make the core available to staff.  It is an old Scape revision.  It will come with Apache and mySQL readily installed, all you will have to do is boot it up and run.  Speak with the programmers of your division and me with your ideas and work to realize them.

[b]&quot;Job&quot; requirements:[/b]

[ul][li][b]STRONG ENGLISH SKILLS[/b] - a must. You will be required to make comments in the program of your changes and revisions (IE, // Streamlined the text load process, it will now...).  If you are prone to spelling mistakes, please make sure you read and reread what you type for clarity and proper language conventions as it will not just be staff who read the comments but also users of the software.  Similarly, I do not want to talk to an NPC just to be asked &quot;can i hlp u ?&quot;.  You only have to type it once - please type it right.[/li]
[li][b]Actual knowledge of what you&#39;re doing...[/b] - If you&#39;re applying to this I am going to trust that you know what you&#39;re talking about.  I realize this is a big risk, but for the majority of the users on this forum you are old enough to be able to think for yourselves and not be baby-sat.  If you apply, please ensure you actually intend to follow these requirements.[/li]
[li][b]Ability and willingness to communicate and work[/b] - Another must. It&#39;s pretty self-explanitory.  I realize it&#39;s free and open source and whatnot, but if you&#39;re going to apply to the core dev team, for God&#39;s sake, please at least have the initiative to work and help.  If you don&#39;t you&#39;ll just be removed, it&#39;s quite simple.[/li][/ul]


[b]Interested?[/b]
If this has caught your eye and you want to get involved, please send me a private message outlining why you would be a wise choice for the JaGOS team.  No specific template, it just needs to be 3 sentences (1 paragraphs) long.  Grammar and spelling WILL be a deciding factor, so please make sure you get them down pat.

At any rate, thanks for your time folks.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2009 00:45:25 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/coders-needed-php-java-xhtml-inquire-within/71968.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Coders needed! - PHP / Java / XHTML, inquire within</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@19spartan94 19spartan94]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/19spartan94">@19spartan94</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I am a PHP and JAVA programmer i can also do mySQL and XHTML email me at <a href="mailto:jilynch4430@hotmail.com">jilynch4430@hotmail.com</a> or <a href="mailto:spartan@urbanassassins.org">spartan@urbanassassins.org</a></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/coders-needed-php-java-xhtml-inquire-within/71968/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/coders-needed-php-java-xhtml-inquire-within/71968/3</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2009 00:45:25 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-71968-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/coders-needed-php-java-xhtml-inquire-within/71968.rss">Coders needed! - PHP / Java / XHTML, inquire within</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Coders needed! - PHP / Java / XHTML, inquire within</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@vartankid vartankid]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/vartankid">@vartankid</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Sounds like a good idea. Say, if you need any help, talk to me in messenger [yahoo=rla_java <a href="mailto:msn=jtooltip@rs2codes.com">msn=jtooltip@rs2codes.com</a>] or talk to me here[Message the user ThatOneServer, i cant use him atm so I’m on a dummy account.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/coders-needed-php-java-xhtml-inquire-within/71968/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/coders-needed-php-java-xhtml-inquire-within/71968/2</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 29 Jun 2007 06:07:14 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-71968-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/coders-needed-php-java-xhtml-inquire-within/71968.rss">Coders needed! - PHP / Java / XHTML, inquire within</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Coders needed! - PHP / Java / XHTML, inquire within</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Phore Phore]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/phore">@Phore</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[center]<span class="bbcode-b">JaGOS - Java Gameserver Operating System</span>[/center]</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Background / Information:</span> JaGOS’ aim is to be a database-driven server, the database being mySQL. “Back in the day”, servers were often backended by such mySQL, but this has been diminishing due to “lag” problems. The benefit of mySQL, however, is easily manageable data in a stable environment. You don’t need to toil through a page and a half of gibberish in a data file, when you can open up one of any number of mySQL editors, search for the row you need and be able to edit it quickly and painlessly!</p>
<p>The problem often lied not in the minute lag the backend produced, but in having to install mySQL to run it. JaGOS plans to integrate the mySQL server with the database files readily installed into it. Start it up and away you go, right out of the box!</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-u">But why mySQL?</span> The answer is quite simple: efficiency.  What logical sense is there in a million lines at the bottom of a file generating text when a function can be used to steamline the process?  Any good programmer will tell you: there is no sense in it.  All it takes - all it really needs to take - is one function to load a speech window.  Another to load a character.  Another to load an NPC.  Instead of defining, stating, scripting, and writing everything in one file, you can write a few functions to grab and process to it from a database. A quickly shortened and more organized script is the result.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-u">Open Source.</span> We will be asking users of the software to actively contribute in bug reporting and testing while they use the software.  Testing is simple - just use the program, and in your using it you will be testing it!  Documentation will (eventually) be provided so everyone may edit at whim and customize the server base to be truely theirs.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-u">What is in a name (JaGOS)?</span> The approach behind JaGOS is a new, fresh look at the server world.  It avoids any copyright infringements (<span class="bbcode-i">Ja</span>va <span class="bbcode-i">G</span>ameserver <span class="bbcode-i">O</span>perating <span class="bbcode-i">S</span>ystem - it’s designed as a Java game server, but it just <span class="bbcode-i">happens</span> to work with Runescape, so so be it!).  It will be built with stability and performance in mind.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-u">The goal?</span> Simply put - to build a fully-functioning, easily modified, official-like server. And learn along the way.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">What I am looking for:</span></p>
<p>[ul][li]<span class="bbcode-b">Java Programmers (5(ish) people):</span> Java programmers will be necessary for the actual building of the server. Primary focus will be core functions and processes, not spawning or creating NPCs / text or any other additionals like those. <em>IMPORTANT</em>: by “Java programmers”, I <span class="bbcode-u">mean</span> Java programmers, people who can readily code in the language.  People who look at a tutorial in the Tutorials section, flip around code and combine it with four other tuts, change the wording and release isn’t what I am looking for.[/li]<br>
[li]<span class="bbcode-b">Web / MySQL Developers (2 people):</span> These folks will be in charge of developing the Website included with the software.  XHTML / CSSknowledge is a MUST, PHP is a definite plus, and graphics are another big boost.[/li][/ul]</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Information / Clarification:</span><br>
In about a week I will make the core available to staff.  It is an old Scape revision.  It will come with Apache and mySQL readily installed, all you will have to do is boot it up and run.  Speak with the programmers of your division and me with your ideas and work to realize them.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">“Job” requirements:</span></p>
<p>[ul][li]<span class="bbcode-b">STRONG ENGLISH SKILLS</span> - a must. You will be required to make comments in the program of your changes and revisions (IE, // Streamlined the text load process, it will now…).  If you are prone to spelling mistakes, please make sure you read and reread what you type for clarity and proper language conventions as it will not just be staff who read the comments but also users of the software.  Similarly, I do not want to talk to an NPC just to be asked “can i hlp u ?”.  You only have to type it once - please type it right.[/li]<br>
[li]<span class="bbcode-b">Actual knowledge of what you’re doing…</span> - If you’re applying to this I am going to trust that you know what you’re talking about.  I realize this is a big risk, but for the majority of the users on this forum you are old enough to be able to think for yourselves and not be baby-sat.  If you apply, please ensure you actually intend to follow these requirements.[/li]<br>
[li]<span class="bbcode-b">Ability and willingness to communicate and work</span> - Another must. It’s pretty self-explanitory.  I realize it’s free and open source and whatnot, but if you’re going to apply to the core dev team, for God’s sake, please at least have the initiative to work and help.  If you don’t you’ll just be removed, it’s quite simple.[/li][/ul]</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Interested?</span><br>
If this has caught your eye and you want to get involved, please send me a private message outlining why you would be a wise choice for the JaGOS team.  No specific template, it just needs to be 3 sentences (1 paragraphs) long.  Grammar and spelling WILL be a deciding factor, so please make sure you get them down pat.</p>
<p>At any rate, thanks for your time folks.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/coders-needed-php-java-xhtml-inquire-within/71968/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/coders-needed-php-java-xhtml-inquire-within/71968/1</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 29 Mar 2007 00:43:53 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-71968-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/coders-needed-php-java-xhtml-inquire-within/71968.rss">Coders needed! - PHP / Java / XHTML, inquire within</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
