<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>[VERY NSFW]Charger&#39;s Fists of Fury:An L4D2 love story</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/very-nsfw-chargers-fists-of-fury-an-l4d2-love-story/340425</link>
    <description>It had been a slow, relentless day. It was full of boring, uneventful tasks. Days like this came often in this barren, soul-sucked world. No longer were there survivors to charge. Charger missed hearing their screams as he pounded them into the ground, never failing to break at least five bones with each pound. No matter the pleas, he never gave mercy, never relented. Unfortunately, there was a shortage of that as of late. The number of survivors had dwindled down. Constantly had he rushed to the scent of fresh, delicious vomit, only to find--to his utter dismay--that Boomer was having Acid Reflux problems again. It was making him frustrated, the lack of releasing his anger at the world. And he was, indeed, angry. He was hateful of the survivors--how dare they shoot at us?! He thought, with disgust at their puny little forms. They thought they were better than his people, even though they were cowardly and stupid. They shot at a man simply eating a cow corpse, because he so much as looked at them. They thought they ruled this godforsaken world, but they didn&#39;t.

He was also angry at his wife. She was such a weak person, like the survivors. She had no courage--always running away at the slightest bit of danger, afraid to run into the heat of battle and die for a noble cause. His people always said that she was the most like the humans of all of them. It was true. She had kept her slender form that her former self had obtained through countless years of watching its weight. Stupid humans, he thought. Why should they care about how large they got? Did they not understand that the larger they were, the more pain they could inflict should they ram their opponents at top speed? No, they wanted to purposefully be slender and weak. It was because of this that he got his wife, so misshapen and barren of strength. She did, however, offer a huge tactical advantage. She could spit acid at enemies, blocking their paths and melting them into oblivion. However, she didn&#39;t last long in a battle--so she stayed at home, wasting away as time went on. Although...her perky body was looking very fine right about now...


He got up from his couch and went over to his wife. She looked up, surprised that she was about to have a conversation with him. They hadn&#39;t really talked in months! He was always too busy working. She opened her mouth, prepared to reprimand him for his actions of late, when suddenly a fist slammed at her ear from the side, tearing it off. She screamed in pain, confused as to what had just happened. She felt herself being turned over as Charger removed any clothes she had scavenged from the humans. She begged, pleaded with Charger not to do this, but he persisted in his removal of the clothes. In a few minutes, all clothes were removed. His dick was already hard. He was excited about what was to come. He slammed his dick into her vagina, pumping huge thrusts as she screamed in pain. His dick was much too massive for it, so she was bleeding profusely. Charger gained a burst of energy from each droplet of blood. It was pouring directly into his urethra, feeding him with adrenaline. She attempted to claw at him, but her scratches had no affect. Charger continued to slam his dick into her bloody vagina, until it was too large to provide any friction against his massive, sopping dick. He looke around for other holes he could fuck. He noticed her ear was missing.


He grabbed spitter&#39;s head and slammed it onto the ground, causing her to scream in extreme pain. He laughed maniacally as he slammed his dick into her ear, tickling her skull. He was pumping so vigorously that her skull began to crack, pouring brain juices out from every hole. He screamed in pleasure, ramming harder and harder until her skull broke open, releasing a torrent of fluid. He bent down and lapped up the fluid, moaning in delight. He sucked up all of the fluid into his body, then puked into her head, all while she screamed in terror and pain. After this was done, she still demanded more! He slammed her onto her back and spread her legs, aiming his dick at her tiny, petite clitoris. Then he paused. Instead of slamming his dick into her clit, he instead shot his dick straight into it, causing her to scream so loudly that her vocal chords bled, choking her. Luckily, his people didn&#39;t need air or even a brain to live. His hand pumped vigorously inside her clit, spreading it to proportions no one has ever seen. She cried, experiencing a pain no one had ever thought possible. His hand continued to pump, until finally he had torn a hole so big that it was possible to stick his head into her clit. He still wanted more, though, so he grabbed her head yet again and began to shove his dick into her mouth. She tried to cry, but her blood was still choking her of air. She could only sit silently as he slammed his cock down into her mouth, moaning in pleasure. As he began to cum, Spitter&#39;s acid reflux began acting up. She shot a load onto his dick right as he was exploding cum from his dick. He screamed in pain, slamming against the wall from shock. He staggered around, trying to wipe the acid off his eroding dick. It was to no avail. His penis was slowly falling off his body, exposing muscle. He began to pass out, just as his penis fell off.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 19 May 2010 03:02:43 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>General Discussion</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/very-nsfw-chargers-fists-of-fury-an-l4d2-love-story/340425.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>[VERY NSFW]Charger&#39;s Fists of Fury:An L4D2 love story</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@geel9 geel9]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/geel9">@geel9</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote no-group" data-post="10" data-topic="340425">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/user_avatar/forum.moparisthebest.com/mopman/40/33_1.png" class="avatar"> Mopman:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>i came multiple times</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>So did the charger.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/very-nsfw-chargers-fists-of-fury-an-l4d2-love-story/340425/11">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/very-nsfw-chargers-fists-of-fury-an-l4d2-love-story/340425/11</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 19 May 2010 03:02:43 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-340425-11</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/very-nsfw-chargers-fists-of-fury-an-l4d2-love-story/340425.rss">[VERY NSFW]Charger&#39;s Fists of Fury:An L4D2 love story</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[VERY NSFW]Charger&#39;s Fists of Fury:An L4D2 love story</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Mopman Mopman]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/mopman">@Mopman</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>i came multiple times</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/very-nsfw-chargers-fists-of-fury-an-l4d2-love-story/340425/10">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/very-nsfw-chargers-fists-of-fury-an-l4d2-love-story/340425/10</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 18 May 2010 20:28:22 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-340425-10</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/very-nsfw-chargers-fists-of-fury-an-l4d2-love-story/340425.rss">[VERY NSFW]Charger&#39;s Fists of Fury:An L4D2 love story</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[VERY NSFW]Charger&#39;s Fists of Fury:An L4D2 love story</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@lawl lawl]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/lawl">@lawl</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>this is sfw</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/very-nsfw-chargers-fists-of-fury-an-l4d2-love-story/340425/9">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/very-nsfw-chargers-fists-of-fury-an-l4d2-love-story/340425/9</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 18 May 2010 19:43:09 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-340425-9</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/very-nsfw-chargers-fists-of-fury-an-l4d2-love-story/340425.rss">[VERY NSFW]Charger&#39;s Fists of Fury:An L4D2 love story</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[VERY NSFW]Charger&#39;s Fists of Fury:An L4D2 love story</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@geel9 geel9]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/geel9">@geel9</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote no-group" data-post="7" data-topic="340425">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 Newty:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Awesome, a former runescape cheater has finaly decided to do something useful with his time!</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I never cheated at runescape <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=5" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/very-nsfw-chargers-fists-of-fury-an-l4d2-love-story/340425/8">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/very-nsfw-chargers-fists-of-fury-an-l4d2-love-story/340425/8</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 18 May 2010 19:02:15 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-340425-8</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/very-nsfw-chargers-fists-of-fury-an-l4d2-love-story/340425.rss">[VERY NSFW]Charger&#39;s Fists of Fury:An L4D2 love story</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[VERY NSFW]Charger&#39;s Fists of Fury:An L4D2 love story</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@NewbieNewty Newty]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/newbienewty">@NewbieNewty</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Awesome, a former runescape cheater has finaly decided to do something useful with his time!</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/very-nsfw-chargers-fists-of-fury-an-l4d2-love-story/340425/7">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/very-nsfw-chargers-fists-of-fury-an-l4d2-love-story/340425/7</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 18 May 2010 17:54:22 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-340425-7</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/very-nsfw-chargers-fists-of-fury-an-l4d2-love-story/340425.rss">[VERY NSFW]Charger&#39;s Fists of Fury:An L4D2 love story</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[VERY NSFW]Charger&#39;s Fists of Fury:An L4D2 love story</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@geel9 geel9]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/geel9">@geel9</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote no-group" data-post="5" data-topic="340425">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/frell/40/5_513041d5f7104045db30895d3b90af16.png" class="avatar"> Frell:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Kickass, who wrote it?</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>…</p>
<p>Me.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/very-nsfw-chargers-fists-of-fury-an-l4d2-love-story/340425/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/very-nsfw-chargers-fists-of-fury-an-l4d2-love-story/340425/6</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 18 May 2010 04:57:31 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-340425-6</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/very-nsfw-chargers-fists-of-fury-an-l4d2-love-story/340425.rss">[VERY NSFW]Charger&#39;s Fists of Fury:An L4D2 love story</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[VERY NSFW]Charger&#39;s Fists of Fury:An L4D2 love story</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Frell Frell]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/frell">@Frell</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Kickass, who wrote it?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/very-nsfw-chargers-fists-of-fury-an-l4d2-love-story/340425/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/very-nsfw-chargers-fists-of-fury-an-l4d2-love-story/340425/5</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 18 May 2010 03:01:37 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-340425-5</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/very-nsfw-chargers-fists-of-fury-an-l4d2-love-story/340425.rss">[VERY NSFW]Charger&#39;s Fists of Fury:An L4D2 love story</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[VERY NSFW]Charger&#39;s Fists of Fury:An L4D2 love story</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Speljohan Speljohan]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/speljohan">@Speljohan</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>That was awesome.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/very-nsfw-chargers-fists-of-fury-an-l4d2-love-story/340425/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/very-nsfw-chargers-fists-of-fury-an-l4d2-love-story/340425/4</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 18 May 2010 03:00:52 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-340425-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/very-nsfw-chargers-fists-of-fury-an-l4d2-love-story/340425.rss">[VERY NSFW]Charger&#39;s Fists of Fury:An L4D2 love story</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[VERY NSFW]Charger&#39;s Fists of Fury:An L4D2 love story</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Natey Natey]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/natey">@Natey</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>you need some help man…</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/very-nsfw-chargers-fists-of-fury-an-l4d2-love-story/340425/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/very-nsfw-chargers-fists-of-fury-an-l4d2-love-story/340425/3</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 17 May 2010 23:43:15 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-340425-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/very-nsfw-chargers-fists-of-fury-an-l4d2-love-story/340425.rss">[VERY NSFW]Charger&#39;s Fists of Fury:An L4D2 love story</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[VERY NSFW]Charger&#39;s Fists of Fury:An L4D2 love story</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@the_bank the bank]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/the_bank">@the_bank</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>You are seriously fucked.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/very-nsfw-chargers-fists-of-fury-an-l4d2-love-story/340425/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/very-nsfw-chargers-fists-of-fury-an-l4d2-love-story/340425/2</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 17 May 2010 23:40:04 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-340425-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/very-nsfw-chargers-fists-of-fury-an-l4d2-love-story/340425.rss">[VERY NSFW]Charger&#39;s Fists of Fury:An L4D2 love story</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[VERY NSFW]Charger&#39;s Fists of Fury:An L4D2 love story</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@geel9 geel9]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/geel9">@geel9</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>It had been a slow, relentless day. It was full of boring, uneventful tasks. Days like this came often in this barren, soul-sucked world. No longer were there survivors to charge. Charger missed hearing their screams as he pounded them into the ground, never failing to break at least five bones with each pound. No matter the pleas, he never gave mercy, never relented. Unfortunately, there was a shortage of that as of late. The number of survivors had dwindled down. Constantly had he rushed to the scent of fresh, delicious vomit, only to find–to his utter dismay–that Boomer was having Acid Reflux problems again. It was making him frustrated, the lack of releasing his anger at the world. And he was, indeed, angry. He was hateful of the survivors–how dare they shoot at us?! He thought, with disgust at their puny little forms. They thought they were better than his people, even though they were cowardly and stupid. They shot at a man simply eating a cow corpse, because he so much as looked at them. They thought they ruled this godforsaken world, but they didn’t.</p>
<p>He was also angry at his wife. She was such a weak person, like the survivors. She had no courage–always running away at the slightest bit of danger, afraid to run into the heat of battle and die for a noble cause. His people always said that she was the most like the humans of all of them. It was true. She had kept her slender form that her former self had obtained through countless years of watching its weight. Stupid humans, he thought. Why should they care about how large they got? Did they not understand that the larger they were, the more pain they could inflict should they ram their opponents at top speed? No, they wanted to purposefully be slender and weak. It was because of this that he got his wife, so misshapen and barren of strength. She did, however, offer a huge tactical advantage. She could spit acid at enemies, blocking their paths and melting them into oblivion. However, she didn’t last long in a battle–so she stayed at home, wasting away as time went on. Although…her perky body was looking very fine right about now…</p>
<p>He got up from his couch and went over to his wife. She looked up, surprised that she was about to have a conversation with him. They hadn’t really talked in months! He was always too busy working. She opened her mouth, prepared to reprimand him for his actions of late, when suddenly a fist slammed at her ear from the side, tearing it off. She screamed in pain, confused as to what had just happened. She felt herself being turned over as Charger removed any clothes she had scavenged from the humans. She begged, pleaded with Charger not to do this, but he persisted in his removal of the clothes. In a few minutes, all clothes were removed. His dick was already hard. He was excited about what was to come. He slammed his dick into her vagina, pumping huge thrusts as she screamed in pain. His dick was much too massive for it, so she was bleeding profusely. Charger gained a burst of energy from each droplet of blood. It was pouring directly into his urethra, feeding him with adrenaline. She attempted to claw at him, but her scratches had no affect. Charger continued to slam his dick into her bloody vagina, until it was too large to provide any friction against his massive, sopping dick. He looke around for other holes he could fuck. He noticed her ear was missing.</p>
<p>He grabbed spitter’s head and slammed it onto the ground, causing her to scream in extreme pain. He laughed maniacally as he slammed his dick into her ear, tickling her skull. He was pumping so vigorously that her skull began to crack, pouring brain juices out from every hole. He screamed in pleasure, ramming harder and harder until her skull broke open, releasing a torrent of fluid. He bent down and lapped up the fluid, moaning in delight. He sucked up all of the fluid into his body, then puked into her head, all while she screamed in terror and pain. After this was done, she still demanded more! He slammed her onto her back and spread her legs, aiming his dick at her tiny, petite clitoris. Then he paused. Instead of slamming his dick into her clit, he instead shot his dick straight into it, causing her to scream so loudly that her vocal chords bled, choking her. Luckily, his people didn’t need air or even a brain to live. His hand pumped vigorously inside her clit, spreading it to proportions no one has ever seen. She cried, experiencing a pain no one had ever thought possible. His hand continued to pump, until finally he had torn a hole so big that it was possible to stick his head into her clit. He still wanted more, though, so he grabbed her head yet again and began to shove his dick into her mouth. She tried to cry, but her blood was still choking her of air. She could only sit silently as he slammed his cock down into her mouth, moaning in pleasure. As he began to cum, Spitter’s acid reflux began acting up. She shot a load onto his dick right as he was exploding cum from his dick. He screamed in pain, slamming against the wall from shock. He staggered around, trying to wipe the acid off his eroding dick. It was to no avail. His penis was slowly falling off his body, exposing muscle. He began to pass out, just as his penis fell off.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/very-nsfw-chargers-fists-of-fury-an-l4d2-love-story/340425/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/very-nsfw-chargers-fists-of-fury-an-l4d2-love-story/340425/1</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 17 May 2010 05:32:39 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-340425-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/very-nsfw-chargers-fists-of-fury-an-l4d2-love-story/340425.rss">[VERY NSFW]Charger&#39;s Fists of Fury:An L4D2 love story</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
