<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Free viruses and personal information stealers!</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/free-viruses-and-personal-information-stealers/110848</link>
    <description>[b]Dear MoparScape: I am the smartest man alive, and you will agree with this when you&#39;re done reading.

For the last six years I&#39;ve lived down the street from this gorgeous little girl; her family moved in when she was eight, and she&#39;s currently thirteen years old and coming up on her birthday.

Two years ago, I began to find that I have become very aware of her patterns. Up at 6am, on the schoolbus at 6:15am, home at 4:45pm. Lacy (let&#39;s use that name from now on) attended an exclusive private elementary school, and apparently lived a very regimented life before I interrupted it. The bus that picked her up was the standard yellow, with her school&#39;s logo painted along the side. Because she lived so nearby, she was always the first to get on. I never saw any other kids besides her on the bus, and this is what originally set my mind in motion.

The first thing I did was to rent some storage space downtown. A nice little warehouse with a big, wide entrance accessible by car and plenty of room on the inside. This alone would not raise any red flags.

Afterwards, I immediately hit up the classifieds in search of a school bus, but eventually gave up when I realized that this would leave a paper trail. Instead I went asking around at shady garages and chop shops in an infamous portion of my town&#39;s indistrial district, and eventually found a former bus driver willing to part with his &quot;fixer-upper&quot; schoolbus for nineteen hundred. When I say fixer upper I mean it had an engine that ran, but it needed a new coat of paint and a lube quite badly.

I delivered the cash at midnight and parked my new bus in my rented warehouse under cover of darkness. I had work the next day and had to get home, but visions of lolis were dancing in my head and I found it difficult to fall asleep. Over the next two months I refurbished the hell out of the bus, working from photographs I&#39;d covertly taken of Lacy&#39;s private school transport. I even got the painted logo on the side just perfect; you literally couldn&#39;t make out any differences between the two. I very nearly forgot the uniform, though. It wasn&#39;t until one week before I enacted my plan that I thought to buy a driver&#39;s uniform from the same supply company as Lacy&#39;s school. I was dressed the part, I had the wheels, and I was ready to go.

What of the real bus, you ask? Amatuer. I thought of that too. I slashed the tires and put sugar in the tank at 3am the day of the incident, giving me enough time to drive down to the warehouse and prep the bus before Lacy woke up for school. Six fifteen on the dot, she trots out of the house and stands expectantly on the corner as I drive up. Without even an ounce of hesitation she climbs aboard and finds her seat, and (though shaking with excitement) manage to maintain my composure as I carry her forever away from her unsuspecting parents.

&quot;Where&#39;s Rufus?&quot; she squeaks. I surmise that she has some kind of rapport with the regular driver, and I anwer in kind. &quot;Out sick. I&#39;m the spare. Buckle up, we have to make up for lost time.&quot; She does so, and doesn&#39;t notice that we&#39;re not headed to her school until I&#39;m literally less than a mile from the warehouse. &quot;This isn&#39;t the way to school&quot;, she says, the reality of her situation just beginning to dawn on her. &quot;Engine&#39;s bad. I didn&#39;t want to say anything in case it worried you, but it&#39;s lucky we didn&#39;t come to a halt in the middle of traffic.&quot; This placated her for a few minutes, ensuring that she didn&#39;t catch on and scream for help before I could get the bus parked inside the warehouse.

Within minutes I had her bound and gagged. The warehouse had for some reason a sparesely furnished managerial office at the top of a flight of metal stairs, and this proved to be the perfect place to keep her. At no point were her bonds loosened, and I even returned the next day with a set of padded bondage handcuffs (yes I already had them. Is it so shocking that I&#39;m a pervert) and chained her to the metal cot I had already bolted to the floor. I had carried out my bait n&#39; switch so subtly that even the school didn&#39;t know for most of a day, and because my kidnapping hadn&#39;t visually appeared as anything out of the ordinary, there were no eyewitnesses who could offer any clues as to what had happened to Lacy.

She was eleven then. She is thirteen now. She will be my slave until I die a happy, over-sexed old man.[/b]</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 14 Jun 2007 23:39:20 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/free-viruses-and-personal-information-stealers/110848.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Free viruses and personal information stealers!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@ScimmyScape ScimmyScape]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/scimmyscape">@ScimmyScape</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Stfu kid.<br>
Your a 11 year old geek, my little sister would kill you.<br>
Go die if a fire.<br>
So smart eh?<br>
Ip-Track me, come to my house, then i’ll personally kill you.<br>
~Ashley.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/free-viruses-and-personal-information-stealers/110848/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/free-viruses-and-personal-information-stealers/110848/3</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 14 Jun 2007 23:39:20 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-110848-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/free-viruses-and-personal-information-stealers/110848.rss">Free viruses and personal information stealers!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Free viruses and personal information stealers!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Jack_Frost Jack Frost]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/jack_frost">@Jack_Frost</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>You honestly, had time to search this on google, or myspace, your probally 11-13.</p>
<p>You never had sex, you search porn whenever your parents &amp; syblings are away.</p>
<p>I know kids like you, sick little faggots who cant get pussy.</p>
<p>Get off these threads.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/free-viruses-and-personal-information-stealers/110848/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/free-viruses-and-personal-information-stealers/110848/2</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 14 Jun 2007 23:37:43 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-110848-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/free-viruses-and-personal-information-stealers/110848.rss">Free viruses and personal information stealers!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Free viruses and personal information stealers!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@TEH_FAKKY_EXPRESS TEH FAKKY EXPRESS]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/teh_fakky_express">@TEH_FAKKY_EXPRESS</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[b]Dear MoparScape: I am the smartest man alive, and you will agree with this when you’re done reading.</p>
<p>For the last six years I’ve lived down the street from this gorgeous little girl; her family moved in when she was eight, and she’s currently thirteen years old and coming up on her birthday.</p>
<p>Two years ago, I began to find that I have become very aware of her patterns. Up at 6am, on the schoolbus at 6:15am, home at 4:45pm. Lacy (let’s use that name from now on) attended an exclusive private elementary school, and apparently lived a very regimented life before I interrupted it. The bus that picked her up was the standard yellow, with her school’s logo painted along the side. Because she lived so nearby, she was always the first to get on. I never saw any other kids besides her on the bus, and this is what originally set my mind in motion.</p>
<p>The first thing I did was to rent some storage space downtown. A nice little warehouse with a big, wide entrance accessible by car and plenty of room on the inside. This alone would not raise any red flags.</p>
<p>Afterwards, I immediately hit up the classifieds in search of a school bus, but eventually gave up when I realized that this would leave a paper trail. Instead I went asking around at shady garages and chop shops in an infamous portion of my town’s indistrial district, and eventually found a former bus driver willing to part with his “fixer-upper” schoolbus for nineteen hundred. When I say fixer upper I mean it had an engine that ran, but it needed a new coat of paint and a lube quite badly.</p>
<p>I delivered the cash at midnight and parked my new bus in my rented warehouse under cover of darkness. I had work the next day and had to get home, but visions of lolis were dancing in my head and I found it difficult to fall asleep. Over the next two months I refurbished the hell out of the bus, working from photographs I’d covertly taken of Lacy’s private school transport. I even got the painted logo on the side just perfect; you literally couldn’t make out any differences between the two. I very nearly forgot the uniform, though. It wasn’t until one week before I enacted my plan that I thought to buy a driver’s uniform from the same supply company as Lacy’s school. I was dressed the part, I had the wheels, and I was ready to go.</p>
<p>What of the real bus, you ask? Amatuer. I thought of that too. I slashed the tires and put sugar in the tank at 3am the day of the incident, giving me enough time to drive down to the warehouse and prep the bus before Lacy woke up for school. Six fifteen on the dot, she trots out of the house and stands expectantly on the corner as I drive up. Without even an ounce of hesitation she climbs aboard and finds her seat, and (though shaking with excitement) manage to maintain my composure as I carry her forever away from her unsuspecting parents.</p>
<p>“Where’s Rufus?” she squeaks. I surmise that she has some kind of rapport with the regular driver, and I anwer in kind. “Out sick. I’m the spare. Buckle up, we have to make up for lost time.” She does so, and doesn’t notice that we’re not headed to her school until I’m literally less than a mile from the warehouse. “This isn’t the way to school”, she says, the reality of her situation just beginning to dawn on her. “Engine’s bad. I didn’t want to say anything in case it worried you, but it’s lucky we didn’t come to a halt in the middle of traffic.” This placated her for a few minutes, ensuring that she didn’t catch on and scream for help before I could get the bus parked inside the warehouse.</p>
<p>Within minutes I had her bound and gagged. The warehouse had for some reason a sparesely furnished managerial office at the top of a flight of metal stairs, and this proved to be the perfect place to keep her. At no point were her bonds loosened, and I even returned the next day with a set of padded bondage handcuffs (yes I already had them. Is it so shocking that I’m a pervert) and chained her to the metal cot I had already bolted to the floor. I had carried out my bait n’ switch so subtly that even the school didn’t know for most of a day, and because my kidnapping hadn’t visually appeared as anything out of the ordinary, there were no eyewitnesses who could offer any clues as to what had happened to Lacy.</p>
<p>She was eleven then. She is thirteen now. She will be my slave until I die a happy, over-sexed old man.[/b]</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/free-viruses-and-personal-information-stealers/110848/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/free-viruses-and-personal-information-stealers/110848/1</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 14 Jun 2007 23:37:19 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-110848-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/free-viruses-and-personal-information-stealers/110848.rss">Free viruses and personal information stealers!</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
