<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Two errors, help please</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/two-errors-help-please/243151</link>
    <description>I fixed the error, I have one question though... and I&#39;m sure I&#39;ll look like a retard for asking this but... I provided the wrong link to connect to the cache, I&#39;m supposed to provide the client with the direct link to the uploaded, the man who made the TuT I was using wasn&#39;t very good at explaining what to do but I&#39;m having problems figuring out what the direct URL is to my uploaded cache, if anybody could help me figure it out it would be greatly appreciated.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2008 15:47:03 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/two-errors-help-please/243151.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Two errors, help please</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@wmashda3000 wmashda3000]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/wmashda3000">@wmashda3000</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>a direct link always ends in the filetype of the file. it should not be like rapidshare or uppit. easy way to get a direct link, is to download and install apache. apache is a webserver and you will also be able to make it into a website. You will need to have dyndns updater, which updates your ip, which no-ip does not. then your website will only work when your pc is on. when you install apache you will need to go to the HTDOC folder which will be in the C:/drive you will put anything you want into the folder and it will instantly be available to other. to make the webserver into a website you will need to have a html file named Index.</p>
<p>Apache 2.2 download<br>
<a href="http://www.apache.org" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">www.apache.org</a></p>
<p>Dyndns<br>
<a href="http://www.dyndns.org" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">www.dyndns.org</a></p>
<p>Hope this helps. if you have trouble installing apache watch this video it will explain everything.<br>
<a href="http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=-r2JnmaWtck" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=-r2JnmaWtck</a></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/two-errors-help-please/243151/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/two-errors-help-please/243151/2</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2008 15:47:03 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-243151-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/two-errors-help-please/243151.rss">Two errors, help please</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Two errors, help please</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Ibehustlin247 Ibehustlin247]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/ibehustlin247">@Ibehustlin247</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I fixed the error, I have one question though… and I’m sure I’ll look like a retard for asking this but… I provided the wrong link to connect to the cache, I’m supposed to provide the client with the direct link to the uploaded, the man who made the TuT I was using wasn’t very good at explaining what to do but I’m having problems figuring out what the direct URL is to my uploaded cache, if anybody could help me figure it out it would be greatly appreciated.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/two-errors-help-please/243151/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/two-errors-help-please/243151/1</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 12 Nov 2008 05:10:19 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-243151-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/two-errors-help-please/243151.rss">Two errors, help please</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
