<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Where to start?</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/where-to-start/529000</link>
    <description>I&#39;m new to the whole RSPS thing and I&#39;m looking to make a PS with pk point system and possible &quot;duel anywhere&quot; deal. Similar to RS1&#39;s pking but not open PK.

Idk where to start though, I see things about like 571 servers and source whatnot but I can&#39;t seem to find a good tutorial that doesn&#39;t have broken links. What would be the best server source+client source available/you would recommend?

Also is it possible to add like a whole new aspect to the game? Say like a custom point system for doing something and adding a npc to the game world to trade said points with? I have programming knowledge in java so i&#39;d be prepared but I wouldn&#39;t know where to start.

Any help would be appreciated :)

EDIT:
Seriously? No recommendations? That&#39;s depressing /:</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2013 05:29:13 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/where-to-start/529000.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Where to start?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@ThatBenderGuy ThatBenderGuy]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/thatbenderguy">@ThatBenderGuy</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I’m new to the whole RSPS thing and I’m looking to make a PS with pk point system and possible “duel anywhere” deal. Similar to RS1’s pking but not open PK.</p>
<p>Idk where to start though, I see things about like 571 servers and source whatnot but I can’t seem to find a good tutorial that doesn’t have broken links. What would be the best server source+client source available/you would recommend?</p>
<p>Also is it possible to add like a whole new aspect to the game? Say like a custom point system for doing something and adding a npc to the game world to trade said points with? I have programming knowledge in java so i’d be prepared but I wouldn’t know where to start.</p>
<p>Any help would be appreciated <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=5" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
<p>EDIT:<br>
Seriously? No recommendations? That’s depressing /:</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/where-to-start/529000/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/where-to-start/529000/1</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2013 05:29:13 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-529000-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/where-to-start/529000.rss">Where to start?</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
