<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>~*Silab Client*~</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/silab-client/257668</link>
    <description>Hi, I am not sure if this is the correct place to put this in, but It&#39;s close enough since their is no &quot;general help, or general talk&quot;

I get this error when I start up silabs.

Error_loader_client - Unable to download client.
silabclient was unable to download the client file 


Login to your computer as an &#39;administator&#39; user, and then try loading silabclient again. This should give it sufficient access to create save client cache file. 


Or, create a new directory called C:\WINDOWS\.silabclient_store_32 or /.silabclient_store_32. If possible, set that directory to have full read+write permissions so that all users can write to it. silabclient should then detect that directory and use it for its files. 


Make sure to accept the java signature it looks like this: 


if the signature does not come up for you, some security software or parental settings may be perventing you from accepting it.

How do I create the &quot;folder&quot; for it. I tried to do what it said, but no luck. A very small guide would be usefull. Thanks for any help and please dont spam my post with comments like &quot;wrong place noob. This is sad.....&quot; or &quot;lawl your a noob for not knowing how to do this!!!&quot; Thank you.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2009 03:47:29 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/silab-client/257668.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>~*Silab Client*~</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@fluster fluster]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/fluster">@fluster</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Hi, I am not sure if this is the correct place to put this in, but It’s close enough since their is no “general help, or general talk”</p>
<p>I get this error when I start up silabs.</p>
<p>Error_loader_client - Unable to download client.<br>
silabclient was unable to download the client file</p>
<p>Login to your computer as an ‘administator’ user, and then try loading silabclient again. This should give it sufficient access to create save client cache file.</p>
<p>Or, create a new directory called C:\WINDOWS.silabclient_store_32 or /.silabclient_store_32. If possible, set that directory to have full read+write permissions so that all users can write to it. silabclient should then detect that directory and use it for its files.</p>
<p>Make sure to accept the java signature it looks like this:</p>
<p>if the signature does not come up for you, some security software or parental settings may be perventing you from accepting it.</p>
<p>How do I create the “folder” for it. I tried to do what it said, but no luck. A very small guide would be usefull. Thanks for any help and please dont spam my post with comments like “wrong place noob. This is sad…” or “lawl your a noob for not knowing how to do this!!!” Thank you.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/silab-client/257668/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/silab-client/257668/1</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2009 03:47:29 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-257668-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/silab-client/257668.rss">~*Silab Client*~</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
