<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>My RS2D project -- scar317</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-rs2d-project-scar317/266024</link>
    <description>Okay, this is my first development that I am going to dedicate my time to &gt;_&gt;[hr]
The server name is Scar317.
The first four letters &quot;Scar&quot; are from my original server ScarNastics. 317 Represents the base.
[hr]About Scar317,
Scar317 is currently created by me Sonis RuZuix; On which the names I usually use are as follows:
 Sonis, test, me, and Scar
Scar317 probably won&#39;t be like any other server on an actual scale; I am using the wL as a map for ideas
(i.e. What are actual good ideas -- X/Y Chords -- EmoteList -- GFX -- sendQuest locations -- etc...)
As of right now, My plan is to support OpenSource, but I do not want to release any half-ass&#39;d project.
I will release some elements of the project -- DB and raw data information for example.
[hr]
This is what I have done so far to a raw/fresh copy of RS2D(v)...

[ul][li]Renamed net.varek.rs2d to tv.sonis.scar317[/li]
[li]Added a update.xml (and xsl.xsl for xslt) to keep track of update loggs...
If you like a RSS-FEED of the update loggs, please go here: http://sonis.tv/RSS/Updates.xml[/li]
[li]I Made a class for Items. example of my class here: http://sonis.tv/RSS/Item.java.txt
I also made another class called Default that inheirts that class. I&#39;m not releasing that as of right now, because It has my sql password, but I can release this awesome db of items that has 20k items with 83 fields each. As of right now, I havn&#39;t combined the notes.dat,twohanded.dat,tradable.dat,sellable.dat,stackable.dat to the sql db file yet. That&#39;s not going to be too hard. The sql db is 50mb of raw data as xml and 6mb as sql.txt download the  http://sonis.tv/RSS/ItemDB.sql.txt -- Last example I&#39;m releasing...[/li]
[li]I&#39;ll Also Make Pictures for you wierdo&#39;s...[/li]
[li][/li]
[li][/li]
[li]And I usually use MySQL GUI Tools 5.0 to edit my MySQL[/li][/ul]

[img]http://sonis.tv/RSS/screen00001.PNG[/img]
[hr]
My plan is mostly to look for a free mysql host with unlimited traffic then I won&#39;t feel bad giving my sql password out.
I know that Oracle is much better, but they aren&#39;t open source, and keeping projects legit will be my best bet.

As of right now, I can spawn Items by command, but I can only have them in the first invotory space... They can&#39;t be moved and I can only equip Items that are weapons as of right now... I can unequip ... I know that I misspelled inventory... But in my class; it&#39;s invotory. I Might fix it later. It&#39;s not really a big deal &gt;_&gt; keep it ironic twist ? I think I uploaded it too, but oh well...

I&#39;d appreciate a review how I have my Item class set up. I have Equipment and Invotory inheirting from Item with a private field. It took me a while; but I found out that the only way to call is from the World.getWorld to get the player class, else the player class will initiate as a new object; and this will not edit the server... All classes have different settings for each thread. And most of the new processes are new threads.... I was going to use HashTable because It auto-sync; but I prefer lock-and-unlock method from the HashMap. I think the HashMap was designed really well to link to each other in unison.

last thing: I know as of right now; The source isn&#39;t java conversion compliant .... Will auto fix that when I actually release. I just started using a IDE today, I was compiling the server like Finality was being compiled, the non-ant way =|

Oh; and the reason I set up the Item class that way was for a reason that You can improve a certain item&#39;s stats with higher smiting levels similar to some of the games out there. Also so you can have more than 1 pile of gold for an example. If you max out a money pile, you&#39;ll auto fill the next available slot is my plan. I also have it so that certain Items keep track of pk scores (which can get stat level ups if you get enough)... And you can have more than 1 track record, and can also sell them... That&#39;s just my idea, and if the hash is different, it&#39;s a different item. I also was thinking of it so that you can enter ::this_item 01 equipSlot 00 and The given Item will then be a hat. So you can wear 2 body plates &gt;_&gt;... or ::this_item 01 equipSlot 10 will make the first Item in invotory now boots according to Item.FEET;

I&#39;ll take the junk out later and I&#39;ll fix grammar mistakes and spelling mistakes out of my thread on a later date of time.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 06 Mar 2009 18:45:51 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-rs2d-project-scar317/266024.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>My RS2D project -- scar317</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@bhpkyeah satesql]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/bhpkyeah">@bhpkyeah</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Nice job, seems like you actually know what your talking about.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-rs2d-project-scar317/266024/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-rs2d-project-scar317/266024/3</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 06 Mar 2009 18:45:51 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-266024-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-rs2d-project-scar317/266024.rss">My RS2D project -- scar317</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>My RS2D project -- scar317</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@WrittenBlade WrittenBlade]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/writtenblade">@WrittenBlade</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>This looks great.  Never got into RS2D, now I wish I had.  <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/frowning.png?v=6" title=":frowning:" class="emoji" alt=":frowning:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-rs2d-project-scar317/266024/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-rs2d-project-scar317/266024/2</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 06 Mar 2009 12:26:32 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-266024-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-rs2d-project-scar317/266024.rss">My RS2D project -- scar317</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>My RS2D project -- scar317</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Sonis Sonis]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/sonis">@Sonis</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Okay, this is my first development that I am going to dedicate my time to &gt;_&gt;[hr]<br>
The server name is Scar317.<br>
The first four letters “Scar” are from my original server ScarNastics. 317 Represents the base.<br>
[hr]About Scar317,<br>
Scar317 is currently created by me Sonis RuZuix; On which the names I usually use are as follows:<br>
Sonis, test, me, and Scar<br>
Scar317 probably won’t be like any other server on an actual scale; I am using the wL as a map for ideas<br>
(i.e. What are actual good ideas – X/Y Chords – EmoteList – GFX – sendQuest locations – etc…)<br>
As of right now, My plan is to support OpenSource, but I do not want to release any half-ass’d project.<br>
I will release some elements of the project – DB and raw data information for example.<br>
[hr]<br>
This is what I have done so far to a raw/fresh copy of RS2D(v)…</p>
<p>[ul][li]Renamed net.varek.rs2d to tv.sonis.scar317[/li]<br>
[li]Added a update.xml (and xsl.xsl for xslt) to keep track of update loggs…<br>
If you like a RSS-FEED of the update loggs, please go here: <a href="http://sonis.tv/RSS/Updates.xml%5B/li%5D" rel="nofollow noopener">http://sonis.tv/RSS/Updates.xml[/li]</a><br>
[li]I Made a class for Items. example of my class here: <a href="http://sonis.tv/RSS/Item.java.txt" rel="nofollow noopener">http://sonis.tv/RSS/Item.java.txt</a><br>
I also made another class called Default that inheirts that class. I’m not releasing that as of right now, because It has my sql password, but I can release this awesome db of items that has 20k items with 83 fields each. As of right now, I havn’t combined the notes.dat,twohanded.dat,tradable.dat,sellable.dat,stackable.dat to the sql db file yet. That’s not going to be too hard. The sql db is 50mb of raw data as xml and 6mb as sql.txt download the  <a href="http://sonis.tv/RSS/ItemDB.sql.txt" rel="nofollow noopener">http://sonis.tv/RSS/ItemDB.sql.txt</a> – Last example I’m releasing…[/li]<br>
[li]I’ll Also Make Pictures for you wierdo’s…[/li]<br>
[li][/li]<br>
[li][/li]<br>
[li]And I usually use MySQL GUI Tools 5.0 to edit my MySQL[/li][/ul]</p>
<p><img src="http://sonis.tv/RSS/screen00001.PNG" alt width="" height=""><br>
[hr]<br>
My plan is mostly to look for a free mysql host with unlimited traffic then I won’t feel bad giving my sql password out.<br>
I know that Oracle is much better, but they aren’t open source, and keeping projects legit will be my best bet.</p>
<p>As of right now, I can spawn Items by command, but I can only have them in the first invotory space… They can’t be moved and I can only equip Items that are weapons as of right now… I can unequip … I know that I misspelled inventory… But in my class; it’s invotory. I Might fix it later. It’s not really a big deal &gt;_&gt; keep it ironic twist ? I think I uploaded it too, but oh well…</p>
<p>I’d appreciate a review how I have my Item class set up. I have Equipment and Invotory inheirting from Item with a private field. It took me a while; but I found out that the only way to call is from the World.getWorld to get the player class, else the player class will initiate as a new object; and this will not edit the server… All classes have different settings for each thread. And most of the new processes are new threads… I was going to use HashTable because It auto-sync; but I prefer lock-and-unlock method from the HashMap. I think the HashMap was designed really well to link to each other in unison.</p>
<p>last thing: I know as of right now; The source isn’t java conversion compliant … Will auto fix that when I actually release. I just started using a IDE today, I was compiling the server like Finality was being compiled, the non-ant way =|</p>
<p>Oh; and the reason I set up the Item class that way was for a reason that You can improve a certain item’s stats with higher smiting levels similar to some of the games out there. Also so you can have more than 1 pile of gold for an example. If you max out a money pile, you’ll auto fill the next available slot is my plan. I also have it so that certain Items keep track of pk scores (which can get stat level ups if you get enough)… And you can have more than 1 track record, and can also sell them… That’s just my idea, and if the hash is different, it’s a different item. I also was thinking of it so that you can enter ::this_item 01 equipSlot 00 and The given Item will then be a hat. So you can wear 2 body plates &gt;_&gt;… or ::this_item 01 equipSlot 10 will make the first Item in invotory now boots according to Item.FEET;</p>
<p>I’ll take the junk out later and I’ll fix grammar mistakes and spelling mistakes out of my thread on a later date of time.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-rs2d-project-scar317/266024/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-rs2d-project-scar317/266024/1</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 06 Mar 2009 12:16:15 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-266024-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-rs2d-project-scar317/266024.rss">My RS2D project -- scar317</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
