<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Thorix - Release</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/thorix-release/548755</link>
    <description>Based On: http://www.rune-server.org/runescape-development/google/downloads/524907-vicious-revolution-true-official-release.html

This server was never ran publicly, its just something I have been working on and off for a couple of months. I&#39;m still working on this so I might release another as a V2, I never had plans to run this publicly anyway, I just used a random name generator to just call it something.

I know a lot of people ripped on that release saying it was full of bugs, but I had a lot of fun adding more content to it and fixing its bugs, and I want to continue doing it. I know these days memory is nothing but I still wanted to reduce it, server-sided so I managed to bring it from over 100MB to around 46MB, this of course can be decreased even more if you disable some features like loading G,E.

I used: https://www.ej-technologies.com/products/jprofiler/overview.html
To profile the server but I was only able to use it for a couple of days and my trial on it ran out already.

Original Features:
[spoiler]
- Summoning
- Re-sizable / Fullscreen
- All skills re-made in more &quot;proper&quot; rs way (All skills should be working except construction, dungeoneering exists but its ghetto (has ring and party interface tho)
- JAGGRAB / OnDemand cache
- Netty Networking
- JSON charachter file saving / loading
- Fishing Trawler
- Pest Control with NPC&#39;s
- &quot;Complete&quot; Duel Arena
- Clan Wars
- Castle Wars
- Galkon&#39;s Clan Chat
- &quot;Re-Done&quot; Combat
- Commands in hashmap
- Hundreds of NPC dialogues
- Alot more that I can&#39;t remember, check out the link to original release and check out Virtue release thread
[/spoiler]

Everything that&#39;s listed such as content and bug fixes was done by me. Most of these (99%) should not be in the base I used.

Content V1:
[spoiler]
- New Shop Interface
- Removed the 668-719 era attack styles interface and changed to 449~ era attack styles interface
- Added melee, range, and mage deflect curses with gfx and animations (Only for NPC&#39;s atm, easy to add for players)
- Removed 668-719 era animations tab and changed to older era animations tab
- New Trade Interface
- Replaced old npc drop system with a new 1, dumped from RSWiki -&gt; /Data/cfg/json/npcdrops.json should contain 1,200+ npcs with drops
- Replaced 600+ IDK with a 562 IDK
- Quick curses / prayers
- Autocasting
- Bank Tabs
- Gnome Agility + Wilderness Agility Maps
- Resting (uses 2 different anims at random)
- Totally re-done following, much better than previous
- Grand Exchange
- Slayer reward interface, buying items, canceling tasks, removing tasks forever, text color changes if you can afford to buy with slayer points
- Object picking i.e(cabbages, wheat, potatos, flax) all handled in Picking.java, using cycle events
- Clue scrolls
- Externally loading NPC sizes and animations
- Random events
- Evil Tree (just replace old object ids with the correct 525+ evil tree objects)
- Farming - Flower, Hops, Bushes, Fruit Trees, and Allotment patches
- Ancient Effigies
- Bank searching
- Removed lots of dead code,unused arrays, int, booleans and methods. Memory usage brought down from 100~ MB to 46~ MB
- Asgarnias quest system
- Asgarnias dialogue system
- Asgarnias python script system
- New quest tab interface
- Reduced client memory usage
- Zoom in/out with mouse wheel
- Global Item drops
[/spoiler]

Content V2:
[spoiler]
- Moved all constants inside player class to their own class
- Loading Item Defintions through JSON instead of the item config
- Weight System(Display in equipment interface, decrease run energy through formula)
- Replaced old Dwarf Cannon with new one (credits to Lare)
- HD Minimap (Toggable)
- Depth-Buffering (Toggable in client constants)
- Fog (Toggable)
- Tweening (Toggable in client constants)
- Console
[/spoiler]

Bug Fixes V1:
[spoiler]
== Curses ==
- Fixed curse tab not showing up
- Cache packed curse head icons so they now show up
- No more double prayer glow for deflect curses
- Curse glow for quick curses
- Added deflect summoning curse sprite + alligned curse tab better
- Fixed the message &quot;you have not selected any quick curses&quot; from showing up when you selected quick curses.
- Removed the random line being drawn in the quick curses interface

== Price Checker ==
- Fixed price checker not showing in equipment
- Fixed unhandeled packets errors in client where price checker addtext was using clanchat ids
- Depositing items x5, x10, etc gets put into price checker not bank
- You can now withdraw items from the price checker
- Price checker items gets put back into your inventory when walking

== Bank Searching ==
- Fixed unhandeled packets errors being thrown in clanchat packet class
- Items now drawn in search
- You can no longer get extra items by right clicking withdraw 1
- You can now use note to withdraw in bank searching
- c.bankItems array no longer being reset which resulted in out of bounds exceptions

== Woodcutting ==
- You now have to walk up to a tree to see the requirement needed to cut it
- All trees now require a certain woodcutting level to cut
- c.wcClick gets reset upon not meeting one of the requirements to chop tree
- sendStatement now tells you the proper level required to cut it
- Getting logs algorithem that takes into account the tree level, woodcutting level, axe power and axe time
- You shoulden&#39;t randomly stop woodcutting

== Fletching ==
- Fixed fletching animation being run an extra time


- Fixed animation images not showing in animation tab
- Pressing on run tab changes your running mode
- 2H&#39;s use the correct standing animation now
- Fixed godsword special attacks
- Removed pink from the new hair and it should not make your charachter invisible
- Removed random book from staff attack style interface, and removed defensive autocasting because wrong id
- Fixed white firecape on female charachters
- Npc death time lowered by 2 seconds
- Fixed the bug where bone beads were being dropped instead of gold
- Book preaching uses cycle events to shout lines instead of having everything said at once
- All new charachter clothing should not make you invisible anymore
- Replaced the bad curse glow ids in the prayerhandler enum with the correct ones
- Replaced the buggy default weapon animation to &#39;390&#39;
- Resting will not go over 100 enegy
- Fixed client crash caused by dwarf cannon projectile gfx
- Autocasting from book and magic interface used spell ids +1 more than correct one, i.e spell id is 70, it was using 71
- Players now drop items on death + death animation shows faster
- You can&#39;t skull in the duel arena now
- Fixed major bug where multiple ground items in same location were being combined into 1 upon region change
- Fixed flashing sendStatement when cleaning herbs
- Fixed client crashing when buy a skillcape
- Special attack works for bows now
- Fixed bolt effects not being applied for chaotic crossbow
- Players now turn to towards the object they are interacting with
- Cheaphaxed player charachter hairs from making the charachters face invisble, check out ChangeAppearence.java,
to correctly fix this just remove the newer hairstyles and keep the 474 ones
- Run button in options appears activated upon login
- Fixed up file naming, should be able to run on a Linux vps
[/spoiler]

Bug Fixes V2:
[spoiler]
- Duel Arena equipment rules show up on second screen now
- Weights in Item Definitions were bad, used weights from ~718 revision and wrote a program to overwrite the weights
and output to a new .json file
- Disabled zooming on slayer reward interface, shop interface, trade interface
- Able to kill the 3-tailed pheasant now
- 3-tailed and 4-tailed pheasants drop raw pheasant
- Stop fishing/woodcutting right when inventory is full instead of waiting for cycle event to finish
- Better fishing animation looping (still needs some work)
- Replaced wrong inferno adze mining id with corrent one
[/spoiler]

Small Additions V1:
[spoiler]
- Added theiving pickpocket x2, x3, x4 loot animations and gfx
- Replaced all the oldschool combat magic spells anims/gfx with 667 ones
- Better ore prospecting, was using a lot of cases before..
- Cockroaches area with correct animations
- Ancient Cavern area with correct animations
- Bork with minions summoning (the class could use some work tho)
- Correct DDS / Dagger attack animations
- Correct 2H / Godsword attack animations + attack styles added to clickingbuttons (c.fightmode)
- Al-Kharid gate + dialogues
- Rocktail effect
- Fixed KQ not engaging a player in combat properly
- Proper staff / wand standing index animation
- Spinning flax uses cycle events, should be almost perfect
- Prayer book preaching
- Chaos druids either snare or punch you
- Mousewheel support for animations tab, clanchat tab, and friends tab
- Replaced all cases for animations with a animationhandler, Content/Emotes.java
- Magic and stomp attack added to corp beast
- Properly reset fight caves when teleporting from it
- Max brightness on login
- SellX
- Brighter items in inventory (more of a HD feel)
- Brighter charachters
[/spoiler]

Small Additions V2:
[spoiler]
- Removed all cases &amp; if statements that check if item is 2H, instead uses Item Definitions
- Removed all cases &amp; if statements that find what slot to put item in, instead uses Item Definitions
- Dragon claws special gfx added
- Spirit Tree random event to woodcutting
- Inferno Adze burning effect (gives xp based on log, instead of a set amount)
[/spoiler]

Bugs:
[spoiler]
- Run tab not turning yellow, most likely &quot;drawRunTab()&quot; is not being used and its being drawn by some other method
- Quick prayer interface not drawing due to prayer tab using &quot;tab.child&quot;, so I wasent sure what numbers to use for &quot;setBounds&quot;
- Some player head models not showing in chat dialogue with NPCs + some new helmets not showing, need to cache pack this data
- Make scrollbar work in grandexchange search + fix default ge box being drawn under the box when an offer is made
- Can&#39;t use rewards option on vannaka until support for 4th click npc is added
- Old 317 spec bar shows up over the new 1, all you have to do is remove it
- Bank searching changes to maintab when player withdraws item instead of staying on search tab, to fix
use resetBank(searchIds, searchItemAmount), lines 1158-1160 in ItemAssistant for more info
- When completing a quest, reward screen flashes bcz when next dialogue is a null it clears interfaces to close it
but it also clears the reward screen, so make it show reward after all dialogues cleared
[/spoiler]

To-Do:
[code]
- Re-do combat
- More quests
- Poison on NPC&#39;s
- Reduce client memory
- Achievements
[/code]

Media V1:
[spoiler]
Replaced that 718 attack interface

[IMG]http://i.imgur.com/Lo4DP5h.png[/img]

Autocasting

[IMG]http://i.imgur.com/C1GBX5W.png[/img]

Bank Tabs

[IMG]http://i.imgur.com/R6oq1xo.png[/img]

Item On Death

[IMG]http://i.imgur.com/jGrGpcH.png[/img]

Replaced the 718 emote tab

[IMG]http://i.imgur.com/zX5GXqO.png[/img]

New game frame

[IMG]http://i.imgur.com/HtOTwXu.png[/img]

GE Selling

[IMG]http://i.imgur.com/RcgG3VF.png[/img]

GE Buying

[IMG]http://i.imgur.com/HAWGH7x.png[/img]

Global Item Drops &lt;XML Loading&gt;

[IMG]http://i.imgur.com/jnowkoF.png[/img]

Tree Gnome Villages Maps + Wilderness Agility Maps + A Couple More

[IMG]http://i.imgur.com/iX4KpsL.png[/img]

Random Events

[IMG]http://i.imgur.com/UokQvqy.png[/img]

NPC Heads + Player Heads In Dialogue

[IMG]http://i.imgur.com/wFZgVjP.png[/img]

Price Checker

[IMG]http://i.imgur.com/BBuVkeh.png[/img]

Quick Curses

[IMG]http://i.imgur.com/Z1esQSs.png[/img]

Resizable + Full Screen

[IMG]http://i.imgur.com/cbjzxL7.png[/img]

Resting

[IMG]http://i.imgur.com/Zm8j0q9.png[/img]

New Shop Interface

[IMG]http://i.imgur.com/4b2ZSia.png[/img]

Slayer Rewards (Everything Works, Buying, Cancel Tasks, Permenantly Cancel Tasks, Color Changing When You Can&#39;t Afford etc)

[IMG]http://i.imgur.com/lxjRvb6.png[/img]

New Magic Spells

[IMG]http://i.imgur.com/CCpXEHr.png[/img]

Farming

[IMG]http://i.imgur.com/7liE4Wa.png[/img]

Global Picking Items

[IMG]http://i.imgur.com/N6jdOCc.png[/img]

Several Cities Populated With NPC&#39;s

[IMG]http://i.imgur.com/zXBXGHg.png[/img]

Clue Scrolls

[IMG]http://i.imgur.com/gX2ksTx.png[/img]

Bork

[IMG]http://i.imgur.com/G7LSoTn.png[/img]

[/spoiler]

Media V2:
[spoiler]
Console

[img]http://i.imgur.com/qnPOMa8.png[/img]

Fog

[img]http://i.imgur.com/fGsD0sM.png[/img]

Hd-minimap

[img]http://i.imgur.com/h9qnBBL.png[/img]

Randoms

[img]http://i.imgur.com/NgcyDL0.png[/img]

Weight System

[img]http://i.imgur.com/qxurhKe.png[/img]
[/spoiler]

Regarding GE: Theres still a couple of bugs I don&#39;t recommend using it until you fixed them all, I managed to draw the scroll bar when searching for items BUT I have no clue where to go actually make it scroll, also when giving up on selling an item the item needs to be cleared from the box, also to get the prices and item names the files are found inside the cache.

Regarding Scripts And Quests: I am still in the prosses of converting it from the Asgarnia release, dialogues should work but the quests still have bugs in them. Also when you complete a quest the reward interface flashes because clearalliterfaces or whatever is called in multiple methods, i.e client and dialogue packet, because its trying to clear the dialogue interface because the npc has nothing more to say but in the process it clears the reward interface.

Regarding Farming: Extremly poor use of OOP, There is a more proper in-place that came with the server, and I kept it, I think its only for herbs, so I suggest using it or creating a new abstract class or interface.

Regarding Chatheads: They work but alot of helmets still don&#39;t show up, thats because they are missing from the cache and you need to cache pack them, but I had no clue where to find these, so its up to you to find them.

Regarding Random Events: As of this moment I got evil chicken, and the freaky forester down, there is some classes for stuff like river troll, rock golem etc but I diden&#39;t implement it. You also will find drill demon, but the maps are missing so I couldn&#39;t implement it, also I couldn&#39;t implement the Evil Tree because its missing the objects for it.

Regarding Cache and File Server: For some reason a lot of people think the file server is a waste, when in reality its a very important feature, it allows the users to be able to download from the cache only the stuff they require instead of downloading the whole thing, also I know the cache is not properly packed, but that&#39;s how it came, so when I added stuff to the cache I tried to cache pack as much as possible.

Regarding Server: I never properly tested it so, you need to stress test it yourself, look for dupes &amp; bugs before putting it online. This server was never open to the public so be ready to expect anything, I also changed up the file naming so this should be able to run on any Linux OS, just make a new screen session and change linux.txt file to a script file.sh and just run it.

Download V1: 
http://uppit.com/ylgicbbxplz8/Thorix.zip
https://mega.co.nz/#!B9piVbqT!sk9nnFjIOvXyGjL8yPA78luieNyrJ_zjUYIByPjxIk4

Download V2:
https://mega.co.nz/#!Rl9WQAhK!kEYiYwAs8jKeJgN8CKcUsSp13Rkx7H-PVCEaQOut2aQ
http://www.4shared.com/zip/sz7VHY8zce/ThorixV2.html
http://uppit.com/fz6epj7gvjzl/ThorixV2.zip
http://multiupload.biz/dt919pt4xtr7/ThorixV2_MultiUpload.biz.zip.html

Cache For V2: (Place in users folder, so for windows C:\Users\USERNAME)
https://mega.co.nz/#!YtMmjQbY!tsWtpgpm7i67CHs_6mDI3kG1GhKtAsezhoGcq5v8GCs
http://uppit.com/59evuhm4kpw7/ad_nauseam32.zip


Credits:
Virtue Team
Vicious Revolutions Team
Asgarnia Team
Jason for the slayer interface
Servers in the projects and advertisment section for ideas to add
Raw Envy for Project Exile and the G.E</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 15 Mar 2015 00:04:06 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>General Discussion</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/thorix-release/548755.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Thorix - Release</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Relieth Relieth]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/relieth">@Relieth</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Ok.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/thorix-release/548755/12">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/thorix-release/548755/12</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 15 Mar 2015 00:04:06 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-548755-12</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/thorix-release/548755.rss">Thorix - Release</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Thorix - Release</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@old_coder_old old coder old]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/old_coder_old">@old_coder_old</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Really nice. Got it running and playing around. definite keeper. thanks dude!</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/thorix-release/548755/11">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/thorix-release/548755/11</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2015 21:42:23 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-548755-11</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/thorix-release/548755.rss">Thorix - Release</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Thorix - Release</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@williams15 williams15]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/williams15">@williams15</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>looks great but can you release a compiler for this <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=5" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/thorix-release/548755/10">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/thorix-release/548755/10</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2015 07:04:57 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-548755-10</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/thorix-release/548755.rss">Thorix - Release</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Thorix - Release</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Coldmedicine Coldmedicine]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/coldmedicine">@Coldmedicine</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“mohammedryan, post:6, topic:548755”]Its with no complite.bat and server has 100 errors and cache dont work , so refix it and repost it[/quote]lolwut</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/thorix-release/548755/9">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/thorix-release/548755/9</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2015 08:42:12 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-548755-9</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/thorix-release/548755.rss">Thorix - Release</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Thorix - Release</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@goudont goudont]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/goudont">@goudont</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>this is great, nice work on it.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/thorix-release/548755/8">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/thorix-release/548755/8</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2014 23:01:11 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-548755-8</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/thorix-release/548755.rss">Thorix - Release</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Thorix - Release</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Gershon Gershon]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/gershon">@Gershon</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Use an IDE…</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/thorix-release/548755/7">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/thorix-release/548755/7</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2014 19:15:58 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-548755-7</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/thorix-release/548755.rss">Thorix - Release</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Thorix - Release</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@mohammedryan mohammedryan]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/mohammedryan">@mohammedryan</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Its with no complite.bat and server has 100 errors and cache dont work , so refix it and repost it</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/thorix-release/548755/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/thorix-release/548755/6</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2014 09:23:04 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-548755-6</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/thorix-release/548755.rss">Thorix - Release</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Thorix - Release</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Gershon Gershon]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/gershon">@Gershon</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“Coldmedicine, post:4, topic:548755”]Just a question; Why ruin the package like that?</p>
<p>I hate it when people release something and yet want ALL the credits.</p>
<p>People who use this as their first base wouldnt know how to change it…[/quote]</p>
<p>You mean com.ad.nauseam ?<br>
That came with the base I didn’t change it</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/thorix-release/548755/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/thorix-release/548755/5</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2014 17:11:32 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-548755-5</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/thorix-release/548755.rss">Thorix - Release</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Thorix - Release</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Coldmedicine Coldmedicine]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/coldmedicine">@Coldmedicine</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Just a question; Why ruin the package like that?</p>
<p>I hate it when people release something and yet want ALL the credits.</p>
<p>People who use this as their first base wouldnt know how to change it…</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/thorix-release/548755/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/thorix-release/548755/4</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2014 08:00:57 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-548755-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/thorix-release/548755.rss">Thorix - Release</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Thorix - Release</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Ix_Soulcist_xI Soulcist]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/ix_soulcist_xi">@Ix_Soulcist_xI</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Doesn’t seem too bad, nice release from the looks of it.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/thorix-release/548755/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/thorix-release/548755/3</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2014 05:26:31 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-548755-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/thorix-release/548755.rss">Thorix - Release</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Thorix - Release</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Gershon Gershon]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/gershon">@Gershon</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Data -&gt; Charchters -&gt; player -&gt; “Rights”</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/thorix-release/548755/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/thorix-release/548755/2</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2014 02:53:20 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-548755-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/thorix-release/548755.rss">Thorix - Release</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Thorix - Release</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Gershon Gershon]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/gershon">@Gershon</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Based On: <a href="http://www.rune-server.org/runescape-development/google/downloads/524907-vicious-revolution-true-official-release.html" rel="nofollow noopener">http://www.rune-server.org/runescape-development/google/downloads/524907-vicious-revolution-true-official-release.html</a></p>
<p>This server was never ran publicly, its just something I have been working on and off for a couple of months. I’m still working on this so I might release another as a V2, I never had plans to run this publicly anyway, I just used a random name generator to just call it something.</p>
<p>I know a lot of people ripped on that release saying it was full of bugs, but I had a lot of fun adding more content to it and fixing its bugs, and I want to continue doing it. I know these days memory is nothing but I still wanted to reduce it, server-sided so I managed to bring it from over 100MB to around 46MB, this of course can be decreased even more if you disable some features like loading G,E.</p>
<p>I used: <a href="https://www.ej-technologies.com/products/jprofiler/overview.html" rel="nofollow noopener">https://www.ej-technologies.com/products/jprofiler/overview.html</a><br>
To profile the server but I was only able to use it for a couple of days and my trial on it ran out already.</p>
<p>Original Features:<br>
[spoiler]</p>
<ul>
<li>Summoning</li>
<li>Re-sizable / Fullscreen</li>
<li>All skills re-made in more “proper” rs way (All skills should be working except construction, dungeoneering exists but its ghetto (has ring and party interface tho)</li>
<li>JAGGRAB / OnDemand cache</li>
<li>Netty Networking</li>
<li>JSON charachter file saving / loading</li>
<li>Fishing Trawler</li>
<li>Pest Control with NPC’s</li>
<li>“Complete” Duel Arena</li>
<li>Clan Wars</li>
<li>Castle Wars</li>
<li>Galkon’s Clan Chat</li>
<li>“Re-Done” Combat</li>
<li>Commands in hashmap</li>
<li>Hundreds of NPC dialogues</li>
<li>Alot more that I can’t remember, check out the link to original release and check out Virtue release thread<br>
[/spoiler]</li>
</ul>
<p>Everything that’s listed such as content and bug fixes was done by me. Most of these (99%) should not be in the base I used.</p>
<p>Content V1:<br>
[spoiler]</p>
<ul>
<li>New Shop Interface</li>
<li>Removed the 668-719 era attack styles interface and changed to 449~ era attack styles interface</li>
<li>Added melee, range, and mage deflect curses with gfx and animations (Only for NPC’s atm, easy to add for players)</li>
<li>Removed 668-719 era animations tab and changed to older era animations tab</li>
<li>New Trade Interface</li>
<li>Replaced old npc drop system with a new 1, dumped from RSWiki -&gt; /Data/cfg/json/npcdrops.json should contain 1,200+ npcs with drops</li>
<li>Replaced 600+ IDK with a 562 IDK</li>
<li>Quick curses / prayers</li>
<li>Autocasting</li>
<li>Bank Tabs</li>
<li>Gnome Agility + Wilderness Agility Maps</li>
<li>Resting (uses 2 different anims at random)</li>
<li>Totally re-done following, much better than previous</li>
<li>Grand Exchange</li>
<li>Slayer reward interface, buying items, canceling tasks, removing tasks forever, text color changes if you can afford to buy with slayer points</li>
<li>Object picking i.e(cabbages, wheat, potatos, flax) all handled in Picking.java, using cycle events</li>
<li>Clue scrolls</li>
<li>Externally loading NPC sizes and animations</li>
<li>Random events</li>
<li>Evil Tree (just replace old object ids with the correct 525+ evil tree objects)</li>
<li>Farming - Flower, Hops, Bushes, Fruit Trees, and Allotment patches</li>
<li>Ancient Effigies</li>
<li>Bank searching</li>
<li>Removed lots of dead code,unused arrays, int, booleans and methods. Memory usage brought down from 100~ MB to 46~ MB</li>
<li>Asgarnias quest system</li>
<li>Asgarnias dialogue system</li>
<li>Asgarnias python script system</li>
<li>New quest tab interface</li>
<li>Reduced client memory usage</li>
<li>Zoom in/out with mouse wheel</li>
<li>Global Item drops<br>
[/spoiler]</li>
</ul>
<p>Content V2:<br>
[spoiler]</p>
<ul>
<li>Moved all constants inside player class to their own class</li>
<li>Loading Item Defintions through JSON instead of the item config</li>
<li>Weight System(Display in equipment interface, decrease run energy through formula)</li>
<li>Replaced old Dwarf Cannon with new one (credits to Lare)</li>
<li>HD Minimap (Toggable)</li>
<li>Depth-Buffering (Toggable in client constants)</li>
<li>Fog (Toggable)</li>
<li>Tweening (Toggable in client constants)</li>
<li>Console<br>
[/spoiler]</li>
</ul>
<p>Bug Fixes V1:<br>
[spoiler]<br>
== Curses ==</p>
<ul>
<li>Fixed curse tab not showing up</li>
<li>Cache packed curse head icons so they now show up</li>
<li>No more double prayer glow for deflect curses</li>
<li>Curse glow for quick curses</li>
<li>Added deflect summoning curse sprite + alligned curse tab better</li>
<li>Fixed the message “you have not selected any quick curses” from showing up when you selected quick curses.</li>
<li>Removed the random line being drawn in the quick curses interface</li>
</ul>
<p>== Price Checker ==</p>
<ul>
<li>Fixed price checker not showing in equipment</li>
<li>Fixed unhandeled packets errors in client where price checker addtext was using clanchat ids</li>
<li>Depositing items x5, x10, etc gets put into price checker not bank</li>
<li>You can now withdraw items from the price checker</li>
<li>Price checker items gets put back into your inventory when walking</li>
</ul>
<p>== Bank Searching ==</p>
<ul>
<li>Fixed unhandeled packets errors being thrown in clanchat packet class</li>
<li>Items now drawn in search</li>
<li>You can no longer get extra items by right clicking withdraw 1</li>
<li>You can now use note to withdraw in bank searching</li>
<li>c.bankItems array no longer being reset which resulted in out of bounds exceptions</li>
</ul>
<p>== Woodcutting ==</p>
<ul>
<li>You now have to walk up to a tree to see the requirement needed to cut it</li>
<li>All trees now require a certain woodcutting level to cut</li>
<li>c.wcClick gets reset upon not meeting one of the requirements to chop tree</li>
<li>sendStatement now tells you the proper level required to cut it</li>
<li>Getting logs algorithem that takes into account the tree level, woodcutting level, axe power and axe time</li>
<li>You shoulden’t randomly stop woodcutting</li>
</ul>
<p>== Fletching ==</p>
<ul>
<li>
<p>Fixed fletching animation being run an extra time</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Fixed animation images not showing in animation tab</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Pressing on run tab changes your running mode</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>2H’s use the correct standing animation now</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Fixed godsword special attacks</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Removed pink from the new hair and it should not make your charachter invisible</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Removed random book from staff attack style interface, and removed defensive autocasting because wrong id</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Fixed white firecape on female charachters</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Npc death time lowered by 2 seconds</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Fixed the bug where bone beads were being dropped instead of gold</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Book preaching uses cycle events to shout lines instead of having everything said at once</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>All new charachter clothing should not make you invisible anymore</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Replaced the bad curse glow ids in the prayerhandler enum with the correct ones</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Replaced the buggy default weapon animation to ‘390’</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Resting will not go over 100 enegy</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Fixed client crash caused by dwarf cannon projectile gfx</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Autocasting from book and magic interface used spell ids +1 more than correct one, i.e spell id is 70, it was using 71</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Players now drop items on death + death animation shows faster</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>You can’t skull in the duel arena now</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Fixed major bug where multiple ground items in same location were being combined into 1 upon region change</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Fixed flashing sendStatement when cleaning herbs</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Fixed client crashing when buy a skillcape</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Special attack works for bows now</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Fixed bolt effects not being applied for chaotic crossbow</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Players now turn to towards the object they are interacting with</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Cheaphaxed player charachter hairs from making the charachters face invisble, check out ChangeAppearence.java,<br>
to correctly fix this just remove the newer hairstyles and keep the 474 ones</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Run button in options appears activated upon login</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Fixed up file naming, should be able to run on a Linux vps<br>
[/spoiler]</p>
</li>
</ul>
<p>Bug Fixes V2:<br>
[spoiler]</p>
<ul>
<li>Duel Arena equipment rules show up on second screen now</li>
<li>Weights in Item Definitions were bad, used weights from ~718 revision and wrote a program to overwrite the weights<br>
and output to a new .json file</li>
<li>Disabled zooming on slayer reward interface, shop interface, trade interface</li>
<li>Able to kill the 3-tailed pheasant now</li>
<li>3-tailed and 4-tailed pheasants drop raw pheasant</li>
<li>Stop fishing/woodcutting right when inventory is full instead of waiting for cycle event to finish</li>
<li>Better fishing animation looping (still needs some work)</li>
<li>Replaced wrong inferno adze mining id with corrent one<br>
[/spoiler]</li>
</ul>
<p>Small Additions V1:<br>
[spoiler]</p>
<ul>
<li>Added theiving pickpocket x2, x3, x4 loot animations and gfx</li>
<li>Replaced all the oldschool combat magic spells anims/gfx with 667 ones</li>
<li>Better ore prospecting, was using a lot of cases before…</li>
<li>Cockroaches area with correct animations</li>
<li>Ancient Cavern area with correct animations</li>
<li>Bork with minions summoning (the class could use some work tho)</li>
<li>Correct DDS / Dagger attack animations</li>
<li>Correct 2H / Godsword attack animations + attack styles added to clickingbuttons (c.fightmode)</li>
<li>Al-Kharid gate + dialogues</li>
<li>Rocktail effect</li>
<li>Fixed KQ not engaging a player in combat properly</li>
<li>Proper staff / wand standing index animation</li>
<li>Spinning flax uses cycle events, should be almost perfect</li>
<li>Prayer book preaching</li>
<li>Chaos druids either snare or punch you</li>
<li>Mousewheel support for animations tab, clanchat tab, and friends tab</li>
<li>Replaced all cases for animations with a animationhandler, Content/Emotes.java</li>
<li>Magic and stomp attack added to corp beast</li>
<li>Properly reset fight caves when teleporting from it</li>
<li>Max brightness on login</li>
<li>SellX</li>
<li>Brighter items in inventory (more of a HD feel)</li>
<li>Brighter charachters<br>
[/spoiler]</li>
</ul>
<p>Small Additions V2:<br>
[spoiler]</p>
<ul>
<li>Removed all cases &amp; if statements that check if item is 2H, instead uses Item Definitions</li>
<li>Removed all cases &amp; if statements that find what slot to put item in, instead uses Item Definitions</li>
<li>Dragon claws special gfx added</li>
<li>Spirit Tree random event to woodcutting</li>
<li>Inferno Adze burning effect (gives xp based on log, instead of a set amount)<br>
[/spoiler]</li>
</ul>
<p>Bugs:<br>
[spoiler]</p>
<ul>
<li>Run tab not turning yellow, most likely “drawRunTab()” is not being used and its being drawn by some other method</li>
<li>Quick prayer interface not drawing due to prayer tab using “tab.child”, so I wasent sure what numbers to use for “setBounds”</li>
<li>Some player head models not showing in chat dialogue with NPCs + some new helmets not showing, need to cache pack this data</li>
<li>Make scrollbar work in grandexchange search + fix default ge box being drawn under the box when an offer is made</li>
<li>Can’t use rewards option on vannaka until support for 4th click npc is added</li>
<li>Old 317 spec bar shows up over the new 1, all you have to do is remove it</li>
<li>Bank searching changes to maintab when player withdraws item instead of staying on search tab, to fix<br>
use resetBank(searchIds, searchItemAmount), lines 1158-1160 in ItemAssistant for more info</li>
<li>When completing a quest, reward screen flashes bcz when next dialogue is a null it clears interfaces to close it<br>
but it also clears the reward screen, so make it show reward after all dialogues cleared<br>
[/spoiler]</li>
</ul>
<p>To-Do:</p>
<pre><code class="lang-auto">- Re-do combat
- More quests
- Poison on NPC's
- Reduce client memory
- Achievements</code></pre>
<p>Media V1:<br>
[spoiler]<br>
Replaced that 718 attack interface</p>
<p><img src="http://i.imgur.com/Lo4DP5h.png" alt width="" height=""></p>
<p>Autocasting</p>
<p><img src="http://i.imgur.com/C1GBX5W.png" alt width="" height=""></p>
<p>Bank Tabs</p>
<p><img src="http://i.imgur.com/R6oq1xo.png" alt width="" height=""></p>
<p>Item On Death</p>
<p><img src="http://i.imgur.com/jGrGpcH.png" alt width="" height=""></p>
<p>Replaced the 718 emote tab</p>
<p><img src="http://i.imgur.com/zX5GXqO.png" alt width="" height=""></p>
<p>New game frame</p>
<p><img src="http://i.imgur.com/HtOTwXu.png" alt width="" height=""></p>
<p>GE Selling</p>
<p><img src="http://i.imgur.com/RcgG3VF.png" alt width="" height=""></p>
<p>GE Buying</p>
<p><img src="http://i.imgur.com/HAWGH7x.png" alt width="" height=""></p>
<p>Global Item Drops </p>
<p><img src="http://i.imgur.com/jnowkoF.png" alt width="" height=""></p>
<p>Tree Gnome Villages Maps + Wilderness Agility Maps + A Couple More</p>
<p><img src="http://i.imgur.com/iX4KpsL.png" alt width="" height=""></p>
<p>Random Events</p>
<p><img src="http://i.imgur.com/UokQvqy.png" alt width="" height=""></p>
<p>NPC Heads + Player Heads In Dialogue</p>
<p><img src="http://i.imgur.com/wFZgVjP.png" alt width="" height=""></p>
<p>Price Checker</p>
<p><img src="http://i.imgur.com/BBuVkeh.png" alt width="" height=""></p>
<p>Quick Curses</p>
<p><img src="http://i.imgur.com/Z1esQSs.png" alt width="" height=""></p>
<p>Resizable + Full Screen</p>
<p><img src="http://i.imgur.com/cbjzxL7.png" alt width="" height=""></p>
<p>Resting</p>
<p><img src="http://i.imgur.com/Zm8j0q9.png" alt width="" height=""></p>
<p>New Shop Interface</p>
<p><img src="http://i.imgur.com/4b2ZSia.png" alt width="" height=""></p>
<p>Slayer Rewards (Everything Works, Buying, Cancel Tasks, Permenantly Cancel Tasks, Color Changing When You Can’t Afford etc)</p>
<p><img src="http://i.imgur.com/lxjRvb6.png" alt width="" height=""></p>
<p>New Magic Spells</p>
<p><img src="http://i.imgur.com/CCpXEHr.png" alt width="" height=""></p>
<p>Farming</p>
<p><img src="http://i.imgur.com/7liE4Wa.png" alt width="" height=""></p>
<p>Global Picking Items</p>
<p><img src="http://i.imgur.com/N6jdOCc.png" alt width="" height=""></p>
<p>Several Cities Populated With NPC’s</p>
<p><img src="http://i.imgur.com/zXBXGHg.png" alt width="" height=""></p>
<p>Clue Scrolls</p>
<p><img src="http://i.imgur.com/gX2ksTx.png" alt width="" height=""></p>
<p>Bork</p>
<p><img src="http://i.imgur.com/G7LSoTn.png" alt width="" height=""></p>
<p>[/spoiler]</p>
<p>Media V2:<br>
[spoiler]<br>
Console</p>
<p><img src="http://i.imgur.com/qnPOMa8.png" alt width="" height=""></p>
<p>Fog</p>
<p><img src="http://i.imgur.com/fGsD0sM.png" alt width="" height=""></p>
<p>Hd-minimap</p>
<p><img src="http://i.imgur.com/h9qnBBL.png" alt width="" height=""></p>
<p>Randoms</p>
<p><img src="http://i.imgur.com/NgcyDL0.png" alt width="" height=""></p>
<p>Weight System</p>
<p><img src="http://i.imgur.com/qxurhKe.png" alt width="" height=""><br>
[/spoiler]</p>
<p>Regarding GE: Theres still a couple of bugs I don’t recommend using it until you fixed them all, I managed to draw the scroll bar when searching for items BUT I have no clue where to go actually make it scroll, also when giving up on selling an item the item needs to be cleared from the box, also to get the prices and item names the files are found inside the cache.</p>
<p>Regarding Scripts And Quests: I am still in the prosses of converting it from the Asgarnia release, dialogues should work but the quests still have bugs in them. Also when you complete a quest the reward interface flashes because clearalliterfaces or whatever is called in multiple methods, i.e client and dialogue packet, because its trying to clear the dialogue interface because the npc has nothing more to say but in the process it clears the reward interface.</p>
<p>Regarding Farming: Extremly poor use of OOP, There is a more proper in-place that came with the server, and I kept it, I think its only for herbs, so I suggest using it or creating a new abstract class or interface.</p>
<p>Regarding Chatheads: They work but alot of helmets still don’t show up, thats because they are missing from the cache and you need to cache pack them, but I had no clue where to find these, so its up to you to find them.</p>
<p>Regarding Random Events: As of this moment I got evil chicken, and the freaky forester down, there is some classes for stuff like river troll, rock golem etc but I diden’t implement it. You also will find drill demon, but the maps are missing so I couldn’t implement it, also I couldn’t implement the Evil Tree because its missing the objects for it.</p>
<p>Regarding Cache and File Server: For some reason a lot of people think the file server is a waste, when in reality its a very important feature, it allows the users to be able to download from the cache only the stuff they require instead of downloading the whole thing, also I know the cache is not properly packed, but that’s how it came, so when I added stuff to the cache I tried to cache pack as much as possible.</p>
<p>Regarding Server: I never properly tested it so, you need to stress test it yourself, look for dupes &amp; bugs before putting it online. This server was never open to the public so be ready to expect anything, I also changed up the file naming so this should be able to run on any Linux OS, just make a new screen session and change linux.txt file to a script file.sh and just run it.</p>
<p>Download V1:<br>
<a href="http://uppit.com/ylgicbbxplz8/Thorix.zip" class="onebox" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">http://uppit.com/ylgicbbxplz8/Thorix.zip</a><br>
<a href="https://mega.co.nz/#!B9piVbqT!sk9nnFjIOvXyGjL8yPA78luieNyrJ_zjUYIByPjxIk4" class="onebox" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">https://mega.co.nz/#!B9piVbqT!sk9nnFjIOvXyGjL8yPA78luieNyrJ_zjUYIByPjxIk4</a></p>
<p>Download V2:<br>
<a href="https://mega.co.nz/#!Rl9WQAhK!kEYiYwAs8jKeJgN8CKcUsSp13Rkx7H-PVCEaQOut2aQ" class="onebox" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">https://mega.co.nz/#!Rl9WQAhK!kEYiYwAs8jKeJgN8CKcUsSp13Rkx7H-PVCEaQOut2aQ</a><br>
<a href="http://www.4shared.com/zip/sz7VHY8zce/ThorixV2.html" class="onebox" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">http://www.4shared.com/zip/sz7VHY8zce/ThorixV2.html</a><br>
<a href="http://uppit.com/fz6epj7gvjzl/ThorixV2.zip" class="onebox" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">http://uppit.com/fz6epj7gvjzl/ThorixV2.zip</a><br>
<a href="http://multiupload.biz/dt919pt4xtr7/ThorixV2_MultiUpload.biz.zip.html" class="onebox" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">http://multiupload.biz/dt919pt4xtr7/ThorixV2_MultiUpload.biz.zip.html</a></p>
<p>Cache For V2: (Place in users folder, so for windows C:\Users\USERNAME)<br>
<a href="https://mega.co.nz/#!YtMmjQbY!tsWtpgpm7i67CHs_6mDI3kG1GhKtAsezhoGcq5v8GCs" class="onebox" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">https://mega.co.nz/#!YtMmjQbY!tsWtpgpm7i67CHs_6mDI3kG1GhKtAsezhoGcq5v8GCs</a><br>
<a href="http://uppit.com/59evuhm4kpw7/ad_nauseam32.zip" class="onebox" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">http://uppit.com/59evuhm4kpw7/ad_nauseam32.zip</a></p>
<p>Credits:<br>
Virtue Team<br>
Vicious Revolutions Team<br>
Asgarnia Team<br>
Jason for the slayer interface<br>
Servers in the projects and advertisment section for ideas to add<br>
Raw Envy for Project Exile and the G.E</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/thorix-release/548755/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/thorix-release/548755/1</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2014 22:35:20 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-548755-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/thorix-release/548755.rss">Thorix - Release</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
