<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Your best fight stories-</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/your-best-fight-stories/340941</link>
    <description>Post your own personal or a friends fist fighting storys!
Hell, even feel free to rate other peoples storys.
And dont make shit up, its not respectable; even if we cant tell its fake. No one likes liers!

My own personal story happened today at about 4:30 eastern time:
It all started about a month ago when a good girl-friend of mine(not dating just friend) came up to me complaining about some kids that were gonna &quot;jump&quot; her at her bus stop, so of corase I show up. Long story short, nothing went down because a lady called the cops on us before I could show the kid some morals. Next day I get called down to the office to have a chat with the deputy and get told that if I lay a hand on this kid without him starting anything first, Ill be arrested for assault.

Present day: For the past 3 days Ive been craving a fight, mostly because me and my girlfriend have been quit pissy lately with each other(I fixed it today after the fight)
So i decide to head down to pick up my brother, Patrick from his bus stop with my sister and my girlfriend and it just so happens that the kid who messed with my friend, Malik, rides this bus too. Now i dident come down here looking for a fight, but after I saw him get off the bus (with a little persuasion from his friends cuz I scared the piss outta him last time he saw me about to tear his head off) and him turn his head at me and gimmi the finger I got PISSED. I have some anger issues and I happen to be a big kid(Im 15, 6&#39;1, 180 LBS, and I bench 245LBS) so this wasent the best idea on his part.
As he gets off the bus and flicks me off, I look to my left and see my boys walk up to the bus stop just by pure coincidence.(I really dident call them or anything lol) So my boys (Tim, Gabe, David AKA Lucky, Nate, Sailor, Kyle, and the CRAZY ASS Steven.)
walk up and ask what going on, So i tell em and basically they say &quot;BEAT HIS ASS&quot; and Im up for it. Malik throws up some gang signs(which if funny as shit cuz hes the perfect example of a wanna be hoodrat in Blooingdale florida aka One of the least ghetto places in the world) and starts walking over and stops about half why to talk some Inaudible shit directed towards us all, And none of us take well to trash talk. Lucky starts to yell stuff at him and says if he wants to fade up hes down for it and i tell lucky &quot;Nahh bro, this is my fight&quot; and he backs down. So I start getting REAL pissed off because i knew what was about to happen and I really start to get pumped up for the fight to come. So I walk until I get about 9 feet away from the kid and he stands there silently looking slightly scared and like hes almost trying to convince himself that hes not gonna get his ass handed to him.(Hes around 5&#39;10, Black, Hood, and a hard looking. But not hard at all) And I get tired of the silence so i decide to talk some shit to really piss him off and to egg him on, so I say &quot;Hey, Im not fuckin scared of you, BITCH&quot; and he says &quot;I aint scared of your soft ass ether bitch&quot; and his calling me soft realllllly pisses me off. Then He makes the mistake of calling me a &quot;Pussy&quot; which to me is the biggest insult a man(If you wanna call a 16 year old hoodboy that) can throw at me. His exact word were &quot;Why dont you shut the fuck up you pussy and get you and your ugly ass girl outta here, Pussy ass Craka!&quot; and he barely got to finish his sentence before his left cheek ate my right fist. I hit him hard enough to knock him off his balance and I hit him another time and he fell on the ground. I had to quickly make a decision as to what I would do so I decided to go with the Ground N&#39; Pound. I Hit him in the face once more before I put my knees on his elbows and hit him in his ugly ass face about 13 times before i moved a bit and let him roll onto his front side, where I hit the back of his head about 5 times(being careful not to knock him out in his tender spot because im not really wanting a court case on my ass lol)  before he decided to roll over again to attempt to fight back, but before he could even defend himself I Punched him about 4 times in the nose and once in the cheek as HARD as I could(actually busting my knuckle open on ether his bone or his earring) and he quickly realized that fucking with me was a mistake so he decided to roll on his front once again and just take hits to his back of the head and back. I persisted to hit him another 4 or 5 times in the head and about 3 times in the spine to really make him hurt before he arched his back up, just enough to where I could fit my arms under him and pick him up by his stomach.
I picked him up and swung him over my head before I slammed him onto his back REAL hard were he lay for a few seconds stunned at what just happened to him before he Hurry&#39;d up, and once again I threw another punch before he could throw up his stance and fight back and he fell down again(Probably because hes dizzy as hell from being his so much) and I decided that this was enough and that he wasnt worth a criminal record and hospital bills and that if he wanted to get his ass beat more that he would keep on Keepin&#39; on and fight back for the first time in the fight,(not that he dident attempt to lol) and he dident throw any more punches, but pulled out his phone and said &quot;Ni**a, Ima call my cousin any you better fear your life bitch&quot; and I yelled &quot;only pussys jump bitch! if I wanted your ass in the hospital I wouldent need no cousins I fight my own shit!&quot; and as he dialed his cousin, I kept yelling every thin that popped into my head(a lot of which was &quot;PUSSY ASS BITCH!&quot;
about 30 seconds later I decide to walk away and leave before I was jumped by REAL hood boys from Clair Mel, but of coarse as I left I just got angryer and angryer and continued to yell stuff. The one thing I remember yelling that really justified the reason I tore him up so bad was &quot;First you called my sister an ugly bitch, THEN you call ME and ugly bitch, and NOW YOUR LOOKIN MY GIRL UP AND DOWN BITCH! YOU BETTER RUN BEFORE I CHANGE MY MIND AND COME BACK THERE!&quot; And I punched a wooden fence which made an extremely loud noise, and is most likely the reason he started to speed walk away(it sounded like a gun!) and I walked by to my house were I took a drink of water, and went back outside to get my girlfriend and my sister and brother and to ask about the fight and to give me details of what happened(if youve ever been insanely pissed like I was and fought, usually you black out and cant remember ANYTHING) and they basically said EVERYthing I just typed out you all you moparians.
So now, I am gooing to have to walk around strapped up and never alone for fear of being jumped :( but it was definatly worth the respect and the lesson he learned
And if I do get jumped by his cousin, Everyone participating in jumping me will definatly regret it.

Anyways thats one of my 4 fight storys, and that is by far my greatest victory in a fist fight considering he nevewr even landed a hit on me and I landed about 50 on him.
Rate mine and share yours, PLEASE!</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 23 May 2010 13:46:02 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>General Discussion</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/your-best-fight-stories/340941.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Your best fight stories-</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@jme jme]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/jme">@jme</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Locked for exsessive spam/flame</p>
<p>And cuz no one cares about your life</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/your-best-fight-stories/340941/49">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/your-best-fight-stories/340941/49</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 23 May 2010 13:46:02 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-340941-49</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/your-best-fight-stories/340941.rss">Your best fight stories-</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Your best fight stories-</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@RunesGAYpe RunesGAYpe]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/runesgaype">@RunesGAYpe</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“krackkid, post:47, topic:340941”][quote author=RunesGAYpe link=topic=437334.msg3214875#msg3214875 date=1274586626]</p>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p>so i read it</p>
<p>basically all i got from it was that youre a dickhead and got mad when someone pointed this out to you??</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Cuz you know me right?<br>
[/quote]<br>
Where is my fucking video :([/quote]<br>
Im sowwwry Krack I forgot to make it <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/frowning.png?v=5" title=":frowning:" class="emoji" alt=":frowning:"><br>
I got carried away in other things with muh girl  :rolleyes:<br>
I swear ill make it! if i dont make it soon imma make a video of me hitting somthing REALLY hard as a punishment <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=5" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/your-best-fight-stories/340941/48">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/your-best-fight-stories/340941/48</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 23 May 2010 05:48:32 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-340941-48</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/your-best-fight-stories/340941.rss">Your best fight stories-</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Your best fight stories-</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@krackkid Krackkid]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/krackkid">@krackkid</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“RunesGAYpe, post:44, topic:340941”][quote author=Mopman link=topic=437334.msg3214688#msg3214688 date=1274576357]<br>
so i read it</p>
<p>basically all i got from it was that youre a dickhead and got mad when someone pointed this out to you??<br>
[/quote]</p>
<p>Cuz you know me right?[/quote]<br>
Where is my fucking video <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/frowning.png?v=5" title=":frowning:" class="emoji" alt=":frowning:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/your-best-fight-stories/340941/47">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/your-best-fight-stories/340941/47</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 23 May 2010 04:54:36 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-340941-47</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/your-best-fight-stories/340941.rss">Your best fight stories-</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Your best fight stories-</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@abraham2119 abraham2119]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/abraham2119">@abraham2119</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>rofl im 6’4 and ill beat ur skinny white ass ill call my dawg tyrone and he’ll pull a gun on you and ur shit ass will fucking run bitch thats right pussy tell me time and place and ill be there unless you pussy out you gay fuck ur shit ur nothing ill grab your gf beat the crap outta her to</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/your-best-fight-stories/340941/46">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/your-best-fight-stories/340941/46</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 23 May 2010 04:27:35 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-340941-46</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/your-best-fight-stories/340941.rss">Your best fight stories-</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Your best fight stories-</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@lawl lawl]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/lawl">@lawl</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>your writing says a lot about you</p>
<blockquote>No one wants people like you who just go around and flame and try and act cool on the fucking INTERNET.</blockquote>
made me laugh, be more of a hypocrite
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/your-best-fight-stories/340941/45">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/your-best-fight-stories/340941/45</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 23 May 2010 04:25:50 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-340941-45</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/your-best-fight-stories/340941.rss">Your best fight stories-</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Your best fight stories-</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@RunesGAYpe RunesGAYpe]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/runesgaype">@RunesGAYpe</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“Mopman, post:33, topic:340941”]so i read it</p>
<p>basically all i got from it was that youre a dickhead and got mad when someone pointed this out to you??[/quote]</p>
<p>Cuz you know me right?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/your-best-fight-stories/340941/44">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/your-best-fight-stories/340941/44</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 23 May 2010 03:50:26 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-340941-44</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/your-best-fight-stories/340941.rss">Your best fight stories-</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Your best fight stories-</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@n10si_t n10si t]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/n10si_t">@n10si_t</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I live in the whitest and most stuck up portion of the united states, overland park, kansas.</p>
<p>There’s a website that ranks us the 3rd “nicest” city in the U.S.A.</p>
<p>So I’ve never gotten into a fight.</p>
<p>Probably because I’m 6’3" and 13 years old.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/your-best-fight-stories/340941/43">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/your-best-fight-stories/340941/43</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 23 May 2010 02:42:58 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-340941-43</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/your-best-fight-stories/340941.rss">Your best fight stories-</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Your best fight stories-</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@whip_of_soulz whip of soulz]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/whip_of_soulz">@whip_of_soulz</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“noobs are ftw, post:41, topic:340941”]im srry i was just mad[/quote]is okai i hd cmin</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/your-best-fight-stories/340941/42">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/your-best-fight-stories/340941/42</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 23 May 2010 01:37:47 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-340941-42</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/your-best-fight-stories/340941.rss">Your best fight stories-</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Your best fight stories-</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@noobs_are_ftw noobs are ftw]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/noobs_are_ftw">@noobs_are_ftw</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>im srry i was just mad</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/your-best-fight-stories/340941/41">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/your-best-fight-stories/340941/41</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 23 May 2010 01:28:06 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-340941-41</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/your-best-fight-stories/340941.rss">Your best fight stories-</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Your best fight stories-</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@whip_of_soulz whip of soulz]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/whip_of_soulz">@whip_of_soulz</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“noobs are ftw, post:39, topic:340941”]i slaped a guy then he cried the end![/quote]Plz dun do agen it relly hurt <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/frowning.png?v=5" title=":frowning:" class="emoji" alt=":frowning:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/your-best-fight-stories/340941/40">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/your-best-fight-stories/340941/40</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 23 May 2010 01:24:17 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-340941-40</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/your-best-fight-stories/340941.rss">Your best fight stories-</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Your best fight stories-</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@noobs_are_ftw noobs are ftw]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/noobs_are_ftw">@noobs_are_ftw</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>i slaped a guy then he cried the end!</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/your-best-fight-stories/340941/39">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/your-best-fight-stories/340941/39</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 23 May 2010 01:16:10 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-340941-39</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/your-best-fight-stories/340941.rss">Your best fight stories-</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Your best fight stories-</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@doom_j doom_j]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/doom_j">@doom_j</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“krackkid, post:37, topic:340941”][quote author=jmood128 link=topic=437334.msg3214699#msg3214699 date=1274577040]<br>
Dam I have to combo break this Cm+ post fest. <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/expressionless.png?v=5" title=":expressionless:" class="emoji" alt=":expressionless:"></p>
<p>But I have doubts your telling the slightest truth.<br>
[/quote]<br>
Its because <span class="bbcode-b">everyone</span> loves me :|[/quote]</p>
<p>Fixed it for you. <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=5" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/your-best-fight-stories/340941/38">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/your-best-fight-stories/340941/38</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 23 May 2010 01:14:06 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-340941-38</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/your-best-fight-stories/340941.rss">Your best fight stories-</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Your best fight stories-</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@krackkid Krackkid]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/krackkid">@krackkid</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“jmood128, post:36, topic:340941”]Dam I have to combo break this Cm+ post fest. <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/expressionless.png?v=5" title=":expressionless:" class="emoji" alt=":expressionless:"></p>
<p>But I have doubts your telling the slightest truth.[/quote]<br>
Its because Cowie` loves me <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/expressionless.png?v=5" title=":expressionless:" class="emoji" alt=":expressionless:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/your-best-fight-stories/340941/37">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/your-best-fight-stories/340941/37</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 23 May 2010 01:12:15 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-340941-37</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/your-best-fight-stories/340941.rss">Your best fight stories-</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Your best fight stories-</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@doom_j doom_j]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/doom_j">@doom_j</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Dam I have to combo break this Cm+ post fest. <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/expressionless.png?v=5" title=":expressionless:" class="emoji" alt=":expressionless:"></p>
<p>But I have doubts your telling the slightest truth.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/your-best-fight-stories/340941/36">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/your-best-fight-stories/340941/36</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 23 May 2010 01:10:40 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-340941-36</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/your-best-fight-stories/340941.rss">Your best fight stories-</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Your best fight stories-</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@eVokki1 Cowie`]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/evokki1">@eVokki1</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“Mopman, post:33, topic:340941”]so i read it</p>
<p>basically all i got from it was that youre a dickhead and got mad when someone pointed this out to you??[/quote]</p>
<p>you forgot the bit where he did mass amounts of pain inflicting to a 5ft 5 skinny negro by punching him in the spine.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/your-best-fight-stories/340941/35">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/your-best-fight-stories/340941/35</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 23 May 2010 01:08:08 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-340941-35</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/your-best-fight-stories/340941.rss">Your best fight stories-</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Your best fight stories-</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Cheese_Police c|p]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/cheese_police">@Cheese_Police</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>wtf did i do RunesGAYpe i naver did sht to u thats right ur just a fucking noob looking for fight u faggot i wood smash u so fucking much u wood be dead u fat fucking ass hole get off the fucking computer and get a fucking life why dont ya</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/your-best-fight-stories/340941/34">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/your-best-fight-stories/340941/34</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 23 May 2010 01:07:43 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-340941-34</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/your-best-fight-stories/340941.rss">Your best fight stories-</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Your best fight stories-</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Mopman Mopman]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/mopman">@Mopman</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>so i read it</p>
<p>basically all i got from it was that youre a dickhead and got mad when someone pointed this out to you??</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/your-best-fight-stories/340941/33">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/your-best-fight-stories/340941/33</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 23 May 2010 00:59:17 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-340941-33</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/your-best-fight-stories/340941.rss">Your best fight stories-</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Your best fight stories-</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@krackkid Krackkid]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/krackkid">@krackkid</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>ok its 7:15 where is the video?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/your-best-fight-stories/340941/32">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/your-best-fight-stories/340941/32</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 22 May 2010 23:11:54 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-340941-32</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/your-best-fight-stories/340941.rss">Your best fight stories-</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Your best fight stories-</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@RunesGAYpe RunesGAYpe]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/runesgaype">@RunesGAYpe</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote no-group quote-modified" data-post="4" data-topic="340941">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/runesgaype/40/5_513041d5f7104045db30895d3b90af16.png" class="avatar"> RunesGAYpe:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>I took my add medication like an hour ago to pull an all nighter:) haha adderall makes me write and write and write! read it tho, its good stuff.[/quote][quote=“marcbob, post:30, topic:340941”]Do you really expect anyone to read all that?</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Yes <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=5" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
<aside class="quote no-group quote-modified" data-post="29" data-topic="340941">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/krackkid/40/5_513041d5f7104045db30895d3b90af16.png" class="avatar"> krackkid:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>So in a half hour?, I can’t wait.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>On her way now! she lives in Fishhawk and I’m in Brandon so only 15 mins drive:)</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/your-best-fight-stories/340941/31">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/your-best-fight-stories/340941/31</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 22 May 2010 21:44:10 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-340941-31</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/your-best-fight-stories/340941.rss">Your best fight stories-</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Your best fight stories-</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@marcbob marcbob]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/marcbob">@marcbob</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“RunesGAYpe, post:1, topic:340941”]Post your own personal or a friends fist fighting storys!<br>
Hell, even feel free to rate other peoples storys.<br>
And dont make shit up, its not respectable; even if we cant tell its fake. No one likes liers!</p>
<p>My own personal story happened today at about 4:30 eastern time:<br>
It all started about a month ago when a good girl-friend of mine(not dating just friend) came up to me complaining about some kids that were gonna “jump” her at her bus stop, so of corase I show up. Long story short, nothing went down because a lady called the cops on us before I could show the kid some morals. Next day I get called down to the office to have a chat with the deputy and get told that if I lay a hand on this kid without him starting anything first, Ill be arrested for assault.</p>
<p>Present day: For the past 3 days Ive been craving a fight, mostly because me and my girlfriend have been quit pissy lately with each other(I fixed it today after the fight)<br>
So i decide to head down to pick up my brother, Patrick from his bus stop with my sister and my girlfriend and it just so happens that the kid who messed with my friend, Malik, rides this bus too. Now i dident come down here looking for a fight, but after I saw him get off the bus (with a little persuasion from his friends cuz I scared the piss outta him last time he saw me about to tear his head off) and him turn his head at me and gimmi the finger I got PISSED. I have some anger issues and I happen to be a big kid(Im 15, 6’1, 180 LBS, and I bench 245LBS) so this wasent the best idea on his part.<br>
As he gets off the bus and flicks me off, I look to my left and see my boys walk up to the bus stop just by pure coincidence.(I really dident call them or anything lol) So my boys (Tim, Gabe, David AKA Lucky, Nate, Sailor, Kyle, and the CRAZY ASS Steven.)<br>
walk up and ask what going on, So i tell em and basically they say “BEAT HIS ASS” and Im up for it. Malik throws up some gang signs(which if funny as shit cuz hes the perfect example of a wanna be hoodrat in Blooingdale florida aka One of the least ghetto places in the world) and starts walking over and stops about half why to talk some Inaudible shit directed towards us all, And none of us take well to trash talk. Lucky starts to yell stuff at him and says if he wants to fade up hes down for it and i tell lucky “Nahh bro, this is my fight” and he backs down. So I start getting REAL pissed off because i knew what was about to happen and I really start to get pumped up for the fight to come. So I walk until I get about 9 feet away from the kid and he stands there silently looking slightly scared and like hes almost trying to convince himself that hes not gonna get his ass handed to him.(Hes around 5’10, Black, Hood, and a hard looking. But not hard at all) And I get tired of the silence so i decide to talk some shit to really piss him off and to egg him on, so I say “Hey, Im not fuckin scared of you, BITCH” and he says “I aint scared of your soft ass ether bitch” and his calling me soft realllllly pisses me off. Then He makes the mistake of calling me a “Pussy” which to me is the biggest insult a man(If you wanna call a 16 year old hoodboy that) can throw at me. His exact word were “Why dont you shut the fuck up you pussy and get you and your ugly ass girl outta here, Pussy ass Craka!” and he barely got to finish his sentence before his left cheek ate my right fist. I hit him hard enough to knock him off his balance and I hit him another time and he fell on the ground. I had to quickly make a decision as to what I would do so I decided to go with the Ground N’ Pound. I Hit him in the face once more before I put my knees on his elbows and hit him in his ugly ass face about 13 times before i moved a bit and let him roll onto his front side, where I hit the back of his head about 5 times(being careful not to knock him out in his tender spot because im not really wanting a court case on my ass lol)  before he decided to roll over again to attempt to fight back, but before he could even defend himself I Punched him about 4 times in the nose and once in the cheek as HARD as I could(actually busting my knuckle open on ether his bone or his earring) and he quickly realized that fucking with me was a mistake so he decided to roll on his front once again and just take hits to his back of the head and back. I persisted to hit him another 4 or 5 times in the head and about 3 times in the spine to really make him hurt before he arched his back up, just enough to where I could fit my arms under him and pick him up by his stomach.<br>
I picked him up and swung him over my head before I slammed him onto his back REAL hard were he lay for a few seconds stunned at what just happened to him before he Hurry’d up, and once again I threw another punch before he could throw up his stance and fight back and he fell down again(Probably because hes dizzy as hell from being his so much) and I decided that this was enough and that he wasnt worth a criminal record and hospital bills and that if he wanted to get his ass beat more that he would keep on Keepin’ on and fight back for the first time in the fight,(not that he dident attempt to lol) and he dident throw any more punches, but pulled out his phone and said “Ni**a, Ima call my cousin any you better fear your life bitch” and I yelled “only pussys jump bitch! if I wanted your ass in the hospital I wouldent need no cousins I fight my own shit!” and as he dialed his cousin, I kept yelling every thin that popped into my head(a lot of which was “PUSSY ASS BITCH!”<br>
about 30 seconds later I decide to walk away and leave before I was jumped by REAL hood boys from Clair Mel, but of coarse as I left I just got angryer and angryer and continued to yell stuff. The one thing I remember yelling that really justified the reason I tore him up so bad was “First you called my sister an ugly bitch, THEN you call ME and ugly bitch, and NOW YOUR LOOKIN MY GIRL UP AND DOWN BITCH! YOU BETTER RUN BEFORE I CHANGE MY MIND AND COME BACK THERE!” And I punched a wooden fence which made an extremely loud noise, and is most likely the reason he started to speed walk away(it sounded like a gun!) and I walked by to my house were I took a drink of water, and went back outside to get my girlfriend and my sister and brother and to ask about the fight and to give me details of what happened(if youve ever been insanely pissed like I was and fought, usually you black out and cant remember ANYTHING) and they basically said EVERYthing I just typed out you all you moparians.<br>
So now, I am gooing to have to walk around strapped up and never alone for fear of being jumped <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/frowning.png?v=5" title=":frowning:" class="emoji" alt=":frowning:"> but it was definatly worth the respect and the lesson he learned<br>
And if I do get jumped by his cousin, Everyone participating in jumping me will definatly regret it.</p>
<p>Anyways thats one of my 4 fight storys, and that is by far my greatest victory in a fist fight considering he nevewr even landed a hit on me and I landed about 50 on him.<br>
Rate mine and share yours, PLEASE![/quote]</p>
<p>Do you really expect anyone to read all that?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/your-best-fight-stories/340941/30">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/your-best-fight-stories/340941/30</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 22 May 2010 21:34:08 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-340941-30</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/your-best-fight-stories/340941.rss">Your best fight stories-</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Your best fight stories-</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@krackkid Krackkid]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/krackkid">@krackkid</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“RunesGAYpe, post:28, topic:340941”][quote author=krackkid link=topic=437334.msg3214403#msg3214403 date=1274562330]<br>
I want that video :(. Post it now.<br>
[/quote]<br>
She’ll be over in a bit<br>
probably 6ish florida time :)[/quote]<br>
So in a half hour?, I can’t wait.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/your-best-fight-stories/340941/29">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/your-best-fight-stories/340941/29</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 22 May 2010 21:29:44 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-340941-29</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/your-best-fight-stories/340941.rss">Your best fight stories-</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Your best fight stories-</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@RunesGAYpe RunesGAYpe]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/runesgaype">@RunesGAYpe</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote no-group" data-post="27" data-topic="340941">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/krackkid/40/5_513041d5f7104045db30895d3b90af16.png" class="avatar"> krackkid:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>I want that video :(. Post it now.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>She’ll be over in a bit<br>
probably 6ish florida time <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=5" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/your-best-fight-stories/340941/28">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/your-best-fight-stories/340941/28</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 22 May 2010 21:23:42 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-340941-28</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/your-best-fight-stories/340941.rss">Your best fight stories-</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Your best fight stories-</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@krackkid Krackkid]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/krackkid">@krackkid</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I want that video :(. Post it now.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/your-best-fight-stories/340941/27">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/your-best-fight-stories/340941/27</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 22 May 2010 21:05:30 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-340941-27</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/your-best-fight-stories/340941.rss">Your best fight stories-</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Your best fight stories-</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Natey Natey]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/natey">@Natey</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“RunesGAYpe, post:24, topic:340941”]Yeah, But I actually like her <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=5" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"><br>
Not you.[/quote]I fucking love Miss Silabsoft, who the fuck are you?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/your-best-fight-stories/340941/26">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/your-best-fight-stories/340941/26</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 22 May 2010 19:27:38 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-340941-26</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/your-best-fight-stories/340941.rss">Your best fight stories-</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Your best fight stories-</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@doom_j doom_j]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/doom_j">@doom_j</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Your throwing this off track your self.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/your-best-fight-stories/340941/25">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/your-best-fight-stories/340941/25</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 22 May 2010 19:26:59 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-340941-25</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/your-best-fight-stories/340941.rss">Your best fight stories-</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
