<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Need Help Transerring Disguise Skill To ZDR Source (Pictures)</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/need-help-transerring-disguise-skill-to-zdr-source-pictures/243056</link>
    <description>[font=Verdana]Hey Guys! I Read My Old Post. Wasn&#39;t To Helpful With No Pictures Was It. I Will Add Pictures And A Little More Information This Time Lol. As You Can See I Use &quot;Webbers Client&quot;. Yes It&#39;s One Of The Best. Connects To Dodian ( Used To ) &amp; Also If you Have A ZDR Source ( Like Me ) It Won&#39;t Freeze Or Log / Lag You Out ^_^ . Ok Now For Business. The Source I&#39;m Using At The Moment Is Zdiddy Reloaded ( ZDR ). I Found This Source After Two Days Of Searching Lol. When Moparscape Went Down So Did The Post Along With ZDR Source. So It&#39;s Sort Of Rare. Also This Was the Very First Private Server I Played So It My Favorite ^_^.

But Then I Thought. Another Great Server I Played Was Something Along The Lines Of Wolfscape I&#39;m Unsure But You Get The Hint  :confused:. It Was Fun. 50 Or So Player And A Unique Skill. &quot;Disguise&quot; It&#39;s In The Music Tab And I Thought Wow This Is Cool! You Can Disguise You Self As A Man , Guard , Cool Mom277 ( From Old Man Video Recording Lol ) And Rocks! And It&#39;s Got Working Exp To. I Played The Server For The Skill. Unique And Different. So I Thought. What If I Removed The &quot;Disguise Skill&quot; From The Music Tab And Placed It Into My ZDR Source. I Thought This Would Be A Great Idea! I&#39;m Hopeless With Coding But I Want To Learn. With Some Help From You Guys I Would Like To Know How To Remove It And Place It Within My Source ZDR Or Any Source For That Fact. The Music Tab Is Useless Because In Private Server You Don&#39;t &quot;Listen&quot; To The Music Because It Doesn&#39;t Work ( Yet  :| ). So I Think I&#39;ve Cleared The Air With This &quot;Small&quot; Information. Detailed Information After Pictures.

Just A [u]WARNING[/u] I Do Really Want To Open Up A Server. Try And Make It Famous Like Frugooscape ( Back In A Few Months ) And Dodian ( Tad Crappy But Famous For Some Reason :| ). Thanks For All That Will Help In Some Way Please If Posting Comment Make It Fairly Long Like A Real Guide On This. I&#39;ve Seen A Lot Of People Asking This And I Hope We Can Help.

[u][i][b]Pictures:[/b][/i][/u] 
Mod Scape Source : Disguise Spell. ( Inside Music Tab )
[url=http://www.freeimagehosting.net/][img]http://www.freeimagehosting.net/uploads/f765523084.jpg[/img][/url]
Zdiddy Reloaded Source : Normal Music Tab. Like To Move Disguise From Modscape To ZDR. ( Inside Music Tab )
[url=http://www.freeimagehosting.net/][img]http://www.freeimagehosting.net/uploads/a72b5711e8.jpg[/img][/url]


No These Are Not The Same Source That Ive Edited. Why Would I Do That Just To Annoy People...

Ok Information, :
Source With Disguise Skill : Modscape - BETA
Source Wanting To Change Disguise Skill To : Zdiddy Reloaded - Editing To My Own ( I Don&#39;t Leech :| )
Any Help Would Be Apreciated. Thank You. Please Post Serious Comments And If You Can Small Pictures. Make It Detailed And Clear So I Can Folow Directly. Ill Post Modscape - BETA For You To Find A Way To Place Onto Another Source. I Will Not Post ZDR Because It Shouldn&#39;t Matter What Source You Want To Move The Stat To.

Modscape : [color=red][url=http://uppit.com/5X33B1]http://uppit.com/5X33B1[/url][/color]

Thanks!

PS If I Can Get This Working Up And Running I Will Post Source :). Thank You To All Who Are Respectful About This Post. No Flammers Who Advertising Please.

Thanks Again! Hope Pictures And Detail Helped! NOTE : Client I Used It Webbers Made By Webber? Just Note Its Not Mine.[/font][br][br][size=1]Posted on: November 11, 2008, 04:14:23 am[/size][hr][quote=&quot;Ravv Shark, post:1, topic:242890&quot;][font=Verdana]
Modscape : [color=red][url=http://uppit.com/5X33B1]http://uppit.com/5X33B1[/url][/color]

I Hope You Guys Aren&#39;t Just Going Here To Take Source And Use For Your Own Free Will o.O . I&#39;m Take Off Link In A Few Hours. Good Night People. Hope You Can Help. Cya In 11 Hours.

[/font][/quote]</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2008 21:52:57 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/need-help-transerring-disguise-skill-to-zdr-source-pictures/243056.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Need Help Transerring Disguise Skill To ZDR Source (Pictures)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Ravv_Shark Ravv Shark]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/ravv_shark">@Ravv_Shark</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I’m Sure That’s What I Have To Do. But The Problem Of The Text Handler. Because The Text HAs Been Changed From “Song” To Man ( Level One ). And Also It Changed Color. Thanks For Helping. But Need A Fair Bit Of Detail Because There Is No Guide To This.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/need-help-transerring-disguise-skill-to-zdr-source-pictures/243056/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/need-help-transerring-disguise-skill-to-zdr-source-pictures/243056/3</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2008 21:52:57 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-243056-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/need-help-transerring-disguise-skill-to-zdr-source-pictures/243056.rss">Need Help Transerring Disguise Skill To ZDR Source (Pictures)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Need Help Transerring Disguise Skill To ZDR Source (Pictures)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Eddie12390 Eddie12390]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/eddie12390">@Eddie12390</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>The so called disguise skill just sounds alot link PNPC. If you can find the songs in your (most likely client.java) and find the disguise menu in your old server, then take all the code that is used by the disguise skill, and replace the code that was your song menu.</p>
<p>I am not quite sure, as I haven’t done anything to my song menu so I can’t really tell you exactly what to do.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/need-help-transerring-disguise-skill-to-zdr-source-pictures/243056/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/need-help-transerring-disguise-skill-to-zdr-source-pictures/243056/2</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2008 21:31:59 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-243056-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/need-help-transerring-disguise-skill-to-zdr-source-pictures/243056.rss">Need Help Transerring Disguise Skill To ZDR Source (Pictures)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Need Help Transerring Disguise Skill To ZDR Source (Pictures)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Ravv_Shark Ravv Shark]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/ravv_shark">@Ravv_Shark</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[font=Verdana]Hey Guys! I Read My Old Post. Wasn’t To Helpful With No Pictures Was It. I Will Add Pictures And A Little More Information This Time Lol. As You Can See I Use “Webbers Client”. Yes It’s One Of The Best. Connects To Dodian ( Used To ) &amp; Also If you Have A ZDR Source ( Like Me ) It Won’t Freeze Or Log / Lag You Out ^<em>^ . Ok Now For Business. The Source I’m Using At The Moment Is Zdiddy Reloaded ( ZDR ). I Found This Source After Two Days Of Searching Lol. When Moparscape Went Down So Did The Post Along With ZDR Source. So It’s Sort Of Rare. Also This Was the Very First Private Server I Played So It My Favorite ^</em>^.</p>
<p>But Then I Thought. Another Great Server I Played Was Something Along The Lines Of Wolfscape I’m Unsure But You Get The Hint  <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/confused.png?v=6" title=":confused:" class="emoji" alt=":confused:">. It Was Fun. 50 Or So Player And A Unique Skill. “Disguise” It’s In The Music Tab And I Thought Wow This Is Cool! You Can Disguise You Self As A Man , Guard , Cool Mom277 ( From Old Man Video Recording Lol ) And Rocks! And It’s Got Working Exp To. I Played The Server For The Skill. Unique And Different. So I Thought. What If I Removed The “Disguise Skill” From The Music Tab And Placed It Into My ZDR Source. I Thought This Would Be A Great Idea! I’m Hopeless With Coding But I Want To Learn. With Some Help From You Guys I Would Like To Know How To Remove It And Place It Within My Source ZDR Or Any Source For That Fact. The Music Tab Is Useless Because In Private Server You Don’t “Listen” To The Music Because It Doesn’t Work ( Yet  <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/expressionless.png?v=6" title=":expressionless:" class="emoji" alt=":expressionless:"> ). So I Think I’ve Cleared The Air With This “Small” Information. Detailed Information After Pictures.</p>
<p>Just A <span class="bbcode-u">WARNING</span> I Do Really Want To Open Up A Server. Try And Make It Famous Like Frugooscape ( Back In A Few Months ) And Dodian ( Tad Crappy But Famous For Some Reason <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/expressionless.png?v=6" title=":expressionless:" class="emoji" alt=":expressionless:"> ). Thanks For All That Will Help In Some Way Please If Posting Comment Make It Fairly Long Like A Real Guide On This. I’ve Seen A Lot Of People Asking This And I Hope We Can Help.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-u"><span class="bbcode-i"><span class="bbcode-b">Pictures:</span></span></span><br>
Mod Scape Source : Disguise Spell. ( Inside Music Tab )<br>
<a href="http://www.freeimagehosting.net/" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener"><img src="http://www.freeimagehosting.net/uploads/f765523084.jpg" alt width="" height=""></a><br>
Zdiddy Reloaded Source : Normal Music Tab. Like To Move Disguise From Modscape To ZDR. ( Inside Music Tab )<br>
<a href="http://www.freeimagehosting.net/" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener"><img src="http://www.freeimagehosting.net/uploads/a72b5711e8.jpg" alt width="" height=""></a></p>
<p>No These Are Not The Same Source That Ive Edited. Why Would I Do That Just To Annoy People…</p>
<p>Ok Information, :<br>
Source With Disguise Skill : Modscape - BETA<br>
Source Wanting To Change Disguise Skill To : Zdiddy Reloaded - Editing To My Own ( I Don’t Leech <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/expressionless.png?v=6" title=":expressionless:" class="emoji" alt=":expressionless:"> )<br>
Any Help Would Be Apreciated. Thank You. Please Post Serious Comments And If You Can Small Pictures. Make It Detailed And Clear So I Can Folow Directly. Ill Post Modscape - BETA For You To Find A Way To Place Onto Another Source. I Will Not Post ZDR Because It Shouldn’t Matter What Source You Want To Move The Stat To.</p>
<p>Modscape : [color=red]<a href="http://uppit.com/5X33B1" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">http://uppit.com/5X33B1</a>[/color]</p>
<p>Thanks!</p>
<p>PS If I Can Get This Working Up And Running I Will Post Source :). Thank You To All Who Are Respectful About This Post. No Flammers Who Advertising Please.</p>
<p>Thanks Again! Hope Pictures And Detail Helped! NOTE : Client I Used It Webbers Made By Webber? Just Note Its Not Mine.[/font][br][br][size=1]Posted on: November 11, 2008, 04:14:23 am[/size][hr][quote=“Ravv Shark, post:1, topic:242890”][font=Verdana]<br>
Modscape : [color=red]<a href="http://uppit.com/5X33B1" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">http://uppit.com/5X33B1</a>[/color]</p>
<p>I Hope You Guys Aren’t Just Going Here To Take Source And Use For Your Own Free Will o.O . I’m Take Off Link In A Few Hours. Good Night People. Hope You Can Help. Cya In 11 Hours.</p>
<p>[/font][/quote]</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/need-help-transerring-disguise-skill-to-zdr-source-pictures/243056/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/need-help-transerring-disguise-skill-to-zdr-source-pictures/243056/1</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2008 21:27:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-243056-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/need-help-transerring-disguise-skill-to-zdr-source-pictures/243056.rss">Need Help Transerring Disguise Skill To ZDR Source (Pictures)</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
