<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>The Purge</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-purge/533667</link>
    <description>[center]https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=K0LLaybEuzA[/center]
So I just got done watching The Purge, a movie I&#39;ve been excited to watch because of the fucking amazing and original idea the writers threw together. So basically there is one night of the year where anything goes, there is no law. This night is called The Purge and basically you&#39;re allowed to do anything at all with no assistance from police, it&#39;s just survival of the fittest and I&#39;d like to stress the term survival of the fittest. America believes that allowing murder to happen on just that one night that the crime rate drops to I think it was 0.01% every other day. They also believe that going out purging on that night cleanses your soul from all the hatred that you build up against the people you are going to kill. So put this into your perspective, you work for your boss and he is a ass butt, no worries because you can kill him on purge night. They also believe it is good for killing the homeless who don&#39;t work to earn safety in a house. While we&#39;re on the topic of houses, one of the main characters sells security for purge night which is basically thick metal that covers all  entrances and windows in your house. Which is what the perspective of the movie is, surviving in a house with their family. In my opinion the movie would have done better if we&#39;d get a perspective from a purgers point of view, I&#39;d like the movie more if it were more outgoing with more freaks in it. I mean all the purgers were average people which is probably a technique they wanted to use to show the audience just how that neighbor next door to you could probably really be like inside.

But moving away from the plot a bit just so I don&#39;t spoil anything, so I guess it&#39;s personal opinion time! I know it sounds sadistic and I don&#39;t know how I would explain myself for saying this but it actually would seem quite fun to participate in a purge, within reasons of course because anger is something we all carry inside us and we bottle it up just to keep ourselves from killing the bullies, the rapist, that one asshole who thinks he better than you because he has a better car... Enough with the demon talking inside of me, have you seen the movie? What did you think comment below and let me know if you would participate in such an event if it were, real. Good night purgers

I would rate this movie a 6.5/7 tabbies - low rating because of the bad writers even though the concept was flawless.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 05 Oct 2013 06:15:04 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>General Discussion</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-purge/533667.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>The Purge</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Null_Amount N_A]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/null_amount">@Null_Amount</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Just from the trailer, the kid pisses me off.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-purge/533667/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-purge/533667/6</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 05 Oct 2013 06:15:04 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-533667-6</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-purge/533667.rss">The Purge</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The Purge</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@nolan2131 nolan2131]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/nolan2131">@nolan2131</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote" data-post="4" data-topic="533667">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/tabbykiller/40/5_e05bb34c421432ee4d40de30c10af3e5.png" class="avatar"> TabbyKiller:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>It’s not a bad movie, it just doesn’t reach its full potential when it could with such a unique story but it seems the movie was made on a really low budget.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Agreed, they had such a perfect idea, just didn’t capitalize very well.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-purge/533667/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-purge/533667/5</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 05 Oct 2013 03:06:44 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-533667-5</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-purge/533667.rss">The Purge</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The Purge</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@TabbyKiller TabbyKiller]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/tabbykiller">@TabbyKiller</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>It’s not a bad movie, it just doesn’t reach its full potential when it could with such a unique story but it seems the movie was made on a really low budget.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-purge/533667/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-purge/533667/4</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 04 Oct 2013 22:02:02 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-533667-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-purge/533667.rss">The Purge</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The Purge</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Ix_Soulcist_xI Soulcist]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/ix_soulcist_xi">@Ix_Soulcist_xI</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>There were A LOT of reviews that I heard about, I didn’t want to waste my time in case the movie was bad but then again, a lot of bad things were said about ‘Lone Ranger’ and I’ve enjoyed it so far (haven’t finished the movie). I suppose when I have a chance I will check it out and leave a more constructive feedback about the movie.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-purge/533667/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-purge/533667/3</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 04 Oct 2013 15:00:26 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-533667-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-purge/533667.rss">The Purge</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The Purge</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@nolan2131 nolan2131]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/nolan2131">@nolan2131</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>It was a pretty good movie, the little kid kept making me mad due to his awful decisions.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-purge/533667/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-purge/533667/2</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 04 Oct 2013 14:40:23 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-533667-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-purge/533667.rss">The Purge</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The Purge</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@TabbyKiller TabbyKiller]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/tabbykiller">@TabbyKiller</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[center]<a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=K0LLaybEuzA%5B/center%5D" rel="nofollow noopener">https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=K0LLaybEuzA[/center]</a><br>
So I just got done watching The Purge, a movie I’ve been excited to watch because of the fucking amazing and original idea the writers threw together. So basically there is one night of the year where anything goes, there is no law. This night is called The Purge and basically you’re allowed to do anything at all with no assistance from police, it’s just survival of the fittest and I’d like to stress the term survival of the fittest. America believes that allowing murder to happen on just that one night that the crime rate drops to I think it was 0.01% every other day. They also believe that going out purging on that night cleanses your soul from all the hatred that you build up against the people you are going to kill. So put this into your perspective, you work for your boss and he is a ass butt, no worries because you can kill him on purge night. They also believe it is good for killing the homeless who don’t work to earn safety in a house. While we’re on the topic of houses, one of the main characters sells security for purge night which is basically thick metal that covers all  entrances and windows in your house. Which is what the perspective of the movie is, surviving in a house with their family. In my opinion the movie would have done better if we’d get a perspective from a purgers point of view, I’d like the movie more if it were more outgoing with more freaks in it. I mean all the purgers were average people which is probably a technique they wanted to use to show the audience just how that neighbor next door to you could probably really be like inside.</p>
<p>But moving away from the plot a bit just so I don’t spoil anything, so I guess it’s personal opinion time! I know it sounds sadistic and I don’t know how I would explain myself for saying this but it actually would seem quite fun to participate in a purge, within reasons of course because anger is something we all carry inside us and we bottle it up just to keep ourselves from killing the bullies, the rapist, that one asshole who thinks he better than you because he has a better car… Enough with the demon talking inside of me, have you seen the movie? What did you think comment below and let me know if you would participate in such an event if it were, real. Good night purgers</p>
<p>I would rate this movie a 6.5/7 tabbies - low rating because of the bad writers even though the concept was flawless.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-purge/533667/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-purge/533667/1</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 04 Oct 2013 12:32:31 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-533667-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-purge/533667.rss">The Purge</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
