<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>[PI] Npc Dialogue Help</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/pi-npc-dialogue-help/434277</link>
    <description>Trying to make a Easter Event and my Npc &quot; Easter Bunny &quot; is supposed to assign my players to search for the missing eggs. Once the user finds the eggs it delete&#39;s them from the Inventory and rewards them with Bunny Ears and the Easter Ring. 

What i have done right now is this. Teleport to the event area. Easter bunny spawned. Objects with Items inside and working. Only thing i need help on is what i explained above is so once you get all 4 eggs you talk to the bunny and he takes them and rewards you. That&#39;s where im clueless. Please Help

[img]http://img19.imageshack.us/img19/5203/48b0ec6a5dba42a28a9f43c.png[/img]</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 26 Feb 2012 07:09:01 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/pi-npc-dialogue-help/434277.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>[PI] Npc Dialogue Help</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@David-mod_of_lordsca David-mod_of_lordscape]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/david-mod_of_lordsca">@David-mod_of_lordsca</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Trying to make a Easter Event and my Npc " Easter Bunny " is supposed to assign my players to search for the missing eggs. Once the user finds the eggs it delete’s them from the Inventory and rewards them with Bunny Ears and the Easter Ring.</p>
<p>What i have done right now is this. Teleport to the event area. Easter bunny spawned. Objects with Items inside and working. Only thing i need help on is what i explained above is so once you get all 4 eggs you talk to the bunny and he takes them and rewards you. That’s where im clueless. Please Help</p>
<p><img src="http://img19.imageshack.us/img19/5203/48b0ec6a5dba42a28a9f43c.png" alt width="" height=""></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/pi-npc-dialogue-help/434277/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/pi-npc-dialogue-help/434277/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 26 Feb 2012 07:09:01 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-434277-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/pi-npc-dialogue-help/434277.rss">[PI] Npc Dialogue Help</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
