<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>[317]Capescape![317]</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/317-capescape-317/354123</link>
    <description>Hey guys!
If your looking for a development team and you just can&#39;t find the right one? Then hopefully we can help!
This IS Capescape!

A 317 Server created by Anthony and Myself.
We&#39;re hoping that we can get as many people as we can at the moment!
I will list a bit of information about the server and stuff...

We are a 317 server and I&#39;m hoping to get our Webclient up and running.
We&#39;re hoping to get LOADS of members in our website and our server and webclient!
We are unfortunately not 24/7 and I&#39;m hoping that we can purchase a package for that sooooon!
If you would like to join then just visit one of these websites:
* (This is the one with the most members.)
* (This is our new one that we can hopefully transfer ALL our members back over to.)

I&#39;m hoping that you guys will be interested in joining and being apart of the development team!

These are the spaces available.
Hoster - Me for now unless I get someone better to do so.
Tester - We need 1 or 2 of these so that we can get different timezones for those who are off when I&#39;m on!
Web Designer - The best will be the Head Web Designer
HTML Coder - You will be following my instructions

And just list your best!
We are not accepting applications for staff but only coding applications but if you want to become a staff member then follow all the rules and be nice and stuff like that and we&#39;ll think about it for a little while!

You will have to fill out this application format!

Name:
Age:
Experience(In Years.):
Your top 3 best skills:
How can you help us:
Do you think you&#39;ve got what it takes:

If your application inspires me then you&#39;ll be accepted into the crew!

Thanks and hopefully you&#39;ll be interested in join because we need as many people as we can at the moment guys!

Thanks
-Nameme123 Capescape Head Owner/ Creator</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 12 Aug 2010 21:06:49 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/317-capescape-317/354123.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>[317]Capescape![317]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@OmgItsShane Shane]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/omgitsshane">@OmgItsShane</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Name: Shane<br>
Age: 21<br>
Experience(In Years.): 2-3<br>
Your top 3 best skills: Im Very good in Website design and good coder and a great player/staff overall :)!<br>
How can you help us: I can help with site and code A bit and help players all i can! I can also start Advertising Servers and make the offical Trailor for your server and i can advertise server on Multiple Website including Moparscape and hell if you need a host i can host. And i will Start Donating a bit to Improve the Server once i join the Team! :)!<br>
Do you think you’ve got what it takes: Yes, i had a server of my own once!<br>
Email?: <a href="mailto:Shane9000100@hotmail.com">Shane9000100@hotmail.com</a></p>
<p>Posituation?: Website Designer or Tester!</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/317-capescape-317/354123/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/317-capescape-317/354123/3</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 12 Aug 2010 21:06:49 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-354123-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/317-capescape-317/354123.rss">[317]Capescape![317]</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[317]Capescape![317]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@kihomura Kihomura]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/kihomura">@kihomura</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Removed website links. Advertising is not allowed, use your signature.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/317-capescape-317/354123/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/317-capescape-317/354123/2</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 11 Aug 2010 09:51:51 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-354123-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/317-capescape-317/354123.rss">[317]Capescape![317]</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[317]Capescape![317]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Nameme123 Nameme123]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/nameme123">@Nameme123</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Hey guys!<br>
If your looking for a development team and you just can’t find the right one? Then hopefully we can help!<br>
This IS Capescape!</p>
<p>A 317 Server created by Anthony and Myself.<br>
We’re hoping that we can get as many people as we can at the moment!<br>
I will list a bit of information about the server and stuff…</p>
<p>We are a 317 server and I’m hoping to get our Webclient up and running.<br>
We’re hoping to get LOADS of members in our website and our server and webclient!<br>
We are unfortunately not 24/7 and I’m hoping that we can purchase a package for that sooooon!<br>
If you would like to join then just visit one of these websites:</p>
<ul>
<li>(This is the one with the most members.)</li>
<li>(This is our new one that we can hopefully transfer ALL our members back over to.)</li>
</ul>
<p>I’m hoping that you guys will be interested in joining and being apart of the development team!</p>
<p>These are the spaces available.<br>
Hoster - Me for now unless I get someone better to do so.<br>
Tester - We need 1 or 2 of these so that we can get different timezones for those who are off when I’m on!<br>
Web Designer - The best will be the Head Web Designer<br>
HTML Coder - You will be following my instructions</p>
<p>And just list your best!<br>
We are not accepting applications for staff but only coding applications but if you want to become a staff member then follow all the rules and be nice and stuff like that and we’ll think about it for a little while!</p>
<p>You will have to fill out this application format!</p>
<p>Name:<br>
Age:<br>
Experience(In Years.):<br>
Your top 3 best skills:<br>
How can you help us:<br>
Do you think you’ve got what it takes:</p>
<p>If your application inspires me then you’ll be accepted into the crew!</p>
<p>Thanks and hopefully you’ll be interested in join because we need as many people as we can at the moment guys!</p>
<p>Thanks<br>
-Nameme123 Capescape Head Owner/ Creator</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/317-capescape-317/354123/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/317-capescape-317/354123/1</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 11 Aug 2010 09:11:06 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-354123-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/317-capescape-317/354123.rss">[317]Capescape![317]</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
