<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Mobo question</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/mobo-question/465467</link>
    <description>recently I had the idea to build mine own computer finally since I have had a job for 2 months now. so this is what I bought http://pcpartpicker.com/p/lqEb but right now the mobo from amazon is unavailable. So I decided to cancel the order. They email back they cannot so I guess they have one for me and they are working on getting it shipped. when I got the z75 pro3 I didn&#39;t think I would ever run 2 cards in sli but after thinking able it I think I would like that option available in case I every changed my mine. so I was wanting to get this http://www.newegg.com/Product/Product.aspx?Item=N82E16813157293&amp;nm_mc=AFC-C8Junction&amp;cm_mmc=AFC-C8Junction-_-na-_-na-_-na&amp;AID=10446076&amp;PID=3938566&amp;SID= instead.

the question should I stick with the mobo I ordered or should I order this other one and send the other one back when I get it? I have like $400+ in my bank that I have to make last til the 8th which shouldn&#39;t be hard unless something comes up like an emergency. That other mobo I am looking at comes with a free 8 gb of ram so I would have 16 gb or I could sell it or something. I want to have all the parts by before november 6th at least. so thats why I was thinking buying the available mobo will get here faster plus newegg&#39;s shipping is almost here I wouldn&#39;t be surprised if I had my cpu, psu, and ram by tuesday or wednesday.

The build was supposed to cost as close to $600 as I could get it. Also I is supposed to be able to play the games I want at pretty high detail and get good fps while also capturing my screen. Idk if I will be able run minecraft with shaders, 256x texture pack, and record at 1080p but if it can do that at 128x then I would be fine.

When I decided it was either buy parts to build my first computer or buy the galaxy note 2 full price. I&#39;ve been waiting a while to be able to buy and build my first computer; like years but only recently within a couple months to get the note 2 even though I just got a galaxy s 2 back in January.

thx in advanced.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 31 Oct 2012 22:43:16 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>General Discussion</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/mobo-question/465467.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Mobo question</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@xryz xryz]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/xryz">@xryz</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>thank you both very helpful. my friend has i think two 460’s in sli but one of them perform better than the 650. I didn’t get the i5 b/c I didn’t look hard enough to notice I could have got one for just $40-50 more… I wasted even more money by buying an i3-3225 b/c it has 4000 gfx over the 2500 in the 3220. I cant return the 3220 so im stuck with it unless I sell it on ebay or something. I’d be selling it for $80-100. it will be brand new un-opened.</p>
<p>The reason I got the 3225 was because my mobo supports <a href="http://www.lucidlogix.com/product-virtu-mvp.shtml" rel="nofollow noopener">http://www.lucidlogix.com/product-virtu-mvp.shtml</a> and I thought that may get some more performance. slightly at least. also benchmarks show the 3225 is like 4% faster. If I would have looked harder b4 I bought I would have paid $10 to get it over my first choice.</p>
<p>Hopefully that will teach me not to make buying decisions so quickly.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/mobo-question/465467/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/mobo-question/465467/4</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 31 Oct 2012 22:43:16 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-465467-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/mobo-question/465467.rss">Mobo question</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Mobo question</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@SilentCJ SilentCJ]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/silentcj">@SilentCJ</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>+1 on the above, I noticed that they’ve already stopped selling the nvidia 400 series almost everywhere, and they’re only just older than 2 years.<br>
I’ve got a single gtx 680 at the moment but will probably throw another one in there when they’re going cheap.</p>
<p>On topic though, why not splash out a tiny bit more for at least an i5?  The price difference is tiny and it’ll be worth the difference in performance.  Also, it’ll have no problem running minecraft and recording, however if you were to run BF3 or a similar game on high or even medium on that card at 1080p AND capture with fraps, it may struggle to keep above 30 fps.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/mobo-question/465467/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/mobo-question/465467/3</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 29 Oct 2012 23:35:09 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-465467-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/mobo-question/465467.rss">Mobo question</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Mobo question</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@The_Un-Named The Un-Named]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/the_un-named">@The_Un-Named</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>If you’re not going to get a second video card within a year, don’t bother aiming for sli compatibility. Mid to High end gfx cards are usually supported 3-4~ years if you want to stay in the loop, but assuming you don’t then you can get away with 6 years for a high end card. My old PC had a 9800gtx and I’d still be using that today if it didn’t start dying on me, the 9800GTX being a 4~ year old card which was essentially a re-branded 8800GTS, a 5 year old card this November.</p>
<p>What am I getting at here? Unless you opt to go for sli within a year, better graphics cards will come out for cheaper and if you go the sli route you’ll be paying about the same for similar performance but will be paying out the ass in electric to run the damn thing.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/mobo-question/465467/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/mobo-question/465467/2</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 29 Oct 2012 05:09:10 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-465467-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/mobo-question/465467.rss">Mobo question</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Mobo question</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@xryz xryz]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/xryz">@xryz</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>recently I had the idea to build mine own computer finally since I have had a job for 2 months now. so this is what I bought <a href="http://pcpartpicker.com/p/lqEb" rel="nofollow noopener">http://pcpartpicker.com/p/lqEb</a> but right now the mobo from amazon is unavailable. So I decided to cancel the order. They email back they cannot so I guess they have one for me and they are working on getting it shipped. when I got the z75 pro3 I didn’t think I would ever run 2 cards in sli but after thinking able it I think I would like that option available in case I every changed my mine. so I was wanting to get this <a href="http://www.newegg.com/Product/Product.aspx?Item=N82E16813157293&amp;nm_mc=AFC-C8Junction&amp;cm_mmc=AFC-C8Junction-" rel="nofollow noopener">http://www.newegg.com/Product/Product.aspx?Item=N82E16813157293&amp;nm_mc=AFC-C8Junction&amp;cm_mmc=AFC-C8Junction-</a><em>-na-</em>-na-_-na&amp;AID=10446076&amp;PID=3938566&amp;SID= instead.</p>
<p>the question should I stick with the mobo I ordered or should I order this other one and send the other one back when I get it? I have like $400+ in my bank that I have to make last til the 8th which shouldn’t be hard unless something comes up like an emergency. That other mobo I am looking at comes with a free 8 gb of ram so I would have 16 gb or I could sell it or something. I want to have all the parts by before november 6th at least. so thats why I was thinking buying the available mobo will get here faster plus newegg’s shipping is almost here I wouldn’t be surprised if I had my cpu, psu, and ram by tuesday or wednesday.</p>
<p>The build was supposed to cost as close to $600 as I could get it. Also I is supposed to be able to play the games I want at pretty high detail and get good fps while also capturing my screen. Idk if I will be able run minecraft with shaders, 256x texture pack, and record at 1080p but if it can do that at 128x then I would be fine.</p>
<p>When I decided it was either buy parts to build my first computer or buy the galaxy note 2 full price. I’ve been waiting a while to be able to buy and build my first computer; like years but only recently within a couple months to get the note 2 even though I just got a galaxy s 2 back in January.</p>
<p>thx in advanced.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/mobo-question/465467/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/mobo-question/465467/1</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 29 Oct 2012 01:28:49 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-465467-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/mobo-question/465467.rss">Mobo question</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
