<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Need Server Programming Guidance</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/need-server-programming-guidance/437128</link>
    <description>[b]About Me[/b]
Hi, I&#39;m making my own server and I would like to have someone knowledgeable that&#39;s willing to help me answer questions that I might have while I&#39;m adding things to the server. I have beginner knowledge in programming Java and C++. I know my way around private servers as I&#39;ve made a 317 before a long time ago. I&#39;m starting again since then, and I&#39;m hoping to put a lot of time into the server. So, if anyone is willing to lend a hand, please add me on msn: win_k@live.com.

Of course, I will also be posting questions I have here, but it&#39;d just be nice to have someone live that I can chat with instantly. I&#39;m planning to make a very stable, efficient and organized server with a strong focus on PvP. I plan to have a fully functioning economy with minigames (PvP &amp; PvM), with skills integrated to help you with various combat tasks. I want to rework various aspects of different skills to my liking, not deviating from the original concepts but just making it more interactive and interesting.

A bit of background story about myself. I&#39;ve been around and out of the RSPS community for a good 3-4 years now. I won&#39;t delve into it much further, as that is not the goal of this post, but just so you know, I was somewhat notable in the RSPS community as I was the coowner of a somewhat famous server called Z508, made by Zach. I was Mod Win, the main person behind Z508, along with Zach, that created one of the best and most perfect combat system at the time and even now.

[b]Progress[/b]
Right now, I&#39;ve already downloaded a source that&#39;s had a large amount of work done to it (http://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php/topic,539463.0.html), so there&#39;s already a lot of things that are already working. However, I have a keen eye for catching small bugs, even spelling mistakes and such, so I&#39;ll be making a lot of adjustments and changing many things. I hope to not leach from anyone or ask for any spoon feeding, I want to figure everything out myself mainly, but any advice or answers to my questions would be highly appreciated.

Currently, I am just at the very beginning stage of testing the features of the server and reading through all the source files to see what I can understand and note things&#39; locations so I can go back to change them when I need to.

[b]RuneSol Project[/b]
I&#39;m also going to be posting a project thread about my server (link here once it&#39;s posted), listing the various features and functions I am hoping to add. Although, some of these ideas are completely unheard of and very innovating imo, so I may not be releasing everything for people to see publicly.

And of course, if you help me, you can expect to be rewarded by gaining administrative rank on my server while in Alpha, Beta, and when it&#39;s live, though I&#39;m not asking for help in payment of this, it is simply a favor back to you as I get to know you more. Of course, I am looking for mature and responsible qualities from whoever it is I choose, and I reserve the right to remove you if you are disruptive, even if you&#39;ve aided me. But as long as you maintain those qualities, I will be honored and glad to have you as part of my staff.

So, feel free to add me and chat. Otherwise, I&#39;ll still be posting all my questions under this post when I have them.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 22 Mar 2012 03:05:15 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/need-server-programming-guidance/437128.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Need Server Programming Guidance</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@eshay_lad eshay lad]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/eshay_lad">@eshay_lad</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I would take this offer up but.<br>
Im not really into 667/704 if u was working off base 317/OR/[PI]474 i would love to help.</p>
<p>If anyone knows someone that would like to do somthing like this off a 317/474/PI let me know.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/need-server-programming-guidance/437128/10">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/need-server-programming-guidance/437128/10</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 22 Mar 2012 03:05:15 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-437128-10</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/need-server-programming-guidance/437128.rss">Need Server Programming Guidance</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Need Server Programming Guidance</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@winK winK]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/wink">@winK</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Spoken true. But it doesn’t hurt to scour for any willing minds. I’m sure once I’ve made things more formal and official, with a list of ideas, features and goals, along with progress shown, people will show. Along with that I’ve shown incentive, whether it interests one or not, by rewarding them with a rank on my server.</p>
<p>The fact is I’m still reliant on myself, but a part of relying on myself is relying on myself to look for others.</p>
<p>Sorry, I don’t use Delta. I’m working on a 667 loading 704 currently (<a href="http://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php/topic,539463.0.html" rel="nofollow noopener">http://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php/topic,539463.0.html</a>). From what I’ve seen so far it’s satisfied my needs, it being stable or a good source or not. I think it is, since Dragonkk was the creator I believe. I’m not sure as whether I should keep at it, but that’ll show as I progress further.</p>
<p>I’m looking for an as up to date server as possible, to match the qualities of current RS. I’m not a fan of the old school revisions, aside from the PKing mechanics.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/need-server-programming-guidance/437128/9">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/need-server-programming-guidance/437128/9</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 22 Mar 2012 02:44:19 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-437128-9</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/need-server-programming-guidance/437128.rss">Need Server Programming Guidance</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Need Server Programming Guidance</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@RandQm RandQm]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/randqm">@RandQm</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“winK, post:7, topic:437128”]I never asked for that. I’m simply asking to keep in touch, as in add me on MSN, or contact me through PM. Just simply state if you’re willing to help, and I’ll look to you when in need. I’m not asking for 24/7 customer support or something like that. That is why I’m posting this in the help section, so many can see, and many, if they wish, can add me. That way, if one’s off, another may be on, whenever I’m in need. That way I can also look to multiple sources for help.</p>
<p>Tutorials may not address specific issues or problems that arise for my own idea or feature I’m implementing. They are set in stone and meant for one specific feature.[/quote]<br>
If you use delta you can add me,<br>
but I’m sayin not much people are waiting for unexperienced beginners to come bother them with there problems</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/need-server-programming-guidance/437128/8">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/need-server-programming-guidance/437128/8</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 22 Mar 2012 02:41:14 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-437128-8</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/need-server-programming-guidance/437128.rss">Need Server Programming Guidance</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Need Server Programming Guidance</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@winK winK]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/wink">@winK</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I never asked for that. I’m simply asking to keep in touch, as in add me on MSN, or contact me through PM. Just simply state if you’re willing to help, and I’ll look to you when in need. I’m not asking for 24/7 customer support or something like that. That is why I’m posting this in the help section, so many can see, and many, if they wish, can add me. That way, if one’s off, another may be on, whenever I’m in need. That way I can also look to multiple sources for help.</p>
<p>Tutorials may not address specific issues or problems that arise for my own idea or feature I’m implementing. They are set in stone and meant for one specific feature. I will however use them, but it would be far more convenient if I could go to someone that I’ve made friends with that are willing to lend me a hand or answer a simple question not as long as a tutorial may be.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/need-server-programming-guidance/437128/7">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/need-server-programming-guidance/437128/7</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 22 Mar 2012 02:37:59 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-437128-7</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/need-server-programming-guidance/437128.rss">Need Server Programming Guidance</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Need Server Programming Guidance</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@RandQm RandQm]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/randqm">@RandQm</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote quote-modified" data-post="5" data-topic="437128">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/wink/40/5_e05bb34c421432ee4d40de30c10af3e5.png" class="avatar"> winK:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Yeah, that makes some sense, however, I’m not looking for a development team, just a helping hand. I’ll be developing the server itself solely by myself. Perhaps I will change my mind later. But this is just to find people that are willing to stay in touch with me in case I need any help. So I’m not sure if I would post here or there. A mod can move this if they wish. I’m going to post a project thread linking to this either way.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I suggest either taking a team member or using the tutorials section if you want to go solo.<br>
Now one is going to stand ready for you all the time.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/need-server-programming-guidance/437128/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/need-server-programming-guidance/437128/6</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 22 Mar 2012 02:34:32 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-437128-6</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/need-server-programming-guidance/437128.rss">Need Server Programming Guidance</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Need Server Programming Guidance</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@winK winK]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/wink">@winK</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Yeah, that makes some sense, however, I’m not looking for a development team, just a helping hand. I’ll be developing the server itself solely by myself. Perhaps I will change my mind later. But this is just to find people that are willing to stay in touch with me in case I need any help. So I’m not sure if I would post here or there. A mod can move this if they wish. I’m going to post a project thread linking to this either way.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/need-server-programming-guidance/437128/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/need-server-programming-guidance/437128/5</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 22 Mar 2012 02:32:40 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-437128-5</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/need-server-programming-guidance/437128.rss">Need Server Programming Guidance</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Need Server Programming Guidance</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@RandQm RandQm]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/randqm">@RandQm</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote quote-modified" data-post="3" data-topic="437128">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/wink/40/5_e05bb34c421432ee4d40de30c10af3e5.png" class="avatar"> winK:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Yes, this was the first thing to do, post a help thread. Next is project thread. Will be working on that. Meanwhile, I’m just messing on the server and testing with my friends. Compiling a list of bugs and small tweaks I want to make while I’m testing.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>If you’re looking for help with the server itself and not with a single problem you have you should post in development teams.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/need-server-programming-guidance/437128/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/need-server-programming-guidance/437128/4</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 22 Mar 2012 02:26:51 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-437128-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/need-server-programming-guidance/437128.rss">Need Server Programming Guidance</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Need Server Programming Guidance</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@winK winK]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/wink">@winK</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Yes, this was the first thing to do, post a help thread. Next is project thread. Will be working on that. Meanwhile, I’m just messing on the server and testing with my friends. Compiling a list of bugs and small tweaks I want to make while I’m testing.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/need-server-programming-guidance/437128/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/need-server-programming-guidance/437128/3</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 22 Mar 2012 02:20:45 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-437128-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/need-server-programming-guidance/437128.rss">Need Server Programming Guidance</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Need Server Programming Guidance</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@RandQm RandQm]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/randqm">@RandQm</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>You should get started already, set some goals and put this in development teams</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/need-server-programming-guidance/437128/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/need-server-programming-guidance/437128/2</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 22 Mar 2012 02:18:47 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-437128-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/need-server-programming-guidance/437128.rss">Need Server Programming Guidance</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Need Server Programming Guidance</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@winK winK]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/wink">@winK</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p><span class="bbcode-b">About Me</span><br>
Hi, I’m making my own server and I would like to have someone knowledgeable that’s willing to help me answer questions that I might have while I’m adding things to the server. I have beginner knowledge in programming Java and C++. I know my way around private servers as I’ve made a 317 before a long time ago. I’m starting again since then, and I’m hoping to put a lot of time into the server. So, if anyone is willing to lend a hand, please add me on msn: <a href="mailto:win_k@live.com">win_k@live.com</a>.</p>
<p>Of course, I will also be posting questions I have here, but it’d just be nice to have someone live that I can chat with instantly. I’m planning to make a very stable, efficient and organized server with a strong focus on PvP. I plan to have a fully functioning economy with minigames (PvP &amp; PvM), with skills integrated to help you with various combat tasks. I want to rework various aspects of different skills to my liking, not deviating from the original concepts but just making it more interactive and interesting.</p>
<p>A bit of background story about myself. I’ve been around and out of the RSPS community for a good 3-4 years now. I won’t delve into it much further, as that is not the goal of this post, but just so you know, I was somewhat notable in the RSPS community as I was the coowner of a somewhat famous server called Z508, made by Zach. I was Mod Win, the main person behind Z508, along with Zach, that created one of the best and most perfect combat system at the time and even now.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Progress</span><br>
Right now, I’ve already downloaded a source that’s had a large amount of work done to it (<a href="http://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php/topic,539463.0.html" rel="nofollow noopener">http://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php/topic,539463.0.html</a>), so there’s already a lot of things that are already working. However, I have a keen eye for catching small bugs, even spelling mistakes and such, so I’ll be making a lot of adjustments and changing many things. I hope to not leach from anyone or ask for any spoon feeding, I want to figure everything out myself mainly, but any advice or answers to my questions would be highly appreciated.</p>
<p>Currently, I am just at the very beginning stage of testing the features of the server and reading through all the source files to see what I can understand and note things’ locations so I can go back to change them when I need to.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">RuneSol Project</span><br>
I’m also going to be posting a project thread about my server (link here once it’s posted), listing the various features and functions I am hoping to add. Although, some of these ideas are completely unheard of and very innovating imo, so I may not be releasing everything for people to see publicly.</p>
<p>And of course, if you help me, you can expect to be rewarded by gaining administrative rank on my server while in Alpha, Beta, and when it’s live, though I’m not asking for help in payment of this, it is simply a favor back to you as I get to know you more. Of course, I am looking for mature and responsible qualities from whoever it is I choose, and I reserve the right to remove you if you are disruptive, even if you’ve aided me. But as long as you maintain those qualities, I will be honored and glad to have you as part of my staff.</p>
<p>So, feel free to add me and chat. Otherwise, I’ll still be posting all my questions under this post when I have them.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/need-server-programming-guidance/437128/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/need-server-programming-guidance/437128/1</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 22 Mar 2012 02:07:38 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-437128-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/need-server-programming-guidance/437128.rss">Need Server Programming Guidance</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
