<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Adding Just veng to spellbooks and an item</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/adding-just-veng-to-spellbooks-and-an-item/451313</link>
    <description>Ok. My Blank PI doesn&#39;t include a lunar spellbook. though it does have sprites for it.

What i am wanting to do is to two things.

First off switch out the final teleport for both ancients and Normal (a wildy one and ape atol i think) And make them veangeance. requiring the runes, and 94 mage. How do I do that so i get the animations right and the red skull to appear above them when it does? *no idea where to start*

second.

I want to take the cosmetic &quot;Skull&quot; item. which has no worth, does nothing etc. and change it so it has a &quot;Vengeance&quot; option. Which will make them do the emote and whatnot. but does NOT require 94 mage and runes. I can change item cost and whatnot. 

also, i want it to be so depending on either one you use, it will require 30 seconds to use it again.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 26 Jul 2012 01:47:45 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/adding-just-veng-to-spellbooks-and-an-item/451313.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Adding Just veng to spellbooks and an item</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@grayzai11 grayzai11]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/grayzai11">@grayzai11</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Ok. My Blank PI doesn’t include a lunar spellbook. though it does have sprites for it.</p>
<p>What i am wanting to do is to two things.</p>
<p>First off switch out the final teleport for both ancients and Normal (a wildy one and ape atol i think) And make them veangeance. requiring the runes, and 94 mage. How do I do that so i get the animations right and the red skull to appear above them when it does? <em>no idea where to start</em></p>
<p>second.</p>
<p>I want to take the cosmetic “Skull” item. which has no worth, does nothing etc. and change it so it has a “Vengeance” option. Which will make them do the emote and whatnot. but does NOT require 94 mage and runes. I can change item cost and whatnot.</p>
<p>also, i want it to be so depending on either one you use, it will require 30 seconds to use it again.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/adding-just-veng-to-spellbooks-and-an-item/451313/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/adding-just-veng-to-spellbooks-and-an-item/451313/1</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jul 2012 01:47:45 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-451313-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/adding-just-veng-to-spellbooks-and-an-item/451313.rss">Adding Just veng to spellbooks and an item</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
