<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>The &quot;advertisement&quot; page</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-advertisement-page/222864</link>
    <description>As a long time member, I am posting this.

Shouldn&#39;t the advertisement page be back.
The reason why it was removed was because 459 server&#39;s were supposed to arrive, so everything was cleaned. But then the person never actually released it, and MoparScape never added it back.

Anyways, mods and admins always tell the people to use the &quot;server status page&quot;.
The status page is hard to advertise now a days.
You will only see players posting their website ip, and so they will get 100% up time.

People say this is a learning community, why was it there in the first place?  :|

MoparScape would really be a more better place, as this community is slowly dying from everybody leaving. I remember everyday I would go on the advertisement section, to see 100 registered users and like 90 guests.

Often on the status page, servers would often get &#39;SYI&#39;

Mods and admins say there is too much people to moderate in that section. Well I thought the goal of every forum was to get a big community?

Mods and admins will also say &quot;We can&#39;t add it back because too many people post useless junk and spam there&quot;.
Well mods and admins don&#39;t have to do anything, people can just stop posting in the topic and let it die.

Also mods and admins say people often mass spam there junk in that section. Perhaps add a longer timer to how much you can post in the advertisement section?

Mods and admins will also say no-ip and hamachi servers get confused. Maybe make 2 child boards, hamachi and no-ip?

I have decided to highlight in red all the servers that use fake IP&#39;s on page 1
[URL=http://imageshack.us][IMG]http://img244.imageshack.us/img244/1986/serverswv8.jpg[/img][/URL]
If that is page 1, I wonder what awaits in the next 10 pages

The good old days in MoparScape advertisement section was fun. Looking for servers to play on, without using the status page which every IP is a fake one. It was fun to find servers quick and easy, but on the moparscape status page all it is are fake IP&#39;s which 10% of the time work.

Mods and admins will probably lock this, but I&#39;m just saying my opinions.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2008 15:40:33 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-advertisement-page/222864.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>The &quot;advertisement&quot; page</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Tom Tom]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/tom">@Tom</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>i think it is unfair to use fake ips because people like me i stay up all night to keep my server on and people enjoying itas much as i an give them but the servers with fake ips just take the 100% uptime on the 1st page and leave you on the 5th page when you work so hard!</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-advertisement-page/222864/7">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-advertisement-page/222864/7</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2008 15:40:33 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-222864-7</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-advertisement-page/222864.rss">The &quot;advertisement&quot; page</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The &quot;advertisement&quot; page</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@bballman28 bballman28]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/bballman28">@bballman28</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>When I joined it was on the forums it was better and people could post more details about there server.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-advertisement-page/222864/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-advertisement-page/222864/6</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2008 15:34:15 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-222864-6</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-advertisement-page/222864.rss">The &quot;advertisement&quot; page</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The &quot;advertisement&quot; page</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Ckstunnerscape Ckstunner]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/ckstunnerscape">@Ckstunnerscape</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Bc, I wasnt around back when we had the server page on here, But The fake ips is really making me mad, I always have to check to see if its online…It’s getting annoying, I hope this gets brought up to an admin, Mainly moparisthebest</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-advertisement-page/222864/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-advertisement-page/222864/5</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2008 00:00:10 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-222864-5</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-advertisement-page/222864.rss">The &quot;advertisement&quot; page</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The &quot;advertisement&quot; page</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@hidendra Hidendra]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/hidendra">@hidendra</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>What is, is. Moparisthebest hasn’t even fixed the server status for the fake port’s. Same as with Rich, when I joined moparscape the advertisement section helped find ‘‘good’’ servers, and people even posted in the topics giving feedback, if it was total shit or not, saying hi etc. We at MoparScape fight for what is now, and for even new sections, so I myself doubt the advertisement section will be resurrected.</p>
<p>If Moparisthebest fixed the server status page and he made ‘moderators’ for it that could delete servers etc, that would help make the server status page more usable and less spammed. However, I doubt on that part as well.</p>
<p>Edit: The so called <span class="bbcode-b">24/7 dedicated</span> servers, why do they use fake ips? Obviously it isn’t 24/7, the pages still get scraped by bots whether fake ip or not.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-advertisement-page/222864/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-advertisement-page/222864/4</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2008 23:58:22 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-222864-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-advertisement-page/222864.rss">The &quot;advertisement&quot; page</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The &quot;advertisement&quot; page</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@bballman28 bballman28]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/bballman28">@bballman28</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I agree and I think that they should keep both. In the forums its fun to search for one if you have time. The server status checker page is good for when you want to find a server quickly.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-advertisement-page/222864/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-advertisement-page/222864/3</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2008 23:24:23 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-222864-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-advertisement-page/222864.rss">The &quot;advertisement&quot; page</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The &quot;advertisement&quot; page</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@_Rich Rich]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/_rich">@_Rich</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I agree. Although I think there should be some sectional moderators for that section since I doubt the current moderators and admins would be too busy cleaning it up.</p>
<p>I remember in late 2006 or so when I registered my first account here and the Advertisement section was here, it was nice. People actually added good information on there server, Pictures, Features, Staff List, Help section, etc.</p>
<p>At least if it came back, add a requirment Format to post one, and if they didn’t it should be locked no matter what.</p>
<p>About the Status page:</p>
<p>Yeah it’s pretty messed up now, the pages didn’t help at all. Along with the fake ip’s are ports to advertise their servers is really annoying. Although if the advertisements never came back, mitb should add a voting system on it, instead of listed by uptime, some servers are actually really good, but don’t have that good of uptime, and are far back in the list where not many people actually look at. Plus most of the servers are 100%, are usually up for a day, then never come back on, so it’s pretty much kicking good ones, and dedicated ones back down the list.</p>
<p>At least with the Advertisement one, you could see the dedicated ones, by how many coments/views it has, or just add another thing to status page. Total uptime &amp; downtime, such as rune server has.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-advertisement-page/222864/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-advertisement-page/222864/2</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2008 22:17:49 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-222864-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-advertisement-page/222864.rss">The &quot;advertisement&quot; page</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The &quot;advertisement&quot; page</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@bcdutton bcdutton]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/bcdutton">@bcdutton</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>As a long time member, I am posting this.</p>
<p>Shouldn’t the advertisement page be back.<br>
The reason why it was removed was because 459 server’s were supposed to arrive, so everything was cleaned. But then the person never actually released it, and MoparScape never added it back.</p>
<p>Anyways, mods and admins always tell the people to use the “server status page”.<br>
The status page is hard to advertise now a days.<br>
You will only see players posting their website ip, and so they will get 100% up time.</p>
<p>People say this is a learning community, why was it there in the first place?  <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/expressionless.png?v=6" title=":expressionless:" class="emoji" alt=":expressionless:"></p>
<p>MoparScape would really be a more better place, as this community is slowly dying from everybody leaving. I remember everyday I would go on the advertisement section, to see 100 registered users and like 90 guests.</p>
<p>Often on the status page, servers would often get ‘SYI’</p>
<p>Mods and admins say there is too much people to moderate in that section. Well I thought the goal of every forum was to get a big community?</p>
<p>Mods and admins will also say “We can’t add it back because too many people post useless junk and spam there”.<br>
Well mods and admins don’t have to do anything, people can just stop posting in the topic and let it die.</p>
<p>Also mods and admins say people often mass spam there junk in that section. Perhaps add a longer timer to how much you can post in the advertisement section?</p>
<p>Mods and admins will also say no-ip and hamachi servers get confused. Maybe make 2 child boards, hamachi and no-ip?</p>
<p>I have decided to highlight in red all the servers that use fake IP’s on page 1<br>
<a href="http://imageshack.us" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener"><img src="http://img244.imageshack.us/img244/1986/serverswv8.jpg" alt width="" height=""></a><br>
If that is page 1, I wonder what awaits in the next 10 pages</p>
<p>The good old days in MoparScape advertisement section was fun. Looking for servers to play on, without using the status page which every IP is a fake one. It was fun to find servers quick and easy, but on the moparscape status page all it is are fake IP’s which 10% of the time work.</p>
<p>Mods and admins will probably lock this, but I’m just saying my opinions.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-advertisement-page/222864/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-advertisement-page/222864/1</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2008 22:09:05 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-222864-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-advertisement-page/222864.rss">The &quot;advertisement&quot; page</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
