<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Religion</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/religion/376624</link>
    <description>hello i would like to know how much people are religious and what religio :P

please post what religion u are (or if u have none)

I am Christian :P</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 21 Jan 2011 13:57:18 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>General Discussion</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/religion/376624.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Religion</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Svitkona Svitkona]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/svitkona">@Svitkona</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote no-group" data-post="107" data-topic="376624">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 the wanderer:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>It is my personal belief that this is hell, and if you dont get it right then you get reincarnated and have to go through hell until you get it right. Is God real? I am indecisive as to whether or not the god that is proclaimed in the bible is real. I know for sure that their is a superior being and that he does have somewhat of a influence over our world, but as to whether the tales in the bible are true, no one knows. I feel there has been too many inexplainable acts that have happened that scientists cannot explain. And then what the people say afterwards is even more shocking. People have described feelings of something protecting them and saving them from harm who have had no religious belief in a superior being, or even say God. To me it is like saying we are the only other intelligent lifeforms in the universe.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>You mean something like Karma?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/religion/376624/108">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/religion/376624/108</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 21 Jan 2011 13:57:18 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-376624-108</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/religion/376624.rss">Religion</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Religion</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@the_wanderer The Wanderer]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/the_wanderer">@the_wanderer</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>It is my personal belief that this is hell, and if you dont get it right then you get reincarnated and have to go through hell until you get it right. Is God real? I am indecisive as to whether or not the god that is proclaimed in the bible is real. I know for sure that their is a superior being and that he does have somewhat of a influence over our world, but as to whether the tales in the bible are true, no one knows. I feel there has been too many inexplainable acts that have happened that scientists cannot explain. And then what the people say afterwards is even more shocking. People have described feelings of something protecting them and saving them from harm who have had no religious belief in a superior being, or even say God. To me it is like saying we are the only other intelligent lifeforms in the universe.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/religion/376624/107">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/religion/376624/107</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 21 Jan 2011 07:39:31 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-376624-107</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/religion/376624.rss">Religion</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Religion</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@deathschaos9 DeathsChaos9]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/deathschaos9">@deathschaos9</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Back on topic, this is suppose to be a <span class="bbcode-b">serious</span> discussion.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/religion/376624/106">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/religion/376624/106</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 16 Jan 2011 07:08:34 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-376624-106</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/religion/376624.rss">Religion</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Religion</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@drubrkletern drubrkletern]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/drubrkletern">@drubrkletern</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“ytuio9, post:104, topic:376624”][quote author=drubrkletern link=topic=472547.msg3469039#msg3469039 date=1295150017]<br>
i know how the world was made k?</p>
<p>Once i journied into the arctic, when i was at the exact middle, i decided to clear up the snow, and i saw some words… it said “Made in China”, and that is how the world was made my friends… glad i could share it with you…<br>
[/quote]<br>
Kewl story bro.<br>
How was China made?[/quote]<br>
China is not a country you fool, China was a atom that developed the universe, and blew up, (AKA big bang) thus putting everything<br>
“Made in China”<br>
DUHHH!!!</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/religion/376624/105">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/religion/376624/105</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 16 Jan 2011 07:00:07 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-376624-105</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/religion/376624.rss">Religion</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Religion</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Svitkona Svitkona]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/svitkona">@Svitkona</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“drubrkletern, post:103, topic:376624”]i know how the world was made k?</p>
<p>Once i journied into the arctic, when i was at the exact middle, i decided to clear up the snow, and i saw some words… it said “Made in China”, and that is how the world was made my friends… glad i could share it with you…[/quote]<br>
Kewl story bro.<br>
How was China made?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/religion/376624/104">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/religion/376624/104</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 16 Jan 2011 06:23:43 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-376624-104</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/religion/376624.rss">Religion</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Religion</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@drubrkletern drubrkletern]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/drubrkletern">@drubrkletern</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>i know how the world was made k?</p>
<p>Once i journied into the arctic, when i was at the exact middle, i decided to clear up the snow, and i saw some words… it said “Made in China”, and that is how the world was made my friends… glad i could share it with you…</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/religion/376624/103">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/religion/376624/103</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 16 Jan 2011 03:53:37 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-376624-103</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/religion/376624.rss">Religion</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Religion</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@eyeownyew Eyeownyew]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/eyeownyew">@eyeownyew</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>This isn’t even a discussion or debate anymore…</p>
<p>Sadly, this is how all religious debates end. Immature people cannot respect other people’s opinions, no matter how independent or suttle they vocalize their opinion.</p>
<p><a class="mention" href="/u/canownueazy">@Canownueazy</a> (last page):<br>
Atheism is not a religion. Atheism does not mean you believe in Science. Atheism has the definition of not believing in a higher power or deity that created us.</p>
<p>I could be an Atheist and not even care how we’re made, and live my life to the fullest.<br>
In the end, if a higher power did exist, I would think they would have the common sense to see our perspective and how we have not believed. They would be forgiving, and would not sentence us to an eternity in “hell” because we have an opinion.</p>
<p>After all, we’re all made with an imagination and the ability to have opinions. Why would we have those abilities if the higher power wanted us to worship it?</p>
<p>Honestly, religion sounds like a dictatorship to me. It’s a dictatorship with a sense of freedom. We live a life, and then live an eternity based on one life. It’s exactly how a dictator would rule out bad and good people.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/religion/376624/102">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/religion/376624/102</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 16 Jan 2011 01:55:46 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-376624-102</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/religion/376624.rss">Religion</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Religion</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@usman555 usman555]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/usman555">@usman555</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“I Vain I”]The internet is no place for religion.</p>
<p>Note <em>this is my own perspective, and I know everyone has different ones, so don’t flame</em></p>
<p>Religion shouldn’t exist. People tend to praise what their parent’s praised, or the turn, in faith, to a higher power. Something that is totally unreal. No one thing, object, person, spirit, or anything does what you think. People say pray to God, and your answers will come. Bull shit. Nothing is due to faith, which isn’t real by the way.</p>
<p>God(s) and/or Godess(es) aren’t real.[/quote]FOr a smart guy, you made yourself look like a dumbass in that post. No offense.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/religion/376624/101">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/religion/376624/101</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 16 Jan 2011 01:04:38 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-376624-101</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/religion/376624.rss">Religion</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Religion</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@k0_twin k0 twin]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/k0_twin">@k0_twin</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“Canownueazy, post:97, topic:376624”][quote author=k0 twin link=topic=472547.msg3468713#msg3468713 date=1295131533]</p>
<p>[quote author=Canownueazy link=topic=472547.msg3468711#msg3468711 date=1295131369]</p>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p>Faith means making a virtue out of not thinking. It’s nothing to brag about. And those who preach faith, and enable and elevate it are intellectual slaveholders, keeping mankind in a bondage to fantasy and nonsense that has spawned and justified so much lunacy and destruction. Religion is dangerous because it allows human beings who don’t have all the answers to think that they do. Most people would think it’s wonderful when someone says, “I’m willing, Lord! I’ll do whatever you want me to do!” Except that since there are no gods actually talking to us, that void is filled in by people with their own corruptions and limitations and agendas. And anyone who tells you they know, they just know what happens when you die, I promise you, you don’t. How can I be so sure? Because I don’t know, and you do not possess mental powers that I do not. The only appropriate attitude for man to have about the big questions is not the arrogant certitude that is the hallmark of religion, but doubt. Doubt is humble, and that’s what man needs to be, considering that human history is just a litany of getting shit dead wrong. This is why rational people, anti-religionists, must end their timidity and come out of the closet and assert themselves. And those who consider themselves only moderately religious really need to look in the mirror and realize that the solace and comfort that religion brings you actually comes at a terrible price. If you belonged to a political party or a social club that was tied to as much bigotry, misogyny, homophobia, violence, and sheer ignorance as religion is, you’d resign in protest. To do otherwise is to be an enabler, a mafia wife, for the true devils of extremism that draw their legitimacy from the billions of their fellow travelers. If the world does come to an end here, or wherever, or if it limps into the future, decimated by the effects of religion-inspired nuclear terrorism, let’s remember what the real problem was that we learned how to precipitate mass death before we got past the neurological disorder of wishing for it. That’s it. Grow up or die. </p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>[/quote]You are stupid. The Bible got everything right, and you’re the confused one sir.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p>arrogant certitude that is the hallmark of religion</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>[/quote]It’s been PROVEN, but unfortunately you’re too arrogant to accept facts</p>
<p>Every part of science that contradicts with religion is a theory, and theories are just ideas[/quote]<br>
I didn’t say anything about science, now did I?</p>
<p>And “theories are just ideas”, is exactly what was addressed in the quote I posted. Saying that you don’t know all the answers to life (doubt) is humble, and does not start wars.</p>
<p>Before you respond to my posts I suggest you actually understand them.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/religion/376624/100">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/religion/376624/100</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 16 Jan 2011 00:44:12 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-376624-100</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/religion/376624.rss">Religion</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Religion</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@_Rich Rich]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/_rich">@_Rich</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>ITT<br>
<img src="http://precariousstudios.nfshost.com/shimmie/_images/31104851d5130ceb144493c4b393bc71/2897%20-%20durr%20graph%20hurr%20hurrdurr.png" alt width="" height=""></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/religion/376624/99">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/religion/376624/99</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 16 Jan 2011 00:10:44 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-376624-99</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/religion/376624.rss">Religion</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Religion</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@krackkid Krackkid]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/krackkid">@krackkid</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Only 1 god, deal with it.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/religion/376624/98">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/religion/376624/98</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 16 Jan 2011 00:09:35 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-376624-98</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/religion/376624.rss">Religion</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Religion</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Canownueazy Canownueazy]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/canownueazy">@Canownueazy</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“k0 twin, post:96, topic:376624”][quote author=Canownueazy link=topic=472547.msg3468711#msg3468711 date=1295131369]</p>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p>Faith means making a virtue out of not thinking. It’s nothing to brag about. And those who preach faith, and enable and elevate it are intellectual slaveholders, keeping mankind in a bondage to fantasy and nonsense that has spawned and justified so much lunacy and destruction. Religion is dangerous because it allows human beings who don’t have all the answers to think that they do. Most people would think it’s wonderful when someone says, “I’m willing, Lord! I’ll do whatever you want me to do!” Except that since there are no gods actually talking to us, that void is filled in by people with their own corruptions and limitations and agendas. And anyone who tells you they know, they just know what happens when you die, I promise you, you don’t. How can I be so sure? Because I don’t know, and you do not possess mental powers that I do not. The only appropriate attitude for man to have about the big questions is not the arrogant certitude that is the hallmark of religion, but doubt. Doubt is humble, and that’s what man needs to be, considering that human history is just a litany of getting shit dead wrong. This is why rational people, anti-religionists, must end their timidity and come out of the closet and assert themselves. And those who consider themselves only moderately religious really need to look in the mirror and realize that the solace and comfort that religion brings you actually comes at a terrible price. If you belonged to a political party or a social club that was tied to as much bigotry, misogyny, homophobia, violence, and sheer ignorance as religion is, you’d resign in protest. To do otherwise is to be an enabler, a mafia wife, for the true devils of extremism that draw their legitimacy from the billions of their fellow travelers. If the world does come to an end here, or wherever, or if it limps into the future, decimated by the effects of religion-inspired nuclear terrorism, let’s remember what the real problem was that we learned how to precipitate mass death before we got past the neurological disorder of wishing for it. That’s it. Grow up or die. </p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>[/quote]You are stupid. The Bible got everything right, and you’re the confused one sir.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>[quote]arrogant certitude that is the hallmark of religion[/quote][/quote]It’s been PROVEN, but unfortunately you’re too arrogant to accept facts</p>
<p>Every part of science that contradicts with religion is a theory, and theories are just ideas</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/religion/376624/97">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/religion/376624/97</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 16 Jan 2011 00:00:17 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-376624-97</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/religion/376624.rss">Religion</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Religion</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@k0_twin k0 twin]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/k0_twin">@k0_twin</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“Canownueazy, post:95, topic:376624”][quote author=k0 twin link=topic=472547.msg3468708#msg3468708 date=1295131154]</p>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p>Faith means making a virtue out of not thinking. It’s nothing to brag about. And those who preach faith, and enable and elevate it are intellectual slaveholders, keeping mankind in a bondage to fantasy and nonsense that has spawned and justified so much lunacy and destruction. Religion is dangerous because it allows human beings who don’t have all the answers to think that they do. Most people would think it’s wonderful when someone says, “I’m willing, Lord! I’ll do whatever you want me to do!” Except that since there are no gods actually talking to us, that void is filled in by people with their own corruptions and limitations and agendas. And anyone who tells you they know, they just know what happens when you die, I promise you, you don’t. How can I be so sure? Because I don’t know, and you do not possess mental powers that I do not. The only appropriate attitude for man to have about the big questions is not the arrogant certitude that is the hallmark of religion, but doubt. Doubt is humble, and that’s what man needs to be, considering that human history is just a litany of getting shit dead wrong. This is why rational people, anti-religionists, must end their timidity and come out of the closet and assert themselves. And those who consider themselves only moderately religious really need to look in the mirror and realize that the solace and comfort that religion brings you actually comes at a terrible price. If you belonged to a political party or a social club that was tied to as much bigotry, misogyny, homophobia, violence, and sheer ignorance as religion is, you’d resign in protest. To do otherwise is to be an enabler, a mafia wife, for the true devils of extremism that draw their legitimacy from the billions of their fellow travelers. If the world does come to an end here, or wherever, or if it limps into the future, decimated by the effects of religion-inspired nuclear terrorism, let’s remember what the real problem was that we learned how to precipitate mass death before we got past the neurological disorder of wishing for it. That’s it. Grow up or die. </p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>[/quote]You are stupid. The Bible got everything right, and you’re the confused one sir.[/quote]</p>
<blockquote>arrogant certitude that is the hallmark of religion</blockquote>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/religion/376624/96">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/religion/376624/96</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 15 Jan 2011 22:45:33 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-376624-96</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/religion/376624.rss">Religion</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Religion</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Canownueazy Canownueazy]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/canownueazy">@Canownueazy</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“k0 twin, post:94, topic:376624”][quote]Faith means making a virtue out of not thinking. It’s nothing to brag about. And those who preach faith, and enable and elevate it are intellectual slaveholders, keeping mankind in a bondage to fantasy and nonsense that has spawned and justified so much lunacy and destruction. Religion is dangerous because it allows human beings who don’t have all the answers to think that they do. Most people would think it’s wonderful when someone says, “I’m willing, Lord! I’ll do whatever you want me to do!” Except that since there are no gods actually talking to us, that void is filled in by people with their own corruptions and limitations and agendas. And anyone who tells you they know, they just know what happens when you die, I promise you, you don’t. How can I be so sure? Because I don’t know, and you do not possess mental powers that I do not. The only appropriate attitude for man to have about the big questions is not the arrogant certitude that is the hallmark of religion, but doubt. Doubt is humble, and that’s what man needs to be, considering that human history is just a litany of getting shit dead wrong. This is why rational people, anti-religionists, must end their timidity and come out of the closet and assert themselves. And those who consider themselves only moderately religious really need to look in the mirror and realize that the solace and comfort that religion brings you actually comes at a terrible price. If you belonged to a political party or a social club that was tied to as much bigotry, misogyny, homophobia, violence, and sheer ignorance as religion is, you’d resign in protest. To do otherwise is to be an enabler, a mafia wife, for the true devils of extremism that draw their legitimacy from the billions of their fellow travelers. If the world does come to an end here, or wherever, or if it limps into the future, decimated by the effects of religion-inspired nuclear terrorism, let’s remember what the real problem was that we learned how to precipitate mass death before we got past the neurological disorder of wishing for it. That’s it. Grow up or die. [/quote][/quote]You are stupid. The Bible got everything right, and you’re the confused one sir.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/religion/376624/95">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/religion/376624/95</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 15 Jan 2011 22:42:49 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-376624-95</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/religion/376624.rss">Religion</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Religion</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@k0_twin k0 twin]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/k0_twin">@k0_twin</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <blockquote>Faith means making a virtue out of not thinking. It's nothing to brag about. And those who preach faith, and enable and elevate it are intellectual slaveholders, keeping mankind in a bondage to fantasy and nonsense that has spawned and justified so much lunacy and destruction. Religion is dangerous because it allows human beings who don't have all the answers to think that they do. Most people would think it's wonderful when someone says, "I'm willing, Lord! I'll do whatever you want me to do!" Except that since there are no gods actually talking to us, that void is filled in by people with their own corruptions and limitations and agendas. And anyone who tells you they know, they just know what happens when you die, I promise you, you don't. How can I be so sure? Because I don't know, and you do not possess mental powers that I do not. The only appropriate attitude for man to have about the big questions is not the arrogant certitude that is the hallmark of religion, but doubt. Doubt is humble, and that's what man needs to be, considering that human history is just a litany of getting shit dead wrong. This is why rational people, anti-religionists, must end their timidity and come out of the closet and assert themselves. And those who consider themselves only moderately religious really need to look in the mirror and realize that the solace and comfort that religion brings you actually comes at a terrible price. If you belonged to a political party or a social club that was tied to as much bigotry, misogyny, homophobia, violence, and sheer ignorance as religion is, you'd resign in protest. To do otherwise is to be an enabler, a mafia wife, for the true devils of extremism that draw their legitimacy from the billions of their fellow travelers. If the world does come to an end here, or wherever, or if it limps into the future, decimated by the effects of religion-inspired nuclear terrorism, let's remember what the real problem was that we learned how to precipitate mass death before we got past the neurological disorder of wishing for it. That's it. Grow up or die.</blockquote>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/religion/376624/94">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/religion/376624/94</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 15 Jan 2011 22:39:14 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-376624-94</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/religion/376624.rss">Religion</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Religion</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@usman555 usman555]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/usman555">@usman555</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>By the way, who ever noticed that all good athiest scientist turned christian or so? That’s because science doesn’t go as far as religion does. I am Muslim, I know a lot that can explain why I am with Islam, but I doubt anyone would read all of it.<br>
Now, every dinosaur died because god only created enough animals for the fossil fuels we need. If he created one more, then it would be useless. It would just be an extra fossil. We have as many as we need.</p>
<p>EDIT:</p>
<p>The size of the universe is not imaginable by the human mind. It expands faster than the speed of light.<br>
Let’s play the size game, where we find how large things are.</p>
<p>We live in the Earth.<br>
The Earth has around 6-7 billion humans<br>
The Earth is one of the eight planets in our solar system.<br>
The Sun manages our solar system.<br>
The Sun is a medium sized star.<br>
The Sun is 1.3 million times larger than Earth.<br>
The Solar System contains eight planets and one Sun.<br>
The Solar System is in a galaxy called the Milky Way<br>
The Milky Way consists of many other systems.<br>
The Milky Way is one of the billions and trillions of galaxys.<br>
The Universe is growing with galaxys as you read this.<br>
And back to us, how large are we?</p>
<p>So if you get a D- or A+ on your math test or so, don’t be afraid. Because we aren’t even 1/1000000000000th of a pixel when we look at an image of the universe itself. And if we die, we are only the 6-7 billions of humans that will all die at some point.</p>
<p>Now, if you want to learn why I am with Islam, go to <a href="http://www.HarunYahya.com" rel="nofollow noopener">http://www.HarunYahya.com</a> where this magnificent scientist explains miracles mixed with Islamic proof and explains Islam mixed with scientific proof.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/religion/376624/93">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/religion/376624/93</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 15 Jan 2011 22:34:19 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-376624-93</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/religion/376624.rss">Religion</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Religion</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Svitkona Svitkona]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/svitkona">@Svitkona</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Well said, COUE; A good debate. This is how I imagine my debating technique should be except I am still learning about the world and am therefore not qualified to answer all your questions about religion. This is how religious debate should always be like.</p>
<p>In short…<br>
I am legend.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/religion/376624/92">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/religion/376624/92</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 15 Jan 2011 22:25:36 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-376624-92</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/religion/376624.rss">Religion</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Religion</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Canownueazy Canownueazy]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/canownueazy">@Canownueazy</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“eyeownyew, post:83, topic:376624”][quote author=flj0yter0p link=topic=472547.msg3468453#msg3468453 date=1295116917]</p>
<p>[quote author=eyeownyew link=topic=472547.msg3468443#msg3468443 date=1295116328]</p>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p><a class="mention" href="/u/casey">@Casey</a> Your damn right</p>
<p>I hate people who tell me god created everything, I ask them something they dont expect. “If god created everything why did he create war?” Usually they say Humans created it to make a balance between good and bad. I end the conversation with “Why did god create bad? You wouldnt need a balance if there was no bad would you?”<br>
[/quote]To easy to answer your little 5 year old pathetic questions. I know far to much even though I can still be 13.</p>
<p>If god created everything why did he create war?: Way to easy. If there wasn’t war, there would be an inbalance in the Earth. Ever wondered how the Earth is perfect and has all that humans need? God knew that we would be using fossil fuels so much, that’s why he created all of these dinosaurs. For them to die, for the fossils, for the fuel! No war, things would never of have changed. Maybe there was a nation or tribe he needed to get rid of.</p>
<p>Why did god create bad?: If all was good, then there would be nothing for good to fight against. For example. If everyone had a million dollars, the people who create these kinds of foods like cereals will stop their business. You know why? Becuz they do it for money and now they have a million dollars. Now if there were people who were poor, then those people would be the ones doing the jobs.</p>
<p>You wouldn’t need a balance if there was no bad: If everything is good, what’s the point for living? Kill yourself, VY Canis Majoris (the largest know star, 8.8 billion times larger than the sun) won’t give a shit.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Why did all dinosaurs die, then?<br>
(Probably going to say “For our safety”)<br>
Reply to ^^: Then how were other animals created, yet only dinosaurs were the animals to die?</p>
<p>Science and Religion are both complicated, yet I definitely side with Science. It’s logical.<br>
[/quote]Like usman555 stated, that could be the reason.</p>
<p>Ever think how there is fire to make you feel warm on cold seasons?<br>
How most of the world is water and is needed ALOT, like i can’t stand 2-3 hours without drinking some.<br>
How every thing in this world has seeds to multiply.</p>
<p>As for other planets existing… A few days ago i saw a national geographic video stating they found a planet that is made of umm… idk how to say it in english but gas and fuel and stuff, it even rains that. Maybe it’s purpose is if in future we get better at technology and run out of materials here to go and get some off those planets?</p>
<p>I just don’t believe all of those stuff are setup all by themselves.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Well.<br>
How can you explain one thing?:<br>
Judaism wasn’t even created until nearly 3,000 B.C.<br>
Christianity/Catholicism wasn’t even created until ~30 B.C.<br>
If we follow the Bible, Adam and Eve should have been Jews themselves.<br>
Following history, the creation of this planet was ~60 Billion years ago.<br>
In the Bible, God creates Earth and puts Adam and Eve on Earth.<br>
How do you explain the 59,999,997,000 years of delay for the creation of the religion?</p>
<p>Another point:<br>
The universe is ever-expanding. If God did create us, he would have created others as well.<br>
Observing how much of the universe exists currently (meaning currently visible), it would be highly unlikely that we are the first self-superior race to exist.<br>
If another race is superior to us, or is similar to us and has aged more, I have another point:<br>
Considering how we have 25% of the visible universe mapped (This is a FACT. I attended a presentation of Astronomy in Boulder, with a professor who is working with NASA and is currently using the Hubble Satellite. He is the Director at the Boulder University Department of Astronomy), another race should have more of the universe mapped.<br>
After considering that, you would think they would have enough technology to reach us.<br>
Seeing as we have no proof of any extra-terrestrial existence, I myself do not believe in the religions of Judaism, Christianity, or Catholicism.<br>
If extra-terrestrials to exist, we may or may not find out.</p>
<p>One last point against religion:<br>
Seeing as we have 25% of the currently visible universe mapped (3D X/Y/Z axis),  we would have visibly noticed any traveling machines or “ships” of any sort within the radius we have mapped.<br>
If no ships are within that radius, we have no proof of extra-terrestrial existence.<br>
If any other race did exist, they knew we were here and they did want to confront us, they would be traveling here.<br>
Which leaves us with… Absolutely no evidence of any sort.<br>
One point against what I said above:<br>
Scientific theory: If you travel above the speed of light, you should not be visible from any distance, angle, or location. In a black hole, it is theorized that you would freeze in one certain location.<br>
One point against that point right there^^:<br>
Black hole theory: If any extra-terrestrial machines or “ships” were traveling here, the odds are that they would encounter a black hole (still unproven to exist). If they did encounter such a devilish natural and spacial disaster, they would be frozen in time to our vision. That would make it even more noticeable if an extra-terrestrial machine or “ship” was heading for us.</p>
<p>From all of what I have said so far, I must conclude:<br>
Science goes against religion and (visible) extra-terrestrial existence. Religion stays neutral with extra-terrestrial existence.<br>
Science is far more easily perceivable to the human mind, or any mind we have knowledge of existing.<br>
Therefore, it is logical for anyone to believe in Science more than Religion.</p>
<p>Note: This is all about Science being correct. I would make another long post about Religion “being correct” that would also be flamed, but I am stating what I personally believe. Therefore, I’d rather not try.</p>
<p>If you actually read all of this post, I respect you.[/quote]Atheism is defined as a lack of belief in a supernatural being, creator, or deity. Briefly, it is a lack of belief in God.</p>
<p>It is one of the major opponents of the Christian Church and Christian beliefs. It has always been diretly related to materialism. Summed up, the more materialistic a society is, the less spiritual it becomes. The less spiritual it becomes, the stronger atheism affects that society.</p>
<p>Therefore, the more materialistic a society becomes, the more atheism strengthens over it.</p>
<p>Atheism relies mostly on logic, analysis, and science. They do not believe in faith, nor the miracles of the Bible.</p>
<p>Atheism, though has major flaws. At first glance, it seems atheism has a strong, irrefutable, non-debatable position. Like so many things in this world, it looks good only on the outside, but actually is weak on the inside - a foundation built on sand.</p>
<p>Atheism has three major flaws:</p>
<p>Atheist Statement No. 1 - “Atheism declares it does not believe in faith, that science is the way to truth because it does not rely on faith unlike religion. Science does not rely on faith and therefore cannot be biased.”</p>
<p>Christian answer: Even in science, we still need a certain degree of faith in scientists and researchers since we ourselves cannot possibly verify all their findings to prove that what they are saying is true.</p>
<p>Unless you can verify scientists’ findings one by one for yourself, you will have to accept their “word” at face value. You will have to believe that what they’re saying is true. You will have to have “faith” in their words.</p>
<p>Look. In the past, we’ve had “scientific errors” committed by scientists. Errors such as scientific facts that were declared as truth but were later found out to be false or in doubt.</p>
<p>Among numerous examples, one example is found in medical science. For many years, scientists/researchers have always declared that damage to the human spinal cord was permanent and irreversible. This was a scientific fact, established as the truth before.</p>
<p>However, only recently, this previous scientific fact was proven to be, well, untrue. Modern findings have proven that the human spinal cord does regenerate, albeit, in a very slow manner. A lot of people with damaged spinal cords have been able to walk, much against the declaration of their doctors that all hope was lost.</p>
<p>That science is not based on faith is totally false. Therefore, this refutes the first statement of atheism.</p>
<p>As St. Francis of Assisi wisely said “Faith is higher than reason. Reason is useless… unless you believe.”</p>
<p>Atheist Statement No. 2 - "Science is based only on purely objective facts, while religion is partially subjective and therefore cannot be purely objective. "</p>
<p>Christian answer: Science relies on objectivity, and needs to utilize a method called the “scientific method”. The scientific method relies on observation, experimentation, data-gathering, etc.</p>
<p>Once science loses its objectivity, or becomes partially subjective, it loses its credibility as a discipline.</p>
<p>Therein lies the problem. The scientific method does provide purely objective data, BUT scientists still have to "interpret them. Since scientists are only human, the interpretation of the data becomes mixed with personal opinions and become “partially subjective”. This cannot be avoided.</p>
<p>Scientists are human beings with different beliefs, religions, philosophies, and come from various countries and cultures throughout the globe.</p>
<p>Take for example the debate on the origin of the universe. This major debate has been going on for centuries, and has divided the scientific community into “creationist scientists” and “evolutionist scientists”.</p>
<p>The creationist scientists believe that the universe has order, design, and was created by an intelligent, omnpiotent being, a god. God is the creator of the universe.</p>
<p>The evolutionist scientists believe otherwise. They state that the universe has no design, has no order and is random. They reject the idea of a god, a creator of our universe.</p>
<p>And it doesn’t even matter who has more numbers on either side. The truth is never based on “majority wins”.</p>
<p>Say for example, my friend and I hid a silver coin inside a box. Now, we make a survey and ask all people around the world if they believe a coin exists in the box or not.</p>
<p>Even if all people around the world said they don’t believe a coin exists in the box, the truth is not affected by their numbers. My friend and I know the truth that a coin does exist because we hid it ourselves! So truth is not based on majority opinion.</p>
<p>Atheist statement number 2 is therefore false.</p>
<p>Atheist Statement No. 3) “Science is better than religion because it relies on an objective method - the scientific method. This method produces truth because it is based on objective data, experimentations, logic, etc. Religion does not use an objective method and is based on opinion, speculation, etc. It lacks “scientific proof”, on “miracles” in the Holy Bible.”</p>
<p>Christian answer: Science does rely on an objective method, but by what authority does the “scientific method” produce truth? By what authority does science possess when it says we must believe science because it utilizes the “scientific method”?</p>
<p>I mean you cannot state that science is an authority of truth simpy because it uses the scientific method. It’s like saying “I therefore conclude that science produces truth because it uses the scientific method.”</p>
<p>By what authority?</p>
<p>How will you prove using the scientific method does produce truth? Because it’s “scientific”? Because science said so? Again, the question “By what authority does science have by proclaiming to be the truth than religion”?</p>
<p>The statement “The results of the scientific method should be followed” is unscientific because it is a value statement that does not get its authority from anywhere but itself.</p>
<p>“We should use the scientific method.” Why should we? “It proves itself.” How does it prove itself? “It uses the scientific method.”</p>
<p>Atheist Statement: “The scientific method is true because it works and because it is axiomatic (self-evident).”</p>
<p>Christian answer: Sounds a lot like faith to me. Who decides what is axiomatic? does the scientific method decide it? That makes it circular if it does. If not, then it is not scientific itself.</p>
<p>I would have to do all the experiments to come to that conclusion. Other than that, I take it on faith that all of the scientists who did the experiments and reviewed them and tested them are not lying to me. That is my point.</p>
<p>You cannot use the “scientific method” as a reason to make science as an authority of truth, simply because the only way to prove science as the truth is to use the “scientific method”! The logic is circular.</p>
<p>And yes, the miracles in the Bible have been verified by both atheist (for objectivity) and theist (God-believing) scientists as true historical events. Events such as the Exodus from Egypt, David slaying Goliath, parting of the Red Sea, etc. were tested and researched using modern scientific methods. Watch “Secrets of the Bible” at Cable TV’s “Discovery Channel”.</p>
<p>At a different cable channel, underwater cameras showed pictures of ancient relics -particularly a large “chariot wheel” deep beneath the Red Sea. When traced back, the design of the wheel was identical to the chariots used in Egypt at around the time Moses’ parting of the Red Sea occurred!</p>
<p>God has been so gracious as to provide solid, irrefutable evidence to believers and non-believers alike.</p>
<p>Atheist statement number 3 is therefore false.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/religion/376624/91">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/religion/376624/91</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 15 Jan 2011 22:09:07 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-376624-91</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/religion/376624.rss">Religion</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Religion</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@k0_twin k0 twin]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/k0_twin">@k0_twin</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>You can’t argue religion with logic.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/religion/376624/90">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/religion/376624/90</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 15 Jan 2011 22:00:46 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-376624-90</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/religion/376624.rss">Religion</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Religion</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@eyeownyew Eyeownyew]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/eyeownyew">@eyeownyew</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“ytuio9, post:88, topic:376624”]Thanks for your explanation, I kind of get it now.</p>
<p>I do believe life exists in places other than on Earth, but Religion never disproved that. I can see why you might think science is more believable, however.[/quote]<br>
Neither Science or Religion proves extra-terrestrial life… Both of them make it likely, but probability is an arguable matter of course.<br>
Thank you for respecting my opinion, I was expecting to be trolled constantly. <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=5" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/religion/376624/89">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/religion/376624/89</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 15 Jan 2011 21:13:07 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-376624-89</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/religion/376624.rss">Religion</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Religion</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Svitkona Svitkona]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/svitkona">@Svitkona</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Thanks for your explanation, I kind of get it now.</p>
<p>I do believe life exists in places other than on Earth, but Religion never disproved that. I can see why you might think science is more believable, however.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/religion/376624/88">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/religion/376624/88</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 15 Jan 2011 20:27:52 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-376624-88</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/religion/376624.rss">Religion</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Religion</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@eyeownyew Eyeownyew]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/eyeownyew">@eyeownyew</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“ytuio9, post:86, topic:376624”][quote]<br>
Visibility of the universe goes with extra-terrestrial existence.<br>
Extra-terrestrial existence goes with Religion and Science. It makes Science more believable.<br>
[/quote]<br>
Kind of don’t understand that… mind explaining?[/quote]<br>
Of course, I don’t mind.</p>
<p>As I posted a few posts ago, we have 25% of the visible universe mapped. That may seem like a small amount to you, but our galaxy (the Milky Way) is less than one quadrillionth of what we visibly see.<br>
For analogy/ratio purposes, picture this:<br>
If the Milky Way was 150 meters in radius…<br>
The solar system is 150/144,000,000 or 0.001 millimeters in radius or 1 micron.<br>
This makes it incredibly hard to believe that we are the only life existing.<br>
We have no proof that we are or are not the only life-forms currently existing in the universe.<br>
Doing the math. our Solar System is 1/1,500,000 of the Milky Way.<br>
Multiply the denominator by 1,000,000,000,000,000…<br>
The answer is: 1,500,000,000,000,000,000,000.<br>
Our Solar System ~1/1,500,000,000,000,000,000,000 of the visible universe (the ~ sign is because some measurements are likely incorrect, and the universe is ever-expanding).<br>
Considering that ratio, you can conclude that it is HIGHLY unlikely that we are the only living life-forms to exist.<br>
Science can depict extra-terrestrial existence, yet religion cannot and never will be able to.<br>
If you know what I’m getting at, Science becomes slightly more believable and provable every day that our technology increases, and never once has a slight bit of religion been proven.<br>
Sure, it’s in history. History has been altered. Majorly or minorly, we are completely unaware of the extent to which it has been altered.<br>
Science cannot be tampered with. Yet it continues to become more and more believable and proven every day.</p>
<p>I conclude that: No matter how long the world-wide debate of Religion vs. Science continues, Science will be come more and more believable and it will eventually prevail.<br>
We may never know the answer. The sun could explode before we have nearly enough information to conclude a scientifically, historically or religiously proven answer.</p>
<p>We have no proven answer. It is personal belief. I personally believe that Science is more believable and will prevail in the end, no matter how long it takes.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/religion/376624/87">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/religion/376624/87</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 15 Jan 2011 20:15:07 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-376624-87</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/religion/376624.rss">Religion</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Religion</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Svitkona Svitkona]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/svitkona">@Svitkona</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <blockquote>Visibility of the universe goes with extra-terrestrial existence.
 Extra-terrestrial existence goes with Religion and Science. It makes Science more believable.</blockquote>
Kind of don't understand that.. mind explaining?
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/religion/376624/86">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/religion/376624/86</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 15 Jan 2011 20:00:05 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-376624-86</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/religion/376624.rss">Religion</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Religion</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@eyeownyew Eyeownyew]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/eyeownyew">@eyeownyew</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Cleaning up the quote a bit…</p>
<p>Visibility of the universe goes with extra-terrestrial existence.<br>
Extra-terrestrial existence goes with Religion and Science. It makes Science more believable.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group quote-modified" data-post="84" data-topic="376624">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 ytuio9:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Also, you say “if we follow the Bible”… what about other religions?</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I have studied multiple other religions. Honestly, every one of the other religions I have studied are less believable than a toddler lying (not meant to be an insult, just an analogy).<br>
Mormonism: Every religiously significant point in Mormonism’s history is unproven. In other religions, they usually have at least some historical proof found by Archaeologists or Scientists of some sort.<br>
Islam: I’m in the process of studying this religion in school. So far, it is nearly as believable or historically proven as Christianity or the other popular religions. Personally, I feel it is incorrect because so few people follow it and the only people I’ve known to follow it live less than comfortable lives. This is just personal belief, so I have no proof against Islam.<br>
Buddhism: This is actually a religion that believes in religious freedom and is open to other beliefs, so I am a personal fan of Buddhism. I won’t state any proof with or against it, because there is far too much to study on such a religion.</p>
<p>Any other religion, I have not studied yet. I don’t see a reason why they would be more believable, as even the most popular religions are unproven.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/religion/376624/85">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/religion/376624/85</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 15 Jan 2011 19:50:34 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-376624-85</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/religion/376624.rss">Religion</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Religion</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Svitkona Svitkona]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/svitkona">@Svitkona</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“eyeownyew, post:83, topic:376624”][quote author=flj0yter0p link=topic=472547.msg3468453#msg3468453 date=1295116917]</p>
<p>[quote author=eyeownyew link=topic=472547.msg3468443#msg3468443 date=1295116328]</p>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p><a class="mention" href="/u/casey">@Casey</a> Your damn right</p>
<p>I hate people who tell me god created everything, I ask them something they dont expect. “If god created everything why did he create war?” Usually they say Humans created it to make a balance between good and bad. I end the conversation with “Why did god create bad? You wouldnt need a balance if there was no bad would you?”<br>
[/quote]To easy to answer your little 5 year old pathetic questions. I know far to much even though I can still be 13.</p>
<p>If god created everything why did he create war?: Way to easy. If there wasn’t war, there would be an inbalance in the Earth. Ever wondered how the Earth is perfect and has all that humans need? God knew that we would be using fossil fuels so much, that’s why he created all of these dinosaurs. For them to die, for the fossils, for the fuel! No war, things would never of have changed. Maybe there was a nation or tribe he needed to get rid of.</p>
<p>Why did god create bad?: If all was good, then there would be nothing for good to fight against. For example. If everyone had a million dollars, the people who create these kinds of foods like cereals will stop their business. You know why? Becuz they do it for money and now they have a million dollars. Now if there were people who were poor, then those people would be the ones doing the jobs.</p>
<p>You wouldn’t need a balance if there was no bad: If everything is good, what’s the point for living? Kill yourself, VY Canis Majoris (the largest know star, 8.8 billion times larger than the sun) won’t give a shit.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Why did all dinosaurs die, then?<br>
(Probably going to say “For our safety”)<br>
Reply to ^^: Then how were other animals created, yet only dinosaurs were the animals to die?</p>
<p>Science and Religion are both complicated, yet I definitely side with Science. It’s logical.<br>
[/quote]Like usman555 stated, that could be the reason.</p>
<p>Ever think how there is fire to make you feel warm on cold seasons?<br>
How most of the world is water and is needed ALOT, like i can’t stand 2-3 hours without drinking some.<br>
How every thing in this world has seeds to multiply.</p>
<p>As for other planets existing… A few days ago i saw a national geographic video stating they found a planet that is made of umm… idk how to say it in english but gas and fuel and stuff, it even rains that. Maybe it’s purpose is if in future we get better at technology and run out of materials here to go and get some off those planets?</p>
<p>I just don’t believe all of those stuff are setup all by themselves.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Well.<br>
How can you explain one thing?:<br>
Judaism wasn’t even created until nearly 3,000 B.C.<br>
Christianity/Catholicism wasn’t even created until ~30 B.C.<br>
If we follow the Bible, Adam and Eve should have been Jews themselves.<br>
Following history, the creation of this planet was ~60 Billion years ago.<br>
In the Bible, God creates Earth and puts Adam and Eve on Earth.<br>
How do you explain the 59,999,997,000 years of delay for the creation of the religion?</p>
<p>Another point:<br>
The universe is ever-expanding. If God did create us, he would have created others as well.<br>
Observing how much of the universe exists currently (meaning currently visible), it would be highly unlikely that we are the first self-superior race to exist.<br>
If another race is superior to us, or is similar to us and has aged more, I have another point:<br>
Considering how we have 25% of the visible universe mapped (This is a FACT. I attended a presentation of Astronomy in Boulder, with a professor who is working with NASA and is currently using the Hubble Satellite. He is the Director at the Boulder University Department of Astronomy), another race should have more of the universe mapped.<br>
After considering that, you would think they would have enough technology to reach us.<br>
Seeing as we have no proof of any extra-terrestrial existence, I myself do not believe in the religions of Judaism, Christianity, or Catholicism.<br>
If extra-terrestrials to exist, we may or may not find out.</p>
<p>One last point against religion:<br>
Seeing as we have 25% of the currently visible universe mapped (3D X/Y/Z axis),  we would have visibly noticed any traveling machines or “ships” of any sort within the radius we have mapped.<br>
If no ships are within that radius, we have no proof of extra-terrestrial existence.<br>
If any other race did exist, they knew we were here and they did want to confront us, they would be traveling here.<br>
Which leaves us with… Absolutely no evidence of any sort.<br>
One point against what I said above:<br>
Scientific theory: If you travel above the speed of light, you should not be visible from any distance, angle, or location. In a black hole, it is theorized that you would freeze in one certain location.<br>
One point against that point right there^^:<br>
Black hole theory: If any extra-terrestrial machines or “ships” were traveling here, the odds are that they would encounter a black hole (still unproven to exist). If they did encounter such a devilish natural and spacial disaster, they would be frozen in time to our vision. That would make it even more noticeable if an extra-terrestrial machine or “ship” was heading for us.</p>
<p>From all of what I have said so far, I must conclude:<br>
Science goes against religion and (visible) extra-terrestrial existence. Religion stays neutral with extra-terrestrial existence.<br>
Science is far more easily perceivable to the human mind, or any mind we have knowledge of existing.<br>
Therefore, it is logical for anyone to believe in Science more than Religion.</p>
<p>Note: This is all about Science being correct. I would make another long post about Religion “being correct” that would also be flamed, but I am stating what I personally believe. Therefore, I’d rather not try.</p>
<p>If you actually read all of this post, I respect you.[/quote]</p>
<p>What does the visibility of the universe have to do with religion?</p>
<p>Also, you say “if we follow the Bible”… what about other religions?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/religion/376624/84">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/religion/376624/84</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 15 Jan 2011 19:31:31 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-376624-84</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/religion/376624.rss">Religion</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
