<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>[525] I need some help please!</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/525-i-need-some-help-please/368488</link>
    <description>Alright so I have a 525, but I have some problems and things I would like to add and I am a nooby coder so please do not judge 

1. When weilding a gmaul and then clicking on DFS or other way around they both are being worn at the same time, giving bonuses that are unfair. If someone can show me how to fix it please do so 
2. I would like to add corp drops, I know how to add them, I just do not know how to add the &quot;rare-ity&quot; if that is even a word lmfao to the drops. Such as sigils, I would like them to be like 1/100 drops.
3. Going with number 2, I would like for the corp to be able to drop sigils and use them on blessed spirit shields (which must be obtained through an economic base, not just spawning it with money) to make the spirit shield. But if you know how to just make the drops 1/100 then I will just make it spirit shields if you do not know how to do the sigil to spirit shield.
4. I would like the server chat &quot;/(message)&quot; to be for donator, mods, and admins only.
5. This one I don&#39;t really mind but I would like to have it working. On my server pvp armors are donator only. So when a non-donor kills a donator risking pvp armors the non-donor does not get the loot. I would like for it to be that the non-donor does get the loot, but cannot wear it and may sell it using the command :ellall because I believe it is unfair to make a kill and then not get any reward for it.
6. If anyone could please show me where I could download sprites for all chaotic weapons and staff of light and could tell me how to set them up I would be very happy. The sprites I have for those now aren&#39;t that good.
7. I think my server is based on turmoil, when I active piety it doesn&#39;t have an animation but when I de-active piety it does a little throwing hands up emote, I would like to get rid of that please 
8. I would also like a jail, if you could just show me how to add the command for admins only and leave the x and y coordinates to me, I will find a place unless I think of one before anyone answers this, then I will edit it.
9. I also need a working ::coords command to add a jail with lmfao 

I used to be able to code 317&#39;s, but the change to 508+&#39;s has got me completely confused and I do not enjoy coding 317&#39;s anymore. =[

And I think that is it for now, I am not asking for someone to do all of these for me but I am asking for as much help as you can help me with if you wouldn&#39;t mind doing that please. 

Thank you!
Noob.Coder</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 13 Nov 2010 04:27:34 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/525-i-need-some-help-please/368488.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>[525] I need some help please!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Noob.Coder Noob.Coder]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/noob.coder">@Noob.Coder</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Alright so I have a 525, but I have some problems and things I would like to add and I am a nooby coder so please do not judge</p>
<ol>
<li>When weilding a gmaul and then clicking on DFS or other way around they both are being worn at the same time, giving bonuses that are unfair. If someone can show me how to fix it please do so</li>
<li>I would like to add corp drops, I know how to add them, I just do not know how to add the “rare-ity” if that is even a word lmfao to the drops. Such as sigils, I would like them to be like 1/100 drops.</li>
<li>Going with number 2, I would like for the corp to be able to drop sigils and use them on blessed spirit shields (which must be obtained through an economic base, not just spawning it with money) to make the spirit shield. But if you know how to just make the drops 1/100 then I will just make it spirit shields if you do not know how to do the sigil to spirit shield.</li>
<li>I would like the server chat “/(message)” to be for donator, mods, and admins only.</li>
<li>This one I don’t really mind but I would like to have it working. On my server pvp armors are donator only. So when a non-donor kills a donator risking pvp armors the non-donor does not get the loot. I would like for it to be that the non-donor does get the loot, but cannot wear it and may sell it using the command :ellall because I believe it is unfair to make a kill and then not get any reward for it.</li>
<li>If anyone could please show me where I could download sprites for all chaotic weapons and staff of light and could tell me how to set them up I would be very happy. The sprites I have for those now aren’t that good.</li>
<li>I think my server is based on turmoil, when I active piety it doesn’t have an animation but when I de-active piety it does a little throwing hands up emote, I would like to get rid of that please</li>
<li>I would also like a jail, if you could just show me how to add the command for admins only and leave the x and y coordinates to me, I will find a place unless I think of one before anyone answers this, then I will edit it.</li>
<li>I also need a working ::coords command to add a jail with lmfao</li>
</ol>
<p>I used to be able to code 317’s, but the change to 508+'s has got me completely confused and I do not enjoy coding 317’s anymore. =[</p>
<p>And I think that is it for now, I am not asking for someone to do all of these for me but I am asking for as much help as you can help me with if you wouldn’t mind doing that please.</p>
<p>Thank you!<br>
Noob.Coder</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/525-i-need-some-help-please/368488/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/525-i-need-some-help-please/368488/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 13 Nov 2010 04:27:34 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-368488-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/525-i-need-some-help-please/368488.rss">[525] I need some help please!</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
