<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>OSHD #530 -: Oldschool Runescape in High Definition</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/oshd-530-oldschool-runescape-in-high-definition/551569</link>
    <description>[center][IMG]http://i.imgur.com/zaz15wX.png[/img]


[IMG]https://cdn1.iconfinder.com/data/icons/basic-ui-elements-color/700/04_download-16.png[/img]Download client: [URL=http://&quot;http://www.oshd530.com&quot;]OSHD Client[/URL]
[IMG]https://cdn1.iconfinder.com/data/icons/social-icons-list-1/256/technorati-16.png[/img] Forums: [url=http://oshd530.com]OSHD Forums[/url]

--

[i][size=10pt]What is &#39;OSHD&#39;?[/size][/i]
[size=8pt]The goal of OSHD is not necessarily to emulate OSRS, but to bring back a classic feeling of early high definition RuneScape while replicating certain aspects of OSRS, whether it be dungeons, bosses, items, interfaces, and more. In order to do this, skills, minigames, general features, dialogues, quests, and many other aspects of the game are slowly being recreated. All content is implemented according to The OSRS RuneScape Wiki.[/size]

--

[i][size=10pt]Some Notable Features[/size][/i]

Full God Wars dungeon-; scrap and fight your way to get killcount, scale insane obstacles, and defend against enemy monsters as you vie for the best drops from the God Wars generals

Farming Skill-; not every server boasts a real-time Farming skill. Crops that grow when you&#39;re sleeping, and mega rewards for having a green thumb, there&#39;s not better time to start planting your potatoes!

Perfect combat-; we strived &amp; spent gruelling hours to ensure that we delivered a combat system that is stable and perfected. You&#39;ll enjoy Player-Versus-Player &amp; Player-Versus-NPC combat like you never have before

Strong economic foundation-; OSHD boasts a strong economy, that where you feel like your gold is worth keeping. We don&#39;t have stacks upon stacks of gold piling up in your bank, and your items are as valuable as ever

Old School RuneScape Items-; OSHD can&#39;t possibly be OSHD without the entire reason OSRS is the way it is: We have the Armadyl Crossbow, Toxic Blowpipe, Abyssal Tentacle, Trident of the Seas, Ardougne Cloak 4, and much more to be released into the game! Come check out your favorite OSRS items in FULL high definition!

Dagganoth Kings-; take on the KINGS of OSHD and see if you&#39;re lucky enough to receive the prized combatant rings! Or perhaps that very valuable Dragon Axe that you just know a skiller will pay top-dollar for.

Barrows-; these formidable brothers are BACK in full high definition, and you have the power to stop them. Defeat them all, and find your way through a maze of tunnels and you may just find yourself in possession of their very valuable armour

Slayer Skill-; what&#39;s OSHD without slayer? We boast one of the most complete Slayer skills in the RSPS community, and it couldn&#39;t be anyway else. With Slayer Masters scattered across the OSHD map, you&#39;ll always have a blast finding new tasks to take on, and earning some valuable loot in the process!

Bonds-; OSHD has them! If you cannot donate, do not worry, OSHD has made sure that you&#39;ll be able to enjoy the membership benefits by paying directly with your OSHD GP. Never pay a dollar again, you&#39;ll get all the comforts without touching your bank account. Bonds can be traded in for 2 weeks of membership, bonus experience, changing your yell color, unlocking weekly events, and even increasing your drop rate.

Hunter-; How many servers have you played with a full blown hunter skill? OSHD takes great pride in saying that we have a near 100% hunter skill the players can enjoy. So get your traps, and participate in the most complete hunter system seen in any RSPS.

Bounty Hunter-; What&#39;s RuneScape without the PKing? We&#39;ve taken the time to fully replicate the RuneScape bounty hunter volcano minigame, with all-working highscores, Low, Medium, and High level caves, PKing has never been more fun! So grab your friend and battle the toughest of foes in this full-blown minigame, Bounty Hunter. 

Clan Wars-; Yes, we even have Clan Wars! Not many servers can say they have an 100% Clan Wars minigame. Well OSHD can! Some features of our Clan Wars include, but are not limited too, Clan Chat based teams, Correct rule interface with all restrictions working, All arenas working, Clan Caller set, Orb-Viewing, and much more! Are you a pure? a hybridder? a zerker? it doesn&#39;t matter! Grab your clan and participate in this full-blown clan wars system!

Warriors Guild-; Battle your way through the defenders one-by-one up to Rune Defender. We boast in a full Warriors Guild minigame. So save up your tokens and head to the cyclops room and fight for the defender drop! This minigame also includes OSRS&#39; dragon defender.

Beautiful HD Graphics and Resizable Client-; Ever want to play OSRS in HD? Now you can! Ever want to see the OSRS&#39; items in HD? Now you can! OSHD boasts in an amazing fullscreen and resizable mode. With features such as Anti-Aliasing, Roof-Top removal, and much, much more!

--

[IMG]http://oshd530.com/img6.png[/img]

[IMG]http://oshd530.com/img7.png[/img]

[IMG]http://oshd530.com/img1.png[/img]

[IMG]http://oshd530.com/img2.png[/img]

[IMG]http://oshd530.com/img3.png[/img]

[IMG]http://oshd530.com/img4.png[/img]

[IMG]http://oshd530.com/img5.png[/img]

[IMG]http://oshd530.com/img8.png[/img]

[IMG]http://oshd530.com/img9.png[/img]


--
[IMG]http://i.imgur.com/GliHkme.jpg[/img]
So get ready for this full-blown OSRS emulation, all in HD graphics.
[/center]</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 06 Jun 2015 11:34:32 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/oshd-530-oldschool-runescape-in-high-definition/551569.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>OSHD #530 -: Oldschool Runescape in High Definition</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@i_dd_s_k0_i i dd s k0 i]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/i_dd_s_k0_i">@i_dd_s_k0_i</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Definetaly worth your time checking it out, especially if you are into oldschool rs yet you can’t stand the graphics, this one is in HD. <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=5" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"> I played RS 05-08 and I like only that period of time, so I approve of this server big time!</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/oshd-530-oldschool-runescape-in-high-definition/551569/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/oshd-530-oldschool-runescape-in-high-definition/551569/6</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 06 Jun 2015 11:34:32 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-551569-6</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/oshd-530-oldschool-runescape-in-high-definition/551569.rss">OSHD #530 -: Oldschool Runescape in High Definition</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>OSHD #530 -: Oldschool Runescape in High Definition</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@OSHD-RSPS OSHD-RSPS]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/oshd-rsps">@OSHD-RSPS</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Thanks, I’ll look into it.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/oshd-530-oldschool-runescape-in-high-definition/551569/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/oshd-530-oldschool-runescape-in-high-definition/551569/5</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 02 Jun 2015 21:12:39 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-551569-5</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/oshd-530-oldschool-runescape-in-high-definition/551569.rss">OSHD #530 -: Oldschool Runescape in High Definition</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>OSHD #530 -: Oldschool Runescape in High Definition</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Ix_Soulcist_xI Soulcist]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/ix_soulcist_xi">@Ix_Soulcist_xI</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I might actually take the time to give this one a shot. The homepage is decent looking, more than most at least. The forum’s theme is as usual the Villain theme or Animate, regardless I will download and give this a shot.</p>
<p>Also, why do you require members to register on the forums to browse? I don’t like that and it only hurts you.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/oshd-530-oldschool-runescape-in-high-definition/551569/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/oshd-530-oldschool-runescape-in-high-definition/551569/4</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 02 Jun 2015 20:18:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-551569-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/oshd-530-oldschool-runescape-in-high-definition/551569.rss">OSHD #530 -: Oldschool Runescape in High Definition</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>OSHD #530 -: Oldschool Runescape in High Definition</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Unrated_ko Unrated ko]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/unrated_ko">@Unrated_ko</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Great server!!</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/oshd-530-oldschool-runescape-in-high-definition/551569/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/oshd-530-oldschool-runescape-in-high-definition/551569/3</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 02 Jun 2015 20:11:59 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-551569-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/oshd-530-oldschool-runescape-in-high-definition/551569.rss">OSHD #530 -: Oldschool Runescape in High Definition</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>OSHD #530 -: Oldschool Runescape in High Definition</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Kongo Kongo]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/kongo">@Kongo</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Amazing server.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/oshd-530-oldschool-runescape-in-high-definition/551569/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/oshd-530-oldschool-runescape-in-high-definition/551569/2</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 31 May 2015 02:29:23 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-551569-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/oshd-530-oldschool-runescape-in-high-definition/551569.rss">OSHD #530 -: Oldschool Runescape in High Definition</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>OSHD #530 -: Oldschool Runescape in High Definition</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@OSHD-RSPS OSHD-RSPS]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/oshd-rsps">@OSHD-RSPS</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[center]<img src="http://i.imgur.com/zaz15wX.png" alt width="" height=""></p>
<p><img src="https://cdn1.iconfinder.com/data/icons/basic-ui-elements-color/700/04_download-16.png" alt width="" height="">Download client: [URL=http://“<a href="http://www.oshd530.com" rel="nofollow noopener">http://www.oshd530.com</a>”]OSHD Client[/URL]<br>
<img src="https://cdn1.iconfinder.com/data/icons/social-icons-list-1/256/technorati-16.png" alt width="" height=""> Forums: <a href="http://oshd530.com" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">OSHD Forums</a></p>
<p>–</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-i">[size=10pt]What is ‘OSHD’?[/size]</span><br>
[size=8pt]The goal of OSHD is not necessarily to emulate OSRS, but to bring back a classic feeling of early high definition RuneScape while replicating certain aspects of OSRS, whether it be dungeons, bosses, items, interfaces, and more. In order to do this, skills, minigames, general features, dialogues, quests, and many other aspects of the game are slowly being recreated. All content is implemented according to The OSRS RuneScape Wiki.[/size]</p>
<p>–</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-i">[size=10pt]Some Notable Features[/size]</span></p>
<p>Full God Wars dungeon-; scrap and fight your way to get killcount, scale insane obstacles, and defend against enemy monsters as you vie for the best drops from the God Wars generals</p>
<p>Farming Skill-; not every server boasts a real-time Farming skill. Crops that grow when you’re sleeping, and mega rewards for having a green thumb, there’s not better time to start planting your potatoes!</p>
<p>Perfect combat-; we strived &amp; spent gruelling hours to ensure that we delivered a combat system that is stable and perfected. You’ll enjoy Player-Versus-Player &amp; Player-Versus-NPC combat like you never have before</p>
<p>Strong economic foundation-; OSHD boasts a strong economy, that where you feel like your gold is worth keeping. We don’t have stacks upon stacks of gold piling up in your bank, and your items are as valuable as ever</p>
<p>Old School RuneScape Items-; OSHD can’t possibly be OSHD without the entire reason OSRS is the way it is: We have the Armadyl Crossbow, Toxic Blowpipe, Abyssal Tentacle, Trident of the Seas, Ardougne Cloak 4, and much more to be released into the game! Come check out your favorite OSRS items in FULL high definition!</p>
<p>Dagganoth Kings-; take on the KINGS of OSHD and see if you’re lucky enough to receive the prized combatant rings! Or perhaps that very valuable Dragon Axe that you just know a skiller will pay top-dollar for.</p>
<p>Barrows-; these formidable brothers are BACK in full high definition, and you have the power to stop them. Defeat them all, and find your way through a maze of tunnels and you may just find yourself in possession of their very valuable armour</p>
<p>Slayer Skill-; what’s OSHD without slayer? We boast one of the most complete Slayer skills in the RSPS community, and it couldn’t be anyway else. With Slayer Masters scattered across the OSHD map, you’ll always have a blast finding new tasks to take on, and earning some valuable loot in the process!</p>
<p>Bonds-; OSHD has them! If you cannot donate, do not worry, OSHD has made sure that you’ll be able to enjoy the membership benefits by paying directly with your OSHD GP. Never pay a dollar again, you’ll get all the comforts without touching your bank account. Bonds can be traded in for 2 weeks of membership, bonus experience, changing your yell color, unlocking weekly events, and even increasing your drop rate.</p>
<p>Hunter-; How many servers have you played with a full blown hunter skill? OSHD takes great pride in saying that we have a near 100% hunter skill the players can enjoy. So get your traps, and participate in the most complete hunter system seen in any RSPS.</p>
<p>Bounty Hunter-; What’s RuneScape without the PKing? We’ve taken the time to fully replicate the RuneScape bounty hunter volcano minigame, with all-working highscores, Low, Medium, and High level caves, PKing has never been more fun! So grab your friend and battle the toughest of foes in this full-blown minigame, Bounty Hunter.</p>
<p>Clan Wars-; Yes, we even have Clan Wars! Not many servers can say they have an 100% Clan Wars minigame. Well OSHD can! Some features of our Clan Wars include, but are not limited too, Clan Chat based teams, Correct rule interface with all restrictions working, All arenas working, Clan Caller set, Orb-Viewing, and much more! Are you a pure? a hybridder? a zerker? it doesn’t matter! Grab your clan and participate in this full-blown clan wars system!</p>
<p>Warriors Guild-; Battle your way through the defenders one-by-one up to Rune Defender. We boast in a full Warriors Guild minigame. So save up your tokens and head to the cyclops room and fight for the defender drop! This minigame also includes OSRS’ dragon defender.</p>
<p>Beautiful HD Graphics and Resizable Client-; Ever want to play OSRS in HD? Now you can! Ever want to see the OSRS’ items in HD? Now you can! OSHD boasts in an amazing fullscreen and resizable mode. With features such as Anti-Aliasing, Roof-Top removal, and much, much more!</p>
<p>–</p>
<p><img src="http://oshd530.com/img6.png" alt width="" height=""></p>
<p><img src="http://oshd530.com/img7.png" alt width="" height=""></p>
<p><img src="http://oshd530.com/img1.png" alt width="" height=""></p>
<p><img src="http://oshd530.com/img2.png" alt width="" height=""></p>
<p><img src="http://oshd530.com/img3.png" alt width="" height=""></p>
<p><img src="http://oshd530.com/img4.png" alt width="" height=""></p>
<p><img src="http://oshd530.com/img5.png" alt width="" height=""></p>
<p><img src="http://oshd530.com/img8.png" alt width="" height=""></p>
<p><img src="http://oshd530.com/img9.png" alt width="" height=""></p>
<p>–<br>
<img src="http://i.imgur.com/GliHkme.jpg" alt width="" height=""><br>
So get ready for this full-blown OSRS emulation, all in HD graphics.<br>
[/center]</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/oshd-530-oldschool-runescape-in-high-definition/551569/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/oshd-530-oldschool-runescape-in-high-definition/551569/1</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 18 May 2015 05:57:42 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-551569-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/oshd-530-oldschool-runescape-in-high-definition/551569.rss">OSHD #530 -: Oldschool Runescape in High Definition</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
