<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Project 803 - [EDIT]</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/project-803-edit/548010</link>
    <description>[CENTER]Welcome - Sunday, November 23rd.[/CENTER]
[HR]
[LEFT]Today I was thinking and got to wondering...What IF? What IF that it were possible that I, and with the help of others, we could make the absolute most advanced RuneScape Private Server? Which lead me to the answer of YES, it is possible. My name is James, and I have been playing RuneScape for 7 years, since 2007, and I have seen ALOT of changes within the years, and even myself miss the first day I played the old school server. But changes sometimes are meant to be. I am currently developing a new Project, (that currently has no name yet), using the VirtusPK 803 Server/Cache/Client, and really needing ALL the help I could get.[/LEFT]
[HR]

As of right now, I&#39;m thinking I&#39;ll need around four (4) people form a Development Team. There&#39;s currently two that are the project right now, (me) and somebody else I personally know in real life. The person I know in real life isn&#39;t much of a java coder or any coder of that sort, so I figure his job could be something simple he could learn like creating shops and spawning NPCs or something like that, so that way he&#39;s useful. So really I&#39;ll need two more. I havn&#39;t programmed a RuneScape Server in almost a year due to my imprisonment, but I had got released on Mandatory supervised parole with an EM (Electronic Monitor) Ankle Bracelet, so I figure I be as productive as possible.
[HR]

[CENTER][SIZE=5]Applications[/CENTER]
[HR]
I currently need two more people to join the Development Team. These two people must meet expectations as listed below:


            You must have atleast ONE year experience with programming java.
            You must provide Contact information, such as e-mails, messengers, or Skype, perferrably skype.
            You must post your age.
            You must show or explain in detail some of your achievements.
            You must be able to solve and fix compiling errors.
            You must have a decent internet connection in case we have to send files back and forth.

[HR]
If me and my other partner feel you meet team expectations, we will contact WITHIN 24 hours. If you do not respond within 48, for ANY reason, your application will be denied. (Some exceptions can be made).
If you need the Server, client or cache for the development of this server, I will gladly post it for you as long as you are wishing to join the team. If you would like pictures, I will also gladly post them. Have any questions? [SIZE=2]Add me on Skype My username is FolkDiss [/SIZE]. Or message me on here, or E-mail me at FolkDiss@outlook.com

Thank-you - James.


[EDIT]: We now have an experienced website/forums developer</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 23 Nov 2014 12:07:09 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/project-803-edit/548010.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Project 803 - [EDIT]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@FolkDiss FolkDiss]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/folkdiss">@FolkDiss</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[CENTER]Welcome - Sunday, November 23rd.[/CENTER]<br>
[HR]<br>
[LEFT]Today I was thinking and got to wondering…What IF? What IF that it were possible that I, and with the help of others, we could make the absolute most advanced RuneScape Private Server? Which lead me to the answer of YES, it is possible. My name is James, and I have been playing RuneScape for 7 years, since 2007, and I have seen ALOT of changes within the years, and even myself miss the first day I played the old school server. But changes sometimes are meant to be. I am currently developing a new Project, (that currently has no name yet), using the VirtusPK 803 Server/Cache/Client, and really needing ALL the help I could get.[/LEFT]<br>
[HR]</p>
<p>As of right now, I’m thinking I’ll need around four (4) people form a Development Team. There’s currently two that are the project right now, (me) and somebody else I personally know in real life. The person I know in real life isn’t much of a java coder or any coder of that sort, so I figure his job could be something simple he could learn like creating shops and spawning NPCs or something like that, so that way he’s useful. So really I’ll need two more. I havn’t programmed a RuneScape Server in almost a year due to my imprisonment, but I had got released on Mandatory supervised parole with an EM (Electronic Monitor) Ankle Bracelet, so I figure I be as productive as possible.<br>
[HR]</p>
<p>[CENTER][SIZE=5]Applications[/CENTER]<br>
[HR]<br>
I currently need two more people to join the Development Team. These two people must meet expectations as listed below:</p>
<pre><code>        You must have atleast ONE year experience with programming java.
        You must provide Contact information, such as e-mails, messengers, or Skype, perferrably skype.
        You must post your age.
        You must show or explain in detail some of your achievements.
        You must be able to solve and fix compiling errors.
        You must have a decent internet connection in case we have to send files back and forth.
</code></pre>
<p>[HR]<br>
If me and my other partner feel you meet team expectations, we will contact WITHIN 24 hours. If you do not respond within 48, for ANY reason, your application will be denied. (Some exceptions can be made).<br>
If you need the Server, client or cache for the development of this server, I will gladly post it for you as long as you are wishing to join the team. If you would like pictures, I will also gladly post them. Have any questions? [SIZE=2]Add me on Skype My username is FolkDiss [/SIZE]. Or message me on here, or E-mail me at <a href="mailto:FolkDiss@outlook.com">FolkDiss@outlook.com</a></p>
<p>Thank-you - James.</p>
<p>[EDIT]: We now have an experienced website/forums developer</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/project-803-edit/548010/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/project-803-edit/548010/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 23 Nov 2014 12:07:09 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-548010-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/project-803-edit/548010.rss">Project 803 - [EDIT]</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
