<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Automatic Updating Client</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/automatic-updating-client/400525</link>
    <description>I&#39;m not new here, but I&#39;m pretty much brand new to coding and hope I can start learning a lot from this community to become a top-notch coder. Sorry, just introducing myself. Anyways....

How would I go about making an auto updating client. I&#39;ve seen servers with them so I know its possible. Basically they would just have to download the client and all the class files and all that would not be viewable. They would just have to open client and if I updated my version of the client, their client would automatically download the update. How would I go about doing this?

-Tchandle</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 23 Jun 2011 05:12:27 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Game Development</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/automatic-updating-client/400525.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Automatic Updating Client</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@tchandle tchandle]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/tchandle">@tchandle</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I’m not new here, but I’m pretty much brand new to coding and hope I can start learning a lot from this community to become a top-notch coder. Sorry, just introducing myself. Anyways…</p>
<p>How would I go about making an auto updating client. I’ve seen servers with them so I know its possible. Basically they would just have to download the client and all the class files and all that would not be viewable. They would just have to open client and if I updated my version of the client, their client would automatically download the update. How would I go about doing this?</p>
<p>-Tchandle</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/automatic-updating-client/400525/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/automatic-updating-client/400525/1</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jun 2011 05:12:27 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-400525-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/automatic-updating-client/400525.rss">Automatic Updating Client</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
