<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Hydrascape talk is allowed again for now</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/hydrascape-talk-is-allowed-again-for-now/231688</link>
    <description>OK, that didn&#39;t take long did it - never let it be said I&#39;m solid and immovable :rolleyes:

After taking a look at Hydrascape and speaking to the owner I realise I am being a little unfair here.

The reason for the restriction was in part due to their reputation and also [i]because they felt the need to hide their identities[/i] - that reeks of trouble.

However, they seem to be running a tight ship over there at the moment and putting far too much effort into this project for it to be a simple scam, so the ban on talking about their server is lifted for now. I&#39;ll be keeping an eye on things.

[b][size=14pt]However, bear in mind that the staff of the site are nmopal, Gander, Ramenryoko and Lumby, no matter what they call themselves these days. Base your desicion on whether to trust them on that.[/size][/b]

Of course the normal forum rules still apply. (ie Hydrascape members: you can stop spamming now)</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2008 01:48:04 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Community Suggestions</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/hydrascape-talk-is-allowed-again-for-now/231688.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Hydrascape talk is allowed again for now</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Mopman Mopman]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/mopman">@Mopman</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>OK, that didn’t take long did it - never let it be said I’m solid and immovable :rolleyes:</p>
<p>After taking a look at Hydrascape and speaking to the owner I realise I am being a little unfair here.</p>
<p>The reason for the restriction was in part due to their reputation and also <span class="bbcode-i">because they felt the need to hide their identities</span> - that reeks of trouble.</p>
<p>However, they seem to be running a tight ship over there at the moment and putting far too much effort into this project for it to be a simple scam, so the ban on talking about their server is lifted for now. I’ll be keeping an eye on things.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">[size=14pt]However, bear in mind that the staff of the site are nmopal, Gander, Ramenryoko and Lumby, no matter what they call themselves these days. Base your desicion on whether to trust them on that.[/size]</span></p>
<p>Of course the normal forum rules still apply. (ie Hydrascape members: you can stop spamming now)</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/hydrascape-talk-is-allowed-again-for-now/231688/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/hydrascape-talk-is-allowed-again-for-now/231688/1</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2008 01:48:04 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-231688-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/hydrascape-talk-is-allowed-again-for-now/231688.rss">Hydrascape talk is allowed again for now</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
