<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>A staff modification</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/a-staff-modification/435742</link>
    <description>It&#39;s not what you think it is, either!  :D

I&#39;ve been doing some web development here and there for a week or so now but I&#39;ve ran out of ideas - I want to make the ultimate staff plugin for Minecraft right now I&#39;m working on core manual features but if I actually get there (motivation wise) I want to make it automatically update as well as implementing some other cool additions such as JS features. 

I&#39;ve not worked on any design up to now, just code, if you&#39;re good with coming up with template designs then please help me out, like Moparisthebest I&#39;ve never been accused of being creative. 

What I&#39;ve got:


[ul][li]Full punishment input[/li][li]Fields such as Time, reason, mod name[/li][li]Full login with sessions (May implement this with SMF - Nothing else because SMF is simply &gt; to the rest)[/li][li]Once the ban has expired it moves it into a different category[/li][li]Fully functioning search function[/li][li]Options such as: Search for expired bans, bans done by a certain moderator and so on...[/li][li]Nice colours on the merger page to make it easier to read![/li][/ul]

update -


[ul][li]Added pages so it looks more presentable (e.g. a maximum of 25 query results per page)[/li][li]In addition to that it can now be edited by the user - You can select how many queries can be dumped onto the page based on your needs.[/li][li]Added a useful link panel (If you can be lazy like me you&#39;d appreciate this!)[/li][/ul]

In the future I want to add full bukkit integration, e.g. when a staff members bans someone its added to the list (even release a new command? /ban name reason time to fit the information required and so on...) but for now I need to get the basics done and work with some Bukkit more.

Right now the time checking is done when the query of the database is dumped onto the different pages, which is probably a bad thing, I hope to write a program (Like with MITBs SSP, he has a java checker and so on) to deal with it into different tables within the database which lowers the amount of work it has to do at once!

My question is, what else should there be? Any suggestions are appreciated. I want to base it around Moparcraft really.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 12 Mar 2012 21:15:09 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Games</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/a-staff-modification/435742.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>A staff modification</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@moparisthebest Moparisthebest]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/moparisthebest">@moparisthebest</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>This sounds neat!  To integrate the bans etc with moparcraft, all you have to do is add user accounts to a banned group, and remove them when it expires.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/a-staff-modification/435742/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/a-staff-modification/435742/2</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Mar 2012 21:15:09 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-435742-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/a-staff-modification/435742.rss">A staff modification</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>A staff modification</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Tom Tom]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/tom">@Tom</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>It’s not what you think it is, either!  <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/smiley.png?v=5" title=":smiley:" class="emoji" alt=":smiley:"></p>
<p>I’ve been doing some web development here and there for a week or so now but I’ve ran out of ideas - I want to make the ultimate staff plugin for Minecraft right now I’m working on core manual features but if I actually get there (motivation wise) I want to make it automatically update as well as implementing some other cool additions such as JS features.</p>
<p>I’ve not worked on any design up to now, just code, if you’re good with coming up with template designs then please help me out, like Moparisthebest I’ve never been accused of being creative.</p>
<p>What I’ve got:</p>
<p>[ul][li]Full punishment input[/li][li]Fields such as Time, reason, mod name[/li][li]Full login with sessions (May implement this with SMF - Nothing else because SMF is simply &gt; to the rest)[/li][li]Once the ban has expired it moves it into a different category[/li][li]Fully functioning search function[/li][li]Options such as: Search for expired bans, bans done by a certain moderator and so on…[/li][li]Nice colours on the merger page to make it easier to read![/li][/ul]</p>
<p>update -</p>
<p>[ul][li]Added pages so it looks more presentable (e.g. a maximum of 25 query results per page)[/li][li]In addition to that it can now be edited by the user - You can select how many queries can be dumped onto the page based on your needs.[/li][li]Added a useful link panel (If you can be lazy like me you’d appreciate this!)[/li][/ul]</p>
<p>In the future I want to add full bukkit integration, e.g. when a staff members bans someone its added to the list (even release a new command? /ban name reason time to fit the information required and so on…) but for now I need to get the basics done and work with some Bukkit more.</p>
<p>Right now the time checking is done when the query of the database is dumped onto the different pages, which is probably a bad thing, I hope to write a program (Like with MITBs SSP, he has a java checker and so on) to deal with it into different tables within the database which lowers the amount of work it has to do at once!</p>
<p>My question is, what else should there be? Any suggestions are appreciated. I want to base it around Moparcraft really.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/a-staff-modification/435742/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/a-staff-modification/435742/1</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Mar 2012 17:45:44 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-435742-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/a-staff-modification/435742.rss">A staff modification</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
