<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Networking model</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/networking-model/414645</link>
    <description>Ok, so I designed a networking model for a MMO project I&#39;m currently working on.
I&#39;d like to get some critism on this model and what could be done better or if this is mad.


So basicly, I&#39;m planning to let the users host my servers.
As in, I host the Master Server, and the users host the actual servers that do the logic and all the handling.
I have a small budget so hence I&#39;m using this model.
I&#39;m integrating server hosting protocols in the client, so that players can host directly from their client by simply clicking create server, and then by setting it up. Then that gets registered in the Master Server and other players can now join a game. This would mean though that a server can&#39;t have more than 64 players at the same time.


Now here are my concerns, this is going to be an MMO, and letting the players host the servers is kindoff dangerous. Because I&#39;m planning to let all those servers connect to the same databases that have information about each player (name, password, ip, information about a custom place he built,...).


So, if you know any games using this method please mention, if you think this is completely idiotic because it is too insecure and people can obtain database information please mention that aswell.
If this is actually a good model that is possible, then mention that aswell.


Or, how would you do this?</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 08 Dec 2012 17:48:03 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Game Development</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/networking-model/414645.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Networking model</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@jal_knight jal knight]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/jal_knight">@jal_knight</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Im curious to hear how the development goes. Keep us informed please <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=5" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"> or give me a link.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/networking-model/414645/8">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/networking-model/414645/8</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 08 Dec 2012 17:48:03 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-414645-8</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/networking-model/414645.rss">Networking model</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Networking model</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@MistaBigBoss MistaBigBoss]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/mistabigboss">@MistaBigBoss</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“HcoJustin, post:6, topic:414645”]Letting a user host their own server for a RPG is never a great idea… The cheating is bad enough with FPS games, and those don’t have any advantage to cheating besides giving an e-boner…</p>
<p>Who says I even have to let it connect to your database? Simply route the connection to mine, and not only have I just gained everyone’s account information, but I’m able to change the data as I see fit</p>
<p>If you absolutely cannot afford more than one server, pull a Jagex and do F2P and P2P worlds, or offer a trial that limits you to 7days or a certain level before you stop gaining xp. Which would force users into payment if they wanted to keep playing[/quote]Thanks man, but I’m going to keep this F2P, because this will be a general new game, and the path to succes is to make it free in the beginning and add payed OPTIONS when you notice you’re game got populair.</p>
<p>I’ll just put 3 ads on every page on the game’s website (forums, main website, the actual game page,…) and I’ll ask for donations in order for keeping the game up and running.</p>
<p>I have a very powerfull laptop but I don’t know if that will be enough for hosting a large scale game. I don’t know, I really don’t.<br>
I think I’ll just go for a big boy server and see what happens from there.</p>
<p>Another problem when hosting for myself is that, I have unlimited bandwidth but with these limitations 25 Mbps (3,1 MB per second) download and 3,5 Mbps (0,4 MB per second) upload. I think 400 kB might be just enough for hosting a server for 45 players. Awesome.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/networking-model/414645/7">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/networking-model/414645/7</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 14 Sep 2011 21:43:11 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-414645-7</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/networking-model/414645.rss">Networking model</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Networking model</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@HcoJustin HcoJustin]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/hcojustin">@HcoJustin</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Letting a user host their own server for a RPG is never a great idea… The cheating is bad enough with FPS games, and those don’t have any advantage to cheating besides giving an e-boner…</p>
<p>Who says I even have to let it connect to your database? Simply route the connection to mine, and not only have I just gained everyone’s account information, but I’m able to change the data as I see fit</p>
<p>If you absolutely cannot afford more than one server, pull a Jagex and do F2P and P2P worlds, or offer a trial that limits you to 7days or a certain level before you stop gaining xp. Which would force users into payment if they wanted to keep playing</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/networking-model/414645/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/networking-model/414645/6</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 14 Sep 2011 16:45:52 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-414645-6</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/networking-model/414645.rss">Networking model</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Networking model</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Wintercanon Wintercanon]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/wintercanon">@Wintercanon</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“Triton, post:3, topic:414645”]This is how FPS usually work, but the servers never change anything in the master server. Now, with TF2, Valve introduced item servers, and I suspect there is some processing going on between them.</p>
<p>Also it doesn’t make sense to talk about an MMO in a generic way. It completely depends on the genre of the game.</p>
<p>But about your original design:</p>
<p>[quote] this is completely idiotic because it is too insecure and people can obtain database information[/quote][/quote]This only works for console gaming. CoD for example can be pretty awful when someone who acts as the host server has a terrible internet connection. It gives them an advantage. Consoles have security measures and sandboxing so that people cannot steal your account information. People cannot directly modify the code, whereas they can on the computer. If you want clean fun, playing an FPS on a console is better than a computer. Even on consoles people find boosting hacks by exploiting the code (without actually modifying it), but it is severely worse on PC games.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/networking-model/414645/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/networking-model/414645/5</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 14 Sep 2011 14:09:49 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-414645-5</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/networking-model/414645.rss">Networking model</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Networking model</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@MistaBigBoss MistaBigBoss]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/mistabigboss">@MistaBigBoss</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“Triton, post:3, topic:414645”]This is how FPS usually work, but the servers never change anything in the master server. Now, with TF2, Valve introduced item servers, and I suspect there is some processing going on between them.</p>
<p>Also it doesn’t make sense to talk about an MMO in a generic way. It completely depends on the genre of the game.</p>
<p>But about your original design:</p>
<p>[quote] this is completely idiotic because it is too insecure and people can obtain database information[/quote][/quote]This game is intended as a MMORPG, with stragetic elements and a first person viewpoint with first person weapons. But mainly RPG, about the networking model, I think you’re right, an advanced hacker can easily sniff all the networking going on, including user information and database information.</p>
<p>I’ll have to either remove the RPG elements for the game, or I’ll have to find a way to host some servers myself.</p>
<p>This sucks, I’m not starting the development until I fully completed the design of it and now I’m pretty much stuck.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/networking-model/414645/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/networking-model/414645/4</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 14 Sep 2011 13:10:45 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-414645-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/networking-model/414645.rss">Networking model</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Networking model</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@ripzone Triton]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/ripzone">@ripzone</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>This is how FPS usually work, but the servers never change anything in the master server. Now, with TF2, Valve introduced item servers, and I suspect there is some processing going on between them.</p>
<p>Also it doesn’t make sense to talk about an MMO in a generic way. It completely depends on the genre of the game.</p>
<p>But about your original design:</p>
<blockquote>this is completely idiotic because it is too insecure and people can obtain database information</blockquote>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/networking-model/414645/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/networking-model/414645/3</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 14 Sep 2011 12:14:37 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-414645-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/networking-model/414645.rss">Networking model</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Networking model</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Wintercanon Wintercanon]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/wintercanon">@Wintercanon</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I wouldn’t want to play a game where my username and password passed through a random’s computer before being sent to the master server. Plus your hosters will rent VPSs and charge for the fastest access to your game. Plus they can decompile the server, modify the code for an unfair advantage and boost their accounts. It sounds like a pretty poor model in my opinion. It would take an insane amount of work to get this secure. If you have a small budget, host the game and allow players the option of donating to keep it running. Do not offer reward incentives for donating. If the game is good, people will donate.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/networking-model/414645/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/networking-model/414645/2</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 14 Sep 2011 12:06:18 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-414645-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/networking-model/414645.rss">Networking model</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Networking model</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@MistaBigBoss MistaBigBoss]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/mistabigboss">@MistaBigBoss</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Ok, so I designed a networking model for a MMO project I’m currently working on.<br>
I’d like to get some critism on this model and what could be done better or if this is mad.</p>
<p>So basicly, I’m planning to let the users host my servers.<br>
As in, I host the Master Server, and the users host the actual servers that do the logic and all the handling.<br>
I have a small budget so hence I’m using this model.<br>
I’m integrating server hosting protocols in the client, so that players can host directly from their client by simply clicking create server, and then by setting it up. Then that gets registered in the Master Server and other players can now join a game. This would mean though that a server can’t have more than 64 players at the same time.</p>
<p>Now here are my concerns, this is going to be an MMO, and letting the players host the servers is kindoff dangerous. Because I’m planning to let all those servers connect to the same databases that have information about each player (name, password, ip, information about a custom place he built,…).</p>
<p>So, if you know any games using this method please mention, if you think this is completely idiotic because it is too insecure and people can obtain database information please mention that aswell.<br>
If this is actually a good model that is possible, then mention that aswell.</p>
<p>Or, how would you do this?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/networking-model/414645/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/networking-model/414645/1</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 14 Sep 2011 11:20:53 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-414645-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/networking-model/414645.rss">Networking model</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
