<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>EdgevillePK - The Fight Awaits! (Looking for Team)</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/edgevillepk-the-fight-awaits-looking-for-team/553952</link>
    <description>[center][img]http://i.imgur.com/ous4Gws.png[/img]

[SIZE=9pt]This banner will change here eventually, I know part of it is hard to read. It is just a placeholder until Rash finishes our new one.[/size][/center]

[CENTER][SIZE=16pt][B][FONT=Comic Sans MS]The Team:[/FONT][/B][/SIZE]
[FONT=Comic Sans MS]
[IMG]http://i.imgur.com/mrbYC5k.gif[/img] [url=https://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php?action=profile;u=509768]RiiPiiNFtW[/url] - Server Developer
[IMG]http://baca-online.pun.bz/files/sun-java.png[/img] Currently None
[IMG]http://www.rune-server.org/static/avatar/design.gif[/img] [url=https://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php?action=profile;u=326819]Thee Rash[/url] - Community Manager and GFX Designer


[b][size=16pt]Server Goals:[/size][/b]

We plan to provide an interactive PvPing experience for players of all sorts. As a PvP dominant server we plan to have content based around PvPing. EdgevillePK intends to be a spawn server but with restrictions. We will have donator ranks for those who choose to have access to many features, but we will not become a P2W (pay to win) game where the donators get lifted restrictions on combat effecting spawnable items. 

To start with, we will provide a PK skill that will unlock access to certain items within shops that are not spawnable. Such items in this store can be accessible of two ways being: 1, either the player can get the proper PK skill and the right amount of PK points to purchase the item from the shop, or 2, the player can achieve the proper prestige to unlock the items to spawn. Every kill in PvP will give a calculated amount of XP towards the PK skill and a calculated amount of PK points. Such calculation will depend on a number of variables, but once that algorithm is written I will explain it in more detail. 

The server will also feature a Burncard system. Now for those of you who never played Titanfall, burncards are PvP modifiers that change the way PvP is handled whether it be &quot;amped&quot; weapons or spawning next to the enemy who just killed you. Of course these are just examples of existing modifiers in Titanfall and will most likely not be added exactly to the word in our system.

To add onto the Prestige system, every time a player hits level 99 in the PK skill, the player will have the option to level up their Prestige. Each prestige will unlock a variety of items that will aid in the success of ones&#39; PvP experience. These items may range from cosmetic to actual combat effecting items. Each prestige, they will also get a free Burncard pack which will have chances of dropping certain &quot;rares&quot; or whatever we want to call it. There will also be different burncard packs which will be offered as donation rewards. Each increased prestige level will increase the percentage of XP you get in the PK skill.

Loadouts are another favorite of most PvP styled games. We will provide 6 default loadouts that players will be able to select before engaging in PvP activities, but also with the leveling up of the PK skill and Prestige levels, players will gain access to custom loadouts where they will be able to drag and drop items they wish to become their custom setup of gear in PvP.

More information will be provided upon completion of all of these systems with their designated interfaces.

[b][size=16pt]Notable Features:[/size][/b]
Prestige System
Burncard System
Custom PK Skill
Loadout System
OnDemand Services

So as far as joining the team, you simply need to send me a PM or leave a post here regarding your interest in helping with this project. I am looking for a website/ forums developer who can make professional forums and website pages, as well as a server/ (preferably) client developer.

I am currently working on adding burncards into the server. Previously it was just a skeleton system, but I am actually integrating them into the game now.

If you&#39;re interested, do let me know. I want to get this server online as soon as possible. Thanks! :D[/FONT][/CENTER]</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 27 Nov 2015 18:52:21 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/edgevillepk-the-fight-awaits-looking-for-team/553952.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>EdgevillePK - The Fight Awaits! (Looking for Team)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@RiiPiiNFtW RiiPiiNFtW]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/riipiinftw">@RiiPiiNFtW</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[center]<div class="lightbox-wrapper"><a class="lightbox" href="http://i.imgur.com/ous4Gws.png" title="ous4Gws.png" rel="nofollow noopener"><img src="http://i.imgur.com/ous4Gws.png" alt width="690" height="130"><div class="meta">
<svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-far-image svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#far-image"></use></svg><span class="filename">ous4Gws.png</span><span class="informations">700×132</span><svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-discourse-expand svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#discourse-expand"></use></svg>
</div></a></div></p>
<p>[SIZE=9pt]This banner will change here eventually, I know part of it is hard to read. It is just a placeholder until Rash finishes our new one.[/size][/center]</p>
<p>[CENTER][SIZE=16pt]<span class="bbcode-b">[FONT=Comic Sans MS]The Team:[/FONT]</span>[/SIZE]<br>
[FONT=Comic Sans MS]<br>
<img src="http://i.imgur.com/mrbYC5k.gif" alt width="13" height="11"> <a href="https://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php?action=profile;u=509768" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">RiiPiiNFtW</a> - Server Developer<br>
<img src="http://baca-online.pun.bz/files/sun-java.png" alt width="1" height="1"> Currently None<br>
<img src="http://www.rune-server.org/static/avatar/design.gif" alt width="14" height="13"> <a href="https://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php?action=profile;u=326819" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">Thee Rash</a> - Community Manager and GFX Designer</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">[size=16pt]Server Goals:[/size]</span></p>
<p>We plan to provide an interactive PvPing experience for players of all sorts. As a PvP dominant server we plan to have content based around PvPing. EdgevillePK intends to be a spawn server but with restrictions. We will have donator ranks for those who choose to have access to many features, but we will not become a P2W (pay to win) game where the donators get lifted restrictions on combat effecting spawnable items.</p>
<p>To start with, we will provide a PK skill that will unlock access to certain items within shops that are not spawnable. Such items in this store can be accessible of two ways being: 1, either the player can get the proper PK skill and the right amount of PK points to purchase the item from the shop, or 2, the player can achieve the proper prestige to unlock the items to spawn. Every kill in PvP will give a calculated amount of XP towards the PK skill and a calculated amount of PK points. Such calculation will depend on a number of variables, but once that algorithm is written I will explain it in more detail.</p>
<p>The server will also feature a Burncard system. Now for those of you who never played Titanfall, burncards are PvP modifiers that change the way PvP is handled whether it be “amped” weapons or spawning next to the enemy who just killed you. Of course these are just examples of existing modifiers in Titanfall and will most likely not be added exactly to the word in our system.</p>
<p>To add onto the Prestige system, every time a player hits level 99 in the PK skill, the player will have the option to level up their Prestige. Each prestige will unlock a variety of items that will aid in the success of ones’ PvP experience. These items may range from cosmetic to actual combat effecting items. Each prestige, they will also get a free Burncard pack which will have chances of dropping certain “rares” or whatever we want to call it. There will also be different burncard packs which will be offered as donation rewards. Each increased prestige level will increase the percentage of XP you get in the PK skill.</p>
<p>Loadouts are another favorite of most PvP styled games. We will provide 6 default loadouts that players will be able to select before engaging in PvP activities, but also with the leveling up of the PK skill and Prestige levels, players will gain access to custom loadouts where they will be able to drag and drop items they wish to become their custom setup of gear in PvP.</p>
<p>More information will be provided upon completion of all of these systems with their designated interfaces.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">[size=16pt]Notable Features:[/size]</span><br>
Prestige System<br>
Burncard System<br>
Custom PK Skill<br>
Loadout System<br>
OnDemand Services</p>
<p>So as far as joining the team, you simply need to send me a PM or leave a post here regarding your interest in helping with this project. I am looking for a website/ forums developer who can make professional forums and website pages, as well as a server/ (preferably) client developer.</p>
<p>I am currently working on adding burncards into the server. Previously it was just a skeleton system, but I am actually integrating them into the game now.</p>
<p>If you’re interested, do let me know. I want to get this server online as soon as possible. Thanks! :D[/FONT][/CENTER]</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/edgevillepk-the-fight-awaits-looking-for-team/553952/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/edgevillepk-the-fight-awaits-looking-for-team/553952/1</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Nov 2015 18:52:21 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-553952-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/edgevillepk-the-fight-awaits-looking-for-team/553952.rss">EdgevillePK - The Fight Awaits! (Looking for Team)</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
