<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>ExecuteX (ventus remake)</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/executex-ventus-remake/525787</link>
    <description>[center][u][b][size=18pt]ExecuteX[/size][/b][/u][/center]

[u][b]Developers[/b][/u]
[b]Demolition AKA me
Jason from Rune-server
Reich from rune-server does really good client work
Possibly going to get Genesis from rune-server as well
Sloth aka Jesse pinkman used to be known for on rune-server[/b]


[size=12pt][b]Note not all these developers are for sure.  Just an idea of who I usually talk with.  I know for sure Jason will be though plus he is well known for his services.[/b][/size]

[b]Currently got my hands on Ventus not to long ago.  I will be updating this thread as we go.  The project will be hosted soon then the updates will be done daily.  The server is a pk server with flawless switching correct animations.  Correct new hit markers.  Fixed the bugs in it already dupes have been fixed as well.  I need some beta testers soon I got a few already but it don&#39;t hurt to have more.  This is something I want to turn into a successful server I am going to pay multiple people to do work on it.  It&#39;s already got bank tabs added.  The home teleports for pking are pretty similiar to spawnscape if you have heard of it.  The custom features this server is going to have well custom minigames and custom events for sure.[/b]

I will keep this update as clean as I possibly can if you have any questions feel free to ask.  I strive for making a successful server I recently am shutting down DiversityX it has enough players for 2 weeks just I wanted to make a pk server I have done way to many ECO servers which were successful a prime example was Land Of Elements.  Used to have over 50+ online and sometimes would see it hit a bit over 70+</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2013 06:43:47 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/executex-ventus-remake/525787.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>ExecuteX (ventus remake)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@dawsonsmokes dawsonsmokes]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/dawsonsmokes">@dawsonsmokes</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[center]<span class="bbcode-u"><span class="bbcode-b">[size=18pt]ExecuteX[/size]</span></span>[/center]</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-u"><span class="bbcode-b">Developers</span></span><br>
<span class="bbcode-b">Demolition AKA me<br>
Jason from Rune-server<br>
Reich from rune-server does really good client work<br>
Possibly going to get Genesis from rune-server as well<br>
Sloth aka Jesse pinkman used to be known for on rune-server</span></p>
<p>[size=12pt]<span class="bbcode-b">Note not all these developers are for sure.  Just an idea of who I usually talk with.  I know for sure Jason will be though plus he is well known for his services.</span>[/size]</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Currently got my hands on Ventus not to long ago.  I will be updating this thread as we go.  The project will be hosted soon then the updates will be done daily.  The server is a pk server with flawless switching correct animations.  Correct new hit markers.  Fixed the bugs in it already dupes have been fixed as well.  I need some beta testers soon I got a few already but it don’t hurt to have more.  This is something I want to turn into a successful server I am going to pay multiple people to do work on it.  It’s already got bank tabs added.  The home teleports for pking are pretty similiar to spawnscape if you have heard of it.  The custom features this server is going to have well custom minigames and custom events for sure.</span></p>
<p>I will keep this update as clean as I possibly can if you have any questions feel free to ask.  I strive for making a successful server I recently am shutting down DiversityX it has enough players for 2 weeks just I wanted to make a pk server I have done way to many ECO servers which were successful a prime example was Land Of Elements.  Used to have over 50+ online and sometimes would see it hit a bit over 70+</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/executex-ventus-remake/525787/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/executex-ventus-remake/525787/1</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2013 06:43:47 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-525787-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/executex-ventus-remake/525787.rss">ExecuteX (ventus remake)</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
