<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>HELP needed BIG time! - Setting currency in a store to a non-stackable item!</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/help-needed-big-time-setting-currency-in-a-store-to-a-non-stackable-item/201548</link>
    <description>This is bugging me now, i&#39;ve been trying to change the shop method carefully so you can use a non-stackable item instead of coins for a shop.

BTW i&#39;m using Project Force source by Force
I need an experienced coder here, I want to add in a function similar to buyItem called buyItemRock.
So i want item ID: Rock (1480) to be used as currency in Shop ID: 17. This &quot;Rock&quot; item is Non-Stackable so i figure i need to delete the item by slot # not by Item Amount when i buy something.

in general, I need a way to have 1 specific shop use a non-stackable item to buy things in that store. Oh, and i&#39;m manually setting the variable that defines how much the item&#39;s worth. If i set the item price in item.cfg, it sets the GP amount, i dun want that.. IM NOT DOING THIS FOR SELL, just buyItem only.

It can be c&amp;p if it&#39;s allowed here but i mostly just want it done by my instruction. If you can&#39;t understand what i&#39;m talking about here, just ask me for some more clarification.

I need help on this, whoever can may get free mod on my new future hamachi server and rep++, if u want.[br][br][size=1]Posted on: April 21, 2008, 05:05:51 PM[/size][hr]Nevermind, I figured it out.
Lock please..</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2008 05:02:27 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/help-needed-big-time-setting-currency-in-a-store-to-a-non-stackable-item/201548.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>HELP needed BIG time! - Setting currency in a store to a non-stackable item!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Escapez Escapez]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/escapez">@Escapez</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>This is bugging me now, i’ve been trying to change the shop method carefully so you can use a non-stackable item instead of coins for a shop.</p>
<p>BTW i’m using Project Force source by Force<br>
I need an experienced coder here, I want to add in a function similar to buyItem called buyItemRock.<br>
So i want item ID: Rock (1480) to be used as currency in Shop ID: 17. This “Rock” item is Non-Stackable so i figure i need to delete the item by slot # not by Item Amount when i buy something.</p>
<p>in general, I need a way to have 1 specific shop use a non-stackable item to buy things in that store. Oh, and i’m manually setting the variable that defines how much the item’s worth. If i set the item price in item.cfg, it sets the GP amount, i dun want that… IM NOT DOING THIS FOR SELL, just buyItem only.</p>
<p>It can be c&amp;p if it’s allowed here but i mostly just want it done by my instruction. If you can’t understand what i’m talking about here, just ask me for some more clarification.</p>
<p>I need help on this, whoever can may get free mod on my new future hamachi server and rep++, if u want.[br][br][size=1]Posted on: April 21, 2008, 05:05:51 PM[/size][hr]Nevermind, I figured it out.<br>
Lock please…</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/help-needed-big-time-setting-currency-in-a-store-to-a-non-stackable-item/201548/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/help-needed-big-time-setting-currency-in-a-store-to-a-non-stackable-item/201548/1</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2008 05:02:27 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-201548-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/help-needed-big-time-setting-currency-in-a-store-to-a-non-stackable-item/201548.rss">HELP needed BIG time! - Setting currency in a store to a non-stackable item!</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
