<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Minecraft Server Official Merkage Craaft Server</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/minecraft-server-official-merkage-craaft-server/526519</link>
    <description>The Official Merkage Craft Server is a great place to be and a great place to play minecraft. initially you will be asked to build a house in the GuestWorld (creative) this is to show the admins what you&#39;re made of and to show that you have the patience needed when building a house. after you have been ranked a player you can get involved in monthly challenges between other members of the server. winning these challenges will get you higher ranks within the Merkage Craft server. Enjoy playing minecraft survival mode in a great community while having the economy option of buying items with your minecraft balance. I hope you decide to join the Merkage Craft Server. Enjoy!

IP- merkagecraftserver.tk</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 29 Jul 2013 21:07:55 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Minecraft</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/minecraft-server-official-merkage-craaft-server/526519.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Minecraft Server Official Merkage Craaft Server</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@XOoMERKAGEoOX XOoMERKAGEoOX]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/xoomerkageoox">@XOoMERKAGEoOX</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>The Official Merkage Craft Server is a great place to be and a great place to play minecraft. initially you will be asked to build a house in the GuestWorld (creative) this is to show the admins what you’re made of and to show that you have the patience needed when building a house. after you have been ranked a player you can get involved in monthly challenges between other members of the server. winning these challenges will get you higher ranks within the Merkage Craft server. Enjoy playing minecraft survival mode in a great community while having the economy option of buying items with your minecraft balance. I hope you decide to join the Merkage Craft Server. Enjoy!</p>
<p>IP- merkagecraftserver.tk</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/minecraft-server-official-merkage-craaft-server/526519/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/minecraft-server-official-merkage-craaft-server/526519/1</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 29 Jul 2013 21:07:55 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-526519-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/minecraft-server-official-merkage-craaft-server/526519.rss">Minecraft Server Official Merkage Craaft Server</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
