<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Help with a loading issue</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/help-with-a-loading-issue/543194</link>
    <description>Hello, I appreciate you took the time to look at my issue. The problem I&#39;m having is that in my endeavors to get world objects to load through the client I have not been successful. 

The reason I was attempting this is because I did not like how objects added server side such as trees, ore deposits, doors, and furnaces took longer to load than usual when someone teleported to/logged in near them.

What I had before was that I had tried to adapt the addGlobalObject code to be run client side, and that wasn&#39;t working, so I came here to see if anyone could guide me in the right direction or even help me come up with a solution to the objects loading slowly. 

I appreciate your time, thank you!</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 19 May 2014 15:47:44 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Game Development</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/help-with-a-loading-issue/543194.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Help with a loading issue</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@shaden shaden]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/shaden">@shaden</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Hello, I appreciate you took the time to look at my issue. The problem I’m having is that in my endeavors to get world objects to load through the client I have not been successful.</p>
<p>The reason I was attempting this is because I did not like how objects added server side such as trees, ore deposits, doors, and furnaces took longer to load than usual when someone teleported to/logged in near them.</p>
<p>What I had before was that I had tried to adapt the addGlobalObject code to be run client side, and that wasn’t working, so I came here to see if anyone could guide me in the right direction or even help me come up with a solution to the objects loading slowly.</p>
<p>I appreciate your time, thank you!</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/help-with-a-loading-issue/543194/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/help-with-a-loading-issue/543194/1</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2014 15:47:44 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-543194-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/help-with-a-loading-issue/543194.rss">Help with a loading issue</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
