<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Welcome to Underground Miner!</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/welcome-to-underground-miner/442455</link>
    <description>Welcome to Underground Miner! Here at Underground Miner, we return to the meaning of Minecraft; Freedom. You, as a player, should have the freedom to choose how you want to play. Does building massive products in a purely Creative world interest you the most? Survival grasp your thoughts as you wage war against creatures and players alike? Or perhaps survival isn&#39;t enough and you seek a harder challenge? We have a challenge that even the best Minecraft players dare to venture into. Here is a further breakdown of our worlds:

Eris Space Station - Spawn
Calliope - Creative, ulimited blocks and flat lands to build to your hearts desire. (Anti-griefing measures in place)
Thanatos - Hardcore Survival. Less focus of RPG, more focused on pure survival. One life. That&#39;s it.
Demios - Survival Mode. Roleplaying, PvP, Towns, Factions
Dolos - Minigames, PvP Arena, Mob Arena, etc.

We use several different plugins at Underground Miner. These include:

Spout -- Our server is spout enabled. We highly recommend Spoutcraft (not required)
Multiverse -- Multiple different worlds to explore and build!
Essentials -- Core commands, providing much needed simple commands.
Falsebook -- Integrated Circuits and advanced Redstone controls.
Massband -- Tape measure! So simple, yet so useful.
Dynmap -- Fully rendered maps. Anytime. Anywhere.
Worldedit -- Cuboid editing, for those &quot;Hard to reach&quot; projects.
Worldguard -- Protection spread across the server
Factions -- Join together to fight the forces of evil!
LWC -- Protect your belongings from those curious griefers.
Blocklog -- Always on patrol from those evil-doer&#39;s. 
iConomy -- Advanced economy system for all players
Showcase -- Our current Shopping System
Minecart Mania -- Absolute control over those pesky Minecarts!
Watchblock -- Creative Anti-griefing measures; very powerful!
Towny -- Towns System (primary land management)

We would love for you to come join us! We have fresh maps and would enjoy all the company we can get. There is no need to apply in order to log in. Please just log on and ask to become a full time player! It&#39;s as simple as that! If you have any questions at all, please do not hesitate to contact any staff members.

IP: play.undergroundminer.com
Website: undergroundminer.com</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 17 May 2012 05:12:23 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Minecraft</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/welcome-to-underground-miner/442455.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Welcome to Underground Miner!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@codyf02 codyf02]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/codyf02">@codyf02</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Welcome to Underground Miner! Here at Underground Miner, we return to the meaning of Minecraft; Freedom. You, as a player, should have the freedom to choose how you want to play. Does building massive products in a purely Creative world interest you the most? Survival grasp your thoughts as you wage war against creatures and players alike? Or perhaps survival isn’t enough and you seek a harder challenge? We have a challenge that even the best Minecraft players dare to venture into. Here is a further breakdown of our worlds:</p>
<p>Eris Space Station - Spawn<br>
Calliope - Creative, ulimited blocks and flat lands to build to your hearts desire. (Anti-griefing measures in place)<br>
Thanatos - Hardcore Survival. Less focus of RPG, more focused on pure survival. One life. That’s it.<br>
Demios - Survival Mode. Roleplaying, PvP, Towns, Factions<br>
Dolos - Minigames, PvP Arena, Mob Arena, etc.</p>
<p>We use several different plugins at Underground Miner. These include:</p>
<p>Spout – Our server is spout enabled. We highly recommend Spoutcraft (not required)<br>
Multiverse – Multiple different worlds to explore and build!<br>
Essentials – Core commands, providing much needed simple commands.<br>
Falsebook – Integrated Circuits and advanced Redstone controls.<br>
Massband – Tape measure! So simple, yet so useful.<br>
Dynmap – Fully rendered maps. Anytime. Anywhere.<br>
Worldedit – Cuboid editing, for those “Hard to reach” projects.<br>
Worldguard – Protection spread across the server<br>
Factions – Join together to fight the forces of evil!<br>
LWC – Protect your belongings from those curious griefers.<br>
Blocklog – Always on patrol from those evil-doer’s.<br>
iConomy – Advanced economy system for all players<br>
Showcase – Our current Shopping System<br>
Minecart Mania – Absolute control over those pesky Minecarts!<br>
Watchblock – Creative Anti-griefing measures; very powerful!<br>
Towny – Towns System (primary land management)</p>
<p>We would love for you to come join us! We have fresh maps and would enjoy all the company we can get. There is no need to apply in order to log in. Please just log on and ask to become a full time player! It’s as simple as that! If you have any questions at all, please do not hesitate to contact any staff members.</p>
<p>IP: <a href="http://play.undergroundminer.com" rel="nofollow noopener">play.undergroundminer.com</a><br>
Website: <a href="http://undergroundminer.com" rel="nofollow noopener">undergroundminer.com</a></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/welcome-to-underground-miner/442455/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/welcome-to-underground-miner/442455/1</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 17 May 2012 05:12:23 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-442455-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/welcome-to-underground-miner/442455.rss">Welcome to Underground Miner!</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
