<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Need help on music and effect buttons</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/need-help-on-music-and-effect-buttons/322308</link>
    <description>[img]http://img704.imageshack.us/img704/754/screenshot039c.png[/img]
I need to make it so the music and effect volume buttons pop up instead of the message saying &quot;Music + Sounds are only available in the high detail version of the game.&quot; I know this isn&#39;t client-sided because I can log into another server with the same client and those buttons will be there. I think it has something to do with a missing setSidebarInterface or possibly a setClientConfig code that needs to go in the initialize method, but I can&#39;t seem to figure out what the codes are. I&#39;ve been looking in another source I have that has those buttons, but I just can&#39;t seem to figure it out. Help? Thanks.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 27 Dec 2009 11:27:56 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/need-help-on-music-and-effect-buttons/322308.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Need help on music and effect buttons</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Spades Spades]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/spades">@Spades</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p><img src="http://img704.imageshack.us/img704/754/screenshot039c.png" alt width="" height=""><br>
I need to make it so the music and effect volume buttons pop up instead of the message saying “Music + Sounds are only available in the high detail version of the game.” I know this isn’t client-sided because I can log into another server with the same client and those buttons will be there. I think it has something to do with a missing setSidebarInterface or possibly a setClientConfig code that needs to go in the initialize method, but I can’t seem to figure out what the codes are. I’ve been looking in another source I have that has those buttons, but I just can’t seem to figure it out. Help? Thanks.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/need-help-on-music-and-effect-buttons/322308/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/need-help-on-music-and-effect-buttons/322308/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 27 Dec 2009 11:27:56 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-322308-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/need-help-on-music-and-effect-buttons/322308.rss">Need help on music and effect buttons</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
