<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Tragedy - A Story</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/tragedy-a-story/35732</link>
    <description>[center][b]Tragedy[/b]
Chapter 1: Horror[/center]
The sun glistened brightly, the day all was calm, everyone was up and about. The busy citizens of this small town were preparing for a feast, in honor of their thousand year civilization, in honor of those who helped bring it up.
There was a rumor going around, though, that the city was cursed, that the founders were the cause of the disease that was starting. People died, engulfed in agony as their last gasp for air was their most painful, and their skin trembled, quaking beneath the fever that they had gotten. The next few weeks were filled with laughter and feasting. Then the day came, where everyone woke up happy but felt ill. They had a fever, not much, but it was still there.
It got worse, everyone was infected. There wasn&#39;t much time for them, so one villager took it upon himself to tell everyone one last story, to attempt to ease the pain.
&quot;There they were, the founders of this once great city where we will have our last breathe,&quot; he gasped as he finished the sentence, his voice low and hoarse, but still understandable, &quot;they flourished because of one man. He saved them all, but cursed us on the journey.
&quot;He was young, around 16, with a broad mind and a will to bring up a vast nation. He succeeded, but only to create this cursed death in the end, the tenth century of darkness.&quot;
The disease sunk in, everyone knew they were going to die, so they listened closely, to what was to be the last words of their home and death place...

[center]Chapter 2: The Beginning of Life[/center]
He pulled up his sword and began to swing it around violently. He had always dreamt of being a soldier of his king&#39;s army. He always took the lead when hunting for food, and he had trained diligently for this day, the day he&#39;d be tested to join.

[i]More to come![/i] I&#39;ll write more when I can think of it. Hopefully you enjoyed what I&#39;ve written so far :) I&#39;ll try to update every day.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 21 Dec 2006 16:48:39 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>General Discussion</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/tragedy-a-story/35732.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Tragedy - A Story</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Zeh_Progage Zeh Progage]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/zeh_progage">@Zeh_Progage</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Writer’s block is killer, sorry if I can’t update lol. I can’t think of anything to write anymore but poems, but they get boring after you write hundreds <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/frowning.png?v=6" title=":frowning:" class="emoji" alt=":frowning:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/tragedy-a-story/35732/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/tragedy-a-story/35732/3</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Dec 2006 16:48:39 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-35732-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/tragedy-a-story/35732.rss">Tragedy - A Story</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Tragedy - A Story</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@leader leader]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/leader">@leader</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“Zeh Progage, post:1, topic:35732”][center]<span class="bbcode-b">Tragedy</span><br>
Chapter 1: Horror[/center]<br>
The sun glistened brightly, the day all was calm, everyone was up and about.</p>
<p>The busy citizens of this small town were preparing for a feast, in honor of their thousand year civilization, in honor of those who helped bring it up.</p>
<p>There was a rumor going around, though, that the city was cursed, that the founders were the cause of the disease that was starting.</p>
<p>They had a fever, not much, but it was still there.</p>
<p>There wasn’t much time for them, so one villager took it upon himself to tell everyone one last story, to attempt to ease the pain.</p>
<p>“There they were, the founders of this once great city where we will have our last breathe,” he gasped as he finished the sentence, his voice low and hoarse, but still understandable, "they flourished because of one man. He saved them all, but cursed us on the journey.[/quote]</p>
<p>Corrections:</p>
<p>The sun glistened brightly, <span class="bbcode-b">choose from below</span>, everyone was up and about.<br>
Choose: <span class="bbcode-b">the day was calm</span> or <span class="bbcode-b">today all was calm</span></p>
<p>The busy citizens of this small town were preparing for a feast, in honor of their thousand year civilization<span class="bbcode-b">;</span> in honor of those who helped bring it up.</p>
<p>There was a rumor going around, though, that the city was cursed. <span class="bbcode-b">It was assumed</span> that the founders <span class="bbcode-b">of city’s name</span> were the cause of the disease that was starting.</p>
<p>They had a fever, not <span class="bbcode-b"> put a different word here</span>, but it was still there.</p>
<p>There wasn’t much time for them, so one villager took it upon himself to tell everyone one last story, to attempt to ease <span class="bbcode-b">their</span> pain.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">So he began…</span> “There they were, the founders of this once great city<span class="bbcode-b">…</span>where we will have our last breathe,” he gasped as he finished the sentence, his voice low and hoarse, but still understandable<span class="bbcode-b">.</span> "<span class="bbcode-b">T</span>hey flourished because of one man. He saved them all, but cursed us on <span class="bbcode-b">his</span> journey.</p>
<p>I would continue on, but I need to go to sleep…tired. Good job though. Try to grab the reader’s attention. I hope my corrections will not discourage you from continuing your story.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/tragedy-a-story/35732/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/tragedy-a-story/35732/2</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 16 Dec 2006 11:49:50 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-35732-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/tragedy-a-story/35732.rss">Tragedy - A Story</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Tragedy - A Story</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Zeh_Progage Zeh Progage]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/zeh_progage">@Zeh_Progage</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[center]<span class="bbcode-b">Tragedy</span><br>
Chapter 1: Horror[/center]<br>
The sun glistened brightly, the day all was calm, everyone was up and about. The busy citizens of this small town were preparing for a feast, in honor of their thousand year civilization, in honor of those who helped bring it up.<br>
There was a rumor going around, though, that the city was cursed, that the founders were the cause of the disease that was starting. People died, engulfed in agony as their last gasp for air was their most painful, and their skin trembled, quaking beneath the fever that they had gotten. The next few weeks were filled with laughter and feasting. Then the day came, where everyone woke up happy but felt ill. They had a fever, not much, but it was still there.<br>
It got worse, everyone was infected. There wasn’t much time for them, so one villager took it upon himself to tell everyone one last story, to attempt to ease the pain.<br>
“There they were, the founders of this once great city where we will have our last breathe,” he gasped as he finished the sentence, his voice low and hoarse, but still understandable, "they flourished because of one man. He saved them all, but cursed us on the journey.<br>
“He was young, around 16, with a broad mind and a will to bring up a vast nation. He succeeded, but only to create this cursed death in the end, the tenth century of darkness.”<br>
The disease sunk in, everyone knew they were going to die, so they listened closely, to what was to be the last words of their home and death place…</p>
<p>[center]Chapter 2: The Beginning of Life[/center]<br>
He pulled up his sword and began to swing it around violently. He had always dreamt of being a soldier of his king’s army. He always took the lead when hunting for food, and he had trained diligently for this day, the day he’d be tested to join.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-i">More to come!</span> I’ll write more when I can think of it. Hopefully you enjoyed what I’ve written so far <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=6" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"> I’ll try to update every day.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/tragedy-a-story/35732/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/tragedy-a-story/35732/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 16 Dec 2006 11:31:53 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-35732-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/tragedy-a-story/35732.rss">Tragedy - A Story</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
