<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Neopets Stock Market Game Script Concept</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/neopets-stock-market-game-script-concept/105111</link>
    <description>Hey guys, I just thought of this concept for a SCAR script for the Neopets Stock Market game. I&#39;m too damn rusty with SCAR and too damn lazy to brush up again after so many years so maybe one of ya&#39;ll can pick up on it if you think you can do it ;)

Basicly what I thought of was that what the script does is basicly reloads the stock portfolio page once every one or two minutes and checks the amount the stocks have gone up. If the amount is the preset amount it will automatically sell that stock and go back to watching the stock market for you. All the user has to do is ensure that he has a good amount of stocks in his portfolio.

I&#39;m not sure of the limitation of the current version of SCAR but if this is too far fetched like it was a few years ago when I used SCAR then perhaps someone could pick up on it with Visual Basic or something else that offers more flexibility. Tell me how it goes if your attempting to do this. I&#39;m curious.  :cool:

Good luck scripters/programmers and everyone else giving this a shot!</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 03 Jun 2007 10:36:01 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/neopets-stock-market-game-script-concept/105111.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Neopets Stock Market Game Script Concept</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@HellHunter HellHunter]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/hellhunter">@HellHunter</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Hey guys, I just thought of this concept for a SCAR script for the Neopets Stock Market game. I’m too damn rusty with SCAR and too damn lazy to brush up again after so many years so maybe one of ya’ll can pick up on it if you think you can do it <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/wink.png?v=6" title=":wink:" class="emoji" alt=":wink:"></p>
<p>Basicly what I thought of was that what the script does is basicly reloads the stock portfolio page once every one or two minutes and checks the amount the stocks have gone up. If the amount is the preset amount it will automatically sell that stock and go back to watching the stock market for you. All the user has to do is ensure that he has a good amount of stocks in his portfolio.</p>
<p>I’m not sure of the limitation of the current version of SCAR but if this is too far fetched like it was a few years ago when I used SCAR then perhaps someone could pick up on it with Visual Basic or something else that offers more flexibility. Tell me how it goes if your attempting to do this. I’m curious.  <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/cool.png?v=6" title=":cool:" class="emoji" alt=":cool:"></p>
<p>Good luck scripters/programmers and everyone else giving this a shot!</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/neopets-stock-market-game-script-concept/105111/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/neopets-stock-market-game-script-concept/105111/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 03 Jun 2007 10:36:01 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-105111-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/neopets-stock-market-game-script-concept/105111.rss">Neopets Stock Market Game Script Concept</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
