<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Thinking about L.A</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/thinking-about-l-a/540121</link>
    <description>So basically this is the jist of my situation. You can skip the quote if you&#39;re not interested in hearing my problems.
[quote=&quot;TabbyKiller, post:13, topic:540072&quot;]Well I was one credit off gaining university entrance this year. I can get that one credit before trimester 2 starts but that&#39;ll just ruin the whole curriculum I was planning on studying this year. I decided instead of going for a bachelors degree of arts I will try filming a few videos/movies and hope to get noticed somehow. Other than that I&#39;m thinking about perusing a career in acting as well as directing and editing. I really am stuck at the moment, I have no clue where to start, equipment costs a lot and I&#39;m trying to apply for a seasonal job that pays $650+ a week which will do the job while I part time study for the 1 credit I need to gain university entrance. I want to move to LA where all the magic happens but that&#39;ll require a lot of money that I don&#39;t have right now. Right now I&#39;m trying to save up for a shoulder rig, tripod and dolly set which would really help out with filming. Things aren&#39;t looking up because most of my mates are either going to university or moving overseas. The friends I am stuck with are either full time gamers who don&#39;t get off their ass if the house was burning down or friends that don&#39;t know how to have a good time, both that wont or aren&#39;t really fit to help me peruse my career in film. Does anyone here have any advice on where I should start with the whole movie scene?[/quote]

I&#39;m thinking about moving to L.A. so I get a better chance of becoming a successful actor and film maker. I do however want to know any perks and let downs of moving to Los Angeles from people who have either lived there, or been there. Is it decent pay for a good job, is it easy to get one? Actually you know what, since I&#39;m from New Zealand, just give me all the information you can about America. By this I mean average wage, accommodation costs, risks etc. Anything that will help me survive in great America. Do you get paid weekly or monthly? Here in New Zealand you get paid weekly and most rental houses are paid off weekly. On a random real estate website I found online I had noticed you pay rent monthly around Palms, so do you get paid monthly?</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 15 Feb 2014 20:15:28 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>General Discussion</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/thinking-about-l-a/540121.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Thinking about L.A</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@lare96 lare96]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/lare96">@lare96</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I agree with David, I wouldn’t move to L.A until you’ve either made it or at least have saved the money for it.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/thinking-about-l-a/540121/9">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/thinking-about-l-a/540121/9</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 15 Feb 2014 20:15:28 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-540121-9</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/thinking-about-l-a/540121.rss">Thinking about L.A</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Thinking about L.A</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@amy_webb1 amy_webb]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/amy_webb1">@amy_webb1</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>You want to move too fast too quickly, this profession in question is very unpredictable. You may see someone get somewhere fast but you might not get that yourself. Your best bet is to get experience, if you must make movies on youtube then do it. That gives you one leg up to the other guy that is qualified but doesn’t know what he is doing, the guy that doesn’t have much proof. You seem like you want this to happen over night, but it is a very difficult career choice. I would tread lightly, don’t try any less harder but be weary of what is going on. Make connections, and show that you are good at your craft.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/thinking-about-l-a/540121/8">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/thinking-about-l-a/540121/8</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 15 Feb 2014 12:13:56 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-540121-8</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/thinking-about-l-a/540121.rss">Thinking about L.A</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Thinking about L.A</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@TabbyKiller TabbyKiller]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/tabbykiller">@TabbyKiller</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Local jobs will do me no good here in New Zealand. I’d be better off being an independent producer on YouTube.</p>
<p>I’ve been looking here and there and every single company/person seems to suggest highly of having a damn bachelors degree. Steven Spielberg is living proof of being a university reject who actually made it big. I don’t want to have to pay or waste my time at a school just to learn what I can now here on the internet and end up with a piece of paper saying I’m qualified. My best bet right at this time is to try and produce a well done film, enter it in a festival and hope it gets noticed. If I do somehow get noticed then the chances of being accepted by a job will increase by having that on my resume, I might even get offered a job. I say screw the bachelors degree, I should go hard out on study and practice, develop and produce, win and profit. Only then I can make my move on L.A. with my new and improved resume and focus on improving my acting.</p>
<p>That’s a bit way off topic I guess… Any other advice about taking the biggest step of my life?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/thinking-about-l-a/540121/7">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/thinking-about-l-a/540121/7</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 15 Feb 2014 11:53:40 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-540121-7</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/thinking-about-l-a/540121.rss">Thinking about L.A</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Thinking about L.A</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@amy_webb1 amy_webb]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/amy_webb1">@amy_webb1</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I’d say just search locally for now, some small jobs here and there for the local NZ tv studios and then go to America. Think of Rebal Wilson, though she is Australian, she started in local tv broadcasts and now she’s really big in America. Probably all i can tell you, your decision but choose wisely, you don’t want to end up like the stereotype “i’m a struggling actor”.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/thinking-about-l-a/540121/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/thinking-about-l-a/540121/6</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 15 Feb 2014 11:34:31 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-540121-6</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/thinking-about-l-a/540121.rss">Thinking about L.A</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Thinking about L.A</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@TabbyKiller TabbyKiller]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/tabbykiller">@TabbyKiller</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I don’t see why not.</p>
<blockquote>You will need a visa, and may not use VWP, if you any of these criteria apply to you:
<p>Want to remain in the United States for longer than 90 days;</p>
<p>Want to <span class="bbcode-b">work or study</span> in the United States, including working as a foreign journalist.  This includes attending secondary or tertiary school, and paid or unpaid employment (including au-pairs, interns, working journalists, and government representatives on official business.) For more on the appropriate visa classifications for these activities, please see <a href="http://travel.state.gov" rel="nofollow noopener">travel.state.gov</a>;</p>
</blockquote><br>
I think what you’re thinking of is a green card, that will be difficult for me to get my hands on.
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/thinking-about-l-a/540121/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/thinking-about-l-a/540121/5</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 15 Feb 2014 09:52:13 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-540121-5</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/thinking-about-l-a/540121.rss">Thinking about L.A</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Thinking about L.A</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@xx_matty_xx Justin Bieber]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/xx_matty_xx">@xx_matty_xx</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Would the US really give you a visa to pursue your dreams in the movie industry?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/thinking-about-l-a/540121/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/thinking-about-l-a/540121/4</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 15 Feb 2014 09:34:26 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-540121-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/thinking-about-l-a/540121.rss">Thinking about L.A</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Thinking about L.A</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@TabbyKiller TabbyKiller]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/tabbykiller">@TabbyKiller</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I’m already looking for a job as a Film &amp; Video Editors, Camera Operators, Television, Video, &amp; Motion Picture and Photographer. Right now I am applying for a job here in New Zealand, save up and hopefully make enough for accommodation in L.A. to last til I have received the chance of getting a full time job. I was hoping that a one on one interview would increase my chances of getting a job, if I show them how bad I want it.</p>
<p>According to <a href="http://www.laalmanac.com/employment/em16.htm#Arts" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">this website</a> all of the following jobs above will successfully get me to scrape past rent monthly.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/thinking-about-l-a/540121/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/thinking-about-l-a/540121/3</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 15 Feb 2014 08:58:37 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-540121-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/thinking-about-l-a/540121.rss">Thinking about L.A</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Thinking about L.A</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@davidi2 Davidi2]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/davidi2">@davidi2</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Moving to LA is the number one way to have overpriced shitty living conditions and an overcompetitve job market. You move there AFTER you get established or AFTER you have a job lined up.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/thinking-about-l-a/540121/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/thinking-about-l-a/540121/2</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 15 Feb 2014 08:50:37 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-540121-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/thinking-about-l-a/540121.rss">Thinking about L.A</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Thinking about L.A</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@TabbyKiller TabbyKiller]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/tabbykiller">@TabbyKiller</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>So basically this is the jist of my situation. You can skip the quote if you’re not interested in hearing my problems.</p>
<aside class="quote" data-post="13" data-topic="540072">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/tabbykiller/40/5_e05bb34c421432ee4d40de30c10af3e5.png" class="avatar"><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/gd-is-dead-so-whats-up/540072/13">GD is dead, so... what's up</a>
</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Well I was one credit off gaining university entrance this year. I can get that one credit before trimester 2 starts but that’ll just ruin the whole curriculum I was planning on studying this year. I decided instead of going for a bachelors degree of arts I will try filming a few videos/movies and hope to get noticed somehow. Other than that I’m thinking about perusing a career in acting as well as directing and editing. I really am stuck at the moment, I have no clue where to start, equipment costs a lot and I’m trying to apply for a seasonal job that pays $650+ a week which will do the job while I part time study for the 1 credit I need to gain university entrance. I want to move to LA where all the magic happens but that’ll require a lot of money that I don’t have right now. Right now I’m trying to save up for a shoulder rig, tripod and dolly set which would really help out with filming. Things aren’t looking up because most of my mates are either going to university or moving overseas. The friends I am stuck with are either full time gamers who don’t get off their ass if the house was burning down or friends that don’t know how to have a good time, both that wont or aren’t really fit to help me peruse my career in film. Does anyone here have any advice on where I should start with the whole movie scene?</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I’m thinking about moving to L.A. so I get a better chance of becoming a successful actor and film maker. I do however want to know any perks and let downs of moving to Los Angeles from people who have either lived there, or been there. Is it decent pay for a good job, is it easy to get one? Actually you know what, since I’m from New Zealand, just give me all the information you can about America. By this I mean average wage, accommodation costs, risks etc. Anything that will help me survive in great America. Do you get paid weekly or monthly? Here in New Zealand you get paid weekly and most rental houses are paid off weekly. On a random real estate website I found online I had noticed you pay rent monthly around Palms, so do you get paid monthly?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/thinking-about-l-a/540121/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/thinking-about-l-a/540121/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 15 Feb 2014 08:47:55 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-540121-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/thinking-about-l-a/540121.rss">Thinking about L.A</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
