<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Hmmm interesting</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/hmmm-interesting/80501</link>
    <description>I don&#39;t know if this is in the wrong section but i&#39;m not allowed to post my own server thread, TheBeanie please read and understand that the Project Satan and Satan isle are very different and we can&#39;t get players if you don&#39;t allow the thread, your accusing me of posting something thats not mine, if i host it, its on my computer and everything, i&#39;m most probably the only one who can tell when its off or on and change the features iv&#39;e added.

Why am i being Muted\Warned for something so un-necessary and its just a mistake you&#39;ve seen or made.

[b]If in the wrong section then Move[/b]</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 15 Apr 2007 20:19:15 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/hmmm-interesting/80501.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Hmmm interesting</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Sir_Jay Sir Jay]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/sir_jay">@Sir_Jay</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I don’t know if this is in the wrong section but i’m not allowed to post my own server thread, TheBeanie please read and understand that the Project Satan and Satan isle are very different and we can’t get players if you don’t allow the thread, your accusing me of posting something thats not mine, if i host it, its on my computer and everything, i’m most probably the only one who can tell when its off or on and change the features iv’e added.</p>
<p>Why am i being Muted\Warned for something so un-necessary and its just a mistake you’ve seen or made.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">If in the wrong section then Move</span></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/hmmm-interesting/80501/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/hmmm-interesting/80501/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 15 Apr 2007 20:19:15 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-80501-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/hmmm-interesting/80501.rss">Hmmm interesting</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
