<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Silvania - RP, Survival, Economy, Quests, Jobs, Races, Skills, Towns and more!</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/silvania-rp-survival-economy-quests-jobs-races-skills-towns-and-more/445265</link>
    <description>Hello, and welcome to Silvania!

Just to clarify, I&#39;m keeping this thread as short as possible. So, a few major notes before you join (If nothing else, at least read these...)
- The server is a greylist. This means you can log in, walk around, and talk to the mod team, as well as a few basic spawn quests. Anything else, you have to register and apply (free!) for.
- The job system is limiting. This means each job can only create certain items and you must buy the rest from eachother - it stimulates the economy and works pretty well.
- It is a roleplay server, and you must post a character bio to get accepted. This just proves you know how to RP, and keeps out the complete idiots...


Now, onto the features!
Silvania is based around two warring factions: Caelum (Good) and Mortalitas (Evil). Pick a side and join the fight! With over 1000 years of lore, there is plenty of scope to roleplay. The two factions have had an ever-lasting war with occasional spats of raids and combat.
Within the factions, there are towns. When you join you can choose any of these towns to join and build yourself a house. From there, you can work your way up the server - earning money to build a shop or eventually found your own town, or completing one of the quests around the land for the hundreds of NPCs. Or you could train up your race, searching and finding over 100 shrines unlocking secret powers unique to one of the 6 races.

Spoutcraft users get a huge boost too. If you use the free custom client, you&#39;ll have access to an informative GUI, showing things like your location, a map, your current amount of money, remaining mana and much more! Of course, there is also over 500 custom blocks and items for your pleasure, including 75 new weapons!!


Sound like something you&#39;d enjoy? Come explore the world as a greylister and apply today!
IP: 74.91.27.186
Web: http://www.silvania.co.uk/

When applying, state &quot;Moparcraft&quot; as your referrer!</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 15 Jun 2012 18:37:40 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Minecraft</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/silvania-rp-survival-economy-quests-jobs-races-skills-towns-and-more/445265.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Silvania - RP, Survival, Economy, Quests, Jobs, Races, Skills, Towns and more!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Flenix1 Flenix1]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/flenix1">@Flenix1</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Hello, and welcome to Silvania!</p>
<p>Just to clarify, I’m keeping this thread as short as possible. So, a few major notes before you join (If nothing else, at least read these…)</p>
<ul>
<li>The server is a greylist. This means you can log in, walk around, and talk to the mod team, as well as a few basic spawn quests. Anything else, you have to register and apply (free!) for.</li>
<li>The job system is limiting. This means each job can only create certain items and you must buy the rest from eachother - it stimulates the economy and works pretty well.</li>
<li>It is a roleplay server, and you must post a character bio to get accepted. This just proves you know how to RP, and keeps out the complete idiots…</li>
</ul>
<p>Now, onto the features!<br>
Silvania is based around two warring factions: Caelum (Good) and Mortalitas (Evil). Pick a side and join the fight! With over 1000 years of lore, there is plenty of scope to roleplay. The two factions have had an ever-lasting war with occasional spats of raids and combat.<br>
Within the factions, there are towns. When you join you can choose any of these towns to join and build yourself a house. From there, you can work your way up the server - earning money to build a shop or eventually found your own town, or completing one of the quests around the land for the hundreds of NPCs. Or you could train up your race, searching and finding over 100 shrines unlocking secret powers unique to one of the 6 races.</p>
<p>Spoutcraft users get a huge boost too. If you use the free custom client, you’ll have access to an informative GUI, showing things like your location, a map, your current amount of money, remaining mana and much more! Of course, there is also over 500 custom blocks and items for your pleasure, including 75 new weapons!!</p>
<p>Sound like something you’d enjoy? Come explore the world as a greylister and apply today!<br>
IP: 74.91.27.186<br>
Web: <a href="http://www.silvania.co.uk/" rel="nofollow noopener">http://www.silvania.co.uk/</a></p>
<p>When applying, state “Moparcraft” as your referrer!</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/silvania-rp-survival-economy-quests-jobs-races-skills-towns-and-more/445265/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/silvania-rp-survival-economy-quests-jobs-races-skills-towns-and-more/445265/1</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Jun 2012 18:37:40 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-445265-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/silvania-rp-survival-economy-quests-jobs-races-skills-towns-and-more/445265.rss">Silvania - RP, Survival, Economy, Quests, Jobs, Races, Skills, Towns and more!</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
