<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Several question about Computers</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/several-question-about-computers/388429</link>
    <description>1. If I were to build a standard gaming computer (mid requirements to play online games such as downloadable MMORPG&#39;s and such), what would be the a recommended place to start?

2. Is there a place on the internet which explains specifically what each part stands for and its functionality towards building the computer? This is so I can understand what does what and what they look like so I&#39;m not wasting money building a computer (or paying someone who doesn&#39;t know what they&#39;re doing either and end up wasting parts).

3. Is there any difference in OS (besides the increasingly popular Ubuntu as I may want to dual-boot) when it comes to building a computer with certain parts or will they all function similarly? (I know about adding compatible drivers when changing OS)

4. Are there any recommended anti-virus when completely starting clean as to keep the computer running top-notch?

5. What exactly is over-clocking?

6. Are there any ways to obtain a HP-version of an XP OS disc (I heard that companies no longer distribute the XP disc) online?

7. Unrelated question; I&#39;m in a graphic design class right now (using Mac OSX) and I need a way to browse websites (to obtain appropriate images of the highest quality) instead of grabbing pixel-destroyed thumbnails. This could be a private proxy (no programs, I don&#39;t want to get in trouble for installing outside software to get around things, such as UltraSurf).</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 30 Mar 2011 11:41:22 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Technology</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/several-question-about-computers/388429.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Several question about Computers</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@teh_spede Teh Spede]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/teh_spede">@teh_spede</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I tunnel irc through ssh with screen</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/several-question-about-computers/388429/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/several-question-about-computers/388429/6</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 30 Mar 2011 11:41:22 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-388429-6</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/several-question-about-computers/388429.rss">Several question about Computers</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Several question about Computers</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@tL tL]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/tl">@tL</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Indeed. I tunnel using ssh from my Macbook Pro to a box at my house.</p>
<p>ssh -D 4567 <a href="mailto:user@domain.com">user@domain.com</a> -p 80 (Many schools/colleges block all traffic except port 80, so run sshd on port 80 on your host box).</p>
<p>System preferences &gt; Network &gt; Airport or Ethernet (whichever you’re using) &gt; Proxies &gt; Socks &gt; SOCKS PROXY SERVER: 127.0.0.1 Port: 4567 (or whichever your chose to create it on above) &gt; Apply</p>
<p>And you should be ready to go! Once that information is in there, you can flick the proxy on and off (assuming you’re still connected to your sshd) with:</p>
<p>networksetup -setsocksfirewallproxystate Ethernet off<br>
networksetup -setsocksfirewallproxystate Ethernet on</p>
<p>Replace ethernet with the network interface you’re using.</p>
<p>Saves you having to go through menus each time you want to configure it.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/several-question-about-computers/388429/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/several-question-about-computers/388429/5</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 30 Mar 2011 09:10:37 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-388429-5</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/several-question-about-computers/388429.rss">Several question about Computers</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Several question about Computers</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@moparisthebest Moparisthebest]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/moparisthebest">@moparisthebest</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Then doing what I said should work well for you, assuming you can run ‘ssh’ from the OSX command line, which you probably can.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/several-question-about-computers/388429/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/several-question-about-computers/388429/4</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 28 Mar 2011 23:24:36 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-388429-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/several-question-about-computers/388429.rss">Several question about Computers</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Several question about Computers</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@LilXCj LilXCj]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/lilxcj">@LilXCj</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“Moparisthebest, post:2, topic:388429”]7. I don’t really understand the question.  In class, they won’t let you browse the web?  You could probably run an ssh server at your house, and do something like this:<br>
<a href="http://wiki.freaks-unidos.net/weblogs/azul/firefox-ssh-tunnel%5B/quote%5D" class="onebox" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">http://wiki.freaks-unidos.net/weblogs/azul/firefox-ssh-tunnel[/quote]</a></p>
<p>Thanks for all the previous answers.</p>
<p>They let me browse the web, but I cannot browse on websites that host high quality landscapes, brushes, renders and alike when in graphic design due to firewalls from the school. I need a way to get around that.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/several-question-about-computers/388429/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/several-question-about-computers/388429/3</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 28 Mar 2011 22:47:24 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-388429-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/several-question-about-computers/388429.rss">Several question about Computers</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Several question about Computers</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@moparisthebest Moparisthebest]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/moparisthebest">@moparisthebest</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <ol>
<li>
<p><a href="https://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php/topic,483858.msg3544840.html#msg3544840">https://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php/topic,483858.msg3544840.html#msg3544840</a></p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Ok, crash computer course:<br>
To build a computer, you need these things:</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Motherboard, RAM, and CPU, these have to be compatible with each other.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Case with PSU (power supply) to put it all in, the only thing you must worry about here is that the PSU has enough watts to run your entire system, if you get a top-of-the-line video card, it might pull most of your power.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Video card, unless you have one integrated into your motherboard, but for a gaming rig, you probably don’t want to do this.  Nowadays you will want a video card that has a PCI-E x16 v2.0 interface, and your motherboard should have an empty slot for this, it probably will.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Optionally, you can have a dvd-burner, or other optical drive, it will run about $20 at newegg.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>You need a hard drive too, you can buy a good one at newegg, or use the one out of your old computer.<br>
Then it just all snaps together, it’s really easy, and we can help you here with it.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Whether or not drivers are available is your only concern here.  The only place I’ve ever ran into large problems with this is with wireless card drivers, hopefully your desktop will be connected with a wire though.  Either way, a quick google of your set up with ‘ubuntu’ will usually tell you if there are any problems.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>I don’t use an anti-virus, but then I spend 99.9% of my computer time using Linux.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Basically, it’s just making your hardware (CPU, RAM, or Video card) run faster than advertised.  It generates more heat, which can damage things, and sometimes makes it less stable.  Generally if you have to ask what over-clocking is, you don’t want to do it.  I’ve never had the need to overclock, another few hundred Mhz on your 3+Ghz CPU isn’t going to make a noticeable difference.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>For a computer you already own?  You should probably call HP and ask.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>I don’t really understand the question.  In class, they won’t let you browse the web?  You could probably run an ssh server at your house, and do something like this:<br>
<a href="http://wiki.freaks-unidos.net/weblogs/azul/firefox-ssh-tunnel">http://wiki.freaks-unidos.net/weblogs/azul/firefox-ssh-tunnel</a></p>
</li>
</ol>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/several-question-about-computers/388429/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/several-question-about-computers/388429/2</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 28 Mar 2011 13:56:19 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-388429-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/several-question-about-computers/388429.rss">Several question about Computers</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Several question about Computers</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@LilXCj LilXCj]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/lilxcj">@LilXCj</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <ol>
<li>
<p>If I were to build a standard gaming computer (mid requirements to play online games such as downloadable MMORPG’s and such), what would be the a recommended place to start?</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Is there a place on the internet which explains specifically what each part stands for and its functionality towards building the computer? This is so I can understand what does what and what they look like so I’m not wasting money building a computer (or paying someone who doesn’t know what they’re doing either and end up wasting parts).</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Is there any difference in OS (besides the increasingly popular Ubuntu as I may want to dual-boot) when it comes to building a computer with certain parts or will they all function similarly? (I know about adding compatible drivers when changing OS)</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Are there any recommended anti-virus when completely starting clean as to keep the computer running top-notch?</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>What exactly is over-clocking?</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Are there any ways to obtain a HP-version of an XP OS disc (I heard that companies no longer distribute the XP disc) online?</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Unrelated question; I’m in a graphic design class right now (using Mac OSX) and I need a way to browse websites (to obtain appropriate images of the highest quality) instead of grabbing pixel-destroyed thumbnails. This could be a private proxy (no programs, I don’t want to get in trouble for installing outside software to get around things, such as UltraSurf).</p>
</li>
</ol>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/several-question-about-computers/388429/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/several-question-about-computers/388429/1</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 28 Mar 2011 13:42:54 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-388429-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/several-question-about-computers/388429.rss">Several question about Computers</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
