<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Port forwarding using a belkin wireless router</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/port-forwarding-using-a-belkin-wireless-router/283298</link>
    <description>I assume this is the correct forum to post this in (If not please move it)...

Heres my problem:

I can setup a Hamachi server no problem. My environment variables, JDK, JRE... everything works just fine. The problem i&#39;m having it port forwarding. All these tutorials are mainly just dealing with Linksy&#39;s  routers and that&#39;s no help for me because my router is like super ghetto walmart brand crap. Now the problem i think that&#39;s occurring is because i&#39;ve made the port accessible through my wireless router but not my modem. The way my internet is wired goes: Cable cord -&gt; Modem -&gt; Wireless Router -&gt; My computer

I have the exception added through the wireless router but not the modem. Is the the problem that&#39;s occurring?

If anyone would be willing to take a look via teamviewer it would be greatly appreciated.

Here&#39;s how i went about enabling the port on my Wireless Router:
Edit:  Sec</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 11 Jun 2009 19:31:46 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/port-forwarding-using-a-belkin-wireless-router/283298.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Port forwarding using a belkin wireless router</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@D_S D S]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/d_s">@D_S</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I assume this is the correct forum to post this in (If not please move it)…</p>
<p>Heres my problem:</p>
<p>I can setup a Hamachi server no problem. My environment variables, JDK, JRE… everything works just fine. The problem i’m having it port forwarding. All these tutorials are mainly just dealing with Linksy’s  routers and that’s no help for me because my router is like super ghetto walmart brand crap. Now the problem i think that’s occurring is because i’ve made the port accessible through my wireless router but not my modem. The way my internet is wired goes: Cable cord -&gt; Modem -&gt; Wireless Router -&gt; My computer</p>
<p>I have the exception added through the wireless router but not the modem. Is the the problem that’s occurring?</p>
<p>If anyone would be willing to take a look via teamviewer it would be greatly appreciated.</p>
<p>Here’s how i went about enabling the port on my Wireless Router:<br>
Edit:  Sec</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/port-forwarding-using-a-belkin-wireless-router/283298/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/port-forwarding-using-a-belkin-wireless-router/283298/1</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jun 2009 19:31:46 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-283298-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/port-forwarding-using-a-belkin-wireless-router/283298.rss">Port forwarding using a belkin wireless router</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
