<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>[Scar] First SRL Script - Autotalker</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/scar-first-srl-script-autotalker/8427</link>
    <description>In this tutorial I will be explaining, and showing you have to create you very own autotalker for trading purposes.

Scripting Level: Novice
SRL Version: 2.32
Things Learnt By This Tutorial:
-Using various procedures by SRL
-Simple loops
-Variables
-Includes

Ok, we begin...


1. All scripts start of with a program name:
[code]
Program Autotalker;
[/code]
This is basically just to name your script to something it relates too. Of course, private scripts can be called anything as long as you know what the name relates to.

2. Then we have to declare includes, more simple than you may think, simply add this to a new line underneath the first:
[code]
{.include SRL\SRL.scar}
{.include SRL\SRL\misc\Trade.scar}
[/code]
Anything with {.include ...} will be included int you script, this allows you to call up procedures and functions which are found inside the included file. Includes are nearly lways used for detecting random events and enabling the script to do more things with much less code involved.

3. Press enter to go onto the next line, now we are going to declare some variables into the script, to do this simple add: &quot;var&quot; followed by a series of variable names and the variable types, for this script we will be using &quot;Msge&quot; as a variable, so add this to the line:
[code]
Var Msge: String;
[/code] &quot;Var&quot; tells the scrip to load up the variables which follow after the tage up to the &quot;:&quot;. &quot;Msge&quot; is the name of the varible we are using and &quot;string;&quot; is telling the script that the variable &quot;Message&quot; is a string value (text value).

4. Next we are going to start the fun part, making the actual, factual script...

    To start of with, every new event which you want the script to do, e.i Type, Open Trade Screen, Check Randoms etc will need to be set as a procedure followed by the actions afterwards:

[code]
Procedure Setup;
[/code] This procedure or event is a &quot;setup&quot; for the script, almost every script has one as it allows the user to alter any parts of the script to make it suitable to run e.i Colour of an item, Ammount of trips to do.
This only works if you call it up in the main loop at the end of the script (we&#39;ll talk about that later).

5. So youve name set a program name, included files, initiallised variables, and created your first procedure, next thing is to fill in the procedure with functions or commands for the script to follow.

    The first function or command we are going to place is &quot;Begin&quot;, which tells the script to begin the procedure.

    e.g.
    [code]
    Procedure Setup;
      Begin;
    [/code]
    The second command we are going to place is &quot;End&quot; which tells the script to finish the procedure.

    e.g.
    [code]
    Procedure Setup;
      Begin;
      End;
    [/code]

Now we have to add filling into the procedure between the &quot;Begin&quot; and &quot;End&quot; functions. For this script I will be adding this:
[code]
Procedure Setup;
  Begin;
    Msge:= &#39; Message Here&#39; // Type your message here
  End;
[/code]
Line &quot;Msge:= &#39; Message Here&#39; // Type your message here&quot; is to set the variable &quot;Msge&quot; to a value of text, the value is determined within the quote marks

6. Next you want to start making the actuall functioning procedure which will perform the autotalking. To do this you will need to start by writing the procedure basics (step 5). Then next we will be using some of SRL&#39;s functions.

The first is going to be &quot;TypeSend&quot; which will effectivly type in your message and then send it into runescape chat (same as pressing &#39;enter&#39;). So lets add that now:

[code]
Procedure Chat;
  Begin
    TypeSend(Msge);
  End;
[/code]
The fact that I have used &quot;TypeSend(Msge)&quot; is so that the function knows that the string to type is the variable &quot;Msge&quot; which has been set in the setup procedure.

Now to add one more function:

[code]
Procedure Chat;
  Begin
    TypeSend(Msge);
    Wait(Random(200)+200);
  End;
[/code]

The &quot;wait&quot; command tells the script to pause for a set time within the ()&#39;s. Using &quot;Random(200)&quot; tells the script to produce a random number from 0-200, this is then added (using the &quot;+&quot; symbol) to the last digit which is  static digit of 200. This means that the highest number and lowest number or waiting time would be 200 milliseconds and 400 milliseconds with all possible integers with the two values.

7.Next we are going to create the procedure to stop the script, once someone wishes to trade with you, because you dont want the script to continue to work once your in trade because thats too obvious. To do this we are going to use some more of SRL fabulous procedures.

Start by writing the basics of a procedure again. And then fill in the code inbetween, as shown:

[code]
Procedure Stop;
  Begin
    If(FindTrade = True)then
      begin
        accepttrade;
          Repeat
            Wait(1000)
          Until(TradeScreen=False)
      end
    else
      begin
      end
  End;
[/code]

Ok, so you know the first two lines... &quot;If(FindTrade=True)then&quot; basically checks if someone wishes to trade with you, &quot;FindTrade: Boolean&quot; is an SRL function, so remember you cannot use this function unless you have included SRL. If the script does find someone who want to trade then the script will accept the trade offer and then go into a loop called up by the &quot;Repeat&quot; command. What ever code is inbetween the &quot;Repeat&quot; and &quot;Until()&quot; commands will loop a set ammount of times. In this case the loop is a pause allowing you to do your trade. This loop is repeat until then tradescreen cannot be seen anymore, &#39; Until(TradeScreen = False)&#39;.

The &#39;Else&#39; command basically means that if any other turnouts of the client other than the ones specified by the &quot;if()then&quot; statements will be handled in the code inbetween the &quot;begin&quot; and &quot;end&quot; tags.

8. So, ok you&#39;ve got a good idea of most things using SRL and some knowledge of SCAR itself. But its not over yet, we will now need to call up the final loop, or the main loop. This is easy, just like most procedures, except that this main loop doesn&#39;t need a procedure name. so...

[code]
Begin
End.
[/code]

Noticed i have used a &#39;.&#39; at the end of the &quot;End&quot; command instead of a &#39;;&#39;, this is because its the main loop, and well it deserves it. You dont need to know why really, as long as you remember the &#39;.&#39; goes on the end of the main loop, the last character you type on your keyboard.

Now to fill in the code..

Start by putting in teh setup, seeing as we only need to call this procedure up once, we will put it outside the loop.

[code]
Begin
  Setup;
End.
[/code]

Then add a loop:
[code]
Begin
  Setup;
    Repeat
    Until(false)
End.
[/code]

Noticed i&#39;ve used &#39;Until(False)&#39;, this will mean that the loop is never ending, well never ending in the sense that you dont manually stop the script.

Next add the procedures which you want to loop, in this case Chat; and Stop;...

[code]
Begin
  Setup;
    Repeat
      Chat;
      Stop;
    Until(false)
End.
[/code]

9. Now lets look at the script as a whole...

[code]
Program Autotalker;
{.include SRL\SRL.scar}
{.include SRL\SRL\misc\Trade.scar}

Var Msge: String;

Procedure Setup;
  Begin;
    Msge:= &#39; Message Here&#39; // Type your message here
  End;
 
Procedure Chat;
  Begin
    TypeSend(Msge);
    Wait(Random(200)+200);
  End;

Procedure Stop;
  Begin
    If(FindTrade = True)then
      begin
        accepttrade;
          Repeat
            Wait(1000)
          Until(TradeScreen=False)
      end
    else
      begin
      end
  End;

Begin
  Setup;
    Repeat
      Chat;
      Stop;
    Until(false)
End.
[/code]

Make sure theres no errors, in this case it should be working just fine, now open runescape, set up the script and select the runecape client with the crosshair and press play.

Watch the script work.

If theres any errors or if you need help with this tutorial please post it here and not email me. Thank you.


Brought to you by http://www.scarforum.com, enjoy</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 19 Aug 2006 08:08:59 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/scar-first-srl-script-autotalker/8427.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>[Scar] First SRL Script - Autotalker</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@R.I.P_RSC R.I.P RSC]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/r.i.p_rsc">@R.I.P_RSC</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>nice tut i made the autotalker but havent tested it yet going to do that now and if it works im going to put some other procedures in it if thats ok</p>
<p>edit: after i accepted a trade it doesnt restart and it says:[Runtime Error] : Exception: Access violation at address 00654087 in module ‘scar.exe’. Read of address 00000008 in line 1662 in script C:\Program Files\SCAR 2.03\includes\srl\srl\core\AntiRandoms.scar</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/scar-first-srl-script-autotalker/8427/7">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/scar-first-srl-script-autotalker/8427/7</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 19 Aug 2006 08:08:59 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-8427-7</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/scar-first-srl-script-autotalker/8427.rss">[Scar] First SRL Script - Autotalker</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Scar] First SRL Script - Autotalker</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Shoker Shoker]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/shoker">@Shoker</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Hey, good tut it really helped me out. Also, the script doesn’t stop typing after the trade box is opened.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/scar-first-srl-script-autotalker/8427/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/scar-first-srl-script-autotalker/8427/6</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 17 Aug 2006 08:09:02 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-8427-6</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/scar-first-srl-script-autotalker/8427.rss">[Scar] First SRL Script - Autotalker</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Scar] First SRL Script - Autotalker</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@vast vast]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/vast">@vast</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>thanks, il give it a try</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/scar-first-srl-script-autotalker/8427/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/scar-first-srl-script-autotalker/8427/5</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 09 Aug 2006 22:29:35 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-8427-5</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/scar-first-srl-script-autotalker/8427.rss">[Scar] First SRL Script - Autotalker</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Scar] First SRL Script - Autotalker</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Ron Ron]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/ron">@Ron</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“Uxalis, post:3, topic:8427”][quote author=Ron link=topic=11930.msg134714#msg134714 date=1154992087]<br>
Nice tutorial. Unfortunately wrong section, sorry. I’ll move it for you. <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=9" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"><br>
[/quote]</p>
<p>You cannot post in SCAR - Tutorials Mods have to move it there.[/quote]<br>
You’re welcome?</p>
<p>You posted it in the tutorials section and I moved it for you… Something wrong? lol…</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/scar-first-srl-script-autotalker/8427/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/scar-first-srl-script-autotalker/8427/4</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 09 Aug 2006 14:14:58 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-8427-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/scar-first-srl-script-autotalker/8427.rss">[Scar] First SRL Script - Autotalker</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Scar] First SRL Script - Autotalker</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Uxalis Uxalis]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/uxalis">@Uxalis</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote no-group quote-modified" data-post="2" data-topic="8427">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/ron/40/5_6259e4fa9dfe0dec282fb0955bb1974c.png" class="avatar"> Ron:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Nice tutorial. Unfortunately wrong section, sorry. I’ll move it for you. <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=9" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>You cannot post in SCAR - Tutorials Mods have to move it there.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/scar-first-srl-script-autotalker/8427/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/scar-first-srl-script-autotalker/8427/3</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 09 Aug 2006 13:48:31 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-8427-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/scar-first-srl-script-autotalker/8427.rss">[Scar] First SRL Script - Autotalker</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Scar] First SRL Script - Autotalker</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Ron Ron]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/ron">@Ron</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Nice tutorial. Unfortunately wrong section, sorry. I’ll move it for you. <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=9" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/scar-first-srl-script-autotalker/8427/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/scar-first-srl-script-autotalker/8427/2</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2006 23:08:07 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-8427-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/scar-first-srl-script-autotalker/8427.rss">[Scar] First SRL Script - Autotalker</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Scar] First SRL Script - Autotalker</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Uxalis Uxalis]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/uxalis">@Uxalis</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>In this tutorial I will be explaining, and showing you have to create you very own autotalker for trading purposes.</p>
<p>Scripting Level: Novice<br>
SRL Version: 2.32<br>
Things Learnt By This Tutorial:<br>
-Using various procedures by SRL<br>
-Simple loops<br>
-Variables<br>
-Includes</p>
<p>Ok, we begin…</p>
<ol>
<li>All scripts start of with a program name:</li>
</ol>
<pre><code class="lang-auto">Program Autotalker;</code></pre>
<p>This is basically just to name your script to something it relates too. Of course, private scripts can be called anything as long as you know what the name relates to.</p>
<ol start="2">
<li>Then we have to declare includes, more simple than you may think, simply add this to a new line underneath the first:</li>
</ol>
<pre><code class="lang-auto">{.include SRL\SRL.scar}
{.include SRL\SRL\misc\Trade.scar}</code></pre>
<p>Anything with {.include …} will be included int you script, this allows you to call up procedures and functions which are found inside the included file. Includes are nearly lways used for detecting random events and enabling the script to do more things with much less code involved.</p>
<ol start="3">
<li>Press enter to go onto the next line, now we are going to declare some variables into the script, to do this simple add: “var” followed by a series of variable names and the variable types, for this script we will be using “Msge” as a variable, so add this to the line:</li>
</ol>
<p><code>
Var Msge: String;
</code> “Var” tells the scrip to load up the variables which follow after the tage up to the “:”. “Msge” is the name of the varible we are using and “string;” is telling the script that the variable “Message” is a string value (text value).</p>
<ol start="4">
<li>
<p>Next we are going to start the fun part, making the actual, factual script…</p>
<p>To start of with, every new event which you want the script to do, e.i Type, Open Trade Screen, Check Randoms etc will need to be set as a procedure followed by the actions afterwards:</p>
</li>
</ol>
<p><code>
Procedure Setup;
</code> This procedure or event is a “setup” for the script, almost every script has one as it allows the user to alter any parts of the script to make it suitable to run e.i Colour of an item, Ammount of trips to do.<br>
This only works if you call it up in the main loop at the end of the script (we’ll talk about that later).</p>
<ol start="5">
<li>
<p>So youve name set a program name, included files, initiallised variables, and created your first procedure, next thing is to fill in the procedure with functions or commands for the script to follow.</p>
<p>The first function or command we are going to place is “Begin”, which tells the script to begin the procedure.</p>
<p>e.g.</p>
<pre><code class="lang-auto">    Procedure Setup;
      Begin;</code></pre>
<p>The second command we are going to place is “End” which tells the script to finish the procedure.</p>
<p>e.g.</p>
<pre><code class="lang-auto">    Procedure Setup;
      Begin;
      End;</code></pre>
</li>
</ol>
<p>Now we have to add filling into the procedure between the “Begin” and “End” functions. For this script I will be adding this:</p>
<pre><code class="lang-auto">Procedure Setup;
  Begin;
    Msge:= ' Message Here' // Type your message here
  End;</code></pre>
<p>Line “Msge:= ’ Message Here’ // Type your message here” is to set the variable “Msge” to a value of text, the value is determined within the quote marks</p>
<ol start="6">
<li>Next you want to start making the actuall functioning procedure which will perform the autotalking. To do this you will need to start by writing the procedure basics (step 5). Then next we will be using some of SRL’s functions.</li>
</ol>
<p>The first is going to be “TypeSend” which will effectivly type in your message and then send it into runescape chat (same as pressing ‘enter’). So lets add that now:</p>
<pre><code class="lang-auto">Procedure Chat;
  Begin
    TypeSend(Msge);
  End;</code></pre>
<p>The fact that I have used “TypeSend(Msge)” is so that the function knows that the string to type is the variable “Msge” which has been set in the setup procedure.</p>
<p>Now to add one more function:</p>
<pre><code class="lang-auto">Procedure Chat;
  Begin
    TypeSend(Msge);
    Wait(Random(200)+200);
  End;</code></pre>
<p>The “wait” command tells the script to pause for a set time within the ()'s. Using “Random(200)” tells the script to produce a random number from 0-200, this is then added (using the “+” symbol) to the last digit which is  static digit of 200. This means that the highest number and lowest number or waiting time would be 200 milliseconds and 400 milliseconds with all possible integers with the two values.</p>
<p>7.Next we are going to create the procedure to stop the script, once someone wishes to trade with you, because you dont want the script to continue to work once your in trade because thats too obvious. To do this we are going to use some more of SRL fabulous procedures.</p>
<p>Start by writing the basics of a procedure again. And then fill in the code inbetween, as shown:</p>
<pre><code class="lang-auto">Procedure Stop;
  Begin
    If(FindTrade = True)then
      begin
        accepttrade;
          Repeat
            Wait(1000)
          Until(TradeScreen=False)
      end
    else
      begin
      end
  End;</code></pre>
<p>Ok, so you know the first two lines… “If(FindTrade=True)then” basically checks if someone wishes to trade with you, “FindTrade: Boolean” is an SRL function, so remember you cannot use this function unless you have included SRL. If the script does find someone who want to trade then the script will accept the trade offer and then go into a loop called up by the “Repeat” command. What ever code is inbetween the “Repeat” and “Until()” commands will loop a set ammount of times. In this case the loop is a pause allowing you to do your trade. This loop is repeat until then tradescreen cannot be seen anymore, ’ Until(TradeScreen = False)’.</p>
<p>The ‘Else’ command basically means that if any other turnouts of the client other than the ones specified by the “if()then” statements will be handled in the code inbetween the “begin” and “end” tags.</p>
<ol start="8">
<li>So, ok you’ve got a good idea of most things using SRL and some knowledge of SCAR itself. But its not over yet, we will now need to call up the final loop, or the main loop. This is easy, just like most procedures, except that this main loop doesn’t need a procedure name. so…</li>
</ol>
<pre><code class="lang-auto">Begin
End.</code></pre>
<p>Noticed i have used a ‘.’ at the end of the “End” command instead of a ‘;’, this is because its the main loop, and well it deserves it. You dont need to know why really, as long as you remember the ‘.’ goes on the end of the main loop, the last character you type on your keyboard.</p>
<p>Now to fill in the code…</p>
<p>Start by putting in teh setup, seeing as we only need to call this procedure up once, we will put it outside the loop.</p>
<pre><code class="lang-auto">Begin
  Setup;
End.</code></pre>
<p>Then add a loop:</p>
<pre><code class="lang-auto">Begin
  Setup;
    Repeat
    Until(false)
End.</code></pre>
<p>Noticed i’ve used ‘Until(False)’, this will mean that the loop is never ending, well never ending in the sense that you dont manually stop the script.</p>
<p>Next add the procedures which you want to loop, in this case Chat; and Stop;…</p>
<pre><code class="lang-auto">Begin
  Setup;
    Repeat
      Chat;
      Stop;
    Until(false)
End.</code></pre>
<ol start="9">
<li>Now lets look at the script as a whole…</li>
</ol>
<pre><code class="lang-auto">Program Autotalker;
{.include SRL\SRL.scar}
{.include SRL\SRL\misc\Trade.scar}

Var Msge: String;

Procedure Setup;
  Begin;
    Msge:= ' Message Here' // Type your message here
  End;
 
Procedure Chat;
  Begin
    TypeSend(Msge);
    Wait(Random(200)+200);
  End;

Procedure Stop;
  Begin
    If(FindTrade = True)then
      begin
        accepttrade;
          Repeat
            Wait(1000)
          Until(TradeScreen=False)
      end
    else
      begin
      end
  End;

Begin
  Setup;
    Repeat
      Chat;
      Stop;
    Until(false)
End.</code></pre>
<p>Make sure theres no errors, in this case it should be working just fine, now open runescape, set up the script and select the runecape client with the crosshair and press play.</p>
<p>Watch the script work.</p>
<p>If theres any errors or if you need help with this tutorial please post it here and not email me. Thank you.</p>
<p>Brought to you by <a href="http://www.scarforum.com" rel="nofollow noopener">http://www.scarforum.com</a>, enjoy</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/scar-first-srl-script-autotalker/8427/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/scar-first-srl-script-autotalker/8427/1</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2006 17:22:50 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-8427-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/scar-first-srl-script-autotalker/8427.rss">[Scar] First SRL Script - Autotalker</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
