<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Pitbulls</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/pitbulls/210630</link>
    <description>What do you think about these dogs i love my pit bull I saved my pit from a dog fighting ring and he acts good with me he sleeps in the house i let him lay on the couch he protect my family treat a pit good and they treat you good back Only one thing i can say is thoe &quot;Pitbull Pride if you have to ask then you wouldnt understand.&quot; So what do you think about this  
beautiful breed here is a vid that might show you what pits really are [url=http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=hdPMIEeVRoY]http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=hdPMIEeVRoY[/url]

This one also got to me http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=-R4x855nHgg&amp;feature=related


This one will also tell you the truth [url=http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=D24igQxIfIY]http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=D24igQxIfIY[/url]</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 30 Jun 2008 20:43:16 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>General Discussion</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/pitbulls/210630.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Pitbulls</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Greeny Greeny]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/greeny">@Greeny</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I really want a German Shepard or ex/current-police dog.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/pitbulls/210630/34">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/pitbulls/210630/34</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 30 Jun 2008 20:43:16 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-210630-34</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/pitbulls/210630.rss">Pitbulls</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Pitbulls</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Chimaera_God Chimaera God]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/chimaera_god">@Chimaera_God</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote no-group" data-post="6" data-topic="210630">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/codeusa/40/5_6bca9977b612b7aeef77ba1ec1cd67b3.png" class="avatar"> codeusa:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Pit bulls are the nicest dogs alive.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>French mastiffs are the nicest dogs alive, and the best guard dogs as well.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/pitbulls/210630/33">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/pitbulls/210630/33</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 30 Jun 2008 19:49:06 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-210630-33</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/pitbulls/210630.rss">Pitbulls</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Pitbulls</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@pk4pk pk4pk]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/pk4pk">@pk4pk</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Pitbulls are gunna be banned where I live. Golden retrievers and hunting dogs ftw.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/pitbulls/210630/32">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/pitbulls/210630/32</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 30 Jun 2008 03:02:36 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-210630-32</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/pitbulls/210630.rss">Pitbulls</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Pitbulls</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@wewaka wewaka]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/wewaka">@wewaka</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I absoloutly love pitbulls, rotties, dobermans and ect, they are all so misunderstood sure they were bred to fight but a good owner can get rid of that instinct. The pitbull attacks you hear about are nit pitbulls that had good owners. Even a golden retreiver or a lab can eb aggressive if they have a bad owner.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/pitbulls/210630/31">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/pitbulls/210630/31</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 24 Jun 2008 11:35:21 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-210630-31</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/pitbulls/210630.rss">Pitbulls</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Pitbulls</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@codeusa codeusa]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/codeusa">@codeusa</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>My pit is kinda retared and i think he is gay  <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/expressionless.png?v=6" title=":expressionless:" class="emoji" alt=":expressionless:"> but there good dogs nun the less</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/pitbulls/210630/30">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/pitbulls/210630/30</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jun 2008 11:22:48 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-210630-30</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/pitbulls/210630.rss">Pitbulls</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Pitbulls</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@army_life army_life]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/army_life">@army_life</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote no-group" data-post="2" data-topic="210630">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 Not X A Alex:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>I DISLIKE dogs.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I disklike you</p>
<p>But I like any dogs except the small ones like yorky’s! I have a Siberian huskey and a Australian shepard (The best and most wel behaved dog in the world) I absolutely love dogs, 9/10 cats I do not like but some are cool XD! Pitbulls are just awesome dogs they look so cool.</p>
<p>(here comes the flame :P)</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/pitbulls/210630/29">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/pitbulls/210630/29</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 15 Jun 2008 07:58:35 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-210630-29</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/pitbulls/210630.rss">Pitbulls</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Pitbulls</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@system system]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/system">@system</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I love Pittbulls, my aunt has one , and I hate how everyone judges them. Yeah there a breed of dog to simply fight , But believe me , they all aren’t. It’s how you raise them , give them attention , play with them and most important … Don’t piss them off <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=6" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/pitbulls/210630/28">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/pitbulls/210630/28</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 15 Jun 2008 05:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-210630-28</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/pitbulls/210630.rss">Pitbulls</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Pitbulls</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@codeusa codeusa]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/codeusa">@codeusa</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Oh, mt god someone seeing my point of view</p>
<p>Pits = good animals</p>
<p>Bad owners= Bad pits = Bad rep</p>
<p>Good owners = Good pits = good rep</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/pitbulls/210630/27">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/pitbulls/210630/27</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 08 Jun 2008 09:05:28 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-210630-27</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/pitbulls/210630.rss">Pitbulls</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Pitbulls</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@For For ( ; ; )]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/for">@For</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>My point exactly. You can’t be angry with the dog for someone being stupid.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/pitbulls/210630/26">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/pitbulls/210630/26</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 08 Jun 2008 09:00:19 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-210630-26</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/pitbulls/210630.rss">Pitbulls</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Pitbulls</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@codeusa codeusa]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/codeusa">@codeusa</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>All dogs would do that would you not hit someone if they were poking you with a stick</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/pitbulls/210630/25">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/pitbulls/210630/25</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 08 Jun 2008 08:55:35 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-210630-25</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/pitbulls/210630.rss">Pitbulls</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Pitbulls</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@For For ( ; ; )]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/for">@For</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I also have a pitbull, it’s a great dog and wouldn’t hurt anyone. Although it does bark when people pass by, but what dog doesn’t ? It’s just being protective.</p>
<p>It did bite a little girl once though, but she was pulling on it’s ears really hard so what can you expect.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/pitbulls/210630/24">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/pitbulls/210630/24</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 08 Jun 2008 08:48:30 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-210630-24</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/pitbulls/210630.rss">Pitbulls</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Pitbulls</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@codeusa codeusa]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/codeusa">@codeusa</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Poodels were more bad then pits back in the day poodels were hunting dogs</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/pitbulls/210630/23">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/pitbulls/210630/23</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 08 Jun 2008 06:29:22 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-210630-23</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/pitbulls/210630.rss">Pitbulls</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Pitbulls</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@93dcthugs93 93dcthugs93]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/93dcthugs93">@93dcthugs93</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>nothing wrong with them.<br>
they only have a bad reputation because of well… many reasons, and the fact that they were raised for fighting and shit like that.</p>
<p>but nowadays, they aren’t raised for fighting (mostly…). so it all depends on how they’re raised, any animal can be perfectly tamed, you just need to treat it right.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/pitbulls/210630/22">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/pitbulls/210630/22</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 08 Jun 2008 06:14:14 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-210630-22</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/pitbulls/210630.rss">Pitbulls</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Pitbulls</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@codeusa codeusa]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/codeusa">@codeusa</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Heres some basic info to anyone who wants a pit</p>
<p>“The following information is based on my personal knowledge, extensive research, and experience in the breed. It is intended primarily for the first time or potential pit bull owner who needs to know what to expect from their dog, both positive and negative. This page will give information on the proper temperament of this breed, typical behavior, proper toys, and training info. This page is intended as a brief overview of the breed, and should be only one of many sources the new or potential pit bull owner should investigate in order to understand the responsibility of owning this breed. Unlike almost any other breed, pit bull ownership comes with some unique responsibilities. As the owner of an American Pit Bull Terrier, your actions and those of your dog will affect not only yourself, but EVERY owner and EVERY dog of this breed. If you are thinking about getting a pit bull, please think about that before committing yourself to an American Pit Bull Terrier.” Susan Thompson</p>
<p>A WORD ABOUT AGGRESSION</p>
<p>In the following sections I will discuss aggression in the American Pit Bull Terrier. It is VERY important to note that, in dogs, and especially with this particular breed, aggression toward humans (called human aggression) is a COMPLETELY separate trait from aggression toward dogs (dog aggression) and/or other animals (animal aggression). While a dog may be both human and animal aggressive, the presence of one kind of aggression DOES NOT mandate or exclude the presence of the other.</p>
<p>TEMPERAMENT, WHAT IS IT?</p>
<p>Simply put, temperament is those behavioral traits and mental attitudes shared by canines and combined with the special characteristics proper to a certain dog breed. Newfoundlands for example, like water and love children, that is part of the breed’s temperament. A Newfoundland that hates to swim or growls at a child is showing improper temperament for the breed. When a person talks about the temperament of their chosen breed, they are describing those traits which most good examples of the breed will have, rather than describing a specific dog. A dog who posses all or most of the characteristics expected for their breed is said to have a proper temperament. This is why it is very important to know about your chosen breed’s temperament and research its specific traits, preferably before you commit to a dog. You may find out that eventhough you like the “look” of a certain breed, the temperament is not for you.</p>
<p>A WORD ABOUT BREED HISTORY</p>
<p>Much of a dog’s temperament relates to it’s breed history and genetic inheritance. I won’t go too deep into the history of the Pit Bull as there are many good books and websites that cover the origin and history of the breed. It is common knowledge however, that the Pit Bull breed was developed for blood sports: Bull baiting, bear baiting, and later, dogfighting. What is not common knowledge is that in the days of organized dogfighting, the handlers of the combatants were habitually IN THE PIT with the dogs for the duration of the fight. They were required to pick up and separate the dogs several times while the dogs were in full fight frenzy. Before the fight, the handlers were required to wash each other’s dogs, and after the fight, the badly injured dogs were often treated at ringside by strangers. Any dog that attacked or bit a handler (even if it was the other dog’s handler) or anyone else at any time was culled, often on the spot, and would never have been bred.</p>
<p>This bit of history will help explain much of the apparently (to novices) contradictory traits common in this breed.</p>
<p>SO, WHAT IS THE PROPER PIT BULL TEMPERAMENT?</p>
<p>As with all breeds, the Pit Bull has positive and negative traits in their temperament. Their breed history has led to a dog unlike any other in the history of purebred dogs. What can you expect from an APBT? First and foremost, memorize the following: THE GOLDEN RULE OF PIT BULL OWNERSHIP- NEVER TRUST YOUR PIT BULL NOT TO FIGHT!!! This breed is descended from pit dogs one way or another, and, given the right circumstances, most Pit Bulls will fight and against any other breed, they will win (you really don’t want to see that!). Scared yet? You should be. Remember, as the owner of a Pit Bull everything you or your dog do will affect all members of the breed and their families. Pit Bull owners have to be extra vigilant 24/7, period. You need to be receptive, have strong leadership, and be able to read canine body language to recognize signs of tension between housemates. You need to be prepared to separate the dogs if tensions develop. You need to know when your dog may become aggressive and you need to have control of your dog under any circumstances.</p>
<p>Sound like a lot of work and hassle? It is. So, what’s the payoff? The payoff is: A well-raised pit bull of proper temperament is the most loyal and loving dog in the world, bar none. This is a dog that truly LOVES people, especially children. Pits are notorious clowns, and will Always make you laugh, even in spite of yourself. They are intelligent, and will often “invent” games to keep themselves amused. They seem to subsist on love and attention, and will do almost anything for a little special “loves n hugs” time. They tolerate the rough play of children, loving every minute of it, and, although poor “guard dogs” for property, they will willingly give their lives to save the people they love. Thousands of responsible owners have dedicated themselves to this breed for it’s positive traits and willingly deal with the negatives.</p>
<p>T0 SUMMARIZE THE PROPER PIT BULL TEMPERAMENT</p>
<ol>
<li>
<p>Pit Bulls are often dog-aggressive to one extent or another (this often shows up at or near sexual maturity). A dog that was previously non-dog aggressive may “turn-on” and suddenly doesn’t like other dogs of the same sex, or, for that matter, any dogs at all, even housemates they have been raised with. Adult Pit Bulls should NEVER be left alone with other dogs and require proper supervision.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Pit Bulls may exhibit intense “prey drive”, leading them to “stalk” small animals such as cats, rats, chickens, livestock, or other pets.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Pit Bulls are precocious and incomparable escape artists, who will often seem to squirt right out of a supposedly secure yard or enclosure. When coupled with # 1 and # 2, you can see why a responsible Pit Bull owner is a vigilant pit bull owner.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Pit bulls are intelligent, and most enjoy training, if it is done properly. This makes them excellent prospects for dog sports such as agility, obedience, weight pull, and Frisbee competitions.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Pit Bulls tend to LOVE people. All people. This makes them a poor choice for a “guardian breed”. Most of them are simply too friendly to protect a house against strangers. A Pit Bull that shows unprovoked human aggression (puppy play nips do NOT count) is showing BAD temperament and in most cases should be put to sleep. Such a dog should obviously NEVER be bred under any circumstances. The breeding of dogs with bad temperaments is one of the largest problems the breed faces today and fuels the fire of breed specific legislation.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Pit bulls tend to be very “soft” with their family, meaning that they are eager to please their humans. They should not have to be “shown who’s boss”, but will thrive under “positive leadership”. A Pit Bull of proper temperament is a devoted and loving family member, inspiring immense loyalty to the breed. You will often hear a Pit Bull’s owner tell you that after owning one, they will never own any other breed.</p>
</li>
</ol>
<p>THE PHYSICAL PIT BULL</p>
<p>Built for performance, the pit bull is a medium sized, very muscular, short coated breed. The head is bricklike, the jaws strong and wide, the ears may be cropped or not (I prefer uncropped dogs for several reasons). The body is typically very strong, with a deep chest, powerful and proportionate hind end and solid legs. The overall impression should be of power and athleticism. This is not a dog for couch potatoes, as it requires A LOT of training and exercise. With this breed it is important to remember to exercise both the dog’s body and mind. Remember, a tired pit bull is a happy pit bull and a bored pit bull is NOT a good thing! They will find some very inventive ways to entertain themselves that the owner may not like (often involving the garbage can, kitchen counter and cabinets, feather pillows, dirty laundry and various items of furniture).</p>
<p>Remember also, that this is a VERY enthusiastic breed that may very well overwhelm young children or older people with it’s affection. This breed needs to be taught to sit and greet people calmly as it’s natural inclination will probably be to climb into their lap, put a paw on each of their shoulders, and attempt to wipe their face off with it’s tongue. Attempts to convince a full grown pit bull that it is too big to be a “lap dog” will, more often than not, fall on deaf ears if it was not taught “manners” as a puppy. Do not allow your puppy to do anything you don’t want your adult dog to do (eg climb on the couch, sleep in the bed, invade your lap, etc.).</p>
<p>TRAINING</p>
<p>First of all, for anyone asking the question, “Do I need to train my pit bull?”, the answer is a resounding YES! As with very young children, dogs need guidance and structure, and should never be left to make decisions on their own. Training teaches the dog and owner to understand and communicate with each other and prevents misunderstandings. In the case of the Pit Bull, training also prevents the kind of headlines that make all good Pit owners cringe.</p>
<p>How should a pit bull be trained? The most important thing is to find a method that works for your dog, and stick with it. There are almost as many methods for dog training as there are dog trainers. Most of those methods fit into one of two categories: Positive training methods or aversive training methods. Positive methods include using food rewards, toy rewards, pure praise, gentle leaders, and clickers. Aversive methods include using praise/correction, choke chains, prong collars, and/or shock collars. Both types of training, done correctly, will result in a trained dog. It is a matter of how you want to get there. As I said in the temperament section, Pit Bulls tend to be very “soft” with their families, and it is very possible to ruin a good dog by “over correcting” with a choke chain, prong collar, and particularly a shock collar. As a very good positive trainer I know put it, “Aversive training is something you do TO your dog, positive training is something you do WITH your dog”.</p>
<p>Finding a good trainer can be a bit of a challenge, depending on where you live. Some things to look for are: Experience with the breed (or at least no breed prejudice against Pit Bulls and a good understanding of the breed’s nature), what methods are used (and are you comfortable with them), recommendations from former students, and, last but not least, take a look at the trainer’s own dogs (are they well behaved). The best way to assess a trainer’s methods is to ask to “sit in” on a training session. If the trainer refuses to let you watch, look elsewhere.</p>
<p>As a special note for Pit Bulls: I would avoid any class that has “forced socialization” between the dogs, particularly adult dogs. Any trainer that wants to muzzle a dog-aggressive pit bull and force it to “socialize” with other dogs is not knowledgeable in the breed , and can actually make dog aggression worse.</p>
<p>Suggested Resource: Turnaround Dog-Training</p>
<p>WHAT IS SOCIALIZATION?</p>
<p>Socialization means introducing your dog to people, and to a lesser extent, to dogs and/or other animals. It is extremely important to socialize a pup of any breed with people, but be sure that the pup’s experiences are ALWAYS positive. The pup should meet all kinds of adults and as many respectful children as possible. Socialization with people should be part of your dog’s training for his/her entire life. Relegating a dog to the backyard or keeping it chained 24/7 can lead to a real disaster. If you are not willing to socialize and train a dog, please don’t get one. Socialization with dogs is a little different for pit bulls.<br>
Socializing a puppy with other dogs may reduce the amount of dog aggression the pup will develop, and many pit puppies get along with other dogs when they are young. As the dog matures, ALWAYS be on the lookout for signs of aggression with other dogs, and be prepared to break up a spat or fight, should one happen. It is up to you, the owner, to decide whether or not to introduce your adult pit bull to other dogs. The amount of dog aggression in an adult pit bulls varies from no aggression at all to a dog that sees ANY other dog as a Happy-Meal with legs, so there are no hard and fast rules. Just remember that as the owner of a pit bull, any fight will always be your fault, no matter who started it.</p>
<p>More about socialization</p>
<p>I feel that to the general public, socialization = allowing dogs to be off leash together. Either playing or figuring out the hierarchy themselves. This is where people get into trouble. It doesn’t have to be this way at all. Being in an obedience class situation in which a dog does NOT get to ‘say hi’ to every dog IS socialization! We have to remember that it’s not normal for adult dogs to come together and play, be friends and interact. This goes against dog behavior. (Especially pit bull behavior!)</p>
<p>I feel the definition of ‘socialize’ needs to be readdressed. I know that my dogs are wonderfully socialized because they can be with me around other dogs and not freak out. I would never force my guys to be what they are not. They will never be Golden Retrievers! I would never force my guys to interact with another dog which is ill mannered or foul tempered. That’s breaking the trust factor. I’m the leader and protector in my family. My guys trust me because I would never put them into a situation in which harm would come to them. There’s where the parenting skills come into play.</p>
<p>When an owner allows their dog to ‘work it out’ on it’s own in a dog park, lack of trust is inevitable. That poor dog is out there all alone with no one to protect it. Scary stuff! They have to learn pretty quickly to protect themselves at all costs. They know that no one will come to save them if something does happen. These are the same owners who ask me, “But, why doesn’t he listen to me?” Well, it’s pretty obvious! That poor dog is living in a house full of people and still has no one to trust and believe in. No<br>
one to look up to. No one to make those hard desicions in life. They have no ‘pack’ to watch out for them. I feel that’s very sad. (Also, have you ever wondered why dogs ‘gang up’ when at the dog park? They’re finally able to have that pack feeling of safety that they don’t get at home.)</p>
<p>My definition of ‘well socialized’ is…The dog being able to be with me in what the dog deems to be scary situations or around other dogs and not have a panic attack. (Notice I didn’t say off leash with other dogs!)</p>
<p>DOG PARKS</p>
<p>If you enjoy off-leash dog parks, you don’t want to hear this. But I am going to tell you anyway. If you choose to become the owner of a Pit Bull, your dog park days are almost surely over, at least when the dog is somewhere over 8 months old. Accidental dogfights in off-leash parks are common, but when a Pit Bull is involved, they are headlines. Following Pit Bull Golden Rule <span class="hashtag">#1</span> “NEVER trust your pit bull not to fight”, you can see why off-leash parks are a very bad idea for our breed. As a Pit Bull owner, you have certain responsibilities. Your responsibility to your dog (to keep him/her out of trouble), your responsibility to other dog owners (to keep their dogs safe from your dog), and your responsibility to your breed (to keep your dog OUT of negative headlines). Even pit bulls that have never exhibited dog aggression may fight back if approached by the wrong dog in an aggressive manner. I will repeat this for you. As the owner of a pit bull, any fight will always be your fault, no matter who started it.</p>
<p>TEN COMMANDMENTS OF PIT BULL OWNERSHIP</p>
<ol>
<li>
<p>Thou shalt NEVER trust thy Pit Bull not to fight</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Thou shalt contain thy Pit Bull securely when not supervised by an adult</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Thou shalt NEVER leave thy adult Pit Bull alone and unsupervised with another dog</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Thou SHALT attend obedience classes most faithfully with thy Pit Bull</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Thou SHALT keep thy Pit Bull socialized with ALL KINDS of people</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Thy Pit Bull wilt NEVER be allowed off-leash in a public place</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Thy Pit Bull wilt NEVER be allowed to roam free in thy neighborhood, EVER!</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Thou SHALT take thy well trained Pit Bull out in public and show him/her off - on leash for good breed PR!</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Thy Pit Bull shalt go forth into the world as an ambassador of the pit bull breed</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>THOU ARE RESPONSIBLE FOR ANY WRONG DONE BY THY DOGS!</p>
</li>
</ol>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/pitbulls/210630/21">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/pitbulls/210630/21</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 08 Jun 2008 04:33:06 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-210630-21</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/pitbulls/210630.rss">Pitbulls</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Pitbulls</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Original_Daniel Original Daniel]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/original_daniel">@Original_Daniel</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Can you think of anything to say about them other than how great they are?</p>
<p>Just because your 1 or 2 pitbulls haven’t eaten anybody yet, it hardly makes you the authority on the best breed of dog.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/pitbulls/210630/20">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/pitbulls/210630/20</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 08 Jun 2008 04:20:05 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-210630-20</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/pitbulls/210630.rss">Pitbulls</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Pitbulls</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@codeusa codeusa]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/codeusa">@codeusa</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“jme, post:18, topic:210630”]Pitbulls were bred simply to fight and be aggressive. They were bred to always win, and for their drive.</p>
<p>So it’s not just how you train them. Good pitbulls exist, but even when you train them right theres still so many bad ones. Some breeds of dogs are naturally aggressive, no matter how you train them.</p>
<p>My brother had a rottweiler, and he trained it very well and gave it a lot of love. It was a very friendly dog, with other peoples and other dogs as well. All of a sudden it ran out onto the road and attacked a lady one day, and he had to put the dog down.</p>
<p>Personally I find them a bit ugly too, I wouldn’t want one. Theres so many better breeds I’d rather have. A nice husky, or golden retriever. We just have a little dog, but he’s still pretty cool lol.[/quote]</p>
<p>golden retriever are good dogs to but i just cant not love a pit see them has the best breed.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/pitbulls/210630/19">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/pitbulls/210630/19</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 07 Jun 2008 21:14:38 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-210630-19</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/pitbulls/210630.rss">Pitbulls</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Pitbulls</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@jme jme]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/jme">@jme</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Pitbulls were bred simply to fight and be aggressive. They were bred to always win, and for their drive.</p>
<p>So it’s not just how you train them. Good pitbulls exist, but even when you train them right theres still so many bad ones. Some breeds of dogs are naturally aggressive, no matter how you train them.</p>
<p>My brother had a rottweiler, and he trained it very well and gave it a lot of love. It was a very friendly dog, with other peoples and other dogs as well. All of a sudden it ran out onto the road and attacked a lady one day, and he had to put the dog down.</p>
<p>Personally I find them a bit ugly too, I wouldn’t want one. Theres so many better breeds I’d rather have. A nice husky, or golden retriever. We just have a little dog, but he’s still pretty cool lol.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/pitbulls/210630/18">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/pitbulls/210630/18</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 07 Jun 2008 20:28:18 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-210630-18</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/pitbulls/210630.rss">Pitbulls</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Pitbulls</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@codeusa codeusa]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/codeusa">@codeusa</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>:eek: you jackass they are the best dogs to have</p>
<p>They are a wonderful dog to own if you know and understand the breed. You have to raise it properly and know the limitations. They are the most loving loyal breed I have ever owned. Mines nothing but a big baby<br>
provide you train them and socialize them, like any other dog, they are great dogs.</p>
<p>The several dogs that I have met are owned by people who have taken the time to socialize and train them, they are very sweet and wouldn’t hurt a fly.</p>
<p>You just need to remember to take the time to train and socialize the dog. Also, do research on the breed, if you are not prepared for the limitations of the breed, then don’t get one.</p>
<p>So, Good dog to have provide you intend to do the proper training.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/pitbulls/210630/17">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/pitbulls/210630/17</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 07 Jun 2008 19:00:02 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-210630-17</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/pitbulls/210630.rss">Pitbulls</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Pitbulls</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Mr.Chris Mr.Chris]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/mr.chris">@Mr.Chris</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Pits are shit, disgusting and horrible dogs to have.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/pitbulls/210630/16">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/pitbulls/210630/16</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 07 Jun 2008 18:53:02 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-210630-16</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/pitbulls/210630.rss">Pitbulls</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Pitbulls</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Gotta_Catch_Them_All Gotta Catch Them All]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/gotta_catch_them_all">@Gotta_Catch_Them_All</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“codeusa, post:12, topic:210630”]That, is true but why knock i dog around in the first place? you have to really have to life to beat a animal.</p>
<p>And be a compleat bitch[/quote]</p>
<p>I found it quite difficult to read any of that. Would you mind working on making your sentences a little but more coherent?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/pitbulls/210630/15">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/pitbulls/210630/15</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 07 Jun 2008 18:52:02 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-210630-15</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/pitbulls/210630.rss">Pitbulls</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Pitbulls</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@codeusa codeusa]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/codeusa">@codeusa</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Well you dont piss them off you dont get hurt.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/pitbulls/210630/14">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/pitbulls/210630/14</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 07 Jun 2008 18:51:45 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-210630-14</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/pitbulls/210630.rss">Pitbulls</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Pitbulls</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@R.I.P_RSC R.I.P RSC]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/r.i.p_rsc">@R.I.P_RSC</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Pitbulls are banned in the Netherlands IIRC, some little kid got killed by one.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/pitbulls/210630/13">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/pitbulls/210630/13</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 07 Jun 2008 18:39:55 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-210630-13</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/pitbulls/210630.rss">Pitbulls</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Pitbulls</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@codeusa codeusa]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/codeusa">@codeusa</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>That, is true but why knock i dog around in the first place? you have to really have to life to beat a animal.</p>
<p>And be a compleat bitch</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/pitbulls/210630/12">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/pitbulls/210630/12</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 07 Jun 2008 16:12:07 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-210630-12</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/pitbulls/210630.rss">Pitbulls</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Pitbulls</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Original_Daniel Original Daniel]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/original_daniel">@Original_Daniel</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Or perhaps the dog is being over protective? ofc if you knock a dog around enough it’s not going to like people, I’m not talking about that.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/pitbulls/210630/11">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/pitbulls/210630/11</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 07 Jun 2008 16:08:34 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-210630-11</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/pitbulls/210630.rss">Pitbulls</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Pitbulls</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@codeusa codeusa]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/codeusa">@codeusa</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Pits are not born bad there trained bad by bad owner that should not be alive like my pits was in dog fight cause he was forced to now that i have him he want even growl</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/pitbulls/210630/10">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/pitbulls/210630/10</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 07 Jun 2008 16:01:57 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-210630-10</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/pitbulls/210630.rss">Pitbulls</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
