<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Mopar Monthly Template #4</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/mopar-monthly-template-4/528655</link>
    <description>---
layout: post
title: &quot;The Mopar Monthly&quot;
date: 2013-08-30 00:00
comments: true
categories: [MoparScape, RSPS, RS, Mopar, Monthly]
author: Flame_
---
The Mopar Monthly
===============
##Edition 4
---

This month on the Mopar Monthly:
Welcome to the second edition of the Mopar Monthly! For those of you who don&#39;t know what this is, the Mopar Monthly is a monthly magazine where users can see the best of the best in the forums for each month, user interviews, rants, and more! Forum members are free to submit controversial news articles, thought-provoking rants, and anything else by contacting any members of the Mopar Monthly team. For those of you that read the previous edition and provided feedback, a big thanks to you all for keeping this possible!

####Included in this edition will be:

* The Overall Most Helpful Member(s) of the Month
* Notable Developments
* Featured Tutorials
* An Interview With Smacktard
* _Undecided_
* User Submission #2
* An Interview With a Forum User

PARAGRAPH HERE

#####Section 1: The Overall Most Helpful Member(s) of the Month:

This category is for users who are willing to help people in need of help. This award doesn&#39;t mean that these users know everything - they may also need help from time to time - but they&#39;re always willing to give up some of their time to help someone who needs it. Users have been listed depending on which section they have the most influence in.

######Server Help:
- []()

######Web Design/Development:
- []()

######General Programming:
- []()

If you have any other nominations for future editions of the Mopar Monthly, please [send a private message to Flame_](//www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php?action=pm;sa=send;u=600800) or [send a private message to Ambokile](//www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php?action=pm;sa=send;u=576712). Please don&#39;t publicly dispute any listings for this month, instead contact a member of the team if you feel one of them is incorrect.

#####Section 2: Notable Developments

#####Section 3: Featured Tutorials

Tutorials are arguably the best way to learn how to do things. They&#39;re a step-by-step guide on how to add features, modify existing features or even in some cases remove features. Here is a list (in no particular order) of tutorials that deserve particular recognition this month. Congratulations to all listed!

Tutorials featured in this section do not necessarily have to have been posted this month, they&#39;re just tutorials that we feel deserve recognition. If your tutorial isn&#39;t featured this month, take a look at these tutorials, improve yours accordingly and you could be featured in the next issue!

######
* Language: 
* Creator(s): 
* What the tutorial is: 
* Link: [click me]()

#####Section 4: An Interview With Smacktard

You asked, it happened. Featured in this month&#39;s edition is a special interview with the mitbnet IRC bot, Smacktard!

* Smacktard, how do you feel about the mopar monthly?

&gt; i&#39;m just telling you serve it with some open sauce

* Smacktard, describe yourself.

&gt; smacktard

* Smacktard, what is your favorite food?

&gt; i like food

* Smacktard, what is your favorite quote?

&gt; vortex_: what the fudge is so intersting about a line

* Smacktard, talk about your career.

&gt; i&#39;ll get you ripped in three weeks

* Smacktard, what do you do in your free time?

&gt; your mother.

* Smacktard, what was life like as a child?

&gt; semi conscious like wtf is going on

* Are there any users on MoparScape who you find particularly inspirational?

&gt; lol wtf newbiehacker could run an allstar server that would crush you

#####Section 5: _Undecided_

#####Section 6: User Submission #2

#####Section 7: An Interview With a Forum User

##

That concludes this month&#39;s edition of the Mopar Monthly! The Mopar Monthly team would like to thank everyone who has taken the time to contribute to the fifth edition, which is still coming strong, and we are always welcome to more contributions. You can view the Mopar Monthly thread on the forums by clicking [here](http://goo.gl/Nh65g). Interested in becoming an editor/writer? Contact [Flame_](http://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php?action=profile;u=600800) or [Ambokile](http://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php?action=profile;u=576712)!

#####This edition of the [Mopar Monthly](http://goo.gl/Nh65g) was published by [Flame_](http://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php?action=profile;u=600800).</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 22 Aug 2013 14:14:53 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Community Suggestions</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/mopar-monthly-template-4/528655.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Mopar Monthly Template #4</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Flame3 John]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/flame3">@Flame3</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <hr>
<h2>layout: post<br>
title: “The Mopar Monthly”<br>
date: 2013-08-30 00:00<br>
comments: true<br>
categories: [MoparScape, RSPS, RS, Mopar, Monthly]<br>
author: Flame_</h2>
<h1>The Mopar Monthly</h1>
<h2>#<span class="hashtag">#Edition</span> 4</h2>
<p>This month on the Mopar Monthly:<br>
Welcome to the second edition of the Mopar Monthly! For those of you who don’t know what this is, the Mopar Monthly is a monthly magazine where users can see the best of the best in the forums for each month, user interviews, rants, and more! Forum members are free to submit controversial news articles, thought-provoking rants, and anything else by contacting any members of the Mopar Monthly team. For those of you that read the previous edition and provided feedback, a big thanks to you all for keeping this possible!</p>
<p>###<span class="hashtag">#Included</span> in this edition will be:</p>
<ul>
<li>The Overall Most Helpful Member(s) of the Month</li>
<li>Notable Developments</li>
<li>Featured Tutorials</li>
<li>An Interview With Smacktard</li>
<li><em>Undecided</em></li>
<li>User Submission <span class="hashtag">#2</span>
</li>
<li>An Interview With a Forum User</li>
</ul>
<p>PARAGRAPH HERE</p>
<p>####<span class="hashtag">#Section</span> 1: The Overall Most Helpful Member(s) of the Month:</p>
<p>This category is for users who are willing to help people in need of help. This award doesn’t mean that these users know everything - they may also need help from time to time - but they’re always willing to give up some of their time to help someone who needs it. Users have been listed depending on which section they have the most influence in.</p>
<p>#####<span class="hashtag">#Server</span> Help:</p>
<ul>
<li><a></a></li>
</ul>
<p>#####<span class="hashtag">#Web</span> Design/Development:</p>
<ul>
<li><a></a></li>
</ul>
<p>#####<span class="hashtag">#General</span> Programming:</p>
<ul>
<li><a></a></li>
</ul>
<p>If you have any other nominations for future editions of the Mopar Monthly, please <a href="//www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php?action=pm;sa=send;u=600800" rel="nofollow noopener">send a private message to Flame_</a> or <a href="//www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php?action=pm;sa=send;u=576712" rel="nofollow noopener">send a private message to Ambokile</a>. Please don’t publicly dispute any listings for this month, instead contact a member of the team if you feel one of them is incorrect.</p>
<p>####<span class="hashtag">#Section</span> 2: Notable Developments</p>
<p>####<span class="hashtag">#Section</span> 3: Featured Tutorials</p>
<p>Tutorials are arguably the best way to learn how to do things. They’re a step-by-step guide on how to add features, modify existing features or even in some cases remove features. Here is a list (in no particular order) of tutorials that deserve particular recognition this month. Congratulations to all listed!</p>
<p>Tutorials featured in this section do not necessarily have to have been posted this month, they’re just tutorials that we feel deserve recognition. If your tutorial isn’t featured this month, take a look at these tutorials, improve yours accordingly and you could be featured in the next issue!</p>
<h6></h6>
<ul>
<li>Language:</li>
<li>Creator(s):</li>
<li>What the tutorial is:</li>
<li>Link: <a>click me</a>
</li>
</ul>
<p>####<span class="hashtag">#Section</span> 4: An Interview With Smacktard</p>
<p>You asked, it happened. Featured in this month’s edition is a special interview with the mitbnet IRC bot, Smacktard!</p>
<ul>
<li>Smacktard, how do you feel about the mopar monthly?</li>
</ul>
<blockquote>
<p>i’m just telling you serve it with some open sauce</p>
</blockquote>
<ul>
<li>Smacktard, describe yourself.</li>
</ul>
<blockquote>
<p>smacktard</p>
</blockquote>
<ul>
<li>Smacktard, what is your favorite food?</li>
</ul>
<blockquote>
<p>i like food</p>
</blockquote>
<ul>
<li>Smacktard, what is your favorite quote?</li>
</ul>
<blockquote>
<p>vortex_: what the fudge is so intersting about a line</p>
</blockquote>
<ul>
<li>Smacktard, talk about your career.</li>
</ul>
<blockquote>
<p>i’ll get you ripped in three weeks</p>
</blockquote>
<ul>
<li>Smacktard, what do you do in your free time?</li>
</ul>
<blockquote>
<p>your mother.</p>
</blockquote>
<ul>
<li>Smacktard, what was life like as a child?</li>
</ul>
<blockquote>
<p>semi conscious like wtf is going on</p>
</blockquote>
<ul>
<li>Are there any users on MoparScape who you find particularly inspirational?</li>
</ul>
<blockquote>
<p>lol wtf newbiehacker could run an allstar server that would crush you</p>
</blockquote>
<p>####<span class="hashtag">#Section</span> 5: <em>Undecided</em></p>
<p>####<span class="hashtag">#Section</span> 6: User Submission <span class="hashtag">#2</span></p>
<p>####<span class="hashtag">#Section</span> 7: An Interview With a Forum User</p>
<h2></h2>
<p>That concludes this month’s edition of the Mopar Monthly! The Mopar Monthly team would like to thank everyone who has taken the time to contribute to the fifth edition, which is still coming strong, and we are always welcome to more contributions. You can view the Mopar Monthly thread on the forums by clicking <a href="http://goo.gl/Nh65g" rel="nofollow noopener">here</a>. Interested in becoming an editor/writer? Contact <a href="http://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php?action=profile;u=600800" rel="nofollow noopener">Flame_</a> or <a href="http://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php?action=profile;u=576712" rel="nofollow noopener">Ambokile</a>!</p>
<p>####<span class="hashtag">#This</span> edition of the <a href="http://goo.gl/Nh65g" rel="nofollow noopener">Mopar Monthly</a> was published by <a href="http://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php?action=profile;u=600800" rel="nofollow noopener">Flame_</a>.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/mopar-monthly-template-4/528655/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/mopar-monthly-template-4/528655/1</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 22 Aug 2013 14:14:53 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-528655-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/mopar-monthly-template-4/528655.rss">Mopar Monthly Template #4</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
