<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>It&#39;s over</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/its-over/1668</link>
    <description>So me and my girlfriend kinda broke up today :( :( :( :(

We&#39;ve been together a year and 19 days. Over the past month we&#39;ve been &quot;fighting&quot; quite a bit, but I wouldn&#39;t call it that. I&#39;m a very calm person, but she isn&#39;t. She is bipolar, her mom lives in NY, and she lives down here in GA with her dad. He doesn&#39;t even take her anywhere or bring her to the doctor. He doesn&#39;t really beleive in medicine so she&#39;s not on medicine for being bipolar. She used to be in NY but when they moved down here he took her off of it. Her boyfriend in NY cheated on her with many other girls, and she moved down here after that and her parents divorced. Her father&#39;s girlfriend is an old bitch who litterally drinks a few cartons of beer a day, along with a few cartons of smokes. Nobody really likes her, and she gambles away the little money they have. Her dad and the girlfriend fight a lot too. 

I met her about a year and a half ago, she was dating one of my friends. They almost never saw each other. Eventually they starting fighting and she started to like me. I liked her also. Then one day she got mad at him, so he ignored her for the next few days. I was there for her. He broke up with her saying he had caused her too much pain. They got back together even though I said not to. Same thing not even a week later. Finally they broke up and she nearly killed herself. I told her not to and stopped her. Later on we started hanging out and then dating. 

Everything was great. We did basically everything together. We had lots of fun. Eventually she just starting being weird. It came to be that basically, I couldn&#39;t tell her anything. If I did, she freaked out, then stopped doing whatever I said she did that made me mad. Say I said it made me mad when she left the dogs outside. She&#39;d start a huge fight over it and from then on she wouldn&#39;t even get near the dogs. I&#39;d ask her why and she gets an attitude and says she wouldn&#39;t want to let them outside or anything. In all the fights we had, she FREAKS out way more than any person should. Call me lots of names, be a smartass, tell me she hates me, everything. When I finally calm her down, she says it&#39;s just because she doesn&#39;t have help. She won&#39;t even ask her dad for it because she says that she knowssssss that he won&#39;t take her to get any. All the time we&#39;ve been together I&#39;ve helped her and bent over backwards for her. However if I told her she was doing something wrong, there was a fight. She says she hates it when I correct her because her sister allllllways did it to her. She finally understands that I&#39;m just trying to help. I know I don&#39;t deserve this, but I stuck in with it because I loved the good times and I was never mad or fighting back with her. She&#39;d get jealous when I was talking to any other girl, but everyday after school her and her neighbor friends would all go out and make bonfires and shit. She could do things, but not me. This kept on and on, but I knew it was just because she&#39;s psycho. I still had feelings for her. Just a week or two ago, she finally made me mad. Something happened, I don&#39;t remember what, and she started freaking out. She eventually said she didn&#39;t even want to come over the next day that I had made her so mad. I said oh well I&#39;ve got a party to goto anyway. It was my friend Cheryl, almost my best friend. She was like omg omg and freaked out. She told me that if I went we were over. I told her that&#39;s not fair at all and to calm down. She got sooo pissed because I told her to calm down. I then said if I can&#39;t goto her party, you can&#39;t hang out with your friends ever. She agreed. Later she changed her mind and said that it&#39;s bs and that she can hang out with them, but I still can&#39;t goto the party. She kept teasing me and shit saying oh you can&#39;t break up with me you don&#39;t want to. I told her I had enough and it&#39;s over. Later that night however, she came back saying she was sorry and I could go. I said no no it&#39;s easter you&#39;re gonna come over and we&#39;ll have fun. She came over, we had fun. We were together again. The other night she was cussing at me and shit so I told her to calm down it&#39;s nothing to get mad over. She freaks out again. She told me I was shit, then broke up with me. I left to go do other things. Later on, she came back to me and I told her how I&#39;ve done everything for her, given everything I had to her. But she still treated me horribly. She said she knows and she trys not to but she couldn&#39;t help it. She had went to her dad to ask if he would get her help and he said ok. I thought about it for a while and decided that maybe things would work out. Turns out he was being himself and didn&#39;t take her. Well today, we were at my house. I was sleepy and she was cooking with my mom so I layed down. She came over a little bit later and started kissing me telling me to wake up. I woke up and she wanted to tickle me. She sat on my legs and tickled me, but I couldn&#39;t get up because I was half under the couch. I told her to stop because I couldn&#39;t breathe, but she just let me breathe and tickled me. I kept telling her to please stop, but she didn&#39;t. I told her if she didn&#39;t stop I was going to kick her. She kept going and laughed at me. I pushed her down with me foot behind her knees. She got up and freaked out and started kicking me like crazy. I got up and layed down. She told me that I was an asshole. My mom comes in and she&#39;s like wtf is up. I was like she&#39;s just too damned mean. She got real mad and I told my side of the story and she denied that I ever said I would kick her. I said if you would have stopped like I asked you you wouldn&#39;t have gotten so mad. She started crying and yelling at me saying I was worthless, and that it&#39;s over, and she called her dad and he came and picked her up. I went outside to wait with her, and when he came I asked for a hug and she told me to shut up and left. I haven&#39;t talked to her since. I don&#39;t even know what to do. I am just so confused right now. No I am not coming here for your advice, I know what to do. I just want to know if anyone here is bipolar and can relate to her, as she has said many times that I don&#39;t understand. I can&#39;t even count on one hand the amount of times she was mad, I told her to calm down, and she freaked out on me. Anyone?


Sorry for the huge block of text.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 23 Apr 2006 22:14:36 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>General Discussion</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/its-over/1668.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>It&#39;s over</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Timelimit10 Timelimit10]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/timelimit10">@Timelimit10</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>My friend x-gf got him into a deep deep depresion and then they got back to gather and now they broke up again. and then now shes making fun of him. she knows nothing about love lol.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/its-over/1668/23">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/its-over/1668/23</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 23 Apr 2006 22:14:36 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-1668-23</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/its-over/1668.rss">It&#39;s over</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>It&#39;s over</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@badboy badboy]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/badboy">@badboy</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>srry to here this</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/its-over/1668/22">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/its-over/1668/22</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 23 Apr 2006 17:11:30 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-1668-22</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/its-over/1668.rss">It&#39;s over</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>It&#39;s over</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@SomethingToHide STH]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/somethingtohide">@SomethingToHide</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote" data-post="19" data-topic="1668"><div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="//forum.moparisthebest.mopar/letter_avatar_proxy/v2/letter/n/76d3ee/40.png" class="avatar">Nashiu:</div>
<blockquote><p>I'm a complete asshole to anyone who isn't my friend most of the time. <img src="//forum.moparisthebest.mopar/images/emoji/emoji_one/slight_smile.png?v=3" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p></blockquote></aside>

<p>She's like that AND she's an asshole to her friends too. She always says how she has no friends too lol. I know of three actual friends she has, one's bipolar, and the other two are preppy girls which is amazing.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/its-over/1668/21">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/its-over/1668/21</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 23 Apr 2006 16:37:33 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-1668-21</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/its-over/1668.rss">It&#39;s over</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>It&#39;s over</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Snipe Snipe]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/snipe">@Snipe</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Sounds like she needs some major help.  She's bipolar, depressed, and suicidal if not that, she still SIs.  You need to get her some damn help before it's too late.  I'd talk to you mother about her, if her had isn't going to do shit.  See if you can atleast have her talk with a doctor and see what yall could do.  If she's cut herself before, she can do it again, and I really doubt you want to get into a big fight and later go back to see her later and find her with slit wrists.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/its-over/1668/20">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/its-over/1668/20</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 23 Apr 2006 16:26:04 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-1668-20</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/its-over/1668.rss">It&#39;s over</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>It&#39;s over</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Nashiu Nashiu]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/nashiu">@Nashiu</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I'm a complete asshole to anyone who isn't my friend most of the time. <img src="//forum.moparisthebest.mopar/images/emoji/emoji_one/slight_smile.png?v=3" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/its-over/1668/19">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/its-over/1668/19</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 23 Apr 2006 15:58:22 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-1668-19</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/its-over/1668.rss">It&#39;s over</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>It&#39;s over</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@SomethingToHide STH]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/somethingtohide">@SomethingToHide</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote" data-post="15" data-topic="1668"><div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="//forum.moparisthebest.mopar/letter_avatar_proxy/v2/letter/s/fbc32d/40.png" class="avatar">Surajd:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Just say this to her and she will snap right out of it:</p>
<p>I will buy you a Super Nintendo for you're birthday.</p>
</blockquote></aside>

<p>Actually, last week I gave her my N64 because she loves to play zelda lmao.</p>

<p>And Snipe, it's hard to do it, but it's worth it. When she's not an ass she is wonderful.</p>

<p>Although I can't walk away. She used to give me a few choices, they were all bad though. If she was mad, I'd always be saying something like a smartass <img src="//forum.moparisthebest.mopar/images/emoji/emoji_one/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=3" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"> and she'd get even more pissed off. Eventually I just started saying Ok and agreeing with her, but that still made her mad. If I left she would get uberrr pissed off and die. One time I left, when I came back she had cuts on her arms. I learned to not do that again. But she hasn't gotten mad in the last few days, which is really good <img src="//forum.moparisthebest.mopar/images/emoji/emoji_one/slight_smile.png?v=3" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/its-over/1668/18">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/its-over/1668/18</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 23 Apr 2006 04:29:23 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-1668-18</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/its-over/1668.rss">It&#39;s over</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>It&#39;s over</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Snipe Snipe]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/snipe">@Snipe</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>My mother was bipolar, well Im sure she still is.  Anyways it was a pain in the ass, we learned if she did something to you youre to walk away and not retaliate or shell go fuck crazy.  Like this one time, I was doing something on the computer and she walked by and slapped the shit out of me and started laughing as she walked away.  I was like wtf, anyways she comes back by and does the same shit, so the next time Im ready for her, when she comes by to slap me upside the head I grab her and put my legs behind hers and ease her down to the floor, I thought about just dropping her ass, anyways that was a big mistake.  She freaks out and starts calling me everything under the sun, my favorite was son of a bitch <img src="//forum.moparisthebest.mopar/images/emoji/emoji_one/wink.png?v=3" title=":wink:" class="emoji" alt=":wink:">  Nevertheless I havent spoken to her in about 4 years.  I left to live with my dad a short while after that, and ended up haveing to call the cops on her one time when she tried to come and force me to live with her again, she slapped me when I told her no and cut my face all up, damn nails.  </p>

<p>I also had a librarian that was bipolar too.  There was this one time I was sleeping in the library and was using some peoples coats as a pillow, and I ended up putting them on the back of the chair so when I stood up the weight of the coats caused the chair to topple over and she went ape shit.  Told me that I was an ignorant child that needs to go play in the streets, that pissed me off, so I was sitting there fuming trying not to say anything and 10 minutes later she comes over to me and starts rubbing on me and was like "Whats the matter?  You seem like youre upset."  Crazy bitch.  I dont see how people can stay with someone like that.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/its-over/1668/17">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/its-over/1668/17</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 23 Apr 2006 02:36:21 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-1668-17</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/its-over/1668.rss">It&#39;s over</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>It&#39;s over</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@kurt pixels]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/kurt">@kurt</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>man, i feel bad for you.  women are heartbreakers...its really sad, but dude everything will be ok!</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/its-over/1668/16">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/its-over/1668/16</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 23 Apr 2006 02:07:08 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-1668-16</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/its-over/1668.rss">It&#39;s over</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>It&#39;s over</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Surajd Surajd]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/surajd">@Surajd</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Just say this to her and she will snap right out of it:</p>

<p>I will buy you a Super Nintendo for you're birthday.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/its-over/1668/15">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/its-over/1668/15</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 23 Apr 2006 02:02:55 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-1668-15</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/its-over/1668.rss">It&#39;s over</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>It&#39;s over</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@SomethingToHide STH]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/somethingtohide">@SomethingToHide</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>rofl nice.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/its-over/1668/14">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/its-over/1668/14</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 23 Apr 2006 01:42:35 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-1668-14</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/its-over/1668.rss">It&#39;s over</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>It&#39;s over</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Nashiu Nashiu]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/nashiu">@Nashiu</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Just tell her I know completely how she feels, except missing the period part. <img src="//forum.moparisthebest.mopar/images/emoji/emoji_one/wink.png?v=3" title=":wink:" class="emoji" alt=":wink:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/its-over/1668/13">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/its-over/1668/13</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 22 Apr 2006 21:13:18 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-1668-13</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/its-over/1668.rss">It&#39;s over</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>It&#39;s over</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@SomethingToHide STH]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/somethingtohide">@SomethingToHide</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>She says she doesn't beleive in anything, yet she always talks about how she's going to Hell and God hates her. Then she says there is no Heaven only Hell. I told her this is impossible because everything in the world is balanced to some degree, so Hell wouldn't even be Hell if that was the only place. She has had a pretty bad life, and nothing really goes good for her.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/its-over/1668/12">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/its-over/1668/12</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 22 Apr 2006 21:07:08 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-1668-12</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/its-over/1668.rss">It&#39;s over</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>It&#39;s over</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Nashiu Nashiu]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/nashiu">@Nashiu</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I'm back, sorry for taking so long. Anyhow, it varies from person to person. I got the disorder from my father. It makes me really indecisive on big decisions. I'm not sure if it has to do with my beliefs but I also think God hates me even though I'm a Christian. You see all these people who have had their prayers answered and been totally changed and talked to God, he hasn't given a clue to me as to whether he even exists or not. He doesn't answer my prayers either. <img src="//forum.moparisthebest.mopar/images/emoji/emoji_one/frowning.png?v=3" title=":frowning:" class="emoji" alt=":frowning:"> Anyhow, it's different with everyone.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/its-over/1668/11">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/its-over/1668/11</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 22 Apr 2006 21:01:32 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-1668-11</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/its-over/1668.rss">It&#39;s over</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>It&#39;s over</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@SomethingToHide STH]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/somethingtohide">@SomethingToHide</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>That's how she is. Sometimes she wants me to help her in school or something and I try. However if I tell her what she's doing wrong, she freaks out thinking I'm saying she's stupid and correcting her and stuff. If I try to help her again and she doesn't get it, she instantly gives up. She has lots of potentional, and I know it. When I met her she was making Fs and Ds. Now that I've told her to not give up like that that she'll get it one time, she now is passing all of her classes with Bs except Biology. However her Biology teacher got pregnant and left so now she has a non-qualified biology teacher who can't teach, so that's the real reason.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/its-over/1668/10">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/its-over/1668/10</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 22 Apr 2006 02:43:19 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-1668-10</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/its-over/1668.rss">It&#39;s over</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>It&#39;s over</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Nashiu Nashiu]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/nashiu">@Nashiu</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I'm bi-polar, just not as bad as her. I know what it's like though, anytime someone tells you to calm down you instantly think they're calling you a psycho and all. Well I'm at school at the moment and I'm not gonna say everything, I will later.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/its-over/1668/9">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/its-over/1668/9</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 21 Apr 2006 18:38:29 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-1668-9</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/its-over/1668.rss">It&#39;s over</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>It&#39;s over</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@SomethingToHide STH]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/somethingtohide">@SomethingToHide</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I just got done talking with her. I had to resort to tactics like you can't talk until I say you can, or else she'd interupt before I got the point across. I told her how much of a bitch she was, and all of that. Then I used some of my personal psycology <img src="//forum.moparisthebest.mopar/images/emoji/emoji_one/slight_smile.png?v=3" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"> Since she always gets mad over small things without thinking. When she was mad I told her to calm down and she was freaking out and I told her not to talk. I told her I was only doing it to try and help, because I don't WANT to fight. Since I made her think before she got real mad, she understood me for once. She realized that instead of freaking out and screaming, if I told her to shut up and we each get our turn to talk like we're actually civilized, things work out MUCH nicer. I told her if she wanted this to work, she needs not freak out and she needs to think a little more. So far it's going pretty well.</p>

<p>Not only is she bipolar, but she is a hypocondriac. Part of that is her dad's fault however, because he never takes her to the doctor. Because of this she's always thinking something's wrong. When she thinks about it too much something does actually seem wrong but it's not. Like one time, a few months ago. Her . was a few weeks late, so she started thinking she was pregnant. She threw up a few times over a few days. Her brother got her a test and it said positive. I told her she was just freaking out and to just forget about it. Over time she stopped talking about it and her . came soon after. <img src="//forum.moparisthebest.mopar/images/emoji/emoji_one/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=3" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"></p>

<p>It is sad how I have to resort to some kindergarden tactics to get my points across. Have you ever noticed that when adults do things you don't like, you get mad. When you start to think about it, and all the conflicts involved, I usually come to the conclusion that I'd make the same choices as them. Two nearly opposite stages of life that share such common things yet are so uncommon.</p>

<p>Thanks for your support guys.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/its-over/1668/8">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/its-over/1668/8</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 21 Apr 2006 03:02:11 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-1668-8</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/its-over/1668.rss">It&#39;s over</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>It&#39;s over</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@yna_ajhear5 yna_ajhear5]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/yna_ajhear5">@yna_ajhear5</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I hate highschool drama.</p>

<p>Sorry for the spam, but im steering of girls for now. Wayyy too complicated.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/its-over/1668/7">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/its-over/1668/7</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 21 Apr 2006 02:36:33 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-1668-7</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/its-over/1668.rss">It&#39;s over</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>It&#39;s over</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@jme jme]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/jme">@jme</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>A year and 19 days, impressive. Doesn't happen often when your young. Most I managed was a month and a half, and now it seems like she has a new bf every month. So, I think I'll stay clear of girls for another year or two, until they realise that feelings do count. </p>

<p>Not much I can do to help you though &gt;.&gt;</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/its-over/1668/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/its-over/1668/6</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 21 Apr 2006 02:26:30 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-1668-6</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/its-over/1668.rss">It&#39;s over</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>It&#39;s over</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@anony2 anony2]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/anony2">@anony2</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>1 good thing bout being bi polar is us army wont take you incase they ever reinitate the draft which is a good thing for me but im on meds...really hope everything goes okay for you and her though</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/its-over/1668/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/its-over/1668/5</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 21 Apr 2006 02:22:48 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-1668-5</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/its-over/1668.rss">It&#39;s over</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>It&#39;s over</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@KyleGut3 KyleGut3]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/kylegut3">@KyleGut3</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Naw man, sorry I can't help.  I just have multiple personalities sometimes, not quite bipolar :x</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/its-over/1668/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/its-over/1668/4</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 21 Apr 2006 02:18:54 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-1668-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/its-over/1668.rss">It&#39;s over</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>It&#39;s over</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@1337h4x 1337h4x]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/1337h4x">@1337h4x</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>i think she just has problems...<br>dont go for the mental ones =\</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/its-over/1668/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/its-over/1668/3</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 21 Apr 2006 01:29:22 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-1668-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/its-over/1668.rss">It&#39;s over</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>It&#39;s over</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@pistolbob pistolbob]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/pistolbob">@pistolbob</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>i cant say im bipolar but im sorry to her this man hope everythings ok</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/its-over/1668/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/its-over/1668/2</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 21 Apr 2006 00:58:16 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-1668-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/its-over/1668.rss">It&#39;s over</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>It&#39;s over</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@SomethingToHide STH]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/somethingtohide">@SomethingToHide</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>So me and my girlfriend kinda broke up today <img src="//forum.moparisthebest.mopar/images/emoji/emoji_one/frowning.png?v=3" title=":frowning:" class="emoji" alt=":frowning:"> <img src="//forum.moparisthebest.mopar/images/emoji/emoji_one/frowning.png?v=3" title=":frowning:" class="emoji" alt=":frowning:"> <img src="//forum.moparisthebest.mopar/images/emoji/emoji_one/frowning.png?v=3" title=":frowning:" class="emoji" alt=":frowning:"> <img src="//forum.moparisthebest.mopar/images/emoji/emoji_one/frowning.png?v=3" title=":frowning:" class="emoji" alt=":frowning:"></p>

<p>We've been together a year and 19 days. Over the past month we've been "fighting" quite a bit, but I wouldn't call it that. I'm a very calm person, but she isn't. She is bipolar, her mom lives in NY, and she lives down here in GA with her dad. He doesn't even take her anywhere or bring her to the doctor. He doesn't really beleive in medicine so she's not on medicine for being bipolar. She used to be in NY but when they moved down here he took her off of it. Her boyfriend in NY cheated on her with many other girls, and she moved down here after that and her parents divorced. Her father's girlfriend is an old bitch who litterally drinks a few cartons of beer a day, along with a few cartons of smokes. Nobody really likes her, and she gambles away the little money they have. Her dad and the girlfriend fight a lot too. </p>

<p>I met her about a year and a half ago, she was dating one of my friends. They almost never saw each other. Eventually they starting fighting and she started to like me. I liked her also. Then one day she got mad at him, so he ignored her for the next few days. I was there for her. He broke up with her saying he had caused her too much pain. They got back together even though I said not to. Same thing not even a week later. Finally they broke up and she nearly killed herself. I told her not to and stopped her. Later on we started hanging out and then dating. </p>

<p>Everything was great. We did basically everything together. We had lots of fun. Eventually she just starting being weird. It came to be that basically, I couldn't tell her anything. If I did, she freaked out, then stopped doing whatever I said she did that made me mad. Say I said it made me mad when she left the dogs outside. She'd start a huge fight over it and from then on she wouldn't even get near the dogs. I'd ask her why and she gets an attitude and says she wouldn't want to let them outside or anything. In all the fights we had, she FREAKS out way more than any person should. Call me lots of names, be a smartass, tell me she hates me, everything. When I finally calm her down, she says it's just because she doesn't have help. She won't even ask her dad for it because she says that she knowssssss that he won't take her to get any. All the time we've been together I've helped her and bent over backwards for her. However if I told her she was doing something wrong, there was a fight. She says she hates it when I correct her because her sister allllllways did it to her. She finally understands that I'm just trying to help. I know I don't deserve this, but I stuck in with it because I loved the good times and I was never mad or fighting back with her. She'd get jealous when I was talking to any other girl, but everyday after school her and her neighbor friends would all go out and make bonfires and shit. She could do things, but not me. This kept on and on, but I knew it was just because she's psycho. I still had feelings for her. Just a week or two ago, she finally made me mad. Something happened, I don't remember what, and she started freaking out. She eventually said she didn't even want to come over the next day that I had made her so mad. I said oh well I've got a party to goto anyway. It was my friend Cheryl, almost my best friend. She was like omg omg and freaked out. She told me that if I went we were over. I told her that's not fair at all and to calm down. She got sooo pissed because I told her to calm down. I then said if I can't goto her party, you can't hang out with your friends ever. She agreed. Later she changed her mind and said that it's bs and that she can hang out with them, but I still can't goto the party. She kept teasing me and shit saying oh you can't break up with me you don't want to. I told her I had enough and it's over. Later that night however, she came back saying she was sorry and I could go. I said no no it's easter you're gonna come over and we'll have fun. She came over, we had fun. We were together again. The other night she was cussing at me and shit so I told her to calm down it's nothing to get mad over. She freaks out again. She told me I was shit, then broke up with me. I left to go do other things. Later on, she came back to me and I told her how I've done everything for her, given everything I had to her. But she still treated me horribly. She said she knows and she trys not to but she couldn't help it. She had went to her dad to ask if he would get her help and he said ok. I thought about it for a while and decided that maybe things would work out. Turns out he was being himself and didn't take her. Well today, we were at my house. I was sleepy and she was cooking with my mom so I layed down. She came over a little bit later and started kissing me telling me to wake up. I woke up and she wanted to tickle me. She sat on my legs and tickled me, but I couldn't get up because I was half under the couch. I told her to stop because I couldn't breathe, but she just let me breathe and tickled me. I kept telling her to please stop, but she didn't. I told her if she didn't stop I was going to kick her. She kept going and laughed at me. I pushed her down with me foot behind her knees. She got up and freaked out and started kicking me like crazy. I got up and layed down. She told me that I was an asshole. My mom comes in and she's like wtf is up. I was like she's just too damned mean. She got real mad and I told my side of the story and she denied that I ever said I would kick her. I said if you would have stopped like I asked you you wouldn't have gotten so mad. She started crying and yelling at me saying I was worthless, and that it's over, and she called her dad and he came and picked her up. I went outside to wait with her, and when he came I asked for a hug and she told me to shut up and left. I haven't talked to her since. I don't even know what to do. I am just so confused right now. No I am not coming here for your advice, I know what to do. I just want to know if anyone here is bipolar and can relate to her, as she has said many times that I don't understand. I can't even count on one hand the amount of times she was mad, I told her to calm down, and she freaked out on me. Anyone?</p>

<p>Sorry for the huge block of text.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/its-over/1668/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/its-over/1668/1</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 20 Apr 2006 22:58:44 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-1668-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/its-over/1668.rss">It&#39;s over</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
