<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Australian federation report</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/australian-federation-report/72108</link>
    <description>ok hey guys i have a task- research and write a report on ONE of the following 

1.federation
2.social reforms in the 1900&#39;s


length
-min-800 words
-max-1000 words


doesnt realy bother me about the 800 words just as long as its long enuf lol
p.s this is all for australian federeation an stuff.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 30 Mar 2007 15:39:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>General Discussion</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/australian-federation-report/72108.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Australian federation report</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@ryanz321 ryanz321]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/ryanz321">@ryanz321</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>thnx man your a god send man your good  <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/smiley.png?v=6" title=":smiley:" class="emoji" alt=":smiley:"> <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/smiley.png?v=6" title=":smiley:" class="emoji" alt=":smiley:"> <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/smiley.png?v=6" title=":smiley:" class="emoji" alt=":smiley:"> <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/smiley.png?v=6" title=":smiley:" class="emoji" alt=":smiley:"> <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/smiley.png?v=6" title=":smiley:" class="emoji" alt=":smiley:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/australian-federation-report/72108/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/australian-federation-report/72108/3</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 30 Mar 2007 15:39:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-72108-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/australian-federation-report/72108.rss">Australian federation report</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Australian federation report</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@marluxia marluxia]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/marluxia">@marluxia</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <blockquote>How &amp; Why did the Federation of Australia occur?:
The Federation of Australia is formed when the six separate colonies of New South Wales, Queensland, Northern Territory, Tasmania, Western Australia and Southern Australia came together under one government. It happened  on the 1st of January 1901. Sir Henry Parkes had a big role in the formation of federation.
<p>Many reasons – social, political and cultural – contributed to forming federation. There were also many problems facing the federation such as jobs cuts and threats, power struggle between the colonies.</p>
<p>Why wasn’t Australia already a nation? When the British first colonised Australia they first settled in New South Wales. After the success of the New South Wales colony other separate colonies were made.</p>
<p>Why – Socially:<br>
People wanted Australia to be one big country so they would feel more united as one nation. People felt more connected because of improvement in transport and communications between the colonies, improvements such as better railroads and the introduction of the telegraph to Australia.</p>
<p>Australia was also inspired to become a nation because of other newly created nations, such as America and Canada.</p>
<p>Why – Politically:<br>
Australia would be taken more seriously by other nations. Forming as one big nation would strengthen the economy, increase the export market and cut the price of taxes.</p>
<p>Politicians were also under a lot of pressure from the people of Australia to become a nation. There was also the threat of Chinese immigration and foreign diseases.</p>
<p>Why – Culturally<br>
Culturally Australian Federation was helped by artists such as Banjo Paterson, whose poems and songs which motivated people to be more concerned with federation.</p>
<p>How:<br>
How did the  Federation occur? In 1867 a young Secretary of New South Wales named Sir Henry Parkes proposed that the colonies of Australia form a central government. It was rejected by the colonies, however in 1880 it was brought up again, by Parkes. It was taken into greater consideration because of the movement towards the nationalism of Australia.</p>
<p>In 1883 German and French colonised New Guinea and New Caledonia, fearing invasion the six colonies proposed a bill to called the Federal Council of Australasia Act 1885. The Council was formed however New South Wales did not join. The forming of the Council was the first sign of cooperation between the colonies. It presented the opportunity for different members of the colonies to talk and express ideas.</p>
<p>On the 24th October 1889 Parkes announced to a Arts School in Tenterfield (This was later known to be the “Tenterfield Address”), New South Wales that “it was time for the colonies to consider Australian Federation”.  The Tenterfield Address massively impacted on the movement towards Federation.</p>
<p>On the 6th of February 1890 a conference was held, the attendees of the conference were from all the different colonies. The conference was held to debate whether or not to go ahead with Federation. The small colonies protested whilst bigger colonies agreed that it was time for Federation.</p>
<p>A conference was held in 1891 to make a draft of the Australian constitution. The first draft of the constitution was written by Sir Samuel Griffith, some of it came from the American constitution.  The draft was given to all of the colonies.</p>
<p>The draft was not taken into much consideration, until when in 1898 a referendum was held to see whether or not to adopt the draft constitution. Despite the low amount of eligible voters at the time, the draft was adopted as the official constitution.</p>
<p>In the UK on the 5th of July 1900, the Act Commonwealth of Australia Constitution was passed. And in Centennial Park on the 1st of January 1901 the Commonwealth of Australia was proclaimed.</p>
<p>The Problems:<br>
There were many problems facing federation. Smaller colonies feared being taken over by larger colonies, Queensland would not be able to get cheap labour, people feared that it would turn out to be another American civil war.</p>
<p>The smaller colonies were afraid of destruction of the foreign trade tax, which helped account for most of their income’s.</p>
<p>Conclusion:<br>
Despite the problems that faced Federation, Australia formed as a Commonwealth on the 1st of January 1901. Without the support from Sir Henry Parkes, Federation could have never had been.</p>
<p>Bibliography:<br>
•	<a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/" rel="nofollow noopener">http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/</a>	Australian_federation<br>
•	<a href="http://www.cultureandrecreation.gov.au/articles/federation/" rel="nofollow noopener">http://www.cultureandrecreation.gov.au/articles/federation/</a></p>
<p>both accessed on 12/3/07</p>
</blockquote>
<p>There’s mine only 712 words (but the teacher doesn’t know that  ;)) mmm my teacher said not to use headings <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/confused.png?v=6" title=":confused:" class="emoji" alt=":confused:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/australian-federation-report/72108/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/australian-federation-report/72108/2</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 29 Mar 2007 16:45:08 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-72108-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/australian-federation-report/72108.rss">Australian federation report</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Australian federation report</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@ryanz321 ryanz321]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/ryanz321">@ryanz321</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>ok hey guys i have a task- research and write a report on ONE of the following</p>
<p>1.federation<br>
2.social reforms in the 1900’s</p>
<p>length<br>
-min-800 words<br>
-max-1000 words</p>
<p>doesnt realy bother me about the 800 words just as long as its long enuf lol<br>
p.s this is all for australian federeation an stuff.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/australian-federation-report/72108/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/australian-federation-report/72108/1</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 29 Mar 2007 16:03:28 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-72108-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/australian-federation-report/72108.rss">Australian federation report</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
