<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Forum Engine - Feedback</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/forum-engine-feedback/364382</link>
    <description>I&#39;ve been developing a forum engine, for learning purposes.  I&#39;ve written it [u]all[/u] in PHP, and since it&#39;s just for that purpose, in particular, there&#39;s no need to correct my fails by adding all the markup in an echo.   :|
I&#39;ve been taking my time, finding newer ways to do things, and more efficient ways as well.  

Anyways.  So far, what I&#39;ve implemented into the engine would be a rather simple user panel and administrator panel.  There are hardly any features in them.  Besides editing some information and changing your password.. also in reason that I&#39;ve been lazy with my development this week.  And in the Administrator&#39;s Panel, you can submit an announcement that will appear in the user panel.  Yet not very similar to any of my other methods.  For security issues.

http://www.atomsai.x10.mx/beta-engine/index.php

Yes.  It does have an account registration/log in system.  And it&#39;s basic mySQL, so there&#39;s not really any reason to get too into this, besides explaining my theory for sessions ^.^

Created from pure scratch.  I&#39;ll most likely release the website source.  And if you read some of the threads that I&#39;ve posted on there (in other words, me talking to myself; feeling as if someone is reading xD), it pretty much says the same thing.

I guess I could give off some example code that I&#39;m using.  If any of you wish to see the code that I&#39;m using for a specific, please ask.

Also.  I do have a custom style sheet for this.  I&#39;ve just redone pretty much everything, because at first, I was primarily focusing on the markup and CSS, and I found out that I should at least finish the engine before the markup, if anything.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 16 Oct 2010 03:17:33 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>General Programming</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/forum-engine-feedback/364382.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Forum Engine - Feedback</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@cruel cruel]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/cruel">@cruel</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Nice, it’s better now. <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/smiley.png?v=5" title=":smiley:" class="emoji" alt=":smiley:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/forum-engine-feedback/364382/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/forum-engine-feedback/364382/5</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 16 Oct 2010 03:17:33 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-364382-5</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/forum-engine-feedback/364382.rss">Forum Engine - Feedback</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Forum Engine - Feedback</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Liquid_Magic Liquid Magic]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/liquid_magic">@Liquid_Magic</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Thanks for the alert.  I almost forgot about that.</p>
<p>Edit:</p>
<p>Alright.  I’ve fixed the form content up.  However.  I must thank you for reminding me, Cruel.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/forum-engine-feedback/364382/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/forum-engine-feedback/364382/4</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 16 Oct 2010 02:27:23 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-364382-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/forum-engine-feedback/364382.rss">Forum Engine - Feedback</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Forum Engine - Feedback</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Cthulu Cthulu]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/cthulu">@Cthulu</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>'ello Governor. As Cruel stated, you really REALLY need to clean ALL inputs before they’re put in the database, as you can see, using your thread titles, you get a lovely picture of goatse instead of your forum.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/forum-engine-feedback/364382/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/forum-engine-feedback/364382/3</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 16 Oct 2010 02:16:24 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-364382-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/forum-engine-feedback/364382.rss">Forum Engine - Feedback</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Forum Engine - Feedback</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@cruel cruel]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/cruel">@cruel</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Lol, fix the login msg:</p>
<blockquote>You have been logged in! 
You have been logged out, click here to go back to the main index. You will not be redirected.</blockquote>
Also, use htmlspecialchars(). It allows for any html and I was able to execute javascript ;)... careful
<p>EDIT: <a href="http://www.atomsai.x10.mx/beta-engine/thread.php?id=13" rel="nofollow noopener">http://www.atomsai.x10.mx/beta-engine/thread.php?id=13</a></p>
<p>Haha sry. I felt like hijacking the thread for lulz of a boy running at the sight of Sythe’s photo.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/forum-engine-feedback/364382/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/forum-engine-feedback/364382/2</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 16 Oct 2010 01:13:57 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-364382-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/forum-engine-feedback/364382.rss">Forum Engine - Feedback</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Forum Engine - Feedback</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Liquid_Magic Liquid Magic]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/liquid_magic">@Liquid_Magic</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I’ve been developing a forum engine, for learning purposes.  I’ve written it <span class="bbcode-u">all</span> in PHP, and since it’s just for that purpose, in particular, there’s no need to correct my fails by adding all the markup in an echo.   <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/expressionless.png?v=5" title=":expressionless:" class="emoji" alt=":expressionless:"><br>
I’ve been taking my time, finding newer ways to do things, and more efficient ways as well.</p>
<p>Anyways.  So far, what I’ve implemented into the engine would be a rather simple user panel and administrator panel.  There are hardly any features in them.  Besides editing some information and changing your password… also in reason that I’ve been lazy with my development this week.  And in the Administrator’s Panel, you can submit an announcement that will appear in the user panel.  Yet not very similar to any of my other methods.  For security issues.</p>
<p><a href="http://www.atomsai.x10.mx/beta-engine/index.php" class="onebox" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">http://www.atomsai.x10.mx/beta-engine/index.php</a></p>
<p>Yes.  It does have an account registration/log in system.  And it’s basic mySQL, so there’s not really any reason to get too into this, besides explaining my theory for sessions ^.^</p>
<p>Created from pure scratch.  I’ll most likely release the website source.  And if you read some of the threads that I’ve posted on there (in other words, me talking to myself; feeling as if someone is reading xD), it pretty much says the same thing.</p>
<p>I guess I could give off some example code that I’m using.  If any of you wish to see the code that I’m using for a specific, please ask.</p>
<p>Also.  I do have a custom style sheet for this.  I’ve just redone pretty much everything, because at first, I was primarily focusing on the markup and CSS, and I found out that I should at least finish the engine before the markup, if anything.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/forum-engine-feedback/364382/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/forum-engine-feedback/364382/1</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Oct 2010 04:03:20 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-364382-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/forum-engine-feedback/364382.rss">Forum Engine - Feedback</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
