<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Reviews Topic</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/reviews-topic/476602</link>
    <description>I&#39;d like to make this as a review thread until a child board has been made for it (or if it doesn&#39;t get made, I will try to keep this alive)

My review is gonna be about RapidModz.com, they sell modded controllers and devices for both PS3 and Xbox 360 and such.
My controller had some ups and downs and half the stuff I payed for didn&#39;t even work, I&#39;m talking to their support team for help.

My overall rating of the company: 6.5

Please help me keep this thread alive!

Edit for the mods: if this in any way counts as advertising notify me by posting here or messaging me and I will only mention names, no links.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 30 Dec 2012 01:47:25 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>General Discussion</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/reviews-topic/476602.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Reviews Topic</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Kodiak Kodiak]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/kodiak">@Kodiak</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Thanks for your review.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/reviews-topic/476602/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/reviews-topic/476602/4</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 30 Dec 2012 01:47:25 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-476602-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/reviews-topic/476602.rss">Reviews Topic</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Reviews Topic</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Immental Immental]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/immental">@Immental</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote quote-modified" data-post="2" data-topic="476602">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/xdeathstarsx/40/5_e05bb34c421432ee4d40de30c10af3e5.png" class="avatar"> xdeathstarsx:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>My review of this review is, pls stop trying. 1/10… Classic could do better AND HE’S AN ARAB.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Leave classic out of this, he’s to good for your comment.<br>
[size=12pt]I like this thread, so here is my review of: Trentahost [/size]</p>
<p>The site is both unreasonably slow, and uses wordpress with a stolen/nulled theme script with all the licenses removed.<br>
The Privacy Policy is hardly a paragraph and the refund policy is slightly longer. While the TOS seems to be the backbone of their site’s motives.<br>
The main reason one should stay away from the site is listed in their TOS</p>
<blockquote>1) Backup and Data Loss
<p>Your use of this service is at your sole risk. TrentaHost doesn’t provide a backup service. TrentaHost is not responsible for files and/or data residing on your account. You agree to take full responsibility for files and data transferred and to maintain all appropriate backup of files and data stored on TrentaHost servers. Backups will not be provided for accounts that have been suspended or terminated for any reason.</p>
</blockquote>
<blockquote>6) Reseller: Client Responsibility
<p>Resellers are responsible for supporting their clients. TrentaHost does not provide support to our Reseller’s Clients. If a reseller’s client contacts us, we reserve the right to place the client account on hold until the reseller can assume their responsibility for their client. All support requests must be made by the reseller on their clients’ behalf for security purposes. Resellers are also responsible for all content stored or transmitted under their reseller account and the actions of their clients’. TrentaHost will hold any reseller responsible for any of their clients actions that violate the law or the terms of service. A $15 administrative charge may be applied to unsuspend a Reseller account if there is abuse under account.</p>
</blockquote>
<blockquote>7) Indemnification
<p>Customer agrees that it shall defend, indemnify, save and hold TrentaHost harmless from any and all demands, liabilities, losses, costs and claims, including reasonable attorney’s fees asserted against trentaHost, its agents, its customers, officers and employees, that may arise or result from any service provided or performed or agreed to be performed or any product sold by customer, its agents, employees or assigns. Customer agrees to defend, indemnify and hold harmless TrentaHost against liabilities arising out of; (1) any injury to person or property caused by any products sold or otherwise distributed in connection with TrentaHost; (2) any material supplied by customer infringing or allegedly infringing on the proprietary rights of a third party; (3) copyright infringement and (4) any defective products sold to customers from TrentaHost server.</p>
</blockquote>
<p>and finally the <span class="hashtag">#1</span> reason to stay away from this site is:</p>
<blockquote>9) Disclaimer
<p>TrentaHost shall not be responsible for any damages your business may suffer. TrentaHost makes no warranties of any kind, expressed or implied for services we provide. TrentaHost disclaims any warranty or merchantability or fitness for a particular purpose. This includes loss of data resulting from delays, no deliveries, wrong delivery, and any and all service interruptions caused by TrentaHost and its employees.</p>
<ol start="14">
<li>Changes to the TOS</li>
</ol>
<p>TrentaHost reserves the right to revise its policies at any time without notice.</p>
</blockquote>
<p>That and they have no record of ever registering their copyright legally.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/reviews-topic/476602/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/reviews-topic/476602/3</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Dec 2012 18:33:56 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-476602-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/reviews-topic/476602.rss">Reviews Topic</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Reviews Topic</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@xdeathstarsx x Albi x]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/xdeathstarsx">@xdeathstarsx</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>My review of this review is, pls stop trying. 1/10… Classic could do better AND HE’S AN ARAB.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/reviews-topic/476602/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/reviews-topic/476602/2</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Dec 2012 12:20:11 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-476602-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/reviews-topic/476602.rss">Reviews Topic</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Reviews Topic</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Kodiak Kodiak]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/kodiak">@Kodiak</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I’d like to make this as a review thread until a child board has been made for it (or if it doesn’t get made, I will try to keep this alive)</p>
<p>My review is gonna be about <a href="http://RapidModz.com" rel="nofollow noopener">RapidModz.com</a>, they sell modded controllers and devices for both PS3 and Xbox 360 and such.<br>
My controller had some ups and downs and half the stuff I payed for didn’t even work, I’m talking to their support team for help.</p>
<p>My overall rating of the company: 6.5</p>
<p>Please help me keep this thread alive!</p>
<p>Edit for the mods: if this in any way counts as advertising notify me by posting here or messaging me and I will only mention names, no links.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/reviews-topic/476602/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/reviews-topic/476602/1</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Dec 2012 01:10:06 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-476602-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/reviews-topic/476602.rss">Reviews Topic</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
