<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>New Prayer</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-prayer/329143</link>
    <description>So i made a new prayer shows up in game in prayer list yes, but Iv&#39;e tryed gettin it to work since its extra strength boost prayer i went to formulae, jus edited few things at bottom where shows prayers for strength boost got no where, I figured if i jus added first of prayer name would compile successfully(becuase thats how the other prayers where set up), but did&#39;t if anyone could kindly help would be nice how do i make this prayer work is main QuEsTiOn? Also, If was to make another attack boost pray how would i add it just lil confused.

Thanks,</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 12 Feb 2010 08:27:04 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-prayer/329143.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>New Prayer</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@skarletdeath skarletdeath]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/skarletdeath">@skarletdeath</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>So i made a new prayer shows up in game in prayer list yes, but Iv’e tryed gettin it to work since its extra strength boost prayer i went to formulae, jus edited few things at bottom where shows prayers for strength boost got no where, I figured if i jus added first of prayer name would compile successfully(becuase thats how the other prayers where set up), but did’t if anyone could kindly help would be nice how do i make this prayer work is main QuEsTiOn? Also, If was to make another attack boost pray how would i add it just lil confused.</p>
<p>Thanks,</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-prayer/329143/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-prayer/329143/1</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 12 Feb 2010 08:27:04 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-329143-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-prayer/329143.rss">New Prayer</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
