<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>More history :P</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/more-history-p/2242</link>
    <description>hmmmmmmmm 30 questions and a comparsion sheets :)
1: The California Gold Rush resulted in all of the following developments EXCEPT the:
influx of over 200,000 people into the region
forcing thousands of Indians off their lands
kidnapping of thousands of Chinese to serve as workers
pressuring the federal government to create an effective government in the area

2: The application for California statehood caused turmoil in Congress because:
it would upset the balance between the slave and free states in the Senate
it would disturb the balance in the House between those who favored slavery and those who opposed it.
Democrats would alow no more slave states into the Union
Whigs would allow no more free states into the Union.

3: Many southerners supported the Compromise of 1850 because it:
provided that cotton be substituted for currency
legalized slavery in all the new territories
provided for the creation of 5 states out of Texas
provided for the return of fugitive slaves

4: Despite earlier efforts to settle the issue, slavery became a major issue in the 1840s and 1850s because the:
US Supreme Court had a northern majority
nation was expanding west
evangelists of the Second Awakening raised the issue frequently
existing political parties needed an issue which would unite their members

5: By opening the territory north of 36o 30&#39; to slavery, the Kansas-Nebraska Act repealed the:
Dred Scott decision
Compromise of 1850
Missouri Compromise
Wilmont Proviso

6: &quot;Bleeding Kansas&quot; gained its reputation for violence because of the:
sporadic warfare between settlers on opposing sides in the battle over the slavery issue
actions of various bandit gangs that roamed the territory before the arrival of federal marshals
general lawlessness of cow towns like Dodge City and Abilene
US Army&#39;s vicious tactics while driving the Indians out of the territory

7: The new Republican Party:
quickly won voter support in the South in the elections of 1854
prospered because of Northern outrage over &quot;Bleeding Kansas&quot;
won the presidency in the 1856 elections
advocated popular sovereignty to defuse the issue of slavery in the territories

8: In the Dred Scott case, the Supreme Court ruled that:
Dred Scott was not a citizen of the United States
the Missouri Compromise was unconstitutional
Congress had no power to ban slavery in any territory
All of the above

9: Which of the following was NOT TRUE about slavery as a labor system?
slavery was worth more in terms of investment than all the land of the South
as slavery spread in the Deep South, power became equally shared among all white southerners
it was slavery that made possible the South&#39;s &quot;mass production&quot; of cotton for export
only a minority of Southerners owned slaves

10: Manufacturing in the Old South lagged behind that in the North because:
black labor was incompatible with industry
white leaders in the South were more concerned with prestige than with profits
the South lacked important natural resources
cotton was more profitable than the industry

11: The southern demand that slavery be allowed to expand into the territories seems to have been motivated by the:
expectation that slavery would be even more profitable in the West than in the South
fear that free territories could be used as bases for spreading abolitionism into the South
belief that expansion was necessary to allow the profitable sale of slaves
none of the above

12: William Lloyd Garrison pledged his dedication to:
shipping freed blacks back to Africa
outlawing the slave trade
preventing the expansion of slavery beyond the South
the immediate abolition of slavery in the South

13: The most controversial aspect of the slavery issue during the first half of the 1800s was:
the status of slavery in the territories
the right of abolitionists to send their literature through the US mail
the enforcement of the Fugitive Slave Law
the prohibition of international slave trade

14: What was the significance of Harriet Beecher Stowe&#39;s Uncle Tom&#39;s Cabin?
It presented a view of slavery as an great good
It presented the idea that slavery did not tear apart the black family
It provoked a more aggressive anti-southern and anti-slavery position in those who were uncertain on the slavery issue
All of the above

15: Harriet Tubman gained fame:
in the gold fields of California
as an African-American poet
as an advocate for the Fugitive Slave Law
by helping slaves escape to Canada

16: The Homestead Act provided:
that indians should own their lands as individuals rather than collectively as tribes
160 acres of free land to anyone who would settle it and improve it over 5 years
40 acres of land to each former slave above the age of 21
that the land of former Confederates should not be confiscated by the government

17: The mining towns which developed in the West between 1860 and 1890:
were often abandoned after the mines closed
were mainly settled by men
frequently suffered from lawlessness
all of the above

18: The rapid development of railroads in the United States West was accomplished:
in large measure from European investments
exclusively through the suport of large numbers of small investors
with the help of some of the largest government grants ever given
almost totally through the investment of a handful of shrewd millionaires

19: The conflict over slavery in Kansas:
came about because the first settlers brough large numbers of slaves to the territory
we resolved by the Crittenden Compromise
was temporarily resolved by the Compromise of 1850
was greatly escalated by abolitionist-funded settlers and proslavery &quot;border ruffians&quot; from Missouri

20: The fanatical abolitionist John Brown made his first entry into violent antislavery politics by
killing five proslavery settlers in Kansas
organizing a slave rebellion in Missouri
leading an armed raid on the federal arsenal at Harper&#39;s Ferry, Virginia
organizing an armed militia of blacks and whites to conduct escaped slaves to Canada

21: The existence of the &quot;underground railroad&quot; added to southern demands for:
the admission of new slave states into the Union
the death penalty for abolitionists
a stricter federal Fugitive Slave Law
the enslavement of free blacks in North and South

22: Among the notable advocates of compromise in the controversy over slaverin in the 1850s were:
William Seward and Zachary Taylor
Henry Clay and Daniel Webster
John C. Calhoun and Abraham Lincoln
Stephen Douglas and Harriet Tubman

23: Under the terms of the Compromise of 1850:
California was admitted to the Union as a free state, and slavery in Utah and New Mexico would be left to popular sovereignty
California was admited as a free state, and Utah and New Mexico were slave states
California, Utah, and New Mexico were kept as territories but with slavery prohibited
New Mexico and Texas were admitted as slave states and Utah and California as free states

24: The invention that transformed the southern cotton industry was the:
sewing machine
mechanical cotton picker
cotton gin
steamboat

25: Most Southern slaveowners held:
over a hundred slaves
over fifty slaves
fewer than ten slaves
only one slave

26: Even though they owned no slaves, most southern whites supported the slave system because:
they were bribed by the planter class
they enjoyed the economic benefits of slavery
they felt racially superior to blacks and hoped to one day be able to buy slaves
they disliked the northern abolitionists

27: Most of the growth in the African-American slave population before 1860 came from:
the illegal importation of slaves from Africa
the re-enslavement of formerly free blacks
natural reproduction
the incorporation into the United States of new slave territories

28: Most slave owners treated their slaves as:
objects to be beaten and brutallized as often as possible
valuable investments
members of the extended family
sources of new technology

29: Most of the early abolitionists were motivated by:
a desire to see an indpendent black republic in Africa
anger at the negative economic consequences of slavery
religious feeling against the sin of slavery
a philosphical commitment to racial integration

30: The most prominent black abolisitonist leader was
Stephen Douglas
Harriet Beecher Stowe
William Lloyd Garrison
Frederick Douglass


	

Compare western culture and slave culture!  You are to create a two column document. One column should be dedicated to the Wild West.  The other column should be dedicated to slavery.

You are to write everything that you can think of that describes each culture (including its people).  When you are finished, you should have one column of facts about western culture and one column about slave culture.





sexyness. doubt anyone will rofl</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2006 17:18:24 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>General Discussion</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/more-history-p/2242.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>More history :P</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Pure_Skill Pure Skill]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/pure_skill">@Pure_Skill</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>i would help but im austrailan we dont learn american history</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/more-history-p/2242/12">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/more-history-p/2242/12</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2006 17:18:24 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-2242-12</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/more-history-p/2242.rss">More history :P</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>More history :P</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@afi afi]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/afi">@afi</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote" data-post="10" data-topic="2242"><div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>jme_009:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>I've said it before, and I'll say it again:</p>
<p>Home schooling does not work! <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/emoji_one/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=3" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"></p>
</blockquote></aside>

<p>tell me about it =\</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/more-history-p/2242/11">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/more-history-p/2242/11</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 01 May 2006 22:01:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-2242-11</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/more-history-p/2242.rss">More history :P</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>More history :P</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@jme jme]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/jme">@jme</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I've said it before, and I'll say it again:</p>

<p>Home schooling does not work! <img src="//forum.moparisthebest.mopar/images/emoji/emoji_one/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=3" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/more-history-p/2242/10">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/more-history-p/2242/10</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 01 May 2006 21:53:44 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-2242-10</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/more-history-p/2242.rss">More history :P</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>More history :P</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@afi afi]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/afi">@afi</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>i did alot of science today <img src="//forum.moparisthebest.mopar/images/emoji/emoji_one/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=3" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/more-history-p/2242/9">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/more-history-p/2242/9</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 01 May 2006 21:47:21 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-2242-9</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/more-history-p/2242.rss">More history :P</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>More history :P</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@yna_ajhear5 yna_ajhear5]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/yna_ajhear5">@yna_ajhear5</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>&lt;3</p>

<p>Do more work afi</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/more-history-p/2242/8">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/more-history-p/2242/8</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 01 May 2006 21:45:35 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-2242-8</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/more-history-p/2242.rss">More history :P</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>More history :P</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@afi afi]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/afi">@afi</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote" data-post="2" data-topic="2242"><div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="//forum.moparisthebest.mopar/letter_avatar_proxy/v2/letter/y/858c86/40.png" class="avatar">yna_ajhear5:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>I'll get right ot it sir. Please Hold.<br>1. kidnapping of thousands of Chinese to serve as workers<br>2../... im gueesing it's: it would upset the balance between the slave and free states in the Senate<br>3.provided for the return of fugitive slaves<br>4.nation was expanding west<br>5.Missouri Compromise<br>6.sporadic warfare between settlers on opposing sides in the battle over the slavery issue<br>7.advocated popular sovereignty to defuse the issue of slavery in the territories<br>8.I think it's none of those. Link: <a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Dred_Scott" rel="nofollow">http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Dred_Scott</a><br>9.it was slavery that made possible the South's "mass production" of cotton for export<br>10.cotton was more profitable than the industry<br>11.fear that free territories could be used as bases for spreading abolitionism into the South<br>12.shipping freed blacks back to Africa<br>13.the status of slavery in the territories (I think)<br>14.It presented the idea that slavery did not tear apart the black family.<br>15.by helping slaves escape to Canada<br>16.160 acres of free land to anyone who would settle it and improve it over 5 years<br>17.all of the above<br>18.with the help of some of the largest government grants ever given<br>19.was greatly escalated by abolitionist-funded settlers and proslavery "border ruffians" from Missouri<br>20. Too many browns sorry.<br>21.a stricter federal Fugitive Slave Law<br>22.Stephen Douglas and Harriet Tubman (Guess)<br>23.California was admitted to the Union as a free state, and slavery in Utah and New Mexico would be left to popular sovereignty<br>24.cotton gin<br>25.over a hundred slaves<br>26.they enjoyed the economic benefits of slavery<br>27.the incorporation into the United States of new slave territories<br>28.objects to be beaten and brutallized as often as possible<br>29.anger at the negative economic consequences of slavery<br>30.No Clue.</p>
<p>I'm not doing your other crap. You need to do SOMETHING. <img src="//forum.moparisthebest.mopar/images/emoji/emoji_one/slight_smile.png?v=3" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
</blockquote></aside>

<p>thanks yna sure doomsday <img src="//forum.moparisthebest.mopar/images/emoji/emoji_one/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=3" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/more-history-p/2242/7">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/more-history-p/2242/7</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 01 May 2006 21:23:29 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-2242-7</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/more-history-p/2242.rss">More history :P</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>More history :P</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@doomsday doomsday]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/doomsday">@doomsday</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <ol><li>Frederick Douglass</li></ol>

<p>and ill do that sheet too(if you want)</p>

<p>becasue i really bored, or should i go make scars for rs?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/more-history-p/2242/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/more-history-p/2242/6</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 01 May 2006 21:09:18 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-2242-6</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/more-history-p/2242.rss">More history :P</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>More history :P</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@afi afi]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/afi">@afi</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>i would install aim but <img src="//forum.moparisthebest.mopar/images/emoji/emoji_one/frowning.png?v=3" title=":frowning:" class="emoji" alt=":frowning:"> it comes with a browser and all th at crap and i can't handle it :d</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/more-history-p/2242/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/more-history-p/2242/5</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 01 May 2006 20:32:55 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-2242-5</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/more-history-p/2242.rss">More history :P</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>More history :P</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@yna_ajhear5 yna_ajhear5]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/yna_ajhear5">@yna_ajhear5</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>No, only AIM</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/more-history-p/2242/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/more-history-p/2242/4</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 01 May 2006 20:27:13 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-2242-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/more-history-p/2242.rss">More history :P</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>More history :P</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@afi afi]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/afi">@afi</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote" data-post="2" data-topic="2242"><div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="//forum.moparisthebest.mopar/letter_avatar_proxy/v2/letter/y/858c86/40.png" class="avatar">yna_ajhear5:</div>
<blockquote><p>I'll get right ot it sir. Please Hold.</p></blockquote></aside>

<p>omg sexyness, do you have msn :o lol;</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/more-history-p/2242/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/more-history-p/2242/3</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 01 May 2006 19:42:52 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-2242-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/more-history-p/2242.rss">More history :P</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>More history :P</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@yna_ajhear5 yna_ajhear5]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/yna_ajhear5">@yna_ajhear5</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I'll get right ot it sir. Please Hold.<br>1. kidnapping of thousands of Chinese to serve as workers<br>2../... im gueesing it's: it would upset the balance between the slave and free states in the Senate<br>3.provided for the return of fugitive slaves<br>4.nation was expanding west<br>5.Missouri Compromise<br>6.sporadic warfare between settlers on opposing sides in the battle over the slavery issue<br>7.advocated popular sovereignty to defuse the issue of slavery in the territories<br>8.I think it's none of those. Link: <a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Dred_Scott" rel="nofollow">http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Dred_Scott</a><br>9.it was slavery that made possible the South's "mass production" of cotton for export<br>10.cotton was more profitable than the industry<br>11.fear that free territories could be used as bases for spreading abolitionism into the South<br>12.shipping freed blacks back to Africa<br>13.the status of slavery in the territories (I think)<br>14.It presented the idea that slavery did not tear apart the black family.<br>15.by helping slaves escape to Canada<br>16.160 acres of free land to anyone who would settle it and improve it over 5 years<br>17.all of the above<br>18.with the help of some of the largest government grants ever given<br>19.was greatly escalated by abolitionist-funded settlers and proslavery "border ruffians" from Missouri<br>20. Too many browns sorry.<br>21.a stricter federal Fugitive Slave Law<br>22.Stephen Douglas and Harriet Tubman (Guess)<br>23.California was admitted to the Union as a free state, and slavery in Utah and New Mexico would be left to popular sovereignty<br>24.cotton gin<br>25.over a hundred slaves<br>26.they enjoyed the economic benefits of slavery<br>27.the incorporation into the United States of new slave territories<br>28.objects to be beaten and brutallized as often as possible<br>29.anger at the negative economic consequences of slavery<br>30.No Clue.</p>

<p>I'm not doing your other crap. You need to do SOMETHING. <img src="//forum.moparisthebest.mopar/images/emoji/emoji_one/slight_smile.png?v=3" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/more-history-p/2242/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/more-history-p/2242/2</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 01 May 2006 19:39:21 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-2242-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/more-history-p/2242.rss">More history :P</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>More history :P</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@afi afi]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/afi">@afi</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>hmmmmmmmm 30 questions and a comparsion sheets <img src="//forum.moparisthebest.mopar/images/emoji/emoji_one/slight_smile.png?v=3" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"><br>1: The California Gold Rush resulted in all of the following developments EXCEPT the:<br>influx of over 200,000 people into the region<br>forcing thousands of Indians off their lands<br>kidnapping of thousands of Chinese to serve as workers<br>pressuring the federal government to create an effective government in the area</p>

<p>2: The application for California statehood caused turmoil in Congress because:<br>it would upset the balance between the slave and free states in the Senate<br>it would disturb the balance in the House between those who favored slavery and those who opposed it.<br>Democrats would alow no more slave states into the Union<br>Whigs would allow no more free states into the Union.</p>

<p>3: Many southerners supported the Compromise of 1850 because it:<br>provided that cotton be substituted for currency<br>legalized slavery in all the new territories<br>provided for the creation of 5 states out of Texas<br>provided for the return of fugitive slaves</p>

<p>4: Despite earlier efforts to settle the issue, slavery became a major issue in the 1840s and 1850s because the:<br>US Supreme Court had a northern majority<br>nation was expanding west<br>evangelists of the Second Awakening raised the issue frequently<br>existing political parties needed an issue which would unite their members</p>

<p>5: By opening the territory north of 36o 30' to slavery, the Kansas-Nebraska Act repealed the:<br>Dred Scott decision<br>Compromise of 1850<br>Missouri Compromise<br>Wilmont Proviso</p>

<p>6: "Bleeding Kansas" gained its reputation for violence because of the:<br>sporadic warfare between settlers on opposing sides in the battle over the slavery issue<br>actions of various bandit gangs that roamed the territory before the arrival of federal marshals<br>general lawlessness of cow towns like Dodge City and Abilene<br>US Army's vicious tactics while driving the Indians out of the territory</p>

<p>7: The new Republican Party:<br>quickly won voter support in the South in the elections of 1854<br>prospered because of Northern outrage over "Bleeding Kansas"<br>won the presidency in the 1856 elections<br>advocated popular sovereignty to defuse the issue of slavery in the territories</p>

<p>8: In the Dred Scott case, the Supreme Court ruled that:<br>Dred Scott was not a citizen of the United States<br>the Missouri Compromise was unconstitutional<br>Congress had no power to ban slavery in any territory<br>All of the above</p>

<p>9: Which of the following was NOT TRUE about slavery as a labor system?<br>slavery was worth more in terms of investment than all the land of the South<br>as slavery spread in the Deep South, power became equally shared among all white southerners<br>it was slavery that made possible the South's "mass production" of cotton for export<br>only a minority of Southerners owned slaves</p>

<p>10: Manufacturing in the Old South lagged behind that in the North because:<br>black labor was incompatible with industry<br>white leaders in the South were more concerned with prestige than with profits<br>the South lacked important natural resources<br>cotton was more profitable than the industry</p>

<p>11: The southern demand that slavery be allowed to expand into the territories seems to have been motivated by the:<br>expectation that slavery would be even more profitable in the West than in the South<br>fear that free territories could be used as bases for spreading abolitionism into the South<br>belief that expansion was necessary to allow the profitable sale of slaves<br>none of the above</p>

<p>12: William Lloyd Garrison pledged his dedication to:<br>shipping freed blacks back to Africa<br>outlawing the slave trade<br>preventing the expansion of slavery beyond the South<br>the immediate abolition of slavery in the South</p>

<p>13: The most controversial aspect of the slavery issue during the first half of the 1800s was:<br>the status of slavery in the territories<br>the right of abolitionists to send their literature through the US mail<br>the enforcement of the Fugitive Slave Law<br>the prohibition of international slave trade</p>

<p>14: What was the significance of Harriet Beecher Stowe's Uncle Tom's Cabin?<br>It presented a view of slavery as an great good<br>It presented the idea that slavery did not tear apart the black family<br>It provoked a more aggressive anti-southern and anti-slavery position in those who were uncertain on the slavery issue<br>All of the above</p>

<p>15: Harriet Tubman gained fame:<br>in the gold fields of California<br>as an African-American poet<br>as an advocate for the Fugitive Slave Law<br>by helping slaves escape to Canada</p>

<p>16: The Homestead Act provided:<br>that indians should own their lands as individuals rather than collectively as tribes<br>160 acres of free land to anyone who would settle it and improve it over 5 years<br>40 acres of land to each former slave above the age of 21<br>that the land of former Confederates should not be confiscated by the government</p>

<p>17: The mining towns which developed in the West between 1860 and 1890:<br>were often abandoned after the mines closed<br>were mainly settled by men<br>frequently suffered from lawlessness<br>all of the above</p>

<p>18: The rapid development of railroads in the United States West was accomplished:<br>in large measure from European investments<br>exclusively through the suport of large numbers of small investors<br>with the help of some of the largest government grants ever given<br>almost totally through the investment of a handful of shrewd millionaires</p>

<p>19: The conflict over slavery in Kansas:<br>came about because the first settlers brough large numbers of slaves to the territory<br>we resolved by the Crittenden Compromise<br>was temporarily resolved by the Compromise of 1850<br>was greatly escalated by abolitionist-funded settlers and proslavery "border ruffians" from Missouri</p>

<p>20: The fanatical abolitionist John Brown made his first entry into violent antislavery politics by<br>killing five proslavery settlers in Kansas<br>organizing a slave rebellion in Missouri<br>leading an armed raid on the federal arsenal at Harper's Ferry, Virginia<br>organizing an armed militia of blacks and whites to conduct escaped slaves to Canada</p>

<p>21: The existence of the "underground railroad" added to southern demands for:<br>the admission of new slave states into the Union<br>the death penalty for abolitionists<br>a stricter federal Fugitive Slave Law<br>the enslavement of free blacks in North and South</p>

<p>22: Among the notable advocates of compromise in the controversy over slaverin in the 1850s were:<br>William Seward and Zachary Taylor<br>Henry Clay and Daniel Webster<br>John C. Calhoun and Abraham Lincoln<br>Stephen Douglas and Harriet Tubman</p>

<p>23: Under the terms of the Compromise of 1850:<br>California was admitted to the Union as a free state, and slavery in Utah and New Mexico would be left to popular sovereignty<br>California was admited as a free state, and Utah and New Mexico were slave states<br>California, Utah, and New Mexico were kept as territories but with slavery prohibited<br>New Mexico and Texas were admitted as slave states and Utah and California as free states</p>

<p>24: The invention that transformed the southern cotton industry was the:<br>sewing machine<br>mechanical cotton picker<br>cotton gin<br>steamboat</p>

<p>25: Most Southern slaveowners held:<br>over a hundred slaves<br>over fifty slaves<br>fewer than ten slaves<br>only one slave</p>

<p>26: Even though they owned no slaves, most southern whites supported the slave system because:<br>they were bribed by the planter class<br>they enjoyed the economic benefits of slavery<br>they felt racially superior to blacks and hoped to one day be able to buy slaves<br>they disliked the northern abolitionists</p>

<p>27: Most of the growth in the African-American slave population before 1860 came from:<br>the illegal importation of slaves from Africa<br>the re-enslavement of formerly free blacks<br>natural reproduction<br>the incorporation into the United States of new slave territories</p>

<p>28: Most slave owners treated their slaves as:<br>objects to be beaten and brutallized as often as possible<br>valuable investments<br>members of the extended family<br>sources of new technology</p>

<p>29: Most of the early abolitionists were motivated by:<br>a desire to see an indpendent black republic in Africa<br>anger at the negative economic consequences of slavery<br>religious feeling against the sin of slavery<br>a philosphical commitment to racial integration</p>

<p>30: The most prominent black abolisitonist leader was<br>Stephen Douglas<br>Harriet Beecher Stowe<br>William Lloyd Garrison<br>Frederick Douglass</p>

<pre><code></code></pre>

<p>Compare western culture and slave culture!  You are to create a two column document. One column should be dedicated to the Wild West.  The other column should be dedicated to slavery.</p>

<p>You are to write everything that you can think of that describes each culture (including its people).  When you are finished, you should have one column of facts about western culture and one column about slave culture.</p>

<p>sexyness. doubt anyone will rofl</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/more-history-p/2242/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/more-history-p/2242/1</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 01 May 2006 15:25:54 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-2242-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/more-history-p/2242.rss">More history :P</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
