<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>SlashScape V3 [advertisement links removed.]</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/slashscape-v3-advertisement-links-removed/330508</link>
    <description>TO MODERATORS: ALL LINKS REMOVED, IF YOU DELETE THIS NOW OTHER THREADS SHOULD BE LOCKED TO SUCH AS THE GELINOR THREAD.

[center][img]http://70.38.83.182/forum/images/bluefox_ambient/misc/images/logo.png[/img]

Welcome to SlashScape.
SlashScape is a very stable and content filled server brought to you by zeebest and Call me bear. The server features many near-perfect skills, along with a player -&gt; player economy.

About:
The server has only been out for 3 days, currently we have an average of 100 people online world 1 alone, and this is before we have advertised at all! So the word of mouth must be playing it&#39;s part.

Economy:
The economy is completly dependant on the player community, there is nothing available in shops that would ruin this, most items apart from the basics are skill or monster drop dependant.

Rates:
SlashScape V3 features a slow and tough training rate aswell as a tough economy, this means that you have to work for your stuff, it also means that when you get a decent drop from killing monsters or PvP it actually has some value, not like the Pking servers which you can buy dragon items in the shop.

All skill rates, including combat, are 7.5x RuneScape&#39;s speeds (Example: 30 exp per damage in combat). This may seem slow but it means that you actually work for levels, for example we have highscores and people are continously fighting to get to the top and it works. 7.5x experience means that the server isn&#39;t rediculously slow, but it is slower than most servers released.

Skills:
Almost ALL skills work on SlashScape, and all are at a higher quality than any skills i&#39;ve seen on any other server, since you have to spend time doing skills we have made sure that the skills are as bug free and as realistic as possible, aswell as being as fair as possible to the players who spend the time to do them.

Player VS NPC:
The PvNpc in our server is very realistic, multi-combat area&#39;s and single combat area&#39;s work perfect, aswell as fully clipped following and walking, meaning that NPC&#39;s and Players cannot walk through objects in combat or following. 

Drops from NPC&#39;s are realistic also, with a very accurate drop system which can use fractions of a percent. Rare items are actually rare, not like every other server where killing a NPC gets you like 100k coins in 1 go.

Player VS Player:
The PvP on this server is also very realistic, hit timers, equipment bonuses and hit damage plays a massive part in the realism, no hitting on full armour with punching every shot, magic and ranging is also very accurate.

Minigames:
Since the server has only just been released we currently have only a few minigames, but these have been well-programmed, for example our dueling system has been checked through multiple times to ensure there is no risk of losing items unfairly by any glitches anyone may have.

Staff:
Unlike every other server the staff on our server DO NOT have commands, which means they also have to train.

The reason our staff system works is because each staff member has a job assigned to them and them only, for example we currently have around 5 support administrators of whos jobs are to help out people on the forum, whether that be bug support or helping them out with general F.A.Q.

Client:
The client i have created for the server features 525 configuration, this means that alot of map area&#39;s have been updated, although textures currently are disabled due to a bug with the models in new engines i hope to fix them soon. The client features no hard-coding at all, all configuration is archived and read only when required, meaning that the client consumes LESS MEMORY THAN A BASIC 317 CLIENT, no more having to add extra memory to the running of the client, the average memory usage is under 100K.

Update server, onDemand and webclient:
We have a fully working update server system implemented into the game server and the client, this means that any time we have a content update which requires us to update the cache we can just change a few values at our end and the next time you run the client it will automatically update the files, unlike &quot;auto-cache downloading&quot; having an update server means you can play instantly, you don&#39;t need to wait for a 50MB cache to download, instead configuration files are sent ONLY WHEN UPDATED and the rest of the files are send on demand, which means they wont update unless you need the model, animation or whatever the request is.

New map content:
As i have said the client uses 525 configuration, this means that we have the ability to import new maps into the game with the most ease, at the moment we have updated a few area&#39;s such as lumbridge, varrock and added places like GODWARS but we may consider updating more areas if we feel it&#39;s worth it on your behalves.

Membership system:
At the current stage of the server we do not have the membership system active, however, it will be soon because of the amount of money it costs us to host the server. Membership benifits will include seperate members worlds, alot more content, including a few more skills *did anyone say hunter and summoning?*, and alot more area&#39;s and extensions to skills.

This will also come with members only items, which will work on non-members worlds, ofcourse, since they can be used on non-members worlds they will not be overpowered weapons which give amazingly high advantages to members.

Multiple world system:
At the moment we currently have 2 worlds running, these worlds are linked by our login server, which monitors worlds online, player counts and mutli-world friends lists and private messaging.

Dedicated server:
Since everyone else seems to show off theirs i thought we would show-off ours, our dedicated server costs over $325 a month which is why we will be introducing membership subscriptions to pay for this.

Login screen:
[img]http://i792.photobucket.com/albums/yy208/slashscape/loginscreen.png[/img]

Firemaking:
[img]http://i792.photobucket.com/albums/yy208/slashscape/firemaking.png[/img]

Godwars:
[img]http://img21.imageshack.us/img21/4684/88992471.png[/img]

More images:
Woodcutting: http://i792.photobucket.com/albums/y...shscape/wc.png
Smithing: http://i792.photobucket.com/albums/y...ape/smelt2.png
Smelting: http://i792.photobucket.com/albums/y...cape/smelt.png
Wilderness: http://i792.photobucket.com/albums/y...scape/wild.png
World select: http://i792.photobucket.com/albums/y...cape/world.png[/center]

[size=18pt]Dont take my word for it... Come try it yourself now![/size]</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 22 Feb 2010 21:58:36 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/slashscape-v3-advertisement-links-removed/330508.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>SlashScape V3 [advertisement links removed.]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@oldschoolscape oldschoolscape]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/oldschoolscape">@oldschoolscape</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>TO MODERATORS: ALL LINKS REMOVED, IF YOU DELETE THIS NOW OTHER THREADS SHOULD BE LOCKED TO SUCH AS THE GELINOR THREAD.</p>
<p>[center]<img src="http://70.38.83.182/forum/images/bluefox_ambient/misc/images/logo.png" alt width="" height=""></p>
<p>Welcome to SlashScape.<br>
SlashScape is a very stable and content filled server brought to you by zeebest and Call me bear. The server features many near-perfect skills, along with a player -&gt; player economy.</p>
<p>About:<br>
The server has only been out for 3 days, currently we have an average of 100 people online world 1 alone, and this is before we have advertised at all! So the word of mouth must be playing it’s part.</p>
<p>Economy:<br>
The economy is completly dependant on the player community, there is nothing available in shops that would ruin this, most items apart from the basics are skill or monster drop dependant.</p>
<p>Rates:<br>
SlashScape V3 features a slow and tough training rate aswell as a tough economy, this means that you have to work for your stuff, it also means that when you get a decent drop from killing monsters or PvP it actually has some value, not like the Pking servers which you can buy dragon items in the shop.</p>
<p>All skill rates, including combat, are 7.5x RuneScape’s speeds (Example: 30 exp per damage in combat). This may seem slow but it means that you actually work for levels, for example we have highscores and people are continously fighting to get to the top and it works. 7.5x experience means that the server isn’t rediculously slow, but it is slower than most servers released.</p>
<p>Skills:<br>
Almost ALL skills work on SlashScape, and all are at a higher quality than any skills i’ve seen on any other server, since you have to spend time doing skills we have made sure that the skills are as bug free and as realistic as possible, aswell as being as fair as possible to the players who spend the time to do them.</p>
<p>Player VS NPC:<br>
The PvNpc in our server is very realistic, multi-combat area’s and single combat area’s work perfect, aswell as fully clipped following and walking, meaning that NPC’s and Players cannot walk through objects in combat or following.</p>
<p>Drops from NPC’s are realistic also, with a very accurate drop system which can use fractions of a percent. Rare items are actually rare, not like every other server where killing a NPC gets you like 100k coins in 1 go.</p>
<p>Player VS Player:<br>
The PvP on this server is also very realistic, hit timers, equipment bonuses and hit damage plays a massive part in the realism, no hitting on full armour with punching every shot, magic and ranging is also very accurate.</p>
<p>Minigames:<br>
Since the server has only just been released we currently have only a few minigames, but these have been well-programmed, for example our dueling system has been checked through multiple times to ensure there is no risk of losing items unfairly by any glitches anyone may have.</p>
<p>Staff:<br>
Unlike every other server the staff on our server DO NOT have commands, which means they also have to train.</p>
<p>The reason our staff system works is because each staff member has a job assigned to them and them only, for example we currently have around 5 support administrators of whos jobs are to help out people on the forum, whether that be bug support or helping them out with general F.A.Q.</p>
<p>Client:<br>
The client i have created for the server features 525 configuration, this means that alot of map area’s have been updated, although textures currently are disabled due to a bug with the models in new engines i hope to fix them soon. The client features no hard-coding at all, all configuration is archived and read only when required, meaning that the client consumes LESS MEMORY THAN A BASIC 317 CLIENT, no more having to add extra memory to the running of the client, the average memory usage is under 100K.</p>
<p>Update server, onDemand and webclient:<br>
We have a fully working update server system implemented into the game server and the client, this means that any time we have a content update which requires us to update the cache we can just change a few values at our end and the next time you run the client it will automatically update the files, unlike “auto-cache downloading” having an update server means you can play instantly, you don’t need to wait for a 50MB cache to download, instead configuration files are sent ONLY WHEN UPDATED and the rest of the files are send on demand, which means they wont update unless you need the model, animation or whatever the request is.</p>
<p>New map content:<br>
As i have said the client uses 525 configuration, this means that we have the ability to import new maps into the game with the most ease, at the moment we have updated a few area’s such as lumbridge, varrock and added places like GODWARS but we may consider updating more areas if we feel it’s worth it on your behalves.</p>
<p>Membership system:<br>
At the current stage of the server we do not have the membership system active, however, it will be soon because of the amount of money it costs us to host the server. Membership benifits will include seperate members worlds, alot more content, including a few more skills <em>did anyone say hunter and summoning?</em>, and alot more area’s and extensions to skills.</p>
<p>This will also come with members only items, which will work on non-members worlds, ofcourse, since they can be used on non-members worlds they will not be overpowered weapons which give amazingly high advantages to members.</p>
<p>Multiple world system:<br>
At the moment we currently have 2 worlds running, these worlds are linked by our login server, which monitors worlds online, player counts and mutli-world friends lists and private messaging.</p>
<p>Dedicated server:<br>
Since everyone else seems to show off theirs i thought we would show-off ours, our dedicated server costs over $325 a month which is why we will be introducing membership subscriptions to pay for this.</p>
<p>Login screen:<br>
<div class="lightbox-wrapper"><a class="lightbox" href="http://i792.photobucket.com/albums/yy208/slashscape/loginscreen.png" title="loginscreen.png" rel="nofollow noopener"><img src="http://i792.photobucket.com/albums/yy208/slashscape/loginscreen.png" alt width="690" height="453"><div class="meta">
<svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-far-image svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#far-image"></use></svg><span class="filename">loginscreen.png</span><span class="informations">765×503</span><svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-discourse-expand svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#discourse-expand"></use></svg>
</div></a></div></p>
<p>Firemaking:<br>
<img src="http://i792.photobucket.com/albums/yy208/slashscape/firemaking.png" alt width="515" height="340"></p>
<p>Godwars:<br>
<img src="http://img21.imageshack.us/img21/4684/88992471.png" alt width="" height=""></p>
<p>More images:<br>
Woodcutting: <a href="http://i792.photobucket.com/albums/y...shscape/wc.png" rel="nofollow noopener">http://i792.photobucket.com/albums/y...shscape/wc.png</a><br>
Smithing: <a href="http://i792.photobucket.com/albums/y...ape/smelt2.png" rel="nofollow noopener">http://i792.photobucket.com/albums/y...ape/smelt2.png</a><br>
Smelting: <a href="http://i792.photobucket.com/albums/y...cape/smelt.png" rel="nofollow noopener">http://i792.photobucket.com/albums/y...cape/smelt.png</a><br>
Wilderness: <a href="http://i792.photobucket.com/albums/y...scape/wild.png" rel="nofollow noopener">http://i792.photobucket.com/albums/y...scape/wild.png</a><br>
World select: <a href="http://i792.photobucket.com/albums/y...cape/world.png%5B/center%5D" rel="nofollow noopener">http://i792.photobucket.com/albums/y...cape/world.png[/center]</a></p>
<p>[size=18pt]Dont take my word for it… Come try it yourself now![/size]</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/slashscape-v3-advertisement-links-removed/330508/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/slashscape-v3-advertisement-links-removed/330508/1</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 22 Feb 2010 21:58:36 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-330508-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/slashscape-v3-advertisement-links-removed/330508.rss">SlashScape V3 [advertisement links removed.]</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
