<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Permanently set permissions (samba/debian)</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/permanently-set-permissions-samba-debian/199963</link>
    <description>I&#39;m not sure if this a samba specific problem, or just something a chmod can fix, so bear with me.
I currently have a debian Linux server, which has apache, mysql, sshd, and samba running on it. I also have a Windows Vista machine in which I do my web development work, and I have mapped my samba share of /var/www to S: drive. Whenever I edit a file (using an editor such as notepad or Dreamweaver in Windows), the &quot;read&quot; permissions for &quot;everybody&quot; are removed, so I get a 403 Forbidden when I navigate to the file in my web browser. The only solution I&#39;ve found is to go under the properties for the file in windows and to check the &quot;read&quot; box under &quot;everybody&quot;. This of course is quite impractical, so I&#39;m wondering if there is a way to permanently allow &quot;everybody&quot; to &quot;read&quot; every file in /var/www? I&#39;m not really sure if this is a Windows or Linux problem, but I&#39;m thinking that the solution will most likely be on the Linux side of things.
Thanks.
Edit: Here&#39;s my addition to /etc/samba/smb.conf if it helps:
[code]
[www]
comment = apache htdocs
path = /var/www
public = yes
writable = yes
valid users = johnr
create mask = 0771
directory mask = 0771
force user johnr
force group = www-users
[/code]
johnr is my samba user, and www-users is my account group with full permissions for /var/www, and their root set to /var/www.


Edit edit: Fixed, I need to learn my chmod permissions better. 775, not 771. Thanks for the help  :|</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 15 Apr 2008 05:16:58 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Technology</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/permanently-set-permissions-samba-debian/199963.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Permanently set permissions (samba/debian)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Unhandled Unhandled]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/unhandled">@Unhandled</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I’m not sure if this a samba specific problem, or just something a chmod can fix, so bear with me.<br>
I currently have a debian Linux server, which has apache, mysql, sshd, and samba running on it. I also have a Windows Vista machine in which I do my web development work, and I have mapped my samba share of /var/www to S: drive. Whenever I edit a file (using an editor such as notepad or Dreamweaver in Windows), the “read” permissions for “everybody” are removed, so I get a 403 Forbidden when I navigate to the file in my web browser. The only solution I’ve found is to go under the properties for the file in windows and to check the “read” box under “everybody”. This of course is quite impractical, so I’m wondering if there is a way to permanently allow “everybody” to “read” every file in /var/www? I’m not really sure if this is a Windows or Linux problem, but I’m thinking that the solution will most likely be on the Linux side of things.<br>
Thanks.<br>
Edit: Here’s my addition to /etc/samba/smb.conf if it helps:</p>
<pre><code class="lang-auto">[www]
comment = apache htdocs
path = /var/www
public = yes
writable = yes
valid users = johnr
create mask = 0771
directory mask = 0771
force user johnr
force group = www-users</code></pre>
<p>johnr is my samba user, and www-users is my account group with full permissions for /var/www, and their root set to /var/www.</p>
<p>Edit edit: Fixed, I need to learn my chmod permissions better. 775, not 771. Thanks for the help  <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/expressionless.png?v=6" title=":expressionless:" class="emoji" alt=":expressionless:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/permanently-set-permissions-samba-debian/199963/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/permanently-set-permissions-samba-debian/199963/1</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 15 Apr 2008 05:16:58 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-199963-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/permanently-set-permissions-samba-debian/199963.rss">Permanently set permissions (samba/debian)</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
