<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Ghost sprite</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/ghost-sprite/467386</link>
    <description>Hey guys,
Basically what I&#39;m looking for a sprite similar to this.
[IMG]http://img545.imageshack.us/img545/6099/itunesartwork.png[/img]
The sprite will be used in a game, the background will be earthy so it will consist of different shades of browns and greys which means the colour scheme used in the sprite will have to be fairly plain and universal. The background must be transparent so when used their isn&#39;t a white bit around the ghost sprite.
The game is aimed at a younger age group so I&#39;d like the ghost sprite to look cute like it does in the example shown. The ghost will be an NPC that attempts to eat the player in the game so bit of an unfriendly look would be perfect. Something similar to the image provided would be ideal.
The size must be 50x50 and the image format would preferably be a Png but I can do that myself if thats an issue. If I have not provided enough information please do tell me what you require to know and I&#39;ll let you know.
Thanks for your time and help!</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 14 Nov 2012 17:12:09 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Graphics</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/ghost-sprite/467386.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Ghost sprite</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Kidpaparoach Kidpaparoach]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/kidpaparoach">@Kidpaparoach</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>That sorta thing could work fine, the cuteness isn’t a big deal as long as it isn’t scary. Its meant to look like its meant to be scary but not actually be scary sorta thing (if that makes sense &gt;&lt;).<br>
Thanks for your time but I need one made for me, not one thats sourced elsewhere as for a start I don’t know what the licencing for it is &gt;&lt;.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/ghost-sprite/467386/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/ghost-sprite/467386/3</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 14 Nov 2012 17:12:09 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-467386-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/ghost-sprite/467386.rss">Ghost sprite</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Ghost sprite</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@RSPS_Mirrors RSPS Mirrors]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/rsps_mirrors">@RSPS_Mirrors</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p><img src="http://www.bogleech.com/gs-smog.gif" alt width="61" height="59"><br>
Not exactly cute but was all I could find.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/ghost-sprite/467386/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/ghost-sprite/467386/2</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 14 Nov 2012 10:49:23 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-467386-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/ghost-sprite/467386.rss">Ghost sprite</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Ghost sprite</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Kidpaparoach Kidpaparoach]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/kidpaparoach">@Kidpaparoach</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Hey guys,<br>
Basically what I’m looking for a sprite similar to this.<br>
<img src="http://img545.imageshack.us/img545/6099/itunesartwork.png" alt width="" height=""><br>
The sprite will be used in a game, the background will be earthy so it will consist of different shades of browns and greys which means the colour scheme used in the sprite will have to be fairly plain and universal. The background must be transparent so when used their isn’t a white bit around the ghost sprite.<br>
The game is aimed at a younger age group so I’d like the ghost sprite to look cute like it does in the example shown. The ghost will be an NPC that attempts to eat the player in the game so bit of an unfriendly look would be perfect. Something similar to the image provided would be ideal.<br>
The size must be 50x50 and the image format would preferably be a Png but I can do that myself if thats an issue. If I have not provided enough information please do tell me what you require to know and I’ll let you know.<br>
Thanks for your time and help!</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/ghost-sprite/467386/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/ghost-sprite/467386/1</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Nov 2012 10:25:56 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-467386-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/ghost-sprite/467386.rss">Ghost sprite</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
