<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Scam &amp; Virus warnings - useful information</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/scam-virus-warnings-useful-information/164453</link>
    <description>This thread contains [b]important[/b] information to keep you safe, it seems long but PLEASE read it!

[b]General information - [/b]
[b]Do not[/b] download anything you don&#39;t trust! This is the number 1 rule of the internet!
[b]NEVER[/b] give your passwords to anyone! Remember, you do [b]NOT[/b] know who they are, it&#39;s easier to lie than you think.
[b]ALWAYS[/b] check what you are running. [b]DO NOT[/b] run a .bat file blindly, right click it and go to edit, if it doesn&#39;t look safe then [b]DO NOT RUN IT[/b]. If you do want to be sure, look in other files, [b]ESPECIALLY JAVA FILES[/b], virus scanners [b]DO NOT[/b] scan java files!
Now, this one is debatable, try to stay away from &quot;hypes&quot;, it&#39;s rare but viruses can &quot;slip&quot; through virus scanners when the virus is new. A new hype could be a virus spreading campaign.

If you are unsure of a files safety, I have provided links to some popular online file scanners:
http://virusscan.jotti.org/  &lt;- Recommended, although the server can be pretty busy.
http://www.kaspersky.com/scanforvirus
http://onlinescan.avast.com/

[b]Personal Messages, PMs etc - [/b]
[b]Do not[/b] download ANY links sent to you through the forums PM system, I guarantee you these will almost [b]ALWAYS[/b] be viruses!
[b]Do not[/b] visit forums sent to you through the PM software, even if your sure there safe, [b]do not[/b] download anything advertised there.

[b]Staff&#39;s &quot;servers&quot; - [/b]
[b]NEVER[/b] join a server when the server owner is a forum staff member, and the person advertising it is not a staff member.
[b]NEVER[/b] download a staff member&#39;s server when the person advertising ti is not a staff member.

[b]Staff asking for passwords - [/b]
[B]NEVER[/B] tell a staff member your password, like I said before, you [b]NEVER[/b] know who you are talking to.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 13 Dec 2007 11:08:29 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Community Suggestions</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/scam-virus-warnings-useful-information/164453.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Scam &amp; Virus warnings - useful information</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@The_Un-Named The Un-Named]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/the_un-named">@The_Un-Named</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>This thread contains <span class="bbcode-b">important</span> information to keep you safe, it seems long but PLEASE read it!</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">General information - </span><br>
<span class="bbcode-b">Do not</span> download anything you don’t trust! This is the number 1 rule of the internet!<br>
<span class="bbcode-b">NEVER</span> give your passwords to anyone! Remember, you do <span class="bbcode-b">NOT</span> know who they are, it’s easier to lie than you think.<br>
<span class="bbcode-b">ALWAYS</span> check what you are running. <span class="bbcode-b">DO NOT</span> run a .bat file blindly, right click it and go to edit, if it doesn’t look safe then <span class="bbcode-b">DO NOT RUN IT</span>. If you do want to be sure, look in other files, <span class="bbcode-b">ESPECIALLY JAVA FILES</span>, virus scanners <span class="bbcode-b">DO NOT</span> scan java files!<br>
Now, this one is debatable, try to stay away from “hypes”, it’s rare but viruses can “slip” through virus scanners when the virus is new. A new hype could be a virus spreading campaign.</p>
<p>If you are unsure of a files safety, I have provided links to some popular online file scanners:<br>
<a href="http://virusscan.jotti.org/" rel="nofollow noopener">http://virusscan.jotti.org/</a>  &lt;- Recommended, although the server can be pretty busy.<br>
<a href="http://www.kaspersky.com/scanforvirus" rel="nofollow noopener">http://www.kaspersky.com/scanforvirus</a><br>
<a href="http://onlinescan.avast.com/" rel="nofollow noopener">http://onlinescan.avast.com/</a></p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Personal Messages, PMs etc - </span><br>
<span class="bbcode-b">Do not</span> download ANY links sent to you through the forums PM system, I guarantee you these will almost <span class="bbcode-b">ALWAYS</span> be viruses!<br>
<span class="bbcode-b">Do not</span> visit forums sent to you through the PM software, even if your sure there safe, <span class="bbcode-b">do not</span> download anything advertised there.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Staff’s “servers” - </span><br>
<span class="bbcode-b">NEVER</span> join a server when the server owner is a forum staff member, and the person advertising it is not a staff member.<br>
<span class="bbcode-b">NEVER</span> download a staff member’s server when the person advertising ti is not a staff member.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Staff asking for passwords - </span><br>
<span class="bbcode-b">NEVER</span> tell a staff member your password, like I said before, you <span class="bbcode-b">NEVER</span> know who you are talking to.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/scam-virus-warnings-useful-information/164453/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/scam-virus-warnings-useful-information/164453/1</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 13 Dec 2007 11:08:29 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-164453-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/scam-virus-warnings-useful-information/164453.rss">Scam &amp; Virus warnings - useful information</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
