<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Private Servers And More</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/private-servers-and-more/222208</link>
    <description>February 22, 2006 Mopar Forums were created and advertisement went all around. Soon the community became huge. People tried hacking/sending viruses and other things. The community soon collapsed and there was nothing but &quot;leecher&quot; and bad words that really weren&#39;t necessary. People started saying bad things because of what others made. Just because others had the same thing people would hate them saying leecher etc. Runescape had a big update on July 1st. The Runescape Private Server Communities went lower. Every day you went on Moparscape or Rune Server or any Private Server Community just remember it will always be the same and it will never become like runescape no matter what. Even if that&#39;s not why you join these communities they still will always be the same thing like New home area, New pk area, New minigame etc. Sometimes it&#39;s really fun to play but you get bored. Most things on these forums are hatred cussing and leeching. Over 75% Of these communities don&#39;t even know what God is or they are just so stupid they don&#39;t spend anytime with their family and stay on the computer all waiting for there life to go by and No God with them. Just the feeling when you go to confession it&#39;s a really nice feeling if only most of you knew. Go ahead and waste your time saying &quot;gtfo nub&quot; or &quot;cunt gay ass bitch&#39; those words all mean nothing as that is not what I am.

Oh and remember it&#39;s not late to quit these forums.

Find out more about God. If you think there is no God well there is.

The bible proves and talks about space how the world is round and so many other things I have no time to explain. Find out more about the bible and God. You&#39;ll soon believe. I hope you enjoy your lifes. I am sure no one back then got to go to space. Also people found the ark that Noah made in china. Communists wouldnt let all go and see it... LEARN WAY MORE.

DId you know? Over half of a science book holds lies? That is true to.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2008 08:42:48 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/private-servers-and-more/222208.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Private Servers And More</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Encouragin Encouragin]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/encouragin">@Encouragin</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Never gonna give you up… Never gonna let you down. Never gonna run around and desert you! Never gonna make you cry and never gonna say goodbye! never gonna tell a lie and hurt you!</p>
<p>Anyway, Gtfo with this piece of shit.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/private-servers-and-more/222208/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/private-servers-and-more/222208/5</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2008 08:42:48 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-222208-5</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/private-servers-and-more/222208.rss">Private Servers And More</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Private Servers And More</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@0wn3r_tom 0wn3r tom]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/0wn3r_tom">@0wn3r_tom</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>cerda go to <a href="http://youfail.org" rel="nofollow noopener">youfail.org</a>  <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/cool.png?v=6" title=":cool:" class="emoji" alt=":cool:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/private-servers-and-more/222208/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/private-servers-and-more/222208/4</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2008 08:39:03 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-222208-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/private-servers-and-more/222208.rss">Private Servers And More</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Private Servers And More</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@SkillersDream SkillersDream]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/skillersdream">@SkillersDream</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>stop spamming the forums with this stuff.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/private-servers-and-more/222208/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/private-servers-and-more/222208/3</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2008 08:27:07 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-222208-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/private-servers-and-more/222208.rss">Private Servers And More</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Private Servers And More</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@mrHoward mrHoward]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/mrhoward">@mrHoward</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>This isn’t necessary, reported.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/private-servers-and-more/222208/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/private-servers-and-more/222208/2</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2008 08:26:02 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-222208-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/private-servers-and-more/222208.rss">Private Servers And More</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Private Servers And More</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@_Cerda1 ``Cerda]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/_cerda1">@_Cerda1</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>February 22, 2006 Mopar Forums were created and advertisement went all around. Soon the community became huge. People tried hacking/sending viruses and other things. The community soon collapsed and there was nothing but “leecher” and bad words that really weren’t necessary. People started saying bad things because of what others made. Just because others had the same thing people would hate them saying leecher etc. Runescape had a big update on July 1st. The Runescape Private Server Communities went lower. Every day you went on Moparscape or Rune Server or any Private Server Community just remember it will always be the same and it will never become like runescape no matter what. Even if that’s not why you join these communities they still will always be the same thing like New home area, New pk area, New minigame etc. Sometimes it’s really fun to play but you get bored. Most things on these forums are hatred cussing and leeching. Over 75% Of these communities don’t even know what God is or they are just so stupid they don’t spend anytime with their family and stay on the computer all waiting for there life to go by and No God with them. Just the feeling when you go to confession it’s a really nice feeling if only most of you knew. Go ahead and waste your time saying “gtfo nub” or "cunt gay ass bitch’ those words all mean nothing as that is not what I am.</p>
<p>Oh and remember it’s not late to quit these forums.</p>
<p>Find out more about God. If you think there is no God well there is.</p>
<p>The bible proves and talks about space how the world is round and so many other things I have no time to explain. Find out more about the bible and God. You’ll soon believe. I hope you enjoy your lifes. I am sure no one back then got to go to space. Also people found the ark that Noah made in china. Communists wouldnt let all go and see it… LEARN WAY MORE.</p>
<p>DId you know? Over half of a science book holds lies? That is true to.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/private-servers-and-more/222208/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/private-servers-and-more/222208/1</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2008 08:20:39 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-222208-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/private-servers-and-more/222208.rss">Private Servers And More</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
