<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Threading?</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/threading/538968</link>
    <description>Hi there.

Just thought I&#39;d join this forums in hope it&#39;s community are fairly knowledgeable when it comes to computing... (Not the only reason, but my interest for private servers aren&#39;t very strong).

I&#39;m currently in a computing class in England where we&#39;ve been working on Python, ruby, VB, HTML, CSS, Php, and C... We&#39;ve spent approximately a month on each of these languages, so not in depth at all. It&#39;s his method of getting brand new programming enthusiasts used to the general syntax (though they&#39;re all different) of what to expect when working with computer science. So I&#39;m now in my second year of the course and the entire of the remaining two years are focussing on Java, OpenGL and Unity3D and we&#39;re studying game development.

We touched on threading this evening and it went right over my head. He mentioned how it acted as a sub-process as opposed to the process you would see in task manager, and that all games use threading as well as a huge variety of languages too. With all this being said, he never touched on the point why it&#39;s required and what it specifically does. I&#39;m one of those learners where I can&#39;t just take it in and ignore it.. I need to know how this threading has an effect on the overall project. Any advice/support is extremely appreciated, i realize this probably isn&#39;t the right place to come but I&#39;ve given it a shot!

Thank you, sorry for dragging it on!

EDIT:

the code was something like this [code] private Thread threading;
threading = new Thread; [/code]

And there was also a method declared with the keyword synchronized which I had also never seen before.. For our 5th lesson on this, it&#39;s all a bit intimidating of what to expect when it gets difficult.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2014 09:40:56 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>General Programming</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/threading/538968.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Threading?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@0xCAFEBABE 0xCAFEBABE]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/0xcafebabe">@0xCAFEBABE</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Cres:</p>
<p>Two threads may very well run in parallel. It all depends on your CPU. If it has more than one core, it may, but is not guaranteed to do so.</p>
<p>In general:</p>
<p>Mutable data (that is, data that can be modified, such as Object instances with setter-methods) must be thread-safe if used by multiple threads simultaneously. Otherwise race-conditions and other problems may occur. Such problems may be quite hard to track down, as they usually occur in, as it may seem, a “random” fashion.</p>
<p>To make something thread-safe, you have to take into account atomicity, ordering and visibility.</p>
<p>Atomiticy practically means that a set of operations should be indivisible. They are considered one atomic operation (on a higher level). Only the one thread that currently runs this atomic operation should be allowed to alter the state of the data needed by it. This only applies at the time this atomic operation is executed. So, both before execution starts and after execution stops, other threads may potentially alter the state of the data.</p>
<p>Ordering practically states the happens-before and happens-after relationships among different threads and their operations. Sometimes, perhaps, you might need to update a GUI with data gathered by a long running operation. The long running operation and the GUI cannot run in the same thread, as that would cause the GUI to freeze, just as Lothy mentioned above. Here the long running operation happens-before the GUI update (and the opposite aswell of course). If the GUI should update after the long running operation has started but before it has stopped, the data shown in the GUI may very well be wrong.</p>
<p>Visibility means that, even if one operation happens-before another operation, just as intended, you’re not guaranteed to see the most up-to-date state of some given data. This is due to thread-caching. Using the volatile-keyword on a field corrects this for you, without any synchronization-overhead. This keyword practically tells the underlying thread-mechanism to not use caching, and directly write updates to the real field.</p>
<p>One easy way to get thread-safety for free, is to program with immutability in mind. It simply means you should not be able to update fields (directly or indirectly) or alter state in itself. If a field is assigned an instance of a mutable class, then you should copy it when assigning it, so no alteration can be done from the outside. If you return it in a getter-method, copy it once again. All fields should be final and the class itself should be final, so no subclassing can be done. If the immutable class is created by subclassing a mutable class, make sure it cannot be altered from the outside and that it does not alter itself from the inside.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/threading/538968/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/threading/538968/5</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2014 09:40:56 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-538968-5</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/threading/538968.rss">Threading?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Threading?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@MateStfu MateStfu]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/matestfu">@MateStfu</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“Lothy, post:2, topic:538968”]In a nutshell, it allows multiple things to happen at the same time (or to be perceived as happening at the same time, in the case of CPUs that don’t actually have multiple cores).</p>
<p>Why is this useful? Imagine any application that performs some writing of data to disk. What would happen if you had to write a massive block of data?<br>
In a single-threaded application the user interface would hang and become non-responsive to user commands (e.g.: buttons would not be clickable, etc) until the IO operation completed.<br>
In a multi-threaded application you can have different threads that do different things. In the case of a windows application written using C#/.NET you’ll find that there’s an event handling thread to handle all user input (such as clicking buttons, entering text in textboxes, etc) and that the developer is encouraged to use another worker thread for especially intensive tasks (such as writing to disk) so that this event handling thread may keep processing user interface events.<br>
As a result the application is quick and responsive to the user even when something is happening in the background at the same time in another thread.</p>
<p>Hopefully that answers the ‘why’. In any case, rest assured that writing concurrent software is challenging and that there are very good reasons for doing so; nobody would do it if it was just for shits and giggles.[/quote]</p>
<p>You’re a life saver. This has helped so much.</p>
<p>So it’s basically instead of reading the code line for line and waiting until it gets to each method, it’s synchronized and running them all at once so it doesn’t need to wait for something to happen before say, the user could input?</p>
<p>and if you had no threads it just wouldn’t work, you’d have to keep waiting for it to get to that method?</p>
<p>also would no threads in a big game crash it? (just curious).</p>
<p>Thank you again Lothy!</p>
<p>Really good at explaining things.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/threading/538968/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/threading/538968/4</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2014 09:21:47 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-538968-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/threading/538968.rss">Threading?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Threading?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Cres Cres]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/cres">@Cres</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>All I know about threads is that, as stated above, they allow for multiple tasks to run at once, but also that you shouldn’t let data from one thread interact with another. Reason to this is that threads are always asynchronous. No threads run at the very same time (and therefore there is no guarantee that an event in a first thread will execute before an event in a second, even if you planned them to execute in that order). This becomes more and more clear when practicing parallel programming.</p>
<p>(if there’s any mistakes, please correct me… haven’t done anything programming related for close to a year :/)</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/threading/538968/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/threading/538968/3</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2014 08:40:31 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-538968-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/threading/538968.rss">Threading?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Threading?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@lothy Lothy]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/lothy">@lothy</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>In a nutshell, it allows multiple things to happen at the same time (or to be perceived as happening at the same time, in the case of CPUs that don’t actually have multiple cores).</p>
<p>Why is this useful? Imagine any application that performs some writing of data to disk. What would happen if you had to write a massive block of data?<br>
In a single-threaded application the user interface would hang and become non-responsive to user commands (e.g.: buttons would not be clickable, etc) until the IO operation completed.<br>
In a multi-threaded application you can have different threads that do different things. In the case of a windows application written using C#/.NET you’ll find that there’s an event handling thread to handle all user input (such as clicking buttons, entering text in textboxes, etc) and that the developer is encouraged to use another worker thread for especially intensive tasks (such as writing to disk) so that this event handling thread may keep processing user interface events.<br>
As a result the application is quick and responsive to the user even when something is happening in the background at the same time in another thread.</p>
<p>Hopefully that answers the ‘why’. In any case, rest assured that writing concurrent software is challenging and that there are very good reasons for doing so; nobody would do it if it was just for shits and giggles.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/threading/538968/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/threading/538968/2</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2014 02:22:44 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-538968-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/threading/538968.rss">Threading?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Threading?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@MateStfu MateStfu]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/matestfu">@MateStfu</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Hi there.</p>
<p>Just thought I’d join this forums in hope it’s community are fairly knowledgeable when it comes to computing… (Not the only reason, but my interest for private servers aren’t very strong).</p>
<p>I’m currently in a computing class in England where we’ve been working on Python, ruby, VB, HTML, CSS, Php, and C… We’ve spent approximately a month on each of these languages, so not in depth at all. It’s his method of getting brand new programming enthusiasts used to the general syntax (though they’re all different) of what to expect when working with computer science. So I’m now in my second year of the course and the entire of the remaining two years are focussing on Java, OpenGL and Unity3D and we’re studying game development.</p>
<p>We touched on threading this evening and it went right over my head. He mentioned how it acted as a sub-process as opposed to the process you would see in task manager, and that all games use threading as well as a huge variety of languages too. With all this being said, he never touched on the point why it’s required and what it specifically does. I’m one of those learners where I can’t just take it in and ignore it… I need to know how this threading has an effect on the overall project. Any advice/support is extremely appreciated, i realize this probably isn’t the right place to come but I’ve given it a shot!</p>
<p>Thank you, sorry for dragging it on!</p>
<p>EDIT:</p>
<p>the code was something like this <code> private Thread threading;
threading = new Thread; </code></p>
<p>And there was also a method declared with the keyword synchronized which I had also never seen before… For our 5th lesson on this, it’s all a bit intimidating of what to expect when it gets difficult.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/threading/538968/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/threading/538968/1</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2014 23:42:14 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-538968-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/threading/538968.rss">Threading?</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
