<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>634 Server</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/634-server/396125</link>
    <description>Okay. I am not a game programmer, so I have little knowledge as to what goes on behind the scenes of RuneScape or Private Servers. My question is: Is there somewhere I can download the source code like the one in Fallen Empire 634 (web client). If i were to get the source, it would not be opened to the public, I only need it to make videos. The Fallen Empire source is the most up to date server I&#39;ve played on and it also has helpful features such as character customization. BUT for the video I was in the middle of creating I was using cheat engine to emote hack and npc hack in RuneScape (to allow myself to become an npc and execute any emote I desired). This has been patched. So I searched for a private server to fit my needs. Fallen Empire gives ordinary players the ability to uses GFX and ANIM, which when combined with character customization it is almost perfect for my video. BUT I also need to be able to change into an NPC (No, cheat engine does not work with the private server to do this) and use noclip (because I cannot get into some houses I was filming in). Unfortunately these two problems require I have admin privileges and the Admin of the server told me he will not grant these to me after I had explained my problem. Long story short: I need the 634 source that is used in the 634 server &quot;Fallen Empire&quot; (webclient) to be able to make myself an admin to use certain admin only privileges to aid me in the completion of my video. Any information you can give me on my problem would be greatly appreciated. Thank You.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 23 May 2011 20:51:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/634-server/396125.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>634 Server</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@maxw30 maxw30]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/maxw30">@maxw30</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Goodluck and ask him for alexs! <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=5" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"> best of wishes</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/634-server/396125/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/634-server/396125/4</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 23 May 2011 20:51:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-396125-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/634-server/396125.rss">634 Server</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>634 Server</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@lildielyn lildielyn]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/lildielyn">@lildielyn</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote quote-modified" data-post="2" data-topic="396125">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/nasz/40/5_e05bb34c421432ee4d40de30c10af3e5.png" class="avatar"> Nasz:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>The closest server I can give to you would be alex’s 634 or Dementhiums 614. But I think alex’s client is 562 Loading 634.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I’ve tried the 614 would you mind sharing the Alex’s Client with me?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/634-server/396125/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/634-server/396125/3</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 23 May 2011 20:50:05 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-396125-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/634-server/396125.rss">634 Server</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>634 Server</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Nasz Nasz]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/nasz">@Nasz</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>The closest server I can give to you would be alex’s 634 or Dementhiums 614. But I think alex’s client is 562 Loading 634.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/634-server/396125/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/634-server/396125/2</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 23 May 2011 20:33:38 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-396125-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/634-server/396125.rss">634 Server</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>634 Server</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@lildielyn lildielyn]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/lildielyn">@lildielyn</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Okay. I am not a game programmer, so I have little knowledge as to what goes on behind the scenes of RuneScape or Private Servers. My question is: Is there somewhere I can download the source code like the one in Fallen Empire 634 (web client). If i were to get the source, it would not be opened to the public, I only need it to make videos. The Fallen Empire source is the most up to date server I’ve played on and it also has helpful features such as character customization. BUT for the video I was in the middle of creating I was using cheat engine to emote hack and npc hack in RuneScape (to allow myself to become an npc and execute any emote I desired). This has been patched. So I searched for a private server to fit my needs. Fallen Empire gives ordinary players the ability to uses GFX and ANIM, which when combined with character customization it is almost perfect for my video. BUT I also need to be able to change into an NPC (No, cheat engine does not work with the private server to do this) and use noclip (because I cannot get into some houses I was filming in). Unfortunately these two problems require I have admin privileges and the Admin of the server told me he will not grant these to me after I had explained my problem. Long story short: I need the 634 source that is used in the 634 server “Fallen Empire” (webclient) to be able to make myself an admin to use certain admin only privileges to aid me in the completion of my video. Any information you can give me on my problem would be greatly appreciated. Thank You.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/634-server/396125/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/634-server/396125/1</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 23 May 2011 20:03:48 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-396125-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/634-server/396125.rss">634 Server</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
