<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Taking Charge of AITP</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/taking-charge-of-aitp/131727</link>
    <description>This topic is just for me to extract some usefull events that I may plan for my college&#39;s AITP chapter. I do consiter this my homework more than a general discusion.

Befor I go about asking the extreamely nice and helpful rs cheating community wich i have been a part of sence kaitnieks about event ideas ill explane why this is important to me.

The current AITP presedent at my college has been running are chapter into the ground. All we have done for the past 11 months is fundraise. Finnaly when we have adequate funds to take a field trip I was not eligible to go because I was 16. Now, I understand the difficulys my age caused for them but, they could have ttold me before I sold 400 hotdogs I had bought myself for them. So now that I&#39;ve spent the $35 fee to join, the $100 for chips, foil, and hot dogs and another $65 for gas to haul their grill they tell me I can&#39;t go with them to the profesional chapter AITP meeting. Aint that a ass? Today, 6 months later the guy sends half the school a emal telling them to go recrute for him

copy of the letter:

Hey guys,
 Get your recruiting hats on, for the months of August and September membership to join AITP has been reduced to $25! I had a few people ask me the last couple times I was on campus last week about the cost, so there are people interested. Lets go bring them in and show them what AITP is about :)


I&#39;ll be on Campus Monday if anyone needs to see me, or talk to me about AITP and as always, if you need to get in touch with me that badly, just call me. 336.456.9126

Jason

------------------------------------------

so I do a &quot;rely all&quot; which sends it to ever one that messgae was sent to my reply:

No point in recruting people to a club that barly exists, come pay us $25  to fundrase &lt;.&lt; 

------------------------------------------

then Jason replys:

Thats exactly the attitude that keeps the club from doing anything A.J, well done.

----------------------------------------------

So now comes the admusing part were the teacher that administrates are studet club over the student president messages me:

AJ, 
You make a good point. A club is only as good as its leaders. Would you like to step up to the plate and take on a leadership role? Its hard to get participation in the summer, but fall is better for clubs. Any other suggestions from the group?

----------------------------------------------
of course I tell her that i would be honnored to lead. ( YAY pride )

so now I&#39;m planning ahead of events that I plan for my chapter of AITP that has to to with IT or just computers in general that will make us money

such as

1.) Have a IT buissness professional come in ant talk and let people come for free but offer food.

2.) Offer to fix peoples comuters

3.) Videogaming contest fee for intry.


so Please if you have any good ideas please reply to this topic</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 10 Aug 2007 10:13:49 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>General Discussion</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/taking-charge-of-aitp/131727.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Taking Charge of AITP</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@newguy45 newguy45]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/newguy45">@newguy45</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Lol,  yea im American I just gradurated a few years early. AITP, is a group of geeks doing geek stuff. Looks good on resume is all.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/taking-charge-of-aitp/131727/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/taking-charge-of-aitp/131727/5</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 Aug 2007 10:13:49 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-131727-5</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/taking-charge-of-aitp/131727.rss">Taking Charge of AITP</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Taking Charge of AITP</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@xxlegitxx xxlegitxx]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/xxlegitxx">@xxlegitxx</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote no-group" data-post="3" data-topic="131727">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/newguy45/40/5_6259e4fa9dfe0dec282fb0955bb1974c.png" class="avatar"> newguy45:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>yea thats AITP. but thats not what im asking lol</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>No I was just wondering throughout the entire thing what the hell AITP is.  And why you’re in college… until I realized you’re not American.</p>
<p>I think the best fundraiser is the gaming tournament 50-50.  50% goes towards 1st, 2nd, and 3rd prize.  The other 50% goes to AITP.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/taking-charge-of-aitp/131727/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/taking-charge-of-aitp/131727/4</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 Aug 2007 01:06:57 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-131727-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/taking-charge-of-aitp/131727.rss">Taking Charge of AITP</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Taking Charge of AITP</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@newguy45 newguy45]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/newguy45">@newguy45</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>yea thats AITP. but thats not what im asking lol</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/taking-charge-of-aitp/131727/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/taking-charge-of-aitp/131727/3</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 09 Aug 2007 23:21:32 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-131727-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/taking-charge-of-aitp/131727.rss">Taking Charge of AITP</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Taking Charge of AITP</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@xxlegitxx xxlegitxx]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/xxlegitxx">@xxlegitxx</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <blockquote>The Association of Information Technology Professionals (AITP) offers opportunities for Information Technology (IT) leadership and education through partnerships with industry, government and academia. AITP provides quality IT related education, information on relevant IT issues and forums for networking with experienced peers and other IT professionals for nearly 9,000 members. AITP is the Information Technology professional organization of choice for providing leadership opportunities, professional development and personal growth. Its headqurters are at 401 N. Michigan Avenue, Chicago, Illinois</blockquote>
From Wikipedia... is this what you're talking about?
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/taking-charge-of-aitp/131727/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/taking-charge-of-aitp/131727/2</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 09 Aug 2007 22:25:03 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-131727-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/taking-charge-of-aitp/131727.rss">Taking Charge of AITP</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Taking Charge of AITP</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@newguy45 newguy45]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/newguy45">@newguy45</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>This topic is just for me to extract some usefull events that I may plan for my college’s AITP chapter. I do consiter this my homework more than a general discusion.</p>
<p>Befor I go about asking the extreamely nice and helpful rs cheating community wich i have been a part of sence kaitnieks about event ideas ill explane why this is important to me.</p>
<p>The current AITP presedent at my college has been running are chapter into the ground. All we have done for the past 11 months is fundraise. Finnaly when we have adequate funds to take a field trip I was not eligible to go because I was 16. Now, I understand the difficulys my age caused for them but, they could have ttold me before I sold 400 hotdogs I had bought myself for them. So now that I’ve spent the $35 fee to join, the $100 for chips, foil, and hot dogs and another $65 for gas to haul their grill they tell me I can’t go with them to the profesional chapter AITP meeting. Aint that a ass? Today, 6 months later the guy sends half the school a emal telling them to go recrute for him</p>
<p>copy of the letter:</p>
<p>Hey guys,<br>
Get your recruiting hats on, for the months of August and September membership to join AITP has been reduced to $25! I had a few people ask me the last couple times I was on campus last week about the cost, so there are people interested. Lets go bring them in and show them what AITP is about <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=6" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
<p>I’ll be on Campus Monday if anyone needs to see me, or talk to me about AITP and as always, if you need to get in touch with me that badly, just call me. 336.456.9126</p>
<p>Jason</p>
<hr>
<p>so I do a “rely all” which sends it to ever one that messgae was sent to my reply:</p>
<p>No point in recruting people to a club that barly exists, come pay us $25  to fundrase &lt;.&lt;</p>
<hr>
<p>then Jason replys:</p>
<p>Thats exactly the attitude that keeps the club from doing anything A.J, well done.</p>
<hr>
<p>So now comes the admusing part were the teacher that administrates are studet club over the student president messages me:</p>
<p>AJ,<br>
You make a good point. A club is only as good as its leaders. Would you like to step up to the plate and take on a leadership role? Its hard to get participation in the summer, but fall is better for clubs. Any other suggestions from the group?</p>
<hr>
<p>of course I tell her that i would be honnored to lead. ( YAY pride )</p>
<p>so now I’m planning ahead of events that I plan for my chapter of AITP that has to to with IT or just computers in general that will make us money</p>
<p>such as</p>
<p>1.) Have a IT buissness professional come in ant talk and let people come for free but offer food.</p>
<p>2.) Offer to fix peoples comuters</p>
<p>3.) Videogaming contest fee for intry.</p>
<p>so Please if you have any good ideas please reply to this topic</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/taking-charge-of-aitp/131727/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/taking-charge-of-aitp/131727/1</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 09 Aug 2007 15:56:25 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-131727-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/taking-charge-of-aitp/131727.rss">Taking Charge of AITP</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
