<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Trying To Get A Shard Server Running</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/trying-to-get-a-shard-server-running/287781</link>
    <description>Hello Everyone,
  I&#39;m a noobie trying to get a server running, I like the way this whole editing and adding objects sounds with Shard, but I need a base, is their a way to get it as a base so I can start editing, run the server,and such? Anyone have a link I could use? Last question, can I add NPC&#39;s and all that stuff while I have the server running and people are playing? Appreciate your help, if you need you can IM me via MSN &quot;slayer51493@live.com&quot;

           Thanks Much,
                :cool: C. Negatory :cool:[br][br][size=1]Posted on: July 08, 2009, 09:32:34 pm[/size][hr]Whenever I run the server and I go to the address in my webbrowser that I registered with No-Ip in Safari I&#39;ll get a blank white page and in IE it will tell me &quot;Oops, broken link!&quot; or Cannot find the webpage, this thing is making me lose my sanity!</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 09 Jul 2009 02:35:57 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/trying-to-get-a-shard-server-running/287781.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Trying To Get A Shard Server Running</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@CaptainNegatory CaptainNegatory]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/captainnegatory">@CaptainNegatory</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Hello Everyone,<br>
I’m a noobie trying to get a server running, I like the way this whole editing and adding objects sounds with Shard, but I need a base, is their a way to get it as a base so I can start editing, run the server,and such? Anyone have a link I could use? Last question, can I add NPC’s and all that stuff while I have the server running and people are playing? Appreciate your help, if you need you can IM me via MSN <a>"slayer51493@live.com</a>"</p>
<pre><code>       Thanks Much,
            :cool: C. Negatory :cool:[br][br][size=1]Posted on: July 08, 2009, 09:32:34 pm[/size][hr]Whenever I run the server and I go to the address in my webbrowser that I registered with No-Ip in Safari I'll get a blank white page and in IE it will tell me "Oops, broken link!" or Cannot find the webpage, this thing is making me lose my sanity!</code></pre>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/trying-to-get-a-shard-server-running/287781/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/trying-to-get-a-shard-server-running/287781/1</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 09 Jul 2009 02:35:57 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-287781-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/trying-to-get-a-shard-server-running/287781.rss">Trying To Get A Shard Server Running</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
