<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>[317]|..Project Corruption..|</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/317-project-corruption/318365</link>
    <description>[CENTER][IMG]http://i33.photobucket.com/albums/d74/hewlett10/Logo_banner1.jpg[/img]

[B]I am Hewlett10 on the silabsoft forums aswell. If you need to contact me, my msn is: [email]j-o-s-h-o-@hotmail.co.uk[/email][/B][/CENTER]

Ok all, I have a bit of spare time on my hands and seing as my freinds server went down, i wanted to see if any of you guys where interested in making a server development team.

For some time now, i have always wanted to work in a team of mature and experienced individuals and produce a server that is successful. As i said before my friends server went down because of many reasons. I&#39;m not going to explain all of them, but i can tell you the server owner was 12 years old and didn&#39;t care. The server had an avarage of around 30 - 40 people online, and they had a fully working website and an vps.

The point that i&#39;m trying to make is the server didn&#39;t work because of the lack of maturity and commitment. Thats why i want to make a team of people that will be commited, mature and polite.

I havent decided on a source yet but depending on the kind of reply i have will depend on if it will be a server/client. We will also have a website and hopefully a vps slot and an active donation system.

My experience in servers is quite short. I have messed around with a few projects and have also co-owned a prety successful server. Although this server didn&#39;t last that long and soon went down because the hoster had personal reasons to attend to. Some of you may know that i make custom models aswell in my spare time. So some models may be custom created just for this server.

Ok, enough about me and my past experiences.

As i said before i am looking for Mature Polite and Commited individuals. Don&#39;t bother posting an application if you are 12, bad mannerd and have no experience what so ever in any of the team possitions.

[center][u]Team Possitions[/u]


[b]General Team Manager[/b][/center] [CENTER][B][U][I]- Taken[/I][/U][/B]
Will be incharge of the team with me. Almost like a co-owner. You will need experience in managment roles, and you need to be a peoples person.
[b]Server Programmer[/b]
Will be programming the server/client. You will need to be experienced in programming. Also, you need to be reliable and can work with deadlines.
[b]Sever Promoter/Advatisment[/b]
Will be incharge of getting the server &quot;Out There&quot; Using advatisment on forums/websites and can also promote the server. You need to be a peoples person.
[b]Server Administrator[/b][/center] [CENTER][B][U][I]- 1 possition left.[/I][/U][/B]
I am not going to just pick anyone for this job. I will need to be able to trust you. Also you need to have experience in working with dificult situations and you need to be generaly polite and mature.
[b]Server Moderator[/b]
Once again, I will need to be able to trust you. The moderators will work along side the administrators to maintaine the rules in the server.
[b]Website Coder/Developer[/b]
Will be incharge of the website. You will need alot of experience in HTML and other website coding languages. I&#39;m not that experienced in website developmet so i will need to be able to rely on you. 
[b]Website Manager[/b]
Will be incharge of all the contents of the website. This person needs to be able to work closley with me and also with the other website team.
[b]Website Administrator[/b]
Will mainly be incharge of the forums and keeping the website tidy and attractive.[/center]

[u]Application[/u]

-Username:
-Rl Name:
-Age:
-Do you have either Msn/Xfire/Steam?:
-Team Possition:
-Proof of experience:
-A little information about you:
-Why should i chose you?:

Ok, well i think that will be all.

I will read your applications as soon as i can.

Thank you.

[B][I]~Mr Hewlett10[/I][/B]</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 08 Dec 2009 09:41:15 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/317-project-corruption/318365.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>[317]|..Project Corruption..|</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@mrhewlett10 mrhewlett10]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/mrhewlett10">@mrhewlett10</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[CENTER]<div class="lightbox-wrapper"><a class="lightbox" href="http://i33.photobucket.com/albums/d74/hewlett10/Logo_banner1.jpg" title="Logo_banner1.jpg" rel="nofollow noopener"><img src="http://i33.photobucket.com/albums/d74/hewlett10/Logo_banner1.jpg" alt width="690" height="197"><div class="meta">
<svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-far-image svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#far-image"></use></svg><span class="filename">Logo_banner1.jpg</span><span class="informations">700×200</span><svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-discourse-expand svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#discourse-expand"></use></svg>
</div></a></div></p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">I am Hewlett10 on the silabsoft forums aswell. If you need to contact me, my msn is: <a href="mailto:j-o-s-h-o-@hotmail.co.uk" data-bbcode="true">j-o-s-h-o-@hotmail.co.uk</a></span>[/CENTER]</p>
<p>Ok all, I have a bit of spare time on my hands and seing as my freinds server went down, i wanted to see if any of you guys where interested in making a server development team.</p>
<p>For some time now, i have always wanted to work in a team of mature and experienced individuals and produce a server that is successful. As i said before my friends server went down because of many reasons. I’m not going to explain all of them, but i can tell you the server owner was 12 years old and didn’t care. The server had an avarage of around 30 - 40 people online, and they had a fully working website and an vps.</p>
<p>The point that i’m trying to make is the server didn’t work because of the lack of maturity and commitment. Thats why i want to make a team of people that will be commited, mature and polite.</p>
<p>I havent decided on a source yet but depending on the kind of reply i have will depend on if it will be a server/client. We will also have a website and hopefully a vps slot and an active donation system.</p>
<p>My experience in servers is quite short. I have messed around with a few projects and have also co-owned a prety successful server. Although this server didn’t last that long and soon went down because the hoster had personal reasons to attend to. Some of you may know that i make custom models aswell in my spare time. So some models may be custom created just for this server.</p>
<p>Ok, enough about me and my past experiences.</p>
<p>As i said before i am looking for Mature Polite and Commited individuals. Don’t bother posting an application if you are 12, bad mannerd and have no experience what so ever in any of the team possitions.</p>
<p>[center]<span class="bbcode-u">Team Possitions</span></p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">General Team Manager</span>[/center] [CENTER]<span class="bbcode-b"><span class="bbcode-u"><span class="bbcode-i">- Taken</span></span></span><br>
Will be incharge of the team with me. Almost like a co-owner. You will need experience in managment roles, and you need to be a peoples person.<br>
<span class="bbcode-b">Server Programmer</span><br>
Will be programming the server/client. You will need to be experienced in programming. Also, you need to be reliable and can work with deadlines.<br>
<span class="bbcode-b">Sever Promoter/Advatisment</span><br>
Will be incharge of getting the server “Out There” Using advatisment on forums/websites and can also promote the server. You need to be a peoples person.<br>
<span class="bbcode-b">Server Administrator</span>[/center] [CENTER]<span class="bbcode-b"><span class="bbcode-u"><span class="bbcode-i">- 1 possition left.</span></span></span><br>
I am not going to just pick anyone for this job. I will need to be able to trust you. Also you need to have experience in working with dificult situations and you need to be generaly polite and mature.<br>
<span class="bbcode-b">Server Moderator</span><br>
Once again, I will need to be able to trust you. The moderators will work along side the administrators to maintaine the rules in the server.<br>
<span class="bbcode-b">Website Coder/Developer</span><br>
Will be incharge of the website. You will need alot of experience in HTML and other website coding languages. I’m not that experienced in website developmet so i will need to be able to rely on you.<br>
<span class="bbcode-b">Website Manager</span><br>
Will be incharge of all the contents of the website. This person needs to be able to work closley with me and also with the other website team.<br>
<span class="bbcode-b">Website Administrator</span><br>
Will mainly be incharge of the forums and keeping the website tidy and attractive.[/center]</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-u">Application</span></p>
<p>-Username:<br>
-Rl Name:<br>
-Age:<br>
-Do you have either Msn/Xfire/Steam?:<br>
-Team Possition:<br>
-Proof of experience:<br>
-A little information about you:<br>
-Why should i chose you?:</p>
<p>Ok, well i think that will be all.</p>
<p>I will read your applications as soon as i can.</p>
<p>Thank you.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b"><span class="bbcode-i">~Mr Hewlett10</span></span></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/317-project-corruption/318365/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/317-project-corruption/318365/1</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 08 Dec 2009 09:41:15 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-318365-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/317-project-corruption/318365.rss">[317]|..Project Corruption..|</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
