<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Request</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/request/174892</link>
    <description>Ok, I have a request, well first if such a program does exist can some one please give me a link, second, if it doesn&#39;t, can some one make it for me? It would be fairly easy for a semi experienced coder, but I cannot do it. What I want is a program for Texas hold&#39;em, where I turn it on, hit new hand, enter my cards/the number of people/anything else that might help, then after the flop I enter those cards in, and it gives me percents of hands that I could get. like if I have 2 hearts and the flop has one heart, assuming no one else has a heart, and the turn is a heart, that leaves me with a 4% chance of getting a flush. I don&#39;t want a program that will play for me, just give me the percentages. Then I enter the turn and it gives me the percent of a chance that I will win the hand and the percent of the river being a card I need, then I enter the river and it gives me the percent of chance or w/e that I have the best hand. 

Thanks for reading my post.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 21 Jan 2008 21:34:56 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>General Programming</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/request/174892.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Request</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@R.I.P_RSC R.I.P RSC]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/r.i.p_rsc">@R.I.P_RSC</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Look here: <a href="http://www.calculatem.com" rel="nofollow noopener">http://www.calculatem.com</a> If that is not what you are looking for or if you have to pay for it just Google for odds calculator for poker.</p>
<p>Edit: a bit more searching got me this: <a href="http://www.pokercalculatoronline.com/" rel="nofollow noopener">http://www.pokercalculatoronline.com/</a> Its browser based, so no downloads needed.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/request/174892/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/request/174892/4</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jan 2008 21:34:56 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-174892-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/request/174892.rss">Request</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Request</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Hiaburi Hiaburi]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/hiaburi">@Hiaburi</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Yea, I will try it and see what I can do but I doubt I can get close to doing it, its a lot of math, and the biggest math method I ever made was a speedometer on a GTA SA private server.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/request/174892/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/request/174892/3</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jan 2008 14:15:45 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-174892-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/request/174892.rss">Request</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Request</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Exception Exception]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/exception">@Exception</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Here’s the equation I found</p>
<pre><code class="lang-auto">add/subtract the cost of my action (calling/raising/etc)
for the next opponent
sum over all possible hole cards by him; weighted by the probability of each hole
he can choose {f,c,r}
for that hole, compute his probabilities of each P(f),P(c),P(r)
branch 3 ways and sum with the weights of his probabilities of each
adjust the pot for his actions in each case
continue</code></pre>
<p>I’d do it, but I’m afraid I just don’t have the time or understanding. I’d be glad to help you out with any programming troubles if you want to take a stab at it yourself.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/request/174892/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/request/174892/2</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jan 2008 04:49:18 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-174892-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/request/174892.rss">Request</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Request</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Hiaburi Hiaburi]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/hiaburi">@Hiaburi</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Ok, I have a request, well first if such a program does exist can some one please give me a link, second, if it doesn’t, can some one make it for me? It would be fairly easy for a semi experienced coder, but I cannot do it. What I want is a program for Texas hold’em, where I turn it on, hit new hand, enter my cards/the number of people/anything else that might help, then after the flop I enter those cards in, and it gives me percents of hands that I could get. like if I have 2 hearts and the flop has one heart, assuming no one else has a heart, and the turn is a heart, that leaves me with a 4% chance of getting a flush. I don’t want a program that will play for me, just give me the percentages. Then I enter the turn and it gives me the percent of a chance that I will win the hand and the percent of the river being a card I need, then I enter the river and it gives me the percent of chance or w/e that I have the best hand.</p>
<p>Thanks for reading my post.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/request/174892/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/request/174892/1</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jan 2008 04:22:54 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-174892-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/request/174892.rss">Request</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
