<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>New RSPS Staff Management System</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-rsps-staff-management-system/459094</link>
    <description>This is my new proposed way of handling staff through an RSPS. This is more handling your staff team like you would a team of workers in the workplace and focuses on cutting out badly explained and drawn out issues. This should solve any form of tardiness due to lack of efficiency in a staff team.

Below you&#39;ll find a list of positions and their proposed spaces and roles. These are in decending order of seniority. 1 being the top, 5 being lowest. Also please bare in mind this is made for the server I&#39;m the community manager/chief of staff on at the minute, with around 130-150 players online.

[b]1 - Senior Management.[/b]
Decides all decisions and handles all serious and escalated reports and appeal systems. ALL decisions and ideas must be ran past the senior management before being put into action. This should cut out all false acts of developers. Senior Management also deal with any and all queries by users upon staff, e.g abusive remarks then hands out the decided punishment if the statement be true.

You must remember that Senior Management must work as a team or this entire system will not work.

[b]2 - Developmental Sector.[/b]
Must be fluent in the programming language of which they were originally recruited with and must not be working on any other major teams and/or projects. Must not have a problem with tight deadlines and must be a mature and trustworthy person. Good programming habits is a must, good documentation, use of conventions etc. Must also have very good grammar and punctual knowledge. Must pass all ideas and suggestions they filter from the forums on to senior management to be inspected and provided with sufficient evidence that it would benefit the server.

[b]3 - Head Of Moderation.[/b]
Has the highest amount of rights as a moderator. Controls the entire moderation team in conjunction with the Senior Management team. Must write up rotas and schedules to be passed by Senior Management and then put up months in advance for when moderators must be on the server. Of course they can come on when they wish, but between x and y hours they must be online. Leave for certain circumstances will be allowed of course. Must have great community interaction and mustn&#39;t have a problem with putting in extra work to make sure the moderation team is as efficient as it can be. ALL serious reports and reports against staff must be reviewed by the head of moderation before being passed onto Senior Management as a quality control method.

[b]4 - Senior Moderation[/b].
Senior Moderation have the second highest rights as a moderator. Moderates all aspects of the server and forums, a global moderator if you will. Must be very knowledgable about the server and have enough free time to manage around 12 hours per week on the server doing their part of the schedule. Must have very wide knowledge range concerning the players and their tendencies and how to handle things quickly and efficiently before everything gets out of hand and has to get further members of staff involved. Must handle reports against all members of the community and be prepared to pass any they believe they can&#39;t fulfil properly onto the head of moderation.

[b]5 - Junior Moderation[/b].
Junior Moderation was previously the rank of support staff, this has been scrapped and all of them promoted to moderators. These members are split into forums and in game. The forums junior moderation team must moderate the forums in their entirety and quality control ALL reports. If these members think that they have found a report that could be true, they lock the post and tell the user they have forwarded it on to the senior moderation staff. This branch just generally keep the forums nice and clean and running smoothly. The in game branch of the junior moderation team must have great presence within a community and be friendly at all times but must be able to be firm when enforcing the rules if it is needed. These moderators are the people who fix out the members in game and handle account recoveries, small outbursts and confrontations and be able to enforce the rules on their closest friends.

As I said before, this is designed for a rather large team and hasn&#39;t been put into place yet which is why I&#39;m posting it here to get your feedback and whether to make slight changes or not regarding that feedback.

Regards,
Ruby.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 09 Sep 2012 19:01:04 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-rsps-staff-management-system/459094.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>New RSPS Staff Management System</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Jaxus Jaxus]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/jaxus">@Jaxus</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I’m very strict on myself when it comes to managing the staff team or other subjects relating to that matter, so this just seems too compact.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-rsps-staff-management-system/459094/16">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-rsps-staff-management-system/459094/16</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 09 Sep 2012 19:01:04 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-459094-16</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-rsps-staff-management-system/459094.rss">New RSPS Staff Management System</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>New RSPS Staff Management System</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Ix_Soulcist_xI Soulcist]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/ix_soulcist_xi">@Ix_Soulcist_xI</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I find this to be a little bit like Battle-Scape’s management. And as said before, this seems a bit too professional for a RSPS, I have an extent on how much of a Nazi I am when managing a community.</p>
<p>Also, I keep it as simple as possible, but do like the idea mate.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-rsps-staff-management-system/459094/15">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-rsps-staff-management-system/459094/15</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 09 Sep 2012 17:17:27 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-459094-15</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-rsps-staff-management-system/459094.rss">New RSPS Staff Management System</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>New RSPS Staff Management System</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@JavaTC JavaTC]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/javatc">@JavaTC</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote" data-post="12" data-topic="459094">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/user_avatar/forum.moparisthebest.com/whackatre/40/7608_1.png" class="avatar"> Whackatre:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>rofl so many fucking comma splices ruby</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>This is moparscape, no one gives a shit about grammar considering the amount of new members who type so fucking horribly and claim to be ‘typing fast’ even though it took them 20 minutes to reply.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-rsps-staff-management-system/459094/14">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-rsps-staff-management-system/459094/14</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 09 Sep 2012 17:14:55 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-459094-14</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-rsps-staff-management-system/459094.rss">New RSPS Staff Management System</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>New RSPS Staff Management System</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@si_force Si Force]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/si_force">@si_force</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“Ruby, post:11, topic:459094”][quote author=Si Force link=topic=561999.msg4098732#msg4098732 date=1347186116]</p>
<aside class="quote">
<blockquote>
<p>I think this is too professional for the average RSPS.  Most people just host servers for fun, or for a little bit of money on the side, so they don’t need this type of system.  But if you run a server as a full time job, then I guess this would be a good way to do things.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I agree with this to be honest, with the way you have it set up with ‘rota systems’ and whatnot, you should really be paying your staff team. I couldn’t work on an RSPS that’d force its moderators to be online at certain time periods. Your junior moderator rank is overkill in my opinion, it’s not as if senior moderation can’t handle the petit arguments that pop up in the server.</p>
<p>From what I can see, this staff system will really just inflate egos as they all scrap for superiority over each other. Just my two cents. <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=5" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"><br>
[/quote]</p>
<p>Thanks for the input, Si Force. However, on Matrix we ran a form of rota system called “rounds” which was where certain moderators paired up and stayed at home to answer questions and greet players, this was hugely effective and reduced the number of spammy help topics being posted on the forums. It also improved communication between members of staff that usual wouldn’t speak to each other.[/quote]</p>
<p>Fair enough, whatever works I suppose. I do like your staff system by the way, it is organised which is essential.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-rsps-staff-management-system/459094/13">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-rsps-staff-management-system/459094/13</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 09 Sep 2012 11:16:30 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-459094-13</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-rsps-staff-management-system/459094.rss">New RSPS Staff Management System</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>New RSPS Staff Management System</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@whackatre Whackatre]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/whackatre">@whackatre</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>rofl so many fucking comma splices ruby</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-rsps-staff-management-system/459094/12">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-rsps-staff-management-system/459094/12</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 09 Sep 2012 11:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-459094-12</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-rsps-staff-management-system/459094.rss">New RSPS Staff Management System</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>New RSPS Staff Management System</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Ruby_Forums_Coder Ruby]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/ruby_forums_coder">@Ruby_Forums_Coder</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“Si Force, post:10, topic:459094”][quote author=vManlyMan link=topic=561999.msg4098619#msg4098619 date=1347163571]<br>
I think this is too professional for the average RSPS.  Most people just host servers for fun, or for a little bit of money on the side, so they don’t need this type of system.  But if you run a server as a full time job, then I guess this would be a good way to do things.<br>
[/quote]</p>
<p>I agree with this to be honest, with the way you have it set up with ‘rota systems’ and whatnot, you should really be paying your staff team. I couldn’t work on an RSPS that’d force its moderators to be online at certain time periods. Your junior moderator rank is overkill in my opinion, it’s not as if senior moderation can’t handle the petit arguments that pop up in the server.</p>
<p>From what I can see, this staff system will really just inflate egos as they all scrap for superiority over each other. Just my two cents. :)[/quote]</p>
<p>Thanks for the input, Si Force. However, on Matrix we ran a form of rota system called “rounds” which was where certain moderators paired up and stayed at home to answer questions and greet players, this was hugely effective and reduced the number of spammy help topics being posted on the forums. It also improved communication between members of staff that usual wouldn’t speak to each other.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-rsps-staff-management-system/459094/11">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-rsps-staff-management-system/459094/11</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 09 Sep 2012 10:40:03 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-459094-11</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-rsps-staff-management-system/459094.rss">New RSPS Staff Management System</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>New RSPS Staff Management System</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@si_force Si Force]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/si_force">@si_force</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote quote-modified" data-post="8" data-topic="459094">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/vmanlyman/40/5_e05bb34c421432ee4d40de30c10af3e5.png" class="avatar"> vManlyMan:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>I think this is too professional for the average RSPS.  Most people just host servers for fun, or for a little bit of money on the side, so they don’t need this type of system.  But if you run a server as a full time job, then I guess this would be a good way to do things.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I agree with this to be honest, with the way you have it set up with ‘rota systems’ and whatnot, you should really be paying your staff team. I couldn’t work on an RSPS that’d force its moderators to be online at certain time periods. Your junior moderator rank is overkill in my opinion, it’s not as if senior moderation can’t handle the petit arguments that pop up in the server.</p>
<p>From what I can see, this staff system will really just inflate egos as they all scrap for superiority over each other. Just my two cents. <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=5" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-rsps-staff-management-system/459094/10">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-rsps-staff-management-system/459094/10</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 09 Sep 2012 10:21:56 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-459094-10</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-rsps-staff-management-system/459094.rss">New RSPS Staff Management System</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>New RSPS Staff Management System</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Ruby_Forums_Coder Ruby]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/ruby_forums_coder">@Ruby_Forums_Coder</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote quote-modified" data-post="8" data-topic="459094">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/vmanlyman/40/5_e05bb34c421432ee4d40de30c10af3e5.png" class="avatar"> vManlyMan:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>I think this is too professional for the average RSPS.  Most people just host servers for fun, or for a little bit of money on the side, so they don’t need this type of system.  But if you run a server as a full time job, then I guess this would be a good way to do things.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>It isn’t a full time job or anything, I just wanted to improve my side of the server, the part that runs the staff and community.</p>
<aside class="quote" data-post="7" data-topic="459094">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/sinisoul/40/5_e05bb34c421432ee4d40de30c10af3e5.png" class="avatar"> sinisoul:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Hahaha.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Thanks sini you butthole.</p>
<p>[quote=“imsuperman05, post:6, topic:459094”]Your staff should also have no economical / material rights at all, meaning they should not be able to spawn, or tamper with their character in any way that a regular player could not do.  Staff should be a part of the player base.  It’s important, in my opinion, for the staff to be involved with the player base and not just stand around chatting with their compadres.  That’s one of the biggest problems that I see in servers nowadays.</p>
<p>It’s a good idea, but keep in mind that most of the players that will login to your server will be ranging from 8 - 16 years old.</p>
<p>Also, part of me is kinda thinking that staff, other than the founder and the main developer for obvious reasons, should not have any visible ranks.  I feel like it’s annoying, but it still does show authority…[/quote]<br>
I should’ve mentioned that the server was matrix before these guys left, it’s the original developers of that. Therefor everyone can spawn :p.</p>
<p>The only reason they have a crown is so people know who to go to if they’re new and what not.</p>
<aside class="quote quote-modified" data-post="5" data-topic="459094">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 runescape sucks:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>I would love to implement this, but the most I’ve had is 20-30 players online at once</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>You could do it in a smaller scale?</p>
<aside class="quote quote-modified" data-post="1" data-topic="459105">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/loveandpower/40/5_e05bb34c421432ee4d40de30c10af3e5.png" class="avatar">
</div>
<blockquote>
<p>it looks like a nice set up the only  drawback is that you don’t need such a  large moderation team on an rsps. Maybe if you had 1k plus members…but not 99% of the time will a server have that.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>We hit like 180 players last night. Before we split from matrix we had over a thousand. I think all in all we have around 400-500 players. And we expect to have at least two moderators on at all times.</p>
<aside class="quote" data-post="4" data-topic="459094">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/wildskiller/40/5_e05bb34c421432ee4d40de30c10af3e5.png" class="avatar"> wildskiller:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>So this is just an idea for anyone who wants a staff system?</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>You can use it if you wish, I don’t mind :p.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-rsps-staff-management-system/459094/9">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-rsps-staff-management-system/459094/9</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 09 Sep 2012 09:46:50 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-459094-9</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-rsps-staff-management-system/459094.rss">New RSPS Staff Management System</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>New RSPS Staff Management System</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@vManlyMan vManlyMan]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/vmanlyman">@vManlyMan</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I think this is too professional for the average RSPS.  Most people just host servers for fun, or for a little bit of money on the side, so they don’t need this type of system.  But if you run a server as a full time job, then I guess this would be a good way to do things.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-rsps-staff-management-system/459094/8">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-rsps-staff-management-system/459094/8</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 09 Sep 2012 04:06:11 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-459094-8</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-rsps-staff-management-system/459094.rss">New RSPS Staff Management System</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>New RSPS Staff Management System</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@sinisoul sini]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/sinisoul">@sinisoul</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Hahaha.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-rsps-staff-management-system/459094/7">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-rsps-staff-management-system/459094/7</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 09 Sep 2012 03:55:08 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-459094-7</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-rsps-staff-management-system/459094.rss">New RSPS Staff Management System</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>New RSPS Staff Management System</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@imsuperman05 imsuperman05]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/imsuperman05">@imsuperman05</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Your staff should also have no economical / material rights at all, meaning they should not be able to spawn, or tamper with their character in any way that a regular player could not do.  Staff should be a part of the player base.  It’s important, in my opinion, for the staff to be involved with the player base and not just stand around chatting with their compadres.  That’s one of the biggest problems that I see in servers nowadays.</p>
<p>It’s a good idea, but keep in mind that most of the players that will login to your server will be ranging from 8 - 16 years old.</p>
<p>Also, part of me is kinda thinking that staff, other than the founder and the main developer for obvious reasons, should not have any visible ranks.  I feel like it’s annoying, but it still does show authority…</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-rsps-staff-management-system/459094/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-rsps-staff-management-system/459094/6</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 09 Sep 2012 03:42:42 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-459094-6</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-rsps-staff-management-system/459094.rss">New RSPS Staff Management System</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>New RSPS Staff Management System</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@runescape_sucks runescape sucks]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/runescape_sucks">@runescape_sucks</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I would love to implement this, but the most I’ve had is 20-30 players online at once</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-rsps-staff-management-system/459094/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-rsps-staff-management-system/459094/5</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 09 Sep 2012 03:23:07 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-459094-5</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-rsps-staff-management-system/459094.rss">New RSPS Staff Management System</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>New RSPS Staff Management System</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@wildskiller wildskiller]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/wildskiller">@wildskiller</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>So this is just an idea for anyone who wants a staff system?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-rsps-staff-management-system/459094/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-rsps-staff-management-system/459094/4</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 09 Sep 2012 02:44:46 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-459094-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-rsps-staff-management-system/459094.rss">New RSPS Staff Management System</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>New RSPS Staff Management System</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Ruby_Forums_Coder Ruby]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/ruby_forums_coder">@Ruby_Forums_Coder</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“AtomicInt_, post:2, topic:459094”]I actually really like this idea.</p>
<p>I’m going to use this if I ever get the chance too, the RSPS scene is… bleh to me now. Not very interesting anymore.[/quote]</p>
<p>Thanks for the feedback Ryley :p.</p>
<p>I feel that way too, I hate it. Hence why I’m trying to change the being a staff and community manager aspect of it by running it like I would a manager in a work place  :o</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-rsps-staff-management-system/459094/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-rsps-staff-management-system/459094/3</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 09 Sep 2012 01:54:04 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-459094-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-rsps-staff-management-system/459094.rss">New RSPS Staff Management System</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>New RSPS Staff Management System</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@ExtremeX-Scape Ryley]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/extremex-scape">@ExtremeX-Scape</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I actually really like this idea.</p>
<p>I’m going to use this if I ever get the chance too, the RSPS scene is… bleh to me now. Not very interesting anymore.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-rsps-staff-management-system/459094/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-rsps-staff-management-system/459094/2</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 09 Sep 2012 01:48:12 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-459094-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-rsps-staff-management-system/459094.rss">New RSPS Staff Management System</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>New RSPS Staff Management System</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Ruby_Forums_Coder Ruby]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/ruby_forums_coder">@Ruby_Forums_Coder</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>This is my new proposed way of handling staff through an RSPS. This is more handling your staff team like you would a team of workers in the workplace and focuses on cutting out badly explained and drawn out issues. This should solve any form of tardiness due to lack of efficiency in a staff team.</p>
<p>Below you’ll find a list of positions and their proposed spaces and roles. These are in decending order of seniority. 1 being the top, 5 being lowest. Also please bare in mind this is made for the server I’m the community manager/chief of staff on at the minute, with around 130-150 players online.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">1 - Senior Management.</span><br>
Decides all decisions and handles all serious and escalated reports and appeal systems. ALL decisions and ideas must be ran past the senior management before being put into action. This should cut out all false acts of developers. Senior Management also deal with any and all queries by users upon staff, e.g abusive remarks then hands out the decided punishment if the statement be true.</p>
<p>You must remember that Senior Management must work as a team or this entire system will not work.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">2 - Developmental Sector.</span><br>
Must be fluent in the programming language of which they were originally recruited with and must not be working on any other major teams and/or projects. Must not have a problem with tight deadlines and must be a mature and trustworthy person. Good programming habits is a must, good documentation, use of conventions etc. Must also have very good grammar and punctual knowledge. Must pass all ideas and suggestions they filter from the forums on to senior management to be inspected and provided with sufficient evidence that it would benefit the server.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">3 - Head Of Moderation.</span><br>
Has the highest amount of rights as a moderator. Controls the entire moderation team in conjunction with the Senior Management team. Must write up rotas and schedules to be passed by Senior Management and then put up months in advance for when moderators must be on the server. Of course they can come on when they wish, but between x and y hours they must be online. Leave for certain circumstances will be allowed of course. Must have great community interaction and mustn’t have a problem with putting in extra work to make sure the moderation team is as efficient as it can be. ALL serious reports and reports against staff must be reviewed by the head of moderation before being passed onto Senior Management as a quality control method.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">4 - Senior Moderation</span>.<br>
Senior Moderation have the second highest rights as a moderator. Moderates all aspects of the server and forums, a global moderator if you will. Must be very knowledgable about the server and have enough free time to manage around 12 hours per week on the server doing their part of the schedule. Must have very wide knowledge range concerning the players and their tendencies and how to handle things quickly and efficiently before everything gets out of hand and has to get further members of staff involved. Must handle reports against all members of the community and be prepared to pass any they believe they can’t fulfil properly onto the head of moderation.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">5 - Junior Moderation</span>.<br>
Junior Moderation was previously the rank of support staff, this has been scrapped and all of them promoted to moderators. These members are split into forums and in game. The forums junior moderation team must moderate the forums in their entirety and quality control ALL reports. If these members think that they have found a report that could be true, they lock the post and tell the user they have forwarded it on to the senior moderation staff. This branch just generally keep the forums nice and clean and running smoothly. The in game branch of the junior moderation team must have great presence within a community and be friendly at all times but must be able to be firm when enforcing the rules if it is needed. These moderators are the people who fix out the members in game and handle account recoveries, small outbursts and confrontations and be able to enforce the rules on their closest friends.</p>
<p>As I said before, this is designed for a rather large team and hasn’t been put into place yet which is why I’m posting it here to get your feedback and whether to make slight changes or not regarding that feedback.</p>
<p>Regards,<br>
Ruby.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-rsps-staff-management-system/459094/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-rsps-staff-management-system/459094/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 09 Sep 2012 01:36:59 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-459094-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-rsps-staff-management-system/459094.rss">New RSPS Staff Management System</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
