<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Some ES6 Macros</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/some-es6-macros/546318</link>
    <description>Since the web dev board has been a bit... boring lately, I&#39;m going to share a small project I&#39;ve been working on.

repo: https://github.com/AnthonyCalandra/ES6Macros (give me a follow if you use github!)

This is a collection of sweet.js macros I&#39;ve been writing to help get me familiar with the upcoming ES6 syntax additions which are really cool. Basically you write ES6 code using the macros that have been provided and they compile down to ES5 code using the sweet.js compiler. I definitely recommend this fantastic library especially if you want to have fun extending JavaScript syntax. It&#39;s the same idea as macros in Scheme (maybe not as powerful but damn good enough) while being more powerful and flexible than C macros.

tyvm
PS: still lots to do so ye</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2014 03:23:43 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>General Programming</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/some-es6-macros/546318.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Some ES6 Macros</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@justaguy justaguy]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/justaguy">@justaguy</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Since the web dev board has been a bit… boring lately, I’m going to share a small project I’ve been working on.</p>
<p>repo: <a href="https://github.com/AnthonyCalandra/ES6Macros" rel="nofollow noopener">https://github.com/AnthonyCalandra/ES6Macros</a> (give me a follow if you use github!)</p>
<p>This is a collection of sweet.js macros I’ve been writing to help get me familiar with the upcoming ES6 syntax additions which are really cool. Basically you write ES6 code using the macros that have been provided and they compile down to ES5 code using the sweet.js compiler. I definitely recommend this fantastic library especially if you want to have fun extending JavaScript syntax. It’s the same idea as macros in Scheme (maybe not as powerful but damn good enough) while being more powerful and flexible than C macros.</p>
<p>tyvm<br>
PS: still lots to do so ye</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/some-es6-macros/546318/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/some-es6-macros/546318/1</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2014 03:23:43 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-546318-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/some-es6-macros/546318.rss">Some ES6 Macros</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
