<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>PHP Tutorial</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/php-tutorial/48299</link>
    <description>[b]PHP Basics[/b]

What is PHP?


in a Windows or Linux machine
    * Install PHP on a Windows or Linux machine
    * Install MySQL on a Windows or Linux machine


[b]What You Need...[/b]

This tutorial will not explain how to install PHP, MySQL, or Apache Server.

If your server supports PHP - you don&#39;t need to do anything! You do not need to compile anything or install any extra tools  - just create some .php files in your web directory - and the server will parse them for you. Most web hosts offer PHP support.

However, if your server does not support PHP, you must install PHP. Below is a link to a good tutorial from PHP.net on how to install PHP5:

[url=http://www.php.net/manual/en/install.php]http://www.php.net/manual/en/install.php[/url]
Download PHP

Download PHP for free here: [url=http://www.php.net/downloads.php]http://www.php.net/downloads.php[/url]
Download MySQL Database

Download MySQL for free here: [url=http://www.mysql.com/downloads/index.html]http://www.mysql.com/downloads/index.html[/url]
Download Apache Server

Download Apache for free here: [url=http://httpd.apache.org/download.cg]http://httpd.apache.org/download.cg[/url]

[b]PHP Syntax[/b]

A PHP scripting block always starts with &lt;?php and ends with ?&gt;. A PHP scripting block can be placed anywhere in the document.

On servers with shorthand support enabled you can start a scripting block with &lt;? and end with ?&gt;.

However, for maximum compatibility, we recommend that you use the standard form (&lt;?php) rather than the shorthand form.

[code]&lt;?php

?&gt;[/code]

A PHP file normally contains HTML tags, just like an HTML file, and some PHP scripting code.

Below, we have an example of a simple PHP script which sends the text &quot;Hello World&quot; to the browser:

[code]&lt;html&gt;
&lt;body&gt;

&lt;?php
echo &quot;Hello World&quot;;
?&gt;

&lt;/body&gt;
&lt;/html&gt;[/code]

Each code line in PHP must end with a semicolon. The semicolon is a separator and is used to distinguish one set of instructions from another.

There are two basic statements to output text with PHP: echo and print. In the example above we have used the echo statement to output the text &quot;Hello World&quot;.

[b]Comments in PHP[/b]

In PHP, we use // to make a single-line comment or /* and */ to make a large comment block.

[code]&lt;html&gt;
&lt;body&gt;

&lt;?php

//This is a comment

/*
This is
a comment
block
*/

?&gt;

&lt;/body&gt;
&lt;/html&gt;[/code]

[b]Variables in PHP[/b]

All variables in PHP start with a $ sign symbol. Variables may contain strings, numbers, or arrays.

Below, the PHP script assigns the string &quot;Hello World&quot; to a variable called $txt:

[code]&lt;html&gt;
&lt;body&gt;

&lt;?php
$txt=&quot;Hello World&quot;;
echo $txt;
?&gt;

&lt;/body&gt;
&lt;/html&gt;[/code]

To concatenate two or more variables together, use the dot (.) operator:

[code]&lt;html&gt;
&lt;body&gt;

&lt;?php
$txt1=&quot;Hello World&quot;;
$txt2=&quot;1234&quot;;
echo $txt1 . &quot; &quot; . $txt2 ;
?&gt;

&lt;/body&gt;
&lt;/html&gt;[/code]

The output of the script above will be: &quot;Hello World 1234&quot;.

[b]Conditional Statements[/b]

Very often when you write code, you want to perform different actions for different decisions.

You can use conditional statements in your code to do this.

    * if...else statement - use this statement if you want to execute a set of code when a condition is true and another if the condition is not true
    * elseif statement - is used with the if...else statement to execute a set of code if one of several condition are true

[b]The If...Else Statement[/b]

If you want to execute some code if a condition is true and another code if a condition is false, use the if....else statement.
Syntax

[code]if (condition)
  code to be executed if condition is true;
else
  code to be executed if condition is false;[/code]

[b]Example[/b]

The following example will output &quot;Have a nice weekend!&quot; if the current day is Friday, otherwise it will output &quot;Have a nice day!&quot;:

[code]&lt;html&gt;
&lt;body&gt;

&lt;?php
$d=date(&quot;D&quot;);
if ($d==&quot;Fri&quot;)
  echo &quot;Have a nice weekend!&quot;; 
else
  echo &quot;Have a nice day!&quot;; 
?&gt;

&lt;/body&gt;
&lt;/html&gt;[/code]

If more than one line should be executed if a condition is true/false, the lines should be enclosed within curly braces:

[code]&lt;html&gt;
&lt;body&gt;

&lt;?php
$d=date(&quot;D&quot;);
if ($d==&quot;Fri&quot;)
  {
  echo &quot;Hello!&lt;br /&gt;&quot;; 
  echo &quot;Have a nice weekend!&quot;;
  echo &quot;See you on Monday!&quot;;
  }
?&gt;

&lt;/body&gt;
&lt;/html&gt;[/code]

[b]The ElseIf Statement[/b]

If you want to execute some code if one of several conditions are true use the elseif statement

[b]Syntax[/b]


[code]if (condition)
  code to be executed if condition is true;
elseif (condition)
  code to be executed if condition is true;
else
  code to be executed if condition is false;[/code]

[b]Example[/b]

The following example will output &quot;Have a nice weekend!&quot; if the current day is Friday, and &quot;Have a nice Sunday!&quot; if the current day is Sunday. Otherwise it will output &quot;Have a nice day!&quot;:

[code]&lt;html&gt;
&lt;body&gt;

&lt;?php
$d=date(&quot;D&quot;);
if ($d==&quot;Fri&quot;)
  echo &quot;Have a nice weekend!&quot;; 
elseif ($d==&quot;Sun&quot;)
  echo &quot;Have a nice Sunday!&quot;; 
else
  echo &quot;Have a nice day!&quot;; 
?&gt;

&lt;/body&gt;
&lt;/html&gt;[/code]

[b]The Switch Statement[/b]

If you want to select one of many blocks of code to be executed, use the Switch statement.

The switch statement is used to avoid long blocks of if..elseif..else code.

Syntax

[code]switch (expression)
{
case label1:
  code to be executed if expression = label1;
  break;  
case label2:
  code to be executed if expression = label2;
  break;
default:
  code to be executed
  if expression is different 
  from both label1 and label2;
}[/code]

Example

This is how it works:

    * A single expression (most often a variable) is evaluated once
    * The value of the expression is compared with the values for each case in the structure
    * If there is a match, the code associated with that case is executed
    * After a code is executed, break is used to stop the code from running into the next case
    * The default statement is used if none of the cases are true

[code]&lt;html&gt;
&lt;body&gt;

&lt;?php
switch ($x)
{
case 1:
  echo &quot;Number 1&quot;;
  break;
case 2:
  echo &quot;Number 2&quot;;
  break;
case 3:
  echo &quot;Number 3&quot;;
  break;
default:
  echo &quot;No number between 1 and 3&quot;;
}
?&gt;

&lt;/body&gt;
&lt;/html&gt;[/code]

[b]What is an array?[/b]

When working with PHP, sooner or later, you might want to create many similar variables.

Instead of having many similar variables, you can store the data as elements in an array.

Each element in the array has its own ID so that it can be easily accessed.

There are three different kind of arrays:

    * Numeric array - An array with a numeric ID key
    * Associative array - An array where each ID key is associated with a value
    * Multidimensional array - An array containing one or more arrays

[b]Numeric Arrays[/b]

A numeric array stores each element with a numeric ID key.

There are different ways to create a numeric array.

[b]Example 1
[/b]
In this example the ID key is automatically assigned:

[code]$names = array(&quot;Peter&quot;,&quot;Quagmire&quot;,&quot;Joe&quot;);[/code]

[b]Example 2[/b]

In this example we assign the ID key manually:

[code]$names[0] = &quot;Peter&quot;;
$names[1] = &quot;Quagmire&quot;;
$names[2] = &quot;Joe&quot;;[/code]

The ID keys can be used in a script:

[code]&lt;?php

$names[0] = &quot;Peter&quot;;
$names[1] = &quot;Quagmire&quot;;
$names[2] = &quot;Joe&quot;;

echo $names[1] . &quot; and &quot; . $names[2] . 
&quot; are &quot;. $names[0] . &quot;&#39;s neighbors&quot;;
?&gt;
[/code]
The code above will output:

Quagmire and Joe are Peter&#39;s neighbors


[b]Associative Arrays[/b]

An associative array, each ID key is associated with a value.

When storing data about specific named values, a numerical array is not always the best way to do it.

With associative arrays we can use the values as keys and assign values to them.
Example 1

In this example we use an array to assign ages to the different persons:

[code]$ages = array(&quot;Peter&quot;=&gt;32, &quot;Quagmire&quot;=&gt;30, &quot;Joe&quot;=&gt;34);[/code]

Example 2

This example is the same as example 1, but shows a different way of creating the array:

[code]$ages[&#39;Peter&#39;] = &quot;32&quot;;
$ages[&#39;Quagmire&#39;] = &quot;30&quot;;
$ages[&#39;Joe&#39;] = &quot;34&quot;;[/code]

The ID keys can be used in a script:

[code]&lt;?php

$ages[&#39;Peter&#39;] = &quot;32&quot;;
$ages[&#39;Quagmire&#39;] = &quot;30&quot;;
$ages[&#39;Joe&#39;] = &quot;34&quot;;

echo &quot;Peter is &quot; . $ages[&#39;Peter&#39;] . &quot; years old.&quot;;
?&gt;[/code]

The code above will output:

Peter is 32 years old.


[b]Multidimensional Arrays[/b]

In a multidimensional array, each element in the main array can also be an array. And each element in the sub-array can be an array, and so on.
Example

In this example we create a multidimensional array, with automatically assigned ID keys:

[code]$families = array
(
  &quot;Griffin&quot;=&gt;array
  (
  &quot;Peter&quot;,
  &quot;Lois&quot;,
  &quot;Megan&quot;
  ),
  &quot;Quagmire&quot;=&gt;array
  (
  &quot;Glenn&quot;
  ),
  &quot;Brown&quot;=&gt;array
  (
  &quot;Cleveland&quot;,
  &quot;Loretta&quot;,
  &quot;Junior&quot;
  )
);
[/code]
The array above would look like this if written to the output:

[code]Array
(
[Griffin] =&gt; Array
  (
  [0] =&gt; Peter
  [1] =&gt; Lois
  [2] =&gt; Megan
  )
[Quagmire] =&gt; Array
  (
  [0] =&gt; Glenn
  )
[Brown] =&gt; Array
  (
  [0] =&gt; Cleveland
  [1] =&gt; Loretta
  [2] =&gt; Junior
  )
) [/code]

Looping

Very often when you write code, you want the same block of code to run a number of times. You can use looping statements in your code to perform this.

In PHP we have the following looping statements:

    * while - loops through a block of code if and as long as a specified condition is true
    * do...while - loops through a block of code once, and then repeats the loop as long as a special condition is true
    * for - loops through a block of code a specified number of times
    * foreach - loops through a block of code for each element in an array

The while Statement

The while statement will execute a block of code if and as long as a condition is true.
Syntax

while (condition)
code to be executed;

Example

The following example demonstrates a loop that will continue to run as long as the variable i is less than, or equal to 5. i will increase by 1 each time the loop runs:

[code]&lt;html&gt;
&lt;body&gt;

&lt;?php 
$i=1;
while($i&lt;=5)
  {
  echo &quot;The number is &quot; . $i . &quot;&lt;br /&gt;&quot;;
  $i++;
  }
?&gt;

&lt;/body&gt;
&lt;/html&gt;[/code]


The do...while Statement

The do...while statement will execute a block of code at least once - it then will repeat the loop as long as a condition is true.
Syntax

[code]do
{
code to be executed;
}
while (condition);[/code]

Example

The following example will increment the value of i at least once, and it will continue incrementing the variable i as long as it has a value of less than 5:

[code]&lt;html&gt;
&lt;body&gt;

&lt;?php 
$i=0;
do
  {
  $i++;
  echo &quot;The number is &quot; . $i . &quot;&lt;br /&gt;&quot;;
  }
while ($i&lt;5);
?&gt;

&lt;/body&gt;
&lt;/html&gt;[/code]


The for Statement

The for statement is used when you know how many times you want to execute a statement or a list of statements.

Syntax

[code]
for (initialization; condition; increment)
{
  code to be executed;
}
[/code]
Note: The for statement has three parameters. The first parameter initializes variables, the second parameter holds the condition, and the third parameter contains the increments required to implement the loop. If more than one variable is included in the initialization or the increment parameter, they should be separated by commas. The condition must evaluate to true or false.
Example

The following example prints the text &quot;Hello World!&quot; five times:

[code]&lt;html&gt;
&lt;body&gt;

&lt;?php
for ($i=1; $i&lt;=5; $i++)
{
  echo &quot;Hello World!&lt;br /&gt;&quot;;
}
?&gt;

&lt;/body&gt;
&lt;/html&gt;[/code]


[b]The foreach Statement[/b]

The foreach statement is used to loop through arrays.

For every loop, the value of the current array element is assigned to $value (and the array pointer is moved by one) - so on the next loop, you&#39;ll be looking at the next element.
Syntax

[code]foreach (array as value)
{
    code to be executed;
}
[/code]
[b]Example[/b]

The following example demonstrates a loop that will print the values of the given array:

[code]&lt;html&gt;
&lt;body&gt;

&lt;?php
$arr=array(&quot;one&quot;, &quot;two&quot;, &quot;three&quot;);

foreach ($arr as $value)
{
  echo &quot;Value: &quot; . $value . &quot;&lt;br /&gt;&quot;;
}
?&gt;

&lt;/body&gt;
&lt;/html&gt;[/code]
[b]
Create a PHP Function[/b]

A function is a block of code that can be executed whenever we need it.

Creating PHP functions:

    * All functions start with the word &quot;function()&quot;
    * Name the function - It should be possible to understand what the function does by its name. The name can start with a letter or underscore (not a number)
    * Add a &quot;{&quot;  - The function code starts after the opening curly brace
    * Insert the function code
    * Add a &quot;}&quot;  - The function is finished by a closing curly brace

Example

A simple function that writes my name when it is called:

[code]&lt;html&gt;
&lt;body&gt;

&lt;?php
function writeMyName()
  {
  echo &quot;Anthony Hines&quot;;
  }

writeMyName();
?&gt;

&lt;/body&gt;
&lt;/html&gt;[/code]


[b]Use a PHP Function[/b]

Now we will use the function in a PHP script:

[code]&lt;html&gt;
&lt;body&gt;

&lt;?php
function writeMyName()
  {
  echo &quot;Anthony Hines&quot;;
  }

echo &quot;Hello world!&lt;br /&gt;&quot;;
echo &quot;My name is &quot;;
writeMyName();
echo &quot;.&lt;br /&gt;That&#39;s right, &quot;;
writeMyName();
echo &quot; is my name.&quot;;
?&gt;

&lt;/body&gt;
&lt;/html&gt;[/code]

The output of the code above will be:

[code]Hello world!
My name is Anthony Hines.
That&#39;s right, Anthony Hines is my name.[/code]


[b]PHP Functions - Adding parameters[/b]

Our first function (writeMyName()) is a very simple function. It only writes a static string.

To add more functionality to a function, we can add parameters. A parameter is just like a variable.

You may have noticed the parentheses after the function name, like: writeMyName(). The parameters are specified inside the parentheses.

[b]Example 1[/b]

The following example will write different first names, but the same last name:

[code]&lt;html&gt;
&lt;body&gt;

&lt;?php
function writeMyName($fname)
  {
  echo $fname . &quot; Refsnes.&lt;br /&gt;&quot;;
  }

echo &quot;My name is &quot;;
writeMyName(&quot;Anthony Hines&quot;);

echo &quot;My name is &quot;;
writeMyName(&quot;Bryson West&quot;);

echo &quot;My name is &quot;;
writeMyName(&quot;Kim&quot;);
?&gt;

&lt;/body&gt;
&lt;/html&gt;[/code]

The output of the code above will be:

[code]My name is Anthony Hines.
My name is Bryson West.
My name is Kim.[/code]

Example 2

The following function has two parameters:

[code]&lt;html&gt;
&lt;body&gt;

&lt;?php
function writeMyName($fname,$punctuation)
  {
  echo $fname . &quot; Refsnes&quot; . $punctuation . &quot;&lt;br /&gt;&quot;;
  }

echo &quot;My name is &quot;;
writeMyName(&quot;Ant Hin&quot;,&quot;.&quot;);

echo &quot;My name is &quot;;
writeMyName(&quot;Bry Wes&quot;,&quot;!&quot;);

echo &quot;My name is &quot;;
writeMyName(&quot;kim&quot;,&quot;...&quot;);
?&gt;

&lt;/body&gt;
&lt;/html&gt;
[/code]
The output of the code above will be:

[code]My name is Anthony Hines.
My name is Bryson West!
My name is Kim Hines...[/code]

 
[b]PHP Functions - Return values[/b]

Functions can also be used to return values.
Example

[code]&lt;html&gt;
&lt;body&gt;

&lt;?php
function add($x,$y)
  {
  $total = $x + $y;
  return $total;
  }

echo &quot;1 + 16 = &quot; . add(1,16)
?&gt;

&lt;/body&gt;
&lt;/html&gt;[/code]

The output of the code above will be:

[code]1 + 16 = 17[/code]

PHP Form Handling

The most important thing to notice when dealing with HTML forms and PHP is that any form element in an HTML page will automatically be available to your PHP scripts.

Form example:

[code]&lt;html&gt;
&lt;body&gt;

&lt;form action=&quot;welcome.php&quot; method=&quot;post&quot;&gt;
Name: &lt;input type=&quot;text&quot; name=&quot;name&quot; /&gt;
Age: &lt;input type=&quot;text&quot; name=&quot;age&quot; /&gt;
&lt;input type=&quot;submit&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/form&gt;

&lt;/body&gt;
&lt;/html&gt;[/code]

The example HTML page above contains two input fields and a submit button. When the user fills in this form and click on the submit button, the form data is sent to the &quot;welcome.php&quot; file.

The &quot;welcome.php&quot; file looks like this:

[code]&lt;html&gt;
&lt;body&gt;

Welcome &lt;?php echo $_POST[&quot;name&quot;]; ?&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;
You are &lt;?php echo $_POST[&quot;age&quot;]; ?&gt; years old.

&lt;/body&gt;
&lt;/html&gt;[/code]

A sample output of the above script may be:

[code]
Welcome Anthony.
You are 28 years old.[/code]

The PHP $_GET and $_POST variables will be explained later.

[b]Form Validation[/b]

User input should be validated on the browser whenever possible (by client scripts (JavaScript)). Browser validation is faster and you reduce the server load.

You should consider using server validation if the user input will be inserted into a database. A good way to validate a form on the server is to post the form to itself, instead of jumping to a different page. The user will then get the error messages on the same page as the form. This makes it easier to discover the error.

The $_GET Variable

The $_GET variable is an array of variable names and values sent by the HTTP GET method.

The $_GET variable is used to collect values from a form with method=&quot;get&quot;. Information sent from a form with the GET method is visible to everyone (it will be displayed in the browser&#39;s address bar) and it has limits on the amount of information to send (max. 100 characters).
Example

[code]&lt;form action=&quot;welcome.php&quot; method=&quot;get&quot;&gt;
Name: &lt;input type=&quot;text&quot; name=&quot;name&quot; /&gt;
Age: &lt;input type=&quot;text&quot; name=&quot;age&quot; /&gt;
&lt;input type=&quot;submit&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/form&gt;[/code]

When the user clicks the &quot;Submit&quot; button, the URL sent could look something like this:

http://www.dastreetstyle.com/welcome.php?name=Peter&amp;age=37

The &quot;welcome.php&quot; file can now use the $_GET variable to catch the form data (notice that the names of the form fields will automatically be the ID keys in the $_GET array):

Welcome &lt;?php echo $_GET[&quot;name&quot;]; ?&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;
You are &lt;?php echo $_GET[&quot;age&quot;]; ?&gt; years old!

Did you like the tutorial? Check out the [url=http://Dastreetstyle.com]http://Dastreetstyle.com [/url]forums and register and tell me what you think of it there :P</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 11 Mar 2007 04:13:50 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>General Discussion</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/php-tutorial/48299.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>PHP Tutorial</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@ilyaostr9 io9]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/ilyaostr9">@ilyaostr9</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Ripped from W3Schools IMO.<br>
l2notleech</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/php-tutorial/48299/7">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/php-tutorial/48299/7</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 11 Mar 2007 04:13:50 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-48299-7</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/php-tutorial/48299.rss">PHP Tutorial</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>PHP Tutorial</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Cabby Cabby]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/cabby">@Cabby</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Post in Web Design.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/php-tutorial/48299/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/php-tutorial/48299/6</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 11 Mar 2007 01:51:09 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-48299-6</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/php-tutorial/48299.rss">PHP Tutorial</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>PHP Tutorial</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@xxlegitxx xxlegitxx]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/xxlegitxx">@xxlegitxx</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>ROFL. Ripped from w3schools.  Lock this please.<br>
<a href="http://www.w3schools.com/php/default.asp" class="onebox" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">http://www.w3schools.com/php/default.asp</a></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/php-tutorial/48299/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/php-tutorial/48299/5</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 19 Jan 2007 02:12:19 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-48299-5</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/php-tutorial/48299.rss">PHP Tutorial</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>PHP Tutorial</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@sicarius99 sicarius99]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/sicarius99">@sicarius99</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>i dont</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/php-tutorial/48299/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/php-tutorial/48299/4</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jan 2007 05:27:53 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-48299-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/php-tutorial/48299.rss">PHP Tutorial</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>PHP Tutorial</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@The_Un-Named The Un-Named]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/the_un-named">@The_Un-Named</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I suggest <a href="http://wampserver.com/en/index.php" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">WampServer</a> for people developing in PHP.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/php-tutorial/48299/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/php-tutorial/48299/3</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jan 2007 23:28:56 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-48299-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/php-tutorial/48299.rss">PHP Tutorial</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>PHP Tutorial</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@sicarius99 sicarius99]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/sicarius99">@sicarius99</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>wow… Did you really make that?[br][size=1]Posted on: January 16, 2007, 09:29:05 AM[/size][hr]s actuALLY REASONABLY GOOD</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/php-tutorial/48299/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/php-tutorial/48299/2</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jan 2007 22:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-48299-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/php-tutorial/48299.rss">PHP Tutorial</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>PHP Tutorial</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@damasta damasta]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/damasta">@damasta</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p><span class="bbcode-b">PHP Basics</span></p>
<p>What is PHP?</p>
<p>in a Windows or Linux machine<br>
* Install PHP on a Windows or Linux machine<br>
* Install MySQL on a Windows or Linux machine</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">What You Need…</span></p>
<p>This tutorial will not explain how to install PHP, MySQL, or Apache Server.</p>
<p>If your server supports PHP - you don’t need to do anything! You do not need to compile anything or install any extra tools  - just create some .php files in your web directory - and the server will parse them for you. Most web hosts offer PHP support.</p>
<p>However, if your server does not support PHP, you must install PHP. Below is a link to a good tutorial from <a href="http://PHP.net" rel="nofollow noopener">PHP.net</a> on how to install PHP5:</p>
<p><a href="http://www.php.net/manual/en/install.php" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">http://www.php.net/manual/en/install.php</a><br>
Download PHP</p>
<p>Download PHP for free here: <a href="http://www.php.net/downloads.php" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">http://www.php.net/downloads.php</a><br>
Download MySQL Database</p>
<p>Download MySQL for free here: <a href="http://www.mysql.com/downloads/index.html" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">http://www.mysql.com/downloads/index.html</a><br>
Download Apache Server</p>
<p>Download Apache for free here: <a href="http://httpd.apache.org/download.cg" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">http://httpd.apache.org/download.cg</a></p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">PHP Syntax</span></p>
<p>A PHP scripting block always starts with &lt;?php and ends with ?&gt;. A PHP scripting block can be placed anywhere in the document.</p>
<p>On servers with shorthand support enabled you can start a scripting block with &lt;? and end with ?&gt;.</p>
<p>However, for maximum compatibility, we recommend that you use the standard form (&lt;?php) rather than the shorthand form.</p>
<p>[code]&lt;?php</p>
<p>?&gt;[/code]</p>
<p>A PHP file normally contains HTML tags, just like an HTML file, and some PHP scripting code.</p>
<p>Below, we have an example of a simple PHP script which sends the text “Hello World” to the browser:</p>
<p>[code]</p>

&lt;?php
echo "Hello World";
?&gt;

[/code]
<p>Each code line in PHP must end with a semicolon. The semicolon is a separator and is used to distinguish one set of instructions from another.</p>
<p>There are two basic statements to output text with PHP: echo and print. In the example above we have used the echo statement to output the text “Hello World”.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Comments in PHP</span></p>
<p>In PHP, we use // to make a single-line comment or /* and */ to make a large comment block.</p>
<p>[code]</p>

&lt;?php

//This is a comment

/*
This is
a comment
block
*/

?&gt;

[/code]
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Variables in PHP</span></p>
<p>All variables in PHP start with a $ sign symbol. Variables may contain strings, numbers, or arrays.</p>
<p>Below, the PHP script assigns the string “Hello World” to a variable called $txt:</p>
<p>[code]</p>

&lt;?php
$txt="Hello World";
echo $txt;
?&gt;

[/code]
<p>To concatenate two or more variables together, use the dot (.) operator:</p>
<p>[code]</p>

&lt;?php
$txt1="Hello World";
$txt2="1234";
echo $txt1 . " " . $txt2 ;
?&gt;

[/code]
<p>The output of the script above will be: “Hello World 1234”.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Conditional Statements</span></p>
<p>Very often when you write code, you want to perform different actions for different decisions.</p>
<p>You can use conditional statements in your code to do this.</p>
<pre><code>* if...else statement - use this statement if you want to execute a set of code when a condition is true and another if the condition is not true
* elseif statement - is used with the if...else statement to execute a set of code if one of several condition are true
</code></pre>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">The If…Else Statement</span></p>
<p>If you want to execute some code if a condition is true and another code if a condition is false, use the if…else statement.<br>
Syntax</p>
<p><code>if (condition)
  code to be executed if condition is true;
else
  code to be executed if condition is false;</code></p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Example</span></p>
<p>The following example will output “Have a nice weekend!” if the current day is Friday, otherwise it will output “Have a nice day!”:</p>
<p>[code]</p>

&lt;?php
$d=date("D");
if ($d=="Fri")
  echo "Have a nice weekend!"; 
else
  echo "Have a nice day!"; 
?&gt;

[/code]
<p>If more than one line should be executed if a condition is true/false, the lines should be enclosed within curly braces:</p>
<p>[code]</p>

&lt;?php
$d=date("D");
if ($d=="Fri")
  {
  echo "Hello!<br>"; 
  echo "Have a nice weekend!";
  echo "See you on Monday!";
  }
?&gt;

[/code]
<p><span class="bbcode-b">The ElseIf Statement</span></p>
<p>If you want to execute some code if one of several conditions are true use the elseif statement</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Syntax</span></p>
<p><code>if (condition)
  code to be executed if condition is true;
elseif (condition)
  code to be executed if condition is true;
else
  code to be executed if condition is false;</code></p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Example</span></p>
<p>The following example will output “Have a nice weekend!” if the current day is Friday, and “Have a nice Sunday!” if the current day is Sunday. Otherwise it will output “Have a nice day!”:</p>
<p>[code]</p>

&lt;?php
$d=date("D");
if ($d=="Fri")
  echo "Have a nice weekend!"; 
elseif ($d=="Sun")
  echo "Have a nice Sunday!"; 
else
  echo "Have a nice day!"; 
?&gt;

[/code]
<p><span class="bbcode-b">The Switch Statement</span></p>
<p>If you want to select one of many blocks of code to be executed, use the Switch statement.</p>
<p>The switch statement is used to avoid long blocks of if…elseif…else code.</p>
<p>Syntax</p>
<p><code>switch (expression)
{
case label1:
  code to be executed if expression = label1;
  break;  
case label2:
  code to be executed if expression = label2;
  break;
default:
  code to be executed
  if expression is different 
  from both label1 and label2;
}</code></p>
<p>Example</p>
<p>This is how it works:</p>
<pre><code>* A single expression (most often a variable) is evaluated once
* The value of the expression is compared with the values for each case in the structure
* If there is a match, the code associated with that case is executed
* After a code is executed, break is used to stop the code from running into the next case
* The default statement is used if none of the cases are true
</code></pre>
<p>[code]</p>

&lt;?php
switch ($x)
{
case 1:
  echo "Number 1";
  break;
case 2:
  echo "Number 2";
  break;
case 3:
  echo "Number 3";
  break;
default:
  echo "No number between 1 and 3";
}
?&gt;

[/code]
<p><span class="bbcode-b">What is an array?</span></p>
<p>When working with PHP, sooner or later, you might want to create many similar variables.</p>
<p>Instead of having many similar variables, you can store the data as elements in an array.</p>
<p>Each element in the array has its own ID so that it can be easily accessed.</p>
<p>There are three different kind of arrays:</p>
<pre><code>* Numeric array - An array with a numeric ID key
* Associative array - An array where each ID key is associated with a value
* Multidimensional array - An array containing one or more arrays
</code></pre>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Numeric Arrays</span></p>
<p>A numeric array stores each element with a numeric ID key.</p>
<p>There are different ways to create a numeric array.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Example 1<br>
</span><br>
In this example the ID key is automatically assigned:</p>
<pre><code class="lang-auto">$names = array("Peter","Quagmire","Joe");</code></pre>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Example 2</span></p>
<p>In this example we assign the ID key manually:</p>
<p><code>$names[0] = "Peter";
$names[1] = "Quagmire";
$names[2] = "Joe";</code></p>
<p>The ID keys can be used in a script:</p>
<p>[code]&lt;?php</p>
<p>$names[0] = “Peter”;<br>
$names[1] = “Quagmire”;<br>
$names[2] = “Joe”;</p>
<p>echo $names[1] . " and " . $names[2] .<br>
" are ". $names[0] . “'s neighbors”;<br>
?&gt;<br>
[/code]<br>
The code above will output:</p>
<p>Quagmire and Joe are Peter’s neighbors</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Associative Arrays</span></p>
<p>An associative array, each ID key is associated with a value.</p>
<p>When storing data about specific named values, a numerical array is not always the best way to do it.</p>
<p>With associative arrays we can use the values as keys and assign values to them.<br>
Example 1</p>
<p>In this example we use an array to assign ages to the different persons:</p>
<pre><code class="lang-auto">$ages = array("Peter"=&gt;32, "Quagmire"=&gt;30, "Joe"=&gt;34);</code></pre>
<p>Example 2</p>
<p>This example is the same as example 1, but shows a different way of creating the array:</p>
<p><code>$ages['Peter'] = "32";
$ages['Quagmire'] = "30";
$ages['Joe'] = "34";</code></p>
<p>The ID keys can be used in a script:</p>
<p>[code]&lt;?php</p>
<p>$ages[‘Peter’] = “32”;<br>
$ages[‘Quagmire’] = “30”;<br>
$ages[‘Joe’] = “34”;</p>
<p>echo “Peter is " . $ages[‘Peter’] . " years old.”;<br>
?&gt;[/code]</p>
<p>The code above will output:</p>
<p>Peter is 32 years old.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Multidimensional Arrays</span></p>
<p>In a multidimensional array, each element in the main array can also be an array. And each element in the sub-array can be an array, and so on.<br>
Example</p>
<p>In this example we create a multidimensional array, with automatically assigned ID keys:</p>
<p><code>$families = array
(
  "Griffin"=&gt;array
  (
  "Peter",
  "Lois",
  "Megan"
  ),
  "Quagmire"=&gt;array
  (
  "Glenn"
  ),
  "Brown"=&gt;array
  (
  "Cleveland",
  "Loretta",
  "Junior"
  )
);
</code><br>
The array above would look like this if written to the output:</p>
<p><code>Array
(
[Griffin] =&gt; Array
  (
  [0] =&gt; Peter
  [1] =&gt; Lois
  [2] =&gt; Megan
  )
[Quagmire] =&gt; Array
  (
  [0] =&gt; Glenn
  )
[Brown] =&gt; Array
  (
  [0] =&gt; Cleveland
  [1] =&gt; Loretta
  [2] =&gt; Junior
  )
) </code></p>
<p>Looping</p>
<p>Very often when you write code, you want the same block of code to run a number of times. You can use looping statements in your code to perform this.</p>
<p>In PHP we have the following looping statements:</p>
<pre><code>* while - loops through a block of code if and as long as a specified condition is true
* do...while - loops through a block of code once, and then repeats the loop as long as a special condition is true
* for - loops through a block of code a specified number of times
* foreach - loops through a block of code for each element in an array
</code></pre>
<p>The while Statement</p>
<p>The while statement will execute a block of code if and as long as a condition is true.<br>
Syntax</p>
<p>while (condition)<br>
code to be executed;</p>
<p>Example</p>
<p>The following example demonstrates a loop that will continue to run as long as the variable i is less than, or equal to 5. i will increase by 1 each time the loop runs:</p>
<p>[code]</p>

&lt;?php 
$i=1;
while($i&lt;=5)
  {
  echo "The number is " . $i . "<br>";
  $i++;
  }
?&gt;

[/code]
<p>The do…while Statement</p>
<p>The do…while statement will execute a block of code at least once - it then will repeat the loop as long as a condition is true.<br>
Syntax</p>
<p><code>do
{
code to be executed;
}
while (condition);</code></p>
<p>Example</p>
<p>The following example will increment the value of i at least once, and it will continue incrementing the variable i as long as it has a value of less than 5:</p>
<p>[code]</p>

&lt;?php 
$i=0;
do
  {
  $i++;
  echo "The number is " . $i . "<br>";
  }
while ($i&lt;5);
?&gt;

[/code]
<p>The for Statement</p>
<p>The for statement is used when you know how many times you want to execute a statement or a list of statements.</p>
<p>Syntax</p>
<pre><code class="lang-auto">for (initialization; condition; increment)
{
  code to be executed;
}</code></pre>
<p>Note: The for statement has three parameters. The first parameter initializes variables, the second parameter holds the condition, and the third parameter contains the increments required to implement the loop. If more than one variable is included in the initialization or the increment parameter, they should be separated by commas. The condition must evaluate to true or false.<br>
Example</p>
<p>The following example prints the text “Hello World!” five times:</p>
<p>[code]</p>

&lt;?php
for ($i=1; $i&lt;=5; $i++)
{
  echo "Hello World!<br>";
}
?&gt;

[/code]
<p><span class="bbcode-b">The foreach Statement</span></p>
<p>The foreach statement is used to loop through arrays.</p>
<p>For every loop, the value of the current array element is assigned to $value (and the array pointer is moved by one) - so on the next loop, you’ll be looking at the next element.<br>
Syntax</p>
<p><code>foreach (array as value)
{
    code to be executed;
}
</code><br>
<span class="bbcode-b">Example</span></p>
<p>The following example demonstrates a loop that will print the values of the given array:</p>
<p>[code]</p>

&lt;?php
$arr=array("one", "two", "three");

foreach ($arr as $value)
{
  echo "Value: " . $value . "<br>";
}
?&gt;

[/code]
[b]
Create a PHP Function[/b]
<p>A function is a block of code that can be executed whenever we need it.</p>
<p>Creating PHP functions:</p>
<pre><code>* All functions start with the word "function()"
* Name the function - It should be possible to understand what the function does by its name. The name can start with a letter or underscore (not a number)
* Add a "{"  - The function code starts after the opening curly brace
* Insert the function code
* Add a "}"  - The function is finished by a closing curly brace
</code></pre>
<p>Example</p>
<p>A simple function that writes my name when it is called:</p>
<p>[code]</p>

&lt;?php
function writeMyName()
  {
  echo "Anthony Hines";
  }

writeMyName();
?&gt;

[/code]
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Use a PHP Function</span></p>
<p>Now we will use the function in a PHP script:</p>
<p>[code]</p>

&lt;?php
function writeMyName()
  {
  echo "Anthony Hines";
  }

echo "Hello world!<br>";
echo "My name is ";
writeMyName();
echo ".<br>That's right, ";
writeMyName();
echo " is my name.";
?&gt;

[/code]
<p>The output of the code above will be:</p>
<p><code>Hello world!
My name is Anthony Hines.
That's right, Anthony Hines is my name.</code></p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">PHP Functions - Adding parameters</span></p>
<p>Our first function (writeMyName()) is a very simple function. It only writes a static string.</p>
<p>To add more functionality to a function, we can add parameters. A parameter is just like a variable.</p>
<p>You may have noticed the parentheses after the function name, like: writeMyName(). The parameters are specified inside the parentheses.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Example 1</span></p>
<p>The following example will write different first names, but the same last name:</p>
<p>[code]</p>

&lt;?php
function writeMyName($fname)
  {
  echo $fname . " Refsnes.<br>";
  }

echo "My name is ";
writeMyName("Anthony Hines");

echo "My name is ";
writeMyName("Bryson West");

echo "My name is ";
writeMyName("Kim");
?&gt;

[/code]
<p>The output of the code above will be:</p>
<p><code>My name is Anthony Hines.
My name is Bryson West.
My name is Kim.</code></p>
<p>Example 2</p>
<p>The following function has two parameters:</p>
<p>[code]</p>

&lt;?php
function writeMyName($fname,$punctuation)
  {
  echo $fname . " Refsnes" . $punctuation . "<br>";
  }

echo "My name is ";
writeMyName("Ant Hin",".");

echo "My name is ";
writeMyName("Bry Wes","!");

echo "My name is ";
writeMyName("kim","...");
?&gt;


[/code]
The output of the code above will be:
<p><code>My name is Anthony Hines.
My name is Bryson West!
My name is Kim Hines...</code></p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">PHP Functions - Return values</span></p>
<p>Functions can also be used to return values.<br>
Example</p>
<p>[code]</p>

&lt;?php
function add($x,$y)
  {
  $total = $x + $y;
  return $total;
  }

echo "1 + 16 = " . add(1,16)
?&gt;

[/code]
<p>The output of the code above will be:</p>
<pre><code class="lang-auto">1 + 16 = 17</code></pre>
<p>PHP Form Handling</p>
<p>The most important thing to notice when dealing with HTML forms and PHP is that any form element in an HTML page will automatically be available to your PHP scripts.</p>
<p>Form example:</p>
<p>[code]</p>


Name: 
Age: 



[/code]
<p>The example HTML page above contains two input fields and a submit button. When the user fills in this form and click on the submit button, the form data is sent to the “welcome.php” file.</p>
<p>The “welcome.php” file looks like this:</p>
<p>[code]</p>

<p>Welcome &lt;?php echo $_POST["name"]; ?&gt;.<br><br>
You are &lt;?php echo $_POST["age"]; ?&gt; years old.</p>

[/code]
<p>A sample output of the above script may be:</p>
<p><code>
Welcome Anthony.
You are 28 years old.</code></p>
<p>The PHP $_GET and $_POST variables will be explained later.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Form Validation</span></p>
<p>User input should be validated on the browser whenever possible (by client scripts (JavaScript)). Browser validation is faster and you reduce the server load.</p>
<p>You should consider using server validation if the user input will be inserted into a database. A good way to validate a form on the server is to post the form to itself, instead of jumping to a different page. The user will then get the error messages on the same page as the form. This makes it easier to discover the error.</p>
<p>The $_GET Variable</p>
<p>The $_GET variable is an array of variable names and values sent by the HTTP GET method.</p>
<p>The $_GET variable is used to collect values from a form with method=“get”. Information sent from a form with the GET method is visible to everyone (it will be displayed in the browser’s address bar) and it has limits on the amount of information to send (max. 100 characters).<br>
Example</p>
<p>[code]<br>
Name: <br>
Age: <br>
</p>
[/code]
<p>When the user clicks the “Submit” button, the URL sent could look something like this:</p>
<p><a href="http://www.dastreetstyle.com/welcome.php?name=Peter&amp;age=37" class="onebox" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">http://www.dastreetstyle.com/welcome.php?name=Peter&amp;age=37</a></p>
<p>The “welcome.php” file can now use the $_GET variable to catch the form data (notice that the names of the form fields will automatically be the ID keys in the $_GET array):</p>
<p>Welcome &lt;?php echo $_GET["name"]; ?&gt;.<br><br>
You are &lt;?php echo $_GET["age"]; ?&gt; years old!</p>
<p>Did you like the tutorial? Check out the <a href="http://Dastreetstyle.com" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">http://Dastreetstyle.com </a>forums and register and tell me what you think of it there <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=6" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/php-tutorial/48299/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/php-tutorial/48299/1</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jan 2007 20:27:50 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-48299-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/php-tutorial/48299.rss">PHP Tutorial</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
