<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>A very flawed way to deal with random events</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/a-very-flawed-way-to-deal-with-random-events/111780</link>
    <description>I realise this is a wall of text, but I promise this eventually leads to a very unique idea. Also, I should mention I haven&#39;t played the game for a long time, so there&#39;s gaps in my knowledge.

We all know it would be useful if we could get humans to respond to random events for us. My first thoughts were that a sleepwalker system (the one where we used to type out each other&#39;s security words for accounts with 100% fatigue) would  be cool, but impossible for security reasons. For someone to address random events for you, you&#39;d have to give them almost complete control over your account, which they could abuse somehow.

But what if we instead made use of all the abusers and thieves?

If a random event completely disables an account, then to steal your items, he would have to address the random event for you. Now what if you have no items worth stealing? [b]Couldn&#39;t, in theory at least, giving your password to hackers be a useful way to deal with the random event, assuming that you can (A) manage to recover the account, and (B) manage to return to whatever you were originally automating?[/b]

Obviously this isn&#39;t a realistic solution, but it does have a lot going for it in theory.

What makes this idea almost feasible is the predictability of hackers; they will always take you to the bank. Ofcourse you will run into the occasional jerk who, after visiting the bank, takes your account on a joy ride then abandons it in a cabbage patch, but then you simply need to give the password away again.

Since there&#39;s a finite number of banks, and which bank you are at can be identified using the minimap, you can simply have a scripted response to being left in each of the different banks. This might sound like a daunting task, but with a bit of ingenuity, the difficulty could be reduce. Here&#39;s a short story illustrating one idea for a solution:

1) Script detects you are in the varrock bank. It then walks you to a point that players can teleport to. 
2) Script logs in a second helper account containing runes. This helper account teleports to the where the main account is located. If this helper account encounteres a random event, then the script logs out, and switches to another helper account in a list of available helper accounts.
3) Script transfers a few runes from the helper account to the main account. The main account teleports to a location from which it can more easily return to work.

This also has problems, for instance it requires the accounts to have a certain magic level, but the point is that there could be a solution out there.

Also, you&#39;d need to address the issue of how to advertise your password. On the one hand, spamming IRC would stop jagex from proving that you&#39;re giving away your account, but on the other hand, this would be harder to implement, and wouldn&#39;t scale well for a large number of cheaters. Simply advertising the account in game would be a very easy solution, but this would draw Jagex&#39;s attention to you.

I can&#39;t comment on how you reclaim the account. I&#39;m kind of assuming it&#39;s as easy as filling out some recovery questions, as it was in my days.

The idea of manipulating the average punny RS thief appeals to me. Who knew these minebags could actually serve some useful purpose - even if they&#39;re totally unaware of it?

Post your thoughts.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 18 Jun 2007 04:50:25 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>General Discussion</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/a-very-flawed-way-to-deal-with-random-events/111780.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>A very flawed way to deal with random events</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@The_Un-Named The Un-Named]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/the_un-named">@The_Un-Named</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Well, phew, nice read. Firstly, there are a lot of flaws with this, first being, jagex (may) disable the account if it logs in from too many computers + ip’s, this being a big problem. Secondly, unless it’s a stupidly hard random, such as a maze, witch (CAN) give stupidly ridiculous rewards(ie, one time I got 300 deaths, 1k iron arrows and some other stuff), would go to waste. Secondly, you would need a bank pin to fully protect against the other flaws(the theft of items), witch would stop a full theft but would slow each account down a lot. Thirdly, and last, it takes time for jagex to recover the account if the password is changed.</p>
<p>Overall, well thought out but not worth it. The current way the <span class="bbcode-b">only</span> updated include works is like this, it tries to solve the random(identified by your name appearing when the random says it), if it doesn’t, it simply changes player! If you think about it, this is better as it levels up 40+ accounts gradually and in time, you have an army of some of the best accounts you will find. Fawki, the creator of SRL has, if I recall, 40+ accounts, 10?+ addy miners and things like that. Check them out at <a href="http://srlforums.com" rel="nofollow noopener">srlforums.com</a>, sorry if you already know this. <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=6" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"></p>
<p>EDIT: Whoops, the link is <a href="http://srl-forums.com" rel="nofollow noopener">srl-forums.com</a>  :o</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/a-very-flawed-way-to-deal-with-random-events/111780/9">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/a-very-flawed-way-to-deal-with-random-events/111780/9</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 18 Jun 2007 04:50:25 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-111780-9</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/a-very-flawed-way-to-deal-with-random-events/111780.rss">A very flawed way to deal with random events</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>A very flawed way to deal with random events</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Tree Tree]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/tree">@Tree</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“Brazen Bull, post:4, topic:111780”][quote author=io9 link=topic=159708.msg1499183#msg1499183 date=1182019928]<br>
I do sort of agree on this, though, maybe we could do something similar to WinXP’s remote assistance, except, as soon as the computer sees the last “frame” (using logic coding), it completely removes control from the person, and gives control back to SCAR, nB, etc.<br>
[/quote]I’m confused. Did you read further than my brief mentioning of the sleepwalker system? It seems implicit in what you’re saying that we can see what’s being done with the account.</p>
<p>I’m not discussing a sleep walker like system.[/quote]</p>
<p>Don’t worry io9, i had to read it three times before i could make sense of it. <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=6" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"> The whole idea has fail all over it.[me=Tree]scratches head.[/me]</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/a-very-flawed-way-to-deal-with-random-events/111780/8">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/a-very-flawed-way-to-deal-with-random-events/111780/8</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 17 Jun 2007 08:19:31 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-111780-8</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/a-very-flawed-way-to-deal-with-random-events/111780.rss">A very flawed way to deal with random events</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>A very flawed way to deal with random events</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Pwnd Pwnd]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/pwnd">@Pwnd</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>This idea has been thought of before back in RSC days with the sleeping.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/a-very-flawed-way-to-deal-with-random-events/111780/7">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/a-very-flawed-way-to-deal-with-random-events/111780/7</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 17 Jun 2007 04:57:37 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-111780-7</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/a-very-flawed-way-to-deal-with-random-events/111780.rss">A very flawed way to deal with random events</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>A very flawed way to deal with random events</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@existingqwer existingqwer]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/existingqwer">@existingqwer</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Well thought out, but walking with SCAR is really difficult so it would be hard to get from the bank to the spot.  Also with the effort setting this up would require it would be easier just to get a team of people to work on scripting random solutions.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/a-very-flawed-way-to-deal-with-random-events/111780/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/a-very-flawed-way-to-deal-with-random-events/111780/6</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 17 Jun 2007 04:30:39 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-111780-6</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/a-very-flawed-way-to-deal-with-random-events/111780.rss">A very flawed way to deal with random events</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>A very flawed way to deal with random events</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Thebeanie TheBeanie]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/thebeanie">@Thebeanie</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>i cant be arsed reading it but if its about runescape then post it in the RUNESCAPE FORUM</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/a-very-flawed-way-to-deal-with-random-events/111780/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/a-very-flawed-way-to-deal-with-random-events/111780/5</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 17 Jun 2007 01:55:27 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-111780-5</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/a-very-flawed-way-to-deal-with-random-events/111780.rss">A very flawed way to deal with random events</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>A very flawed way to deal with random events</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Brazen_Bull Brazen Bull]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/brazen_bull">@Brazen_Bull</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“io9, post:3, topic:111780”]I do sort of agree on this, though, maybe we could do something similar to WinXP’s remote assistance, except, as soon as the computer sees the last “frame” (using logic coding), it completely removes control from the person, and gives control back to SCAR, nB, etc.[/quote]I’m confused. Did you read further than my brief mentioning of the sleepwalker system? It seems implicit in what you’re saying that we can see what’s being done with the account.</p>
<p>I’m not discussing a sleep walker like system.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/a-very-flawed-way-to-deal-with-random-events/111780/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/a-very-flawed-way-to-deal-with-random-events/111780/4</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 16 Jun 2007 18:56:51 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-111780-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/a-very-flawed-way-to-deal-with-random-events/111780.rss">A very flawed way to deal with random events</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>A very flawed way to deal with random events</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@ilyaostr9 io9]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/ilyaostr9">@ilyaostr9</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I do sort of agree on this, though, maybe we could do something similar to WinXP’s remote assistance, except, as soon as the computer sees the last “frame” (using logic coding), it completely removes control from the person, and gives control back to SCAR, nB, etc.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/a-very-flawed-way-to-deal-with-random-events/111780/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/a-very-flawed-way-to-deal-with-random-events/111780/3</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 16 Jun 2007 18:52:08 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-111780-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/a-very-flawed-way-to-deal-with-random-events/111780.rss">A very flawed way to deal with random events</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>A very flawed way to deal with random events</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Frell Frell]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/frell">@Frell</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>nicely said. no real thoughts though didnt read all, bit too busy</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/a-very-flawed-way-to-deal-with-random-events/111780/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/a-very-flawed-way-to-deal-with-random-events/111780/2</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 16 Jun 2007 18:42:11 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-111780-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/a-very-flawed-way-to-deal-with-random-events/111780.rss">A very flawed way to deal with random events</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>A very flawed way to deal with random events</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Brazen_Bull Brazen Bull]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/brazen_bull">@Brazen_Bull</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I realise this is a wall of text, but I promise this eventually leads to a very unique idea. Also, I should mention I haven’t played the game for a long time, so there’s gaps in my knowledge.</p>
<p>We all know it would be useful if we could get humans to respond to random events for us. My first thoughts were that a sleepwalker system (the one where we used to type out each other’s security words for accounts with 100% fatigue) would  be cool, but impossible for security reasons. For someone to address random events for you, you’d have to give them almost complete control over your account, which they could abuse somehow.</p>
<p>But what if we instead made use of all the abusers and thieves?</p>
<p>If a random event completely disables an account, then to steal your items, he would have to address the random event for you. Now what if you have no items worth stealing? <span class="bbcode-b">Couldn’t, in theory at least, giving your password to hackers be a useful way to deal with the random event, assuming that you can (A) manage to recover the account, and (B) manage to return to whatever you were originally automating?</span></p>
<p>Obviously this isn’t a realistic solution, but it does have a lot going for it in theory.</p>
<p>What makes this idea almost feasible is the predictability of hackers; they will always take you to the bank. Ofcourse you will run into the occasional jerk who, after visiting the bank, takes your account on a joy ride then abandons it in a cabbage patch, but then you simply need to give the password away again.</p>
<p>Since there’s a finite number of banks, and which bank you are at can be identified using the minimap, you can simply have a scripted response to being left in each of the different banks. This might sound like a daunting task, but with a bit of ingenuity, the difficulty could be reduce. Here’s a short story illustrating one idea for a solution:</p>
<ol>
<li>Script detects you are in the varrock bank. It then walks you to a point that players can teleport to.</li>
<li>Script logs in a second helper account containing runes. This helper account teleports to the where the main account is located. If this helper account encounteres a random event, then the script logs out, and switches to another helper account in a list of available helper accounts.</li>
<li>Script transfers a few runes from the helper account to the main account. The main account teleports to a location from which it can more easily return to work.</li>
</ol>
<p>This also has problems, for instance it requires the accounts to have a certain magic level, but the point is that there could be a solution out there.</p>
<p>Also, you’d need to address the issue of how to advertise your password. On the one hand, spamming IRC would stop jagex from proving that you’re giving away your account, but on the other hand, this would be harder to implement, and wouldn’t scale well for a large number of cheaters. Simply advertising the account in game would be a very easy solution, but this would draw Jagex’s attention to you.</p>
<p>I can’t comment on how you reclaim the account. I’m kind of assuming it’s as easy as filling out some recovery questions, as it was in my days.</p>
<p>The idea of manipulating the average punny RS thief appeals to me. Who knew these minebags could actually serve some useful purpose - even if they’re totally unaware of it?</p>
<p>Post your thoughts.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/a-very-flawed-way-to-deal-with-random-events/111780/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/a-very-flawed-way-to-deal-with-random-events/111780/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 16 Jun 2007 18:37:12 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-111780-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/a-very-flawed-way-to-deal-with-random-events/111780.rss">A very flawed way to deal with random events</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
