<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Stargate Resistance</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/stargate-resistance/342958</link>
    <description>A 3rd person shooter based on the popular Stargate franchise. The original development company Cheyenne Mountain went bankrupted and sold off the game to pay for debts to FireSky. The game is still being actively developed with an update being released about once a month. The game engine is based on that of the MMO Stargate Worlds which is still the property of Cheyenne Mountain and won&#39;t be released until the whole bankruptcy is resolved even though it&#39;s shelf-ready. Stargate Resistance has 4 servers which each represent a different planet. These planets are converted Stargate Worlds maps and they look very well in full detail. The game uses the Unreal3 engine which performs quite nicely. There&#39;s several gametypes amongst which Team Deathmatch where you kill members of the opposite team until you reach a score of 160, Arena where you play rounds and try to kill all opposing team members, and more, some specific to certain servers. There&#39;s 2 teams, the SGC and the System Lords, each have 3 classes. Soldier, Commando (sniper) and Scientist for the SGC. Jaffa, Goauld and Ahrak for the System Lords.

My opinion:
Great game, I don&#39;t usually play 3rd person shooters, but they did a nice job. Certainly worth it for Stargate fans like me, the worlds are pure eyecandy, they are finished in great detail and certainly honors the show in every way. It&#39;s fun to find destroyable objects in every world and for a low price of €15 it seems well worth buying it. The game is however still experiencing a couple of nasty bus that require you to suicide or even rejoin a server at times and there&#39;s a few other things going wrong there, but overall it&#39;s still a great experience.

http://store.steampowered.com/app/49700/</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 08 Jun 2010 22:06:01 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Games</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/stargate-resistance/342958.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Stargate Resistance</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@chrisn2323 chrisn2323]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/chrisn2323">@chrisn2323</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>3rd person sucks</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/stargate-resistance/342958/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/stargate-resistance/342958/3</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 08 Jun 2010 22:06:01 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-342958-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/stargate-resistance/342958.rss">Stargate Resistance</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Stargate Resistance</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Cheese_Police c|p]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/cheese_police">@Cheese_Police</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>this game is fucking crap, huge letdown.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/stargate-resistance/342958/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/stargate-resistance/342958/2</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 06 Jun 2010 17:56:24 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-342958-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/stargate-resistance/342958.rss">Stargate Resistance</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Stargate Resistance</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Freddy1990 Freddy1990]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/freddy1990">@Freddy1990</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>A 3rd person shooter based on the popular Stargate franchise. The original development company Cheyenne Mountain went bankrupted and sold off the game to pay for debts to FireSky. The game is still being actively developed with an update being released about once a month. The game engine is based on that of the MMO Stargate Worlds which is still the property of Cheyenne Mountain and won’t be released until the whole bankruptcy is resolved even though it’s shelf-ready. Stargate Resistance has 4 servers which each represent a different planet. These planets are converted Stargate Worlds maps and they look very well in full detail. The game uses the Unreal3 engine which performs quite nicely. There’s several gametypes amongst which Team Deathmatch where you kill members of the opposite team until you reach a score of 160, Arena where you play rounds and try to kill all opposing team members, and more, some specific to certain servers. There’s 2 teams, the SGC and the System Lords, each have 3 classes. Soldier, Commando (sniper) and Scientist for the SGC. Jaffa, Goauld and Ahrak for the System Lords.</p>
<p>My opinion:<br>
Great game, I don’t usually play 3rd person shooters, but they did a nice job. Certainly worth it for Stargate fans like me, the worlds are pure eyecandy, they are finished in great detail and certainly honors the show in every way. It’s fun to find destroyable objects in every world and for a low price of €15 it seems well worth buying it. The game is however still experiencing a couple of nasty bus that require you to suicide or even rejoin a server at times and there’s a few other things going wrong there, but overall it’s still a great experience.</p>
<p>          <iframe src="https://store.steampowered.com/widget/49700" frameborder="0" width="100%" height="190" seamless="seamless" sandbox="allow-same-origin allow-scripts allow-forms allow-popups allow-popups-to-escape-sandbox allow-presentation">
          </iframe>
</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/stargate-resistance/342958/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/stargate-resistance/342958/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 06 Jun 2010 12:55:48 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-342958-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/stargate-resistance/342958.rss">Stargate Resistance</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
