<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Saros - Success is our number one priority</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/saros-success-is-our-number-one-priority/550949</link>
    <description>[CENTER]

[IMG]http://i62.tinypic.com/2iu9k7n.jpg[/img]
  The next leading rsps


[url=http://www.sarosps.com]Home[/url] - [url=http://www.sarosps.com/forum]Forums[/url] - [URL=http://www.sarosps.com/forum/index.php?/forum/28-download-client//&quot;]Play Now[/URL] 
Saros is a 317 server, loading lower and higher game-frame data, At Saros we strive for perfection, we listen to everyone&#39;s feedback as even the smallest of bugs are important to fix!

Have you ever played a server for a few hours and didn&#39;t think it was the right server for you? well Saros is the right server for you! with many unique features, making the game play endless without the community being bored.

Why are we different? we may not be the best, but we are defiantly worth your time! we are different because we care about you! your game play experience, anything that&#39;s reported we will
immediately get onto fixing it, any suggestions we think is fit to be implemented into Saros we will try our hardest to get it done as soon as possible for you members to enjoy! all of our content releases will make your game play experience more enjoyable!
Constantly improving our content you will enjoy, from little features to massive improvements!

We&#39;re constantly developing the server, adding features for the members of Saros! we want to give to the community, give you a server you want to come back and play. Our staff team at Saros have experience in development, also professionalism and we&#39;re also looking to help out the community in anyway we can!

Any Saros staff member will help you out in anyway possible, from a question to helping you fight bosses in-game, anything you&#39;re stuck on we will help you! So you can enjoy your game play.

At Saros we believe that every member should enjoy their game play, no matter what. Weather you&#39;re a new member to the community or an existing member, so we offer the best user experience around.

We dedicate our time to sorting the smallest and biggest of problems out, no matter what the problem is, we will fix it so the member is happy and active with our growing and thriving community,

We&#39;re full of unique content, constantly updating our content to make your game experience even better! So why not join Saros? make friends within the community, want to best among others? come and battle your way up through the highscores being the best!

We care about your game experience, the staff members at Saros do not believe in the &#39;pay to win&#39; method. Every member has equal chances to become a wealthy member, also a strong mighty adventurer! if you contribute towards Saros you get many benefits but it does not mean you will be better than any non-contributer. This is to make all users game experience equal,fair, and enjoyable.

Most items that are in the shop for the people who contributer towards Saros are also a boss drop, so you can try your luck and camp the bosses to obtain these items!

Saros has a good economy, we manage it well, so do you like a challenge? try to be one of the wealthiest !
We make sure it&#39;s a challenge to become some what wealthy, yet it isn&#39;t to much of a challenge for the new members.

We have discontinued items, such as: basket of eggs, bunny ears, santa hats, party hats, sled.
They&#39;re all items obtained from special offers or holiday events, so they actually have a value of rarity.[/ADMIN]

[SPOILER=Saros&#39;s Team]
[SIZE=3]Matt - Founder
Jeremy - Developer[/SIZE]

[SIZE=1]*Recruiting Web &amp; Game Developers*[/SIZE]
[SIZE=1]Message Matt on the community forums[/SIZE]
[/SPOILER]

[SPOILER=Development Log]

Run energy no longer drains UNLESS you are in the wilderness. This should help a few of the skillers out quite a bit.
 
Fixed Callisto showing up as a combat stone in the wilderness that attacks players.
 
Fixed elegant pieces so they equipped correctly as well as removed the level requirements to equip black pieces.
 
Added iron arrow support to regular longbow and shortbow
 
Added the following bosses to the npc log:
 
Bandos
Zamorak
Saradomin
Armadyl
Dagannoth Supreme
Dagannoth Prime
Dagannoth Rex
Scorpia
Vet&#39;ion
Venenatis
Callisto
Chaos Elemental
Sea Troll Queen
Sea Snake
Penance Queen
Dark Beast
Abyssal Demon 
 
Added more drops to all monsters. You will obtain uncut gems, herb seeds, rune essence, and key halves from most NPC&#39;s now. If there needs to be any tweaks let the development team know!
 
Edited a few more shop prices due to this drop update.
 
Removed uncut gems, dragon leather, and rune essence from the skilling supply shop. I feel it&#39;ll make skilling more rewarding this way.
 
Removed infinity from slayer shop, and replaced (i) rings with regular ones.
 
Rewrote fishing skill so now you can no longer bank and fish at the same time. Fishing Zone is now at the fishing guild.
 
Rewrote cooking skill so it doesn&#39;t do the inventory all at once, and brings up the interface for cooking.
 
Added Minigames teleport with the option for pest control and fight caves.
 
Made firemaking move you west one spot, unless there is an object west of you, then it&#39;ll push you back east. Also you cannot light fires around or inside of banks.
 
Dagannoth kings now drop imbued rings
 
DKS will announce when you get dragon axe, and any imbued ring
 
Added in 2x exp ring for extreme donators +

Fixed shop price on blue d&#39;hide bodies
 
Lowered shop prices on mystic pieces and runes
 
Made it so if your slayer is greater than 30 you can&#39;t get an easy task, and if it&#39;s greater than 50 you can&#39;t get a medium task (this is to prevent slayer point farming).
 
 
Slayer System
 
Here is how the slayer system works:
 
All monsters give NPC HP * 50 experience per kill.
If your combat level is 3-49 you get 3 slayer points per task (8 points if wearing slayer helm)
On the completion of the task you get the npcs HP  400 bonus experience (with slayer helm you get NPC HP  250 bonus experience on top of the normal bonus)
[EXAMPLE] If you kill a hill giant with 35 hp you get 1750 xp per kill, and on task completion you get 14,000 bonus exp or 14,000 + 8,750 bonus exp with helm
 
If your combat level is 50-90 you get 5 points per task (10 if wearing slayer helm)
On the completion of the task you get NPC Hp  500 bonus experience (with slayer helm you get NPC HP  250 bonus experience on top of the normal bonus)
 
If your combat level is 91-120 you get 8 slayer points per task (13 if wearing slayer helm)
On the completion of the task you get NPC Hp  600 bonus experience (with slayer helm you get NPC HP  250 bonus experience on top of the normal bonus)
 
If your combat level is 121-126 you get 10 slayer points per task (15 if wearing slayer helm)
On the completion of the task you get NPC Hp  700 bonus experience (with slayer helm you get NPC HP  250 bonus experience on top of the normal bonus)
 
Removed the wilderness gate in level 50 wild.
 
Lowered seed prices to shop as I will be adding in seeds to all monsters.
 
Fixed several command issues. ::forum will now send you to the forums, and ::updates will send you to the updates section on forums.
 
Client Updates:
 
Fixed private message bug causing double messages from donators to other players.
 
Client Fixes:
 
Matching Item IDs client sided so they match the item ID server sided. (Please note, if you find any Dwarf Remains pick them up and let me know where you found
them so I can add the real item to the drop)
 
Made ::osrs and ::525 actually switch the gameframe.
 
Fixed clan chat errors client sided, so you can now use CC&#39;s again.
 
Added normal skin colors to the make-over mage. May add custom colors to donator zone in future.
 
Server Fixes:
 
Made Morrigan&#39;s throwing axes and javelins stackable
 
Removed the announcement when staff logs in to server.
 
Changed the default clan chat to &quot;Help&quot;
 
Changed the message received from Vannaka when you already have a slayer task.
 
Fixed several shop price issues.
 
Disabled yell messages for staff and donators logging in.
 
Lowered prayer drain at Venenatis (chance to lower it 0-15 points).
 
Added correct teleporting to dueling ring, games necklace, and amulet of glory. //TODO add fountain of rune to recharge glory
 
Boss teleports fixed, so you can tele to wildy bosses
 
Added NPC kill total + boss kill total
 
Cleaned up the quest tab
 
Dragon darts now act as a ranged weapon
 
The chest at edgevile now faces the correct direction
 
Commands are no longer case sensitive, you can type ::train or ::Train or even ::TrAiN
 
Better player following system
 
Fixed clipping through walls when attacking NPCS
 
Fixed slayer tower staircase bugs + temporary system to go through doors
 
Fixed an issue causing players to teleport after clicking a tele, then clicking away, then clicking an npc with tele options
 
Fixed skillcape shop so it autoupdates a new cape when you hit 99
 
Added a preventative measure to donator shop, if an item isn&#39;t priced by default it shows up as 10,000 instead of 0
 
Reworked the starter packages
 
Fixed issue where you continued woodcutting after clicking away from tree.
 
Added Bandos Boss kill counter + achivement points when killing 50, 175, 250, 500, 1000, 1350, and 2000 kills.
 
Started moving skill locations around
 
Fixed donator shop prices
 
Added drops to black dragons
 
Fixed hard slayer tasks, it was giving a server error and not assigning tasks correctly
 
Made thieving rates 800xp, 3000xp, 8000xp, 12500xp, and 15000xp per stall.
 
You can now cut uncut dragonstones into cut dragonstones.
 
You can now cut uncut diamonds into cut diamonds.
 
Changed donator zone location
 
Added more NPCs to the donator zone 
 
Added rocktail fishing, rune ore mining and magic tree woodcutting to the donator zone

17.04.2015

Added ::shops

Tided up the NPC spawns

Added more mystery box rewards

Added more crystal key rewards

Improved NPC drops (added more drops)

Added more bosses

Changed the donator zone location

Made the Giant Sea Snake attack-able 

Made the Sea Troll Queen multi-combat

Fixed the dragonfire shield.

Added rocktail fishing and magic trees in the donator zone

Tided up the shops.
[/SPOILER]

[SPOILER=Server Media]

* Achievements have been added, released in future updates (content release) *
[IMG]http://i58.tinypic.com/2a4uyds.png[/img][IMG]http://i61.tinypic.com/2yk0uv5.png[/img]

More total boss kills have been added

[IMG]http://i61.tinypic.com/2qdto4o.png[/img]


[IMG]http://i57.tinypic.com/35bcx7t.png[/img]
[IMG]http://i59.tinypic.com/257hpjs.png[/img]
[IMG]http://i58.tinypic.com/2m5dr1i.png[/img]
[IMG]http://i61.tinypic.com/34tevf7.png[/img]
[IMG]http://i62.tinypic.com/28grxms.png[/img]
[IMG]http://i57.tinypic.com/fkbg3l.png[/img][/SPOILER]

[SPOILER=Features] 
Achievements (added in future updates, content release)
Daily Updates
Re-worked slayer
Stable, combat system
A load of enjoyable minigames
Hosted on a server guaranteeing 99.9% uptime
Clan chat system
Team bossing abilities
Re-worked combat system
21 working skills
Cleaned NPCs
Stable Economy (correct rarity of items) 
active community
A change of osrs to 525 game-frame
10 + bosses
Pking highscores
Skill cape emotes
IPB forum software[/SPOILER]


[/CENTER]</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 13 May 2015 20:31:05 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/saros-success-is-our-number-one-priority/550949.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Saros - Success is our number one priority</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Saros Saros]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/saros">@Saros</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Thank you very much, the development log will be updated often.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/saros-success-is-our-number-one-priority/550949/25">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/saros-success-is-our-number-one-priority/550949/25</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 13 May 2015 20:31:05 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-550949-25</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/saros-success-is-our-number-one-priority/550949.rss">Saros - Success is our number one priority</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Saros - Success is our number one priority</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@WarTusk-RSPS WarTusk-RSPS]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/wartusk-rsps">@WarTusk-RSPS</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote" data-post="23" data-topic="550949">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/saros/40/5_e05bb34c421432ee4d40de30c10af3e5.png" class="avatar"> Saros:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Thank you for the positive feedback, we’re updating the server often to improve the member’s game experience.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Liking your development so far! Keep it up! <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/smiley.png?v=5" title=":smiley:" class="emoji" alt=":smiley:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/saros-success-is-our-number-one-priority/550949/24">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/saros-success-is-our-number-one-priority/550949/24</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 11 May 2015 17:40:13 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-550949-24</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/saros-success-is-our-number-one-priority/550949.rss">Saros - Success is our number one priority</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Saros - Success is our number one priority</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Saros Saros]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/saros">@Saros</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Thank you for the positive feedback, we’re updating the server often to improve the member’s game experience.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/saros-success-is-our-number-one-priority/550949/23">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/saros-success-is-our-number-one-priority/550949/23</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 11 May 2015 16:39:23 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-550949-23</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/saros-success-is-our-number-one-priority/550949.rss">Saros - Success is our number one priority</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Saros - Success is our number one priority</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@ancientscape1 ancientscape1]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/ancientscape1">@ancientscape1</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>best server i ever played guys you should join this!!!</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/saros-success-is-our-number-one-priority/550949/22">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/saros-success-is-our-number-one-priority/550949/22</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 04 May 2015 22:10:59 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-550949-22</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/saros-success-is-our-number-one-priority/550949.rss">Saros - Success is our number one priority</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Saros - Success is our number one priority</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Saros Saros]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/saros">@Saros</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Thank you, you will enjoy your game experience.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/saros-success-is-our-number-one-priority/550949/21">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/saros-success-is-our-number-one-priority/550949/21</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 30 Apr 2015 18:58:27 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-550949-21</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/saros-success-is-our-number-one-priority/550949.rss">Saros - Success is our number one priority</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Saros - Success is our number one priority</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@DevilXsummoner DevilXsummoner]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/devilxsummoner">@DevilXsummoner</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Will get on when I get home from school. 7-8 hours/</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/saros-success-is-our-number-one-priority/550949/20">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/saros-success-is-our-number-one-priority/550949/20</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 30 Apr 2015 10:56:37 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-550949-20</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/saros-success-is-our-number-one-priority/550949.rss">Saros - Success is our number one priority</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Saros - Success is our number one priority</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Saros Saros]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/saros">@Saros</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>No I have not, it is up to the moparscape community to leave a comment if they wish, so if they leave a comment that’s their choice.</p>
<p>Also I updated the development log, I have added a lot more of Saros updates to the log.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/saros-success-is-our-number-one-priority/550949/19">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/saros-success-is-our-number-one-priority/550949/19</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 27 Apr 2015 17:11:37 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-550949-19</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/saros-success-is-our-number-one-priority/550949.rss">Saros - Success is our number one priority</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Saros - Success is our number one priority</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@system system]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/system">@system</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote" data-post="16" data-topic="550949">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/saros/40/5_e05bb34c421432ee4d40de30c10af3e5.png" class="avatar"> Saros:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Thank you very much for the positive feedback, at Saros we strive to be the best.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>You’ve told these people in-game to come and comment on here/bump the topic.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/saros-success-is-our-number-one-priority/550949/18">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/saros-success-is-our-number-one-priority/550949/18</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 22 Apr 2015 22:05:55 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-550949-18</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/saros-success-is-our-number-one-priority/550949.rss">Saros - Success is our number one priority</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Saros - Success is our number one priority</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Jonathan66 Jonathan66]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/jonathan66">@Jonathan66</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I have had fun times on this server, anyone looking st this at least try the server out</p>
<p>thanks!</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/saros-success-is-our-number-one-priority/550949/17">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/saros-success-is-our-number-one-priority/550949/17</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 22 Apr 2015 21:19:58 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-550949-17</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/saros-success-is-our-number-one-priority/550949.rss">Saros - Success is our number one priority</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Saros - Success is our number one priority</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Saros Saros]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/saros">@Saros</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Thank you very much for the positive feedback, at Saros we strive to be the best.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/saros-success-is-our-number-one-priority/550949/16">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/saros-success-is-our-number-one-priority/550949/16</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 20 Apr 2015 21:55:45 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-550949-16</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/saros-success-is-our-number-one-priority/550949.rss">Saros - Success is our number one priority</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Saros - Success is our number one priority</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Jonathan66 Jonathan66]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/jonathan66">@Jonathan66</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Love the pace as well, Playing on this server has been quite an experience if you need a good paced server this is it! Recommended to join!</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/saros-success-is-our-number-one-priority/550949/15">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/saros-success-is-our-number-one-priority/550949/15</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 19 Apr 2015 19:24:04 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-550949-15</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/saros-success-is-our-number-one-priority/550949.rss">Saros - Success is our number one priority</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Saros - Success is our number one priority</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Saros Saros]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/saros">@Saros</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Thank you for the good feedback.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/saros-success-is-our-number-one-priority/550949/14">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/saros-success-is-our-number-one-priority/550949/14</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Apr 2015 20:50:02 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-550949-14</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/saros-success-is-our-number-one-priority/550949.rss">Saros - Success is our number one priority</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Saros - Success is our number one priority</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@ShadowRSPS ShadowRSPS]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/shadowrsps">@ShadowRSPS</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Been playing for a couple weeks now and enjoying the pace.  Leveling isn’t to crazy, and the double xp weekends are nice for skilling.  Owners are receptive to ideas and listen to feedback.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/saros-success-is-our-number-one-priority/550949/13">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/saros-success-is-our-number-one-priority/550949/13</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Apr 2015 12:29:40 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-550949-13</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/saros-success-is-our-number-one-priority/550949.rss">Saros - Success is our number one priority</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Saros - Success is our number one priority</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Saros Saros]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/saros">@Saros</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Thank you very much</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/saros-success-is-our-number-one-priority/550949/12">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/saros-success-is-our-number-one-priority/550949/12</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 11 Apr 2015 21:00:01 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-550949-12</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/saros-success-is-our-number-one-priority/550949.rss">Saros - Success is our number one priority</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Saros - Success is our number one priority</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Jonathan66 Jonathan66]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/jonathan66">@Jonathan66</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Good server, check it out <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=5" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/saros-success-is-our-number-one-priority/550949/11">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/saros-success-is-our-number-one-priority/550949/11</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 11 Apr 2015 17:56:37 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-550949-11</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/saros-success-is-our-number-one-priority/550949.rss">Saros - Success is our number one priority</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Saros - Success is our number one priority</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Saros Saros]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/saros">@Saros</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>This server is unique with many features, I’ll be uploading the images soon, thanks everyone.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/saros-success-is-our-number-one-priority/550949/10">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/saros-success-is-our-number-one-priority/550949/10</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 08 Apr 2015 17:52:52 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-550949-10</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/saros-success-is-our-number-one-priority/550949.rss">Saros - Success is our number one priority</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Saros - Success is our number one priority</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Jonathan66 Jonathan66]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/jonathan66">@Jonathan66</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>There is uniqueness about this server… I’ve actually played… Try it and see yourself…</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/saros-success-is-our-number-one-priority/550949/9">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/saros-success-is-our-number-one-priority/550949/9</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 08 Apr 2015 13:26:06 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-550949-9</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/saros-success-is-our-number-one-priority/550949.rss">Saros - Success is our number one priority</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Saros - Success is our number one priority</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@dwarfs222 dwarfs222]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/dwarfs222">@dwarfs222</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>If you are searching for another developer, feel free to PM me on here.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/saros-success-is-our-number-one-priority/550949/8">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/saros-success-is-our-number-one-priority/550949/8</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 08 Apr 2015 13:00:27 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-550949-8</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/saros-success-is-our-number-one-priority/550949.rss">Saros - Success is our number one priority</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Saros - Success is our number one priority</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@sorecheeny sorecheeny]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/sorecheeny">@sorecheeny</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Looks like every single Oldschool RSPS out there. Good luck anyways.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/saros-success-is-our-number-one-priority/550949/7">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/saros-success-is-our-number-one-priority/550949/7</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 08 Apr 2015 03:32:52 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-550949-7</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/saros-success-is-our-number-one-priority/550949.rss">Saros - Success is our number one priority</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Saros - Success is our number one priority</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Jonathan66 Jonathan66]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/jonathan66">@Jonathan66</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Its a good challenging server once you start</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/saros-success-is-our-number-one-priority/550949/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/saros-success-is-our-number-one-priority/550949/6</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 08 Apr 2015 01:15:33 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-550949-6</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/saros-success-is-our-number-one-priority/550949.rss">Saros - Success is our number one priority</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Saros - Success is our number one priority</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Ix_Soulcist_xI Soulcist]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/ix_soulcist_xi">@Ix_Soulcist_xI</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“popcorn57, post:4, topic:550949”][quote author=Soulcist link=topic=669863.msg4479194#msg4479194 date=1428452220]<br>
More than half of the media is showing what we already know is in a RSPS. How about showing us something that is unique? You would be better off doing this than showing us the bosses. Good luck.<br>
[/quote]</p>
<p>And how is the forums soulcist? ;)[/quote]<br>
<em>Sigh</em></p>
<p>I think we both know that answer not to mention the way the crowns are…   <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/frowning.png?v=5" title=":frowning:" class="emoji" alt=":frowning:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/saros-success-is-our-number-one-priority/550949/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/saros-success-is-our-number-one-priority/550949/5</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 08 Apr 2015 00:35:11 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-550949-5</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/saros-success-is-our-number-one-priority/550949.rss">Saros - Success is our number one priority</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Saros - Success is our number one priority</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@popcorn57 popcorn57]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/popcorn57">@popcorn57</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote" data-post="3" data-topic="550949">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 Soulcist:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>More than half of the media is showing what we already know is in a RSPS. How about showing us something that is unique? You would be better off doing this than showing us the bosses. Good luck.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>And how is the forums soulcist? <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/wink.png?v=5" title=":wink:" class="emoji" alt=":wink:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/saros-success-is-our-number-one-priority/550949/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/saros-success-is-our-number-one-priority/550949/4</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 08 Apr 2015 00:19:11 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-550949-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/saros-success-is-our-number-one-priority/550949.rss">Saros - Success is our number one priority</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Saros - Success is our number one priority</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Ix_Soulcist_xI Soulcist]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/ix_soulcist_xi">@Ix_Soulcist_xI</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>More than half of the media is showing what we already know is in a RSPS. How about showing us something that is unique? You would be better off doing this than showing us the bosses. Good luck.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/saros-success-is-our-number-one-priority/550949/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/saros-success-is-our-number-one-priority/550949/3</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 08 Apr 2015 00:17:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-550949-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/saros-success-is-our-number-one-priority/550949.rss">Saros - Success is our number one priority</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Saros - Success is our number one priority</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@codwalkers codwalkers]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/codwalkers">@codwalkers</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Looks interesting, good luck with it!</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/saros-success-is-our-number-one-priority/550949/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/saros-success-is-our-number-one-priority/550949/2</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 07 Apr 2015 23:19:07 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-550949-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/saros-success-is-our-number-one-priority/550949.rss">Saros - Success is our number one priority</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Saros - Success is our number one priority</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Saros Saros]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/saros">@Saros</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[CENTER]</p>
<p><img src="http://i62.tinypic.com/2iu9k7n.jpg" alt width="" height=""><br>
The next leading rsps</p>
<p><a href="http://www.sarosps.com" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">Home</a> - <a href="http://www.sarosps.com/forum" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">Forums</a> - [URL=http://www.sarosps.com/forum/index.php?/forum/28-download-client//"]Play Now[/URL]<br>
Saros is a 317 server, loading lower and higher game-frame data, At Saros we strive for perfection, we listen to everyone’s feedback as even the smallest of bugs are important to fix!</p>
<p>Have you ever played a server for a few hours and didn’t think it was the right server for you? well Saros is the right server for you! with many unique features, making the game play endless without the community being bored.</p>
<p>Why are we different? we may not be the best, but we are defiantly worth your time! we are different because we care about you! your game play experience, anything that’s reported we will<br>
immediately get onto fixing it, any suggestions we think is fit to be implemented into Saros we will try our hardest to get it done as soon as possible for you members to enjoy! all of our content releases will make your game play experience more enjoyable!<br>
Constantly improving our content you will enjoy, from little features to massive improvements!</p>
<p>We’re constantly developing the server, adding features for the members of Saros! we want to give to the community, give you a server you want to come back and play. Our staff team at Saros have experience in development, also professionalism and we’re also looking to help out the community in anyway we can!</p>
<p>Any Saros staff member will help you out in anyway possible, from a question to helping you fight bosses in-game, anything you’re stuck on we will help you! So you can enjoy your game play.</p>
<p>At Saros we believe that every member should enjoy their game play, no matter what. Weather you’re a new member to the community or an existing member, so we offer the best user experience around.</p>
<p>We dedicate our time to sorting the smallest and biggest of problems out, no matter what the problem is, we will fix it so the member is happy and active with our growing and thriving community,</p>
<p>We’re full of unique content, constantly updating our content to make your game experience even better! So why not join Saros? make friends within the community, want to best among others? come and battle your way up through the highscores being the best!</p>
<p>We care about your game experience, the staff members at Saros do not believe in the ‘pay to win’ method. Every member has equal chances to become a wealthy member, also a strong mighty adventurer! if you contribute towards Saros you get many benefits but it does not mean you will be better than any non-contributer. This is to make all users game experience equal,fair, and enjoyable.</p>
<p>Most items that are in the shop for the people who contributer towards Saros are also a boss drop, so you can try your luck and camp the bosses to obtain these items!</p>
<p>Saros has a good economy, we manage it well, so do you like a challenge? try to be one of the wealthiest !<br>
We make sure it’s a challenge to become some what wealthy, yet it isn’t to much of a challenge for the new members.</p>
<p>We have discontinued items, such as: basket of eggs, bunny ears, santa hats, party hats, sled.<br>
They’re all items obtained from special offers or holiday events, so they actually have a value of rarity.[/ADMIN]</p>
<p>[SPOILER=Saros’s Team]<br>
[SIZE=3]Matt - Founder<br>
Jeremy - Developer[/SIZE]</p>
<p>[SIZE=1]<em>Recruiting Web &amp; Game Developers</em>[/SIZE]<br>
[SIZE=1]Message Matt on the community forums[/SIZE]<br>
[/SPOILER]</p>
<p>[SPOILER=Development Log]</p>
<p>Run energy no longer drains UNLESS you are in the wilderness. This should help a few of the skillers out quite a bit.</p>
<p>Fixed Callisto showing up as a combat stone in the wilderness that attacks players.</p>
<p>Fixed elegant pieces so they equipped correctly as well as removed the level requirements to equip black pieces.</p>
<p>Added iron arrow support to regular longbow and shortbow</p>
<p>Added the following bosses to the npc log:</p>
<p>Bandos<br>
Zamorak<br>
Saradomin<br>
Armadyl<br>
Dagannoth Supreme<br>
Dagannoth Prime<br>
Dagannoth Rex<br>
Scorpia<br>
Vet’ion<br>
Venenatis<br>
Callisto<br>
Chaos Elemental<br>
Sea Troll Queen<br>
Sea Snake<br>
Penance Queen<br>
Dark Beast<br>
Abyssal Demon</p>
<p>Added more drops to all monsters. You will obtain uncut gems, herb seeds, rune essence, and key halves from most NPC’s now. If there needs to be any tweaks let the development team know!</p>
<p>Edited a few more shop prices due to this drop update.</p>
<p>Removed uncut gems, dragon leather, and rune essence from the skilling supply shop. I feel it’ll make skilling more rewarding this way.</p>
<p>Removed infinity from slayer shop, and replaced (i) rings with regular ones.</p>
<p>Rewrote fishing skill so now you can no longer bank and fish at the same time. Fishing Zone is now at the fishing guild.</p>
<p>Rewrote cooking skill so it doesn’t do the inventory all at once, and brings up the interface for cooking.</p>
<p>Added Minigames teleport with the option for pest control and fight caves.</p>
<p>Made firemaking move you west one spot, unless there is an object west of you, then it’ll push you back east. Also you cannot light fires around or inside of banks.</p>
<p>Dagannoth kings now drop imbued rings</p>
<p>DKS will announce when you get dragon axe, and any imbued ring</p>
<p>Added in 2x exp ring for extreme donators +</p>
<p>Fixed shop price on blue d’hide bodies</p>
<p>Lowered shop prices on mystic pieces and runes</p>
<p>Made it so if your slayer is greater than 30 you can’t get an easy task, and if it’s greater than 50 you can’t get a medium task (this is to prevent slayer point farming).</p>
<p>Slayer System</p>
<p>Here is how the slayer system works:</p>
<p>All monsters give NPC HP * 50 experience per kill.<br>
If your combat level is 3-49 you get 3 slayer points per task (8 points if wearing slayer helm)<br>
On the completion of the task you get the npcs HP  400 bonus experience (with slayer helm you get NPC HP  250 bonus experience on top of the normal bonus)<br>
[EXAMPLE] If you kill a hill giant with 35 hp you get 1750 xp per kill, and on task completion you get 14,000 bonus exp or 14,000 + 8,750 bonus exp with helm</p>
<p>If your combat level is 50-90 you get 5 points per task (10 if wearing slayer helm)<br>
On the completion of the task you get NPC Hp  500 bonus experience (with slayer helm you get NPC HP  250 bonus experience on top of the normal bonus)</p>
<p>If your combat level is 91-120 you get 8 slayer points per task (13 if wearing slayer helm)<br>
On the completion of the task you get NPC Hp  600 bonus experience (with slayer helm you get NPC HP  250 bonus experience on top of the normal bonus)</p>
<p>If your combat level is 121-126 you get 10 slayer points per task (15 if wearing slayer helm)<br>
On the completion of the task you get NPC Hp  700 bonus experience (with slayer helm you get NPC HP  250 bonus experience on top of the normal bonus)</p>
<p>Removed the wilderness gate in level 50 wild.</p>
<p>Lowered seed prices to shop as I will be adding in seeds to all monsters.</p>
<p>Fixed several command issues. ::forum will now send you to the forums, and ::updates will send you to the updates section on forums.</p>
<p>Client Updates:</p>
<p>Fixed private message bug causing double messages from donators to other players.</p>
<p>Client Fixes:</p>
<p>Matching Item IDs client sided so they match the item ID server sided. (Please note, if you find any Dwarf Remains pick them up and let me know where you found<br>
them so I can add the real item to the drop)</p>
<p>Made ::osrs and ::525 actually switch the gameframe.</p>
<p>Fixed clan chat errors client sided, so you can now use CC’s again.</p>
<p>Added normal skin colors to the make-over mage. May add custom colors to donator zone in future.</p>
<p>Server Fixes:</p>
<p>Made Morrigan’s throwing axes and javelins stackable</p>
<p>Removed the announcement when staff logs in to server.</p>
<p>Changed the default clan chat to “Help”</p>
<p>Changed the message received from Vannaka when you already have a slayer task.</p>
<p>Fixed several shop price issues.</p>
<p>Disabled yell messages for staff and donators logging in.</p>
<p>Lowered prayer drain at Venenatis (chance to lower it 0-15 points).</p>
<p>Added correct teleporting to dueling ring, games necklace, and amulet of glory. //TODO add fountain of rune to recharge glory</p>
<p>Boss teleports fixed, so you can tele to wildy bosses</p>
<p>Added NPC kill total + boss kill total</p>
<p>Cleaned up the quest tab</p>
<p>Dragon darts now act as a ranged weapon</p>
<p>The chest at edgevile now faces the correct direction</p>
<p>Commands are no longer case sensitive, you can type ::train or ::Train or even ::TrAiN</p>
<p>Better player following system</p>
<p>Fixed clipping through walls when attacking NPCS</p>
<p>Fixed slayer tower staircase bugs + temporary system to go through doors</p>
<p>Fixed an issue causing players to teleport after clicking a tele, then clicking away, then clicking an npc with tele options</p>
<p>Fixed skillcape shop so it autoupdates a new cape when you hit 99</p>
<p>Added a preventative measure to donator shop, if an item isn’t priced by default it shows up as 10,000 instead of 0</p>
<p>Reworked the starter packages</p>
<p>Fixed issue where you continued woodcutting after clicking away from tree.</p>
<p>Added Bandos Boss kill counter + achivement points when killing 50, 175, 250, 500, 1000, 1350, and 2000 kills.</p>
<p>Started moving skill locations around</p>
<p>Fixed donator shop prices</p>
<p>Added drops to black dragons</p>
<p>Fixed hard slayer tasks, it was giving a server error and not assigning tasks correctly</p>
<p>Made thieving rates 800xp, 3000xp, 8000xp, 12500xp, and 15000xp per stall.</p>
<p>You can now cut uncut dragonstones into cut dragonstones.</p>
<p>You can now cut uncut diamonds into cut diamonds.</p>
<p>Changed donator zone location</p>
<p>Added more NPCs to the donator zone</p>
<p>Added rocktail fishing, rune ore mining and magic tree woodcutting to the donator zone</p>
<p>17.04.2015</p>
<p>Added ::shops</p>
<p>Tided up the NPC spawns</p>
<p>Added more mystery box rewards</p>
<p>Added more crystal key rewards</p>
<p>Improved NPC drops (added more drops)</p>
<p>Added more bosses</p>
<p>Changed the donator zone location</p>
<p>Made the Giant Sea Snake attack-able</p>
<p>Made the Sea Troll Queen multi-combat</p>
<p>Fixed the dragonfire shield.</p>
<p>Added rocktail fishing and magic trees in the donator zone</p>
<p>Tided up the shops.<br>
[/SPOILER]</p>
<p>[SPOILER=Server Media]</p>
<ul>
<li>Achievements have been added, released in future updates (content release) *<br>
<img src="http://i58.tinypic.com/2a4uyds.png" alt width="" height=""><img src="http://i61.tinypic.com/2yk0uv5.png" alt width="" height="">
</li>
</ul>
<p>More total boss kills have been added</p>
<p><img src="http://i61.tinypic.com/2qdto4o.png" alt width="" height=""></p>
<p><img src="http://i57.tinypic.com/35bcx7t.png" alt width="" height=""><br>
<img src="http://i59.tinypic.com/257hpjs.png" alt width="" height=""><br>
<img src="http://i58.tinypic.com/2m5dr1i.png" alt width="" height=""><br>
<img src="http://i61.tinypic.com/34tevf7.png" alt width="" height=""><br>
<img src="http://i62.tinypic.com/28grxms.png" alt width="" height=""><br>
<img src="http://i57.tinypic.com/fkbg3l.png" alt width="" height="">[/SPOILER]</p>
<p>[SPOILER=Features]<br>
Achievements (added in future updates, content release)<br>
Daily Updates<br>
Re-worked slayer<br>
Stable, combat system<br>
A load of enjoyable minigames<br>
Hosted on a server guaranteeing 99.9% uptime<br>
Clan chat system<br>
Team bossing abilities<br>
Re-worked combat system<br>
21 working skills<br>
Cleaned NPCs<br>
Stable Economy (correct rarity of items)<br>
active community<br>
A change of osrs to 525 game-frame<br>
10 + bosses<br>
Pking highscores<br>
Skill cape emotes<br>
IPB forum software[/SPOILER]</p>
<p>[/CENTER]</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/saros-success-is-our-number-one-priority/550949/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/saros-success-is-our-number-one-priority/550949/1</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 07 Apr 2015 15:37:58 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-550949-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/saros-success-is-our-number-one-priority/550949.rss">Saros - Success is our number one priority</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
