<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Omg! holy shittinh fucking ahhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhh</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/omg-holy-shittinh-fucking-ahhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhh/78511</link>
    <description>


no fucxking way i got scammed i  did not get scammed 30 dollars someone [plz help me figure out this runescape stat chnager plzpzlzplzplzplzpzlzplzpzlzplzplzplz any body ill give them a free santa if they play</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 12 Apr 2007 01:22:46 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/omg-holy-shittinh-fucking-ahhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhh/78511.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Omg! holy shittinh fucking ahhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhh</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@yoyjay yoyjay...]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/yoyjay">@yoyjay</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>dude u r the best ill show u the guide Runescape Stat Changer Guide</p>
<p>Thank you for purchasing our product. We have taken a long time in making this guide user-friendly. First, we would like to explain how memory hacking works in runescape as well as other games (WoW, Lineage 2, etc)</p>
<p>We first discovered this while trying to hack World of Warcraft. We realized that buffs were client side. With that knowledge, we knew that if anything is stored client-side, then it is indeed hackable. People have been using memory sector changers for a while now. It has proven to be a very viable and mostly easy way to hack Online Games.</p>
<p>Most Games store very little information client-side for that very reason. But, for reasons I can only guess at, what they do store is often very valuable and powerful information on our computers. Take this for example:</p>
<p>In World of Warcraft, for example, both buffs and stats are currently stored client side. We guess this is because most people still use dialup, the World of Warcraft makers made the decision to store the most bandwidth-intensive properties on our computers.</p>
<p>We realized that to hack World of Warcraft buffs, for example, all we needed to do was find the correct memory address for that buff, and freeze &amp; change it. This might sound simple enough, but in the very early stages there was no guide on how to do this, only trial and error. Once we found a clear-cut way to do this, we realized we can make any buff we want to last forever (most buffs in World of Warcraft are very powerful and only last a few minutes if that). We were then able to solo the most powerful mobs and even boses in the game SOLO!</p>
<p>As you can see, this is very powerful. Imagine being healed constantly. Imagine if you drank a potion, instead of just healing you or giving you a particular buff for X amount of time, it lasted forever. Imagine having a very powerful buff on your character on the entire time you play the game.</p>
<p>Hacking the buff’s is much, I say MUCH easier than hacking stats directly. In most games, hacking/freezing buffs and changing their individual stats is 100% accomplishable.  This is why we have concluded that before we help you hack the stats DIRECTLY, you must first pass the test of hacking the buffs.</p>
<p>A little disclaimer: This isn’t just pressing a few buttons here and there, this requires work on your part. I can’t hold your hand in doing this. This is why I have included this guide to help you achieve your goals.</p>
<p>Now onto the Instructions:</p>
<p>First install the memory optimizer. The program included in this package is very memory-intensive, so you need your computer running in optimum condition before starting.</p>
<p>1)Use Ctrl+Alt+Del. End all processes that isn’t System excluding explorer.exe</p>
<ol start="2">
<li>Once everything is cleared, log into <a href="http://runescape.com" rel="nofollow noopener">runescape.com</a> and load your character.</li>
</ol>
<p>Log into your character. Turn your graphics settings to their lowest.</p>
<p>To load your game’s exe, you must do the following:</p>
<p>Load Game<br>
Login to your character<br>
Load Tsearch.exe<br>
Load Permedit.exe</p>
<p>Select Permedit and grant permissions to Tsearch</p>
<p>Open up Tsearch.</p>
<ol>
<li>
<p>Use the Arrow thing on the top left of tsearch and scroll down to the process. This will designate all searches toward Your Game.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Go back into Your game and cast any spell or buff - or attack / use something.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Quickly, go into T-search and search for “Has Changed”. Wait a few moments and click on Has Changed again.</p>
</li>
</ol>
<p>As long as the buff is on, keep searching Value has not changed. Keep on doing this. This will shorten the gigantic list of spells a little bit. The more you do it the shorter it gets.</p>
<p>Sound easy? Easier said than done. Realize that with each freeze you run the risk of crashing yourself due to some error in the memory address when you freeze. If you crash, the addresses may/may not reset. And you will have to restart all over again. Fear not, once you’ve found the right memory address, you can save it to Tsearch so you never will have to search for this again!</p>
<p>Note: Each address is different for each spell and each player that casts it. That said, an address you’ve saved to Tsearch only works for your computer, not anyone elses. That is why I have not included any memory addresses for you to use, as they would be of zero help!</p>
<p>Now onto Hacking Stats:</p>
<p>You cannot hack Core Stats directly. You must do it by changing the values of buffs and potions. You simply follow the same directions as you did for the buffs.</p>
<p>+++++++++++++++++++++++++++===</p>
<p>That is the end of the guide. Now, to understand and maximize this, you need to understand this.</p>
<p>A memory address symbolizes the spell’s activation. When the spell is active, the memory address pops up. When it is not, it disappears. You want to seek this address and when you find it, you want to freeze it. Freeze it will make it unchangeable, undisappearable - that means the spell is always active.</p>
<p>NOTE : Magnifying glass = search button</p>
<p>Need help? Contact me at <a href="mailto:redoct2k7@yahoo.com">redoct2k7@yahoo.com</a></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/omg-holy-shittinh-fucking-ahhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhh/78511/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/omg-holy-shittinh-fucking-ahhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhh/78511/3</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 12 Apr 2007 01:22:46 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-78511-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/omg-holy-shittinh-fucking-ahhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhh/78511.rss">Omg! holy shittinh fucking ahhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhh</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Omg! holy shittinh fucking ahhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhh</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@foxfire60 foxfire60]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/foxfire60">@foxfire60</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>i will help… post a picture of what shows…</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/omg-holy-shittinh-fucking-ahhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhh/78511/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/omg-holy-shittinh-fucking-ahhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhh/78511/2</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 12 Apr 2007 01:20:37 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-78511-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/omg-holy-shittinh-fucking-ahhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhh/78511.rss">Omg! holy shittinh fucking ahhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhh</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Omg! holy shittinh fucking ahhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhh</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@yoyjay yoyjay...]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/yoyjay">@yoyjay</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>no fucxking way i got scammed i  did not get scammed 30 dollars someone [plz help me figure out this runescape stat chnager plzpzlzplzplzplzpzlzplzpzlzplzplzplz any body ill give them a free santa if they play</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/omg-holy-shittinh-fucking-ahhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhh/78511/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/omg-holy-shittinh-fucking-ahhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhh/78511/1</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 12 Apr 2007 01:13:33 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-78511-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/omg-holy-shittinh-fucking-ahhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhh/78511.rss">Omg! holy shittinh fucking ahhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhh</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
