<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Adding Quest Problems</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/adding-quest-problems/527911</link>
    <description>So I added the names of the quest to the list but when I downloaded &quot;xrunes&quot; quests. For example, I copied Romeo&#39;s script and changed it to Redbeardfrank. I then replaced everything with &quot;RomeoJuliet&quot; to &quot;PiratesTreasure&quot;. I than added Red Beard Frank into the NpcHandler exactly how I named Redbeardfrank. Than I compile it, and it gives me an error about &quot;owner.setPiratesTreasure&quot; and I don&#39;t know where to go from there. I deleted everything so when I get help I can just start out fresh. Here is a picture of what I added to the list.

[img]http://s24.postimg.org/o3kzgwevp/screenshot0.png[/img]</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2013 19:14:04 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/adding-quest-problems/527911.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Adding Quest Problems</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@ALLSTAR-PK ALLSTAR-PK]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/allstar-pk">@ALLSTAR-PK</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>So I added the names of the quest to the list but when I downloaded “xrunes” quests. For example, I copied Romeo’s script and changed it to Redbeardfrank. I then replaced everything with “RomeoJuliet” to “PiratesTreasure”. I than added Red Beard Frank into the NpcHandler exactly how I named Redbeardfrank. Than I compile it, and it gives me an error about “owner.setPiratesTreasure” and I don’t know where to go from there. I deleted everything so when I get help I can just start out fresh. Here is a picture of what I added to the list.</p>
<p><img src="http://s24.postimg.org/o3kzgwevp/screenshot0.png" alt width="" height=""></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/adding-quest-problems/527911/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/adding-quest-problems/527911/1</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2013 19:14:04 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-527911-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/adding-quest-problems/527911.rss">Adding Quest Problems</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
