<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Need Help with Cache Structure</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/need-help-with-cache-structure/359191</link>
    <description>I haven&#39;t received any posts on my last topic so I&#39;ll just ask a more general question. For the past few weeks, I have been trying to build a 562 Cache Editor/Packer/Unpacker, but the confusing, obfuscated architecture of the Jagex Client is really making it difficult to accomplish. It would really help me if someone could tell me the general structure of Jagex cache files.

So far, I have discovered that the idx files (idx0 through idx28, including idx255) contain 6 byte sections, all pertaining to a specific section within the &quot;main_file_cache.dat2&quot; file. For instance, the 1407th 6-byte section of &quot;main_file_cache.idx8&quot; points to the 888th section of &quot;main_file_cache.dat2&quot;, which is the title screen for my client. Similarly, the 1241th (or around there) section of the dat2 file is the logo for my client (the one that is shown above the login interface). It would really help me if someone knew where to go from here, because at the moment, I&#39;m stuck.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 08 Sep 2010 03:21:57 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Game Development</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/need-help-with-cache-structure/359191.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Need Help with Cache Structure</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Project_Realm Project Realm]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/project_realm">@Project_Realm</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I haven’t received any posts on my last topic so I’ll just ask a more general question. For the past few weeks, I have been trying to build a 562 Cache Editor/Packer/Unpacker, but the confusing, obfuscated architecture of the Jagex Client is really making it difficult to accomplish. It would really help me if someone could tell me the general structure of Jagex cache files.</p>
<p>So far, I have discovered that the idx files (idx0 through idx28, including idx255) contain 6 byte sections, all pertaining to a specific section within the “main_file_cache.dat2” file. For instance, the 1407th 6-byte section of “main_file_cache.idx8” points to the 888th section of “main_file_cache.dat2”, which is the title screen for my client. Similarly, the 1241th (or around there) section of the dat2 file is the logo for my client (the one that is shown above the login interface). It would really help me if someone knew where to go from here, because at the moment, I’m stuck.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/need-help-with-cache-structure/359191/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/need-help-with-cache-structure/359191/1</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 08 Sep 2010 03:21:57 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-359191-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/need-help-with-cache-structure/359191.rss">Need Help with Cache Structure</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
