<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Come join Creative-scape.net! Dedicated Staff, large player base, Oldschool!</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/come-join-creative-scape-net-dedicated-staff-large-player-base-oldschool/547560</link>
    <description>[img]http://i.imgur.com/6mhqrbl.png[/img]
 
[url=http://www.creative-scape.net]Homepage[/url]
[url=http://creative-scape.net/forums]Forums[/url]  
[url=http://creative-scape.net/client/]Webclient[/url]
[url=http://creative-scape.net/client/index.php?page=download]DL Desktop Client[/url]
 
Promo Video:
 
https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=KqQoqSYgapY
 
 
Introduction:
 
Hello there, Adventurer!  Looks like you&#39;ve stumbled upon the wonderful server known as &quot;CreativeScape.&quot;  This isn&#39;t your ordinary Runescape Private Server.  CreativeScape is dedicated to bringing you back to that incredible time period that we all fell in love with, Old School Runescape.  Our main objective is to make sure the player enjoys his/herself thoroughly, so we spend hours upon hours on perfecting that old school feeling we all love so much, with a hint of creativity, hence the name &quot;Creative&quot;Scape.  Below you&#39;ll be able to enrich your mind with the incredible history behind this wonderful server, as well as some of the best features of it.  We hope you continue reading onward, because we know you won&#39;t regret it!
 
History:
 
CreativeScape originally began its journey in April 2008, following it&#39;s creation by R0cky 0wnz.  Since then, we&#39;ve moved through the years delving into many different versions, such as CreativeScape Classic, Vexillum, CreativeScape V1 and CreativeScape V2.  We are currently moving through V3, which has been running since December 2012.  Here we&#39;ve sat on the throne of private server royalty, remaining one of the #1 Old School Runescape private servers of ALL TIME.
 
 
Our MANY Features:
 
- A fun, loving, happy community of 300+, where anyone can fit in and make TONS of friends!
 
- An incredibly well balanced economy, with prices that aren&#39;t too easy to reach, yet they aren&#39;t too hard either.
 
- Every single skill from Old School Runescape (excluding construction and hunter) can be fully trained, with multiple ways to go about raising your levels.
 
- Four custom and creative quests for you to enjoy, so that you don&#39;t just finish leveling up and have nothing else to do.
 
- A FLAWLESS combat system, giving you the PERFECT old school PKing/PvMing experience.
 
- Extremely smooth chatting system, with zero delays.
 
- Fully functioning clan chat system, with working ranks, as well as an extremely charismatic ::help clan chat in game
 
- A beyond creative ::home area, which includes all of your basic shops for getting started on CreativeScape, portals for getting to the important Slayer/PvMing/PKing areas, as well as being one of the main trading areas, and most highly used banking spot in the game.
 
- A fully working webclient (the link is at the top) for players who don&#39;t enjoy a desktop/downloadable client.
 
- A fully working desktop/downloadable client (the link is at the top) for players who don&#39;t enjoy a webclient.
 
- Fully working, extremely well made Highscores, that allow you to compete with the hundreds of other players on CreativeScape for dominance.
 
- Daily community/staff held events, which help players get together and bond to become more than just a private server, but a family.
 
Extremely hard working staff team, that puts your needs above their own.  Respectful, helpful, and most importantly, fun to be around!
 
 
Pictures (PLAYER COUNT AT THE TOP ARE UP TO DATE PICTURES):
 
[IMG]http://i.imgur.com/yxpTcIg.png[/img]
[IMG]http://i.imgur.com/CD53rsq.png[/img]
[IMG]http://i.imgur.com/XsXIO9O.png[/img]
[IMG]http://i.imgur.com/OixOFIj.png[/img]
[img]http://i.imgur.com/gxgT6Cw.png[/img]  
[img]http://i.imgur.com/8D6VdV8.png[/img]  
[img]http://i.imgur.com/ykWopr4.png[/img]
 
 
 
 
So, how &#39;bout it adventurer, are you ready to dive into the adventure of a life time, meet tons of new friends, and enjoy a server that really does take you back to the glory days of Old School Runescape without 100s of customs/new school items that ruin it?  The world of CreativeScape awaits you, and so do we.  Enjoy!
 
[img]http://i.imgur.com/6mhqrbl.png[/img]
 
[url=http://www.creative-scape.net]Homepage[/url]
[url=http://creative-scape.net/forums]Forums[/url]  
[url=http://creative-scape.net/client/]Webclient[/url]
[url=http://creative-scape.net/client/index.php?page=download]DL Desktop Client[/url]</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 01 Nov 2014 02:39:05 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/come-join-creative-scape-net-dedicated-staff-large-player-base-oldschool/547560.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Come join Creative-scape.net! Dedicated Staff, large player base, Oldschool!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Bionicle Bionicle]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/bionicle">@Bionicle</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p><img src="http://i.imgur.com/6mhqrbl.png" alt width="" height=""></p>
<p><a href="http://www.creative-scape.net" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">Homepage</a><br>
<a href="http://creative-scape.net/forums" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">Forums</a><br>
<a href="http://creative-scape.net/client/" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">Webclient</a><br>
<a href="http://creative-scape.net/client/index.php?page=download" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">DL Desktop Client</a></p>
<p>Promo Video:</p>
<p><a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=KqQoqSYgapY" class="onebox" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=KqQoqSYgapY</a></p>
<p>Introduction:</p>
<p>Hello there, Adventurer!  Looks like you’ve stumbled upon the wonderful server known as “CreativeScape.”  This isn’t your ordinary Runescape Private Server.  CreativeScape is dedicated to bringing you back to that incredible time period that we all fell in love with, Old School Runescape.  Our main objective is to make sure the player enjoys his/herself thoroughly, so we spend hours upon hours on perfecting that old school feeling we all love so much, with a hint of creativity, hence the name "Creative"Scape.  Below you’ll be able to enrich your mind with the incredible history behind this wonderful server, as well as some of the best features of it.  We hope you continue reading onward, because we know you won’t regret it!</p>
<p>History:</p>
<p>CreativeScape originally began its journey in April 2008, following it’s creation by R0cky 0wnz.  Since then, we’ve moved through the years delving into many different versions, such as CreativeScape Classic, Vexillum, CreativeScape V1 and CreativeScape V2.  We are currently moving through V3, which has been running since December 2012.  Here we’ve sat on the throne of private server royalty, remaining one of the <span class="hashtag">#1</span> Old School Runescape private servers of ALL TIME.</p>
<p>Our MANY Features:</p>
<ul>
<li>
<p>A fun, loving, happy community of 300+, where anyone can fit in and make TONS of friends!</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>An incredibly well balanced economy, with prices that aren’t too easy to reach, yet they aren’t too hard either.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Every single skill from Old School Runescape (excluding construction and hunter) can be fully trained, with multiple ways to go about raising your levels.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Four custom and creative quests for you to enjoy, so that you don’t just finish leveling up and have nothing else to do.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>A FLAWLESS combat system, giving you the PERFECT old school PKing/PvMing experience.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Extremely smooth chatting system, with zero delays.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Fully functioning clan chat system, with working ranks, as well as an extremely charismatic ::help clan chat in game</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>A beyond creative ::home area, which includes all of your basic shops for getting started on CreativeScape, portals for getting to the important Slayer/PvMing/PKing areas, as well as being one of the main trading areas, and most highly used banking spot in the game.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>A fully working webclient (the link is at the top) for players who don’t enjoy a desktop/downloadable client.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>A fully working desktop/downloadable client (the link is at the top) for players who don’t enjoy a webclient.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Fully working, extremely well made Highscores, that allow you to compete with the hundreds of other players on CreativeScape for dominance.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Daily community/staff held events, which help players get together and bond to become more than just a private server, but a family.</p>
</li>
</ul>
<p>Extremely hard working staff team, that puts your needs above their own.  Respectful, helpful, and most importantly, fun to be around!</p>
<p>Pictures (PLAYER COUNT AT THE TOP ARE UP TO DATE PICTURES):</p>
<p><img src="http://i.imgur.com/yxpTcIg.png" alt width="" height=""><br>
<img src="http://i.imgur.com/CD53rsq.png" alt width="" height=""><br>
<img src="http://i.imgur.com/XsXIO9O.png" alt width="" height=""><br>
<img src="http://i.imgur.com/OixOFIj.png" alt width="" height=""><br>
<img src="http://i.imgur.com/gxgT6Cw.png" alt width="" height=""><br>
<img src="http://i.imgur.com/8D6VdV8.png" alt width="" height=""><br>
<img src="http://i.imgur.com/ykWopr4.png" alt width="" height=""></p>
<p>So, how 'bout it adventurer, are you ready to dive into the adventure of a life time, meet tons of new friends, and enjoy a server that really does take you back to the glory days of Old School Runescape without 100s of customs/new school items that ruin it?  The world of CreativeScape awaits you, and so do we.  Enjoy!</p>
<p><img src="http://i.imgur.com/6mhqrbl.png" alt width="" height=""></p>
<p><a href="http://www.creative-scape.net" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">Homepage</a><br>
<a href="http://creative-scape.net/forums" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">Forums</a><br>
<a href="http://creative-scape.net/client/" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">Webclient</a><br>
<a href="http://creative-scape.net/client/index.php?page=download" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">DL Desktop Client</a></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/come-join-creative-scape-net-dedicated-staff-large-player-base-oldschool/547560/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/come-join-creative-scape-net-dedicated-staff-large-player-base-oldschool/547560/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 01 Nov 2014 02:39:05 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-547560-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/come-join-creative-scape-net-dedicated-staff-large-player-base-oldschool/547560.rss">Come join Creative-scape.net! Dedicated Staff, large player base, Oldschool!</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
