<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Reconstruction -My Essay On Us =)</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/reconstruction-my-essay-on-us/116413</link>
    <description>Hello,

     Has anyone else noticed, or am I the only one, that the community of cheating has become in users, quantity over quality. Here is my essay, on how this can be fixed by showing how things used to be, how things are in present time, how we should be, and the path to that road. Please enjoy.


[center][b][size=24pt]Where We Were[/size][/b][/center]
In the beginning of the cheating era, no I am not saying I was there, as I doubt most of the people who are reading this were, was great. There were few people, who were all for the development and moving forward in the cheating world. Almost everyone had their own automation tool, or was a huge part in the development of someone else&#39;s. Then, after using purely coordinations was no longer an option, a new big thing came out. A young man from New Zealand came out with an ingenious idea, color picking. Without going into a history lecture, this was a humongous step forward, as there was nothing like it so far. This brought more players, as the interface was user-friendly, not saying this is a bad thing. The majority of users that came after the color picking were not there to help out the community, but to just leech off of it, using it, abusing it, and bringing much attention upon us all, metaphorically speaking, the spotlight of Jagex was on us, and there was no where to run because these &quot;leeches&quot; refused to stop. No game as big as RuneScape ever expects there to be [b]zero[/b] cheating, but they do want it to be low. But, &quot;Leeches&quot; don&#39;t care about that. So, in turn Jagex was forced to take time away from development of the game to make it better, and find a fix for the cheating. In fact, if you look at every incident of a huge new leap in the cheating community and you will find every time, that leeches have ruined them by overuse and abuse. Which takes us to our next section, &quot;Where we are now.&quot;


[center][b][size=24pt]Where We Are Now[/size][/b][/center]
This isn&#39;t going to be the kindest part of my essay, but it will all be fair in true. At the moment there is 144 RuneScape worlds. 73 Of them being free to play, and 71 of them being pay to play. If you were to walk around all throughout a server, you would find on average about 40-50 level 3 accounts that are using macros. They have been made for the soul purpose of gathering items to get money, or money itself. These accounts will be banned, but they still leave a lasting impression on the economy. Drops in prices and inflation is the main problem with these disposable moneymaking vessels. Another big problem with them is the fact that they take away a lot of opportunities from legit, or responsible autoers. You may be asking yourself, what the hell is a responsible autoer? Isn&#39;t that an oxymoron? Well, it is the opposite of a leech. He/she doesn&#39;t make dozens of accounts to make him/her money, he/she autos on one account, and contributes to the community in the best way he/she can. It&#39;s sad to say that to my estimations, there might be one of these people in every 20 or so people who use macros. We are killing ourselves. Without rambling on, let&#39;s go to our next section, &quot;Where We Should Be&quot;.


[center][b][size=24pt]Where We Should Be[/size][/b][/center]
Imagine a universal cheating forum/community utopia. Everyone gets along, we produce new cheating utilities everyday. Jagex is happy, and macro associated banning is at an all time low. You can go on a search engine, and search for RuneScape cheats, and get maybe 1-2 pages of content, which will all be either fake, or outdated cheats that ensure your account to be banned. This is the perfect cheating community. Whether or not we will ever achieve this level is entirely up to us all. Whether we can put aside our petty differences, and  use our brains. We can fight for the greater good. It will most surely tax us all with temptation, having to use your brain, and a lot of sacrifices. Along the way, it may seem like things that are impossible, but if you open your eyes, and look ahead to see what we will obtain through these acts, then whether or not we accomplish this is up to you. I know that we can do it with the great minds we all have, and the great minds we will attract on the way with our hopes for the future. But now you are asking yourself, how are we supposed to achieve this? Well, that&#39;s what I wrote the next session for. So move on, I hope you enjoyed this part.


[center][b][size=24pt]How To Get There[/size][/b][/center]
If you read my last section, then you are probably either eager to get to that craved utopia, or you are skeptical that it is possible at all. Well, I assure you that if you have the will, I have the way. See, in my eyes, Jagex&#39;s Anti-Cheating squad, is like the average guard. The guard is guarding a room, in the room is what we wish to accomplish. See, it would be very easy for one person to make a path to the room of accomplishment, without the guard seeing him get in. All the cheater needs to be, is smart. But let&#39;s say that one cheater who is a good person, and believes that all people should be able to join him in the coveted room of accomplishment. So, he sends out his route (or cheating utility) on how to get in (accomplish happiness). Some people, that are like that one cheater, go into the room, and make new paths, and they too release the plans. But, then there is the people that go in, and abuse the plans(leeches). When they are in, they don&#39;t make new plans, but become greedy. They don&#39;t care if the guard finds the way everyone is getting in. They don&#39;t care, if because of their greed, the room is ruined because of them. Leeches are the death of us. They are ruining the community, and the game itself. Jagex has to expect that [b]some[/b] people will get in. No, of course they aren&#39;t saying that this is ok, but they are saying that some people will get past their anti-cheating system. But right now your thinking, Buzzy, how the hell are we supposed to stop leeches? Well this is simple. On RuneScape, as your walking through, report level 3 bots. They are leeches to the community, and are killing us. Here&#39;s an idea, let&#39;s produce new utilities. Let&#39;s make something [i]better[/i] than SCAR. But then your saying, but Buzzy, we did that, remember AutoRune and Aryan dumbshit? Well, look what happened to them both when people found out about them. They were abused and killed. I suggest, an Authorization system. But, I do not suggest paying for them with money. I suggest instead, paying with contribution to the community. Any leech can get a few bucks, but no leech can be called just that if he/she were to contribute to the community. But still, you can be saying once again, what about the about the automation systems that are already out there. Well, here is 2 fixes to that, stop all of the development of them. Eventually, the now existing scripts and utilities will become outdated and unusable. But that can take a very long time. A faster way, but one many people will disagree with, is to contribute to the enemy, for the cause of the greater good. If we were to come up with an anti-cheat fix for all existing macros, and told Jagex, then that would mean that leeches could no longer use the systems out now, and would either have to quit cheating, or stop leeching. So, here is our to do list for achieving the top level of cheating, without being caught.

1.) Extinguish leeches- It&#39;s like trying to run from the police with a 200 lb. ball chained to your ankle, good luck with that.

2.) Create New Utopia- Create a new community that has a surplus of undetectable cheating utilities, that all require authorizations that are acquired through community respect and contribution. This community would not be anti-noob, but anti-leech. I am a firm believer in the term &quot;Don&#39;t hate, educate.&quot; That is why, I believe that we should help educate them, so that we will be able to develop more cheating utilities. At the moment, we are certainly quantity over quality. But it would be much better the other way around. Not only would this mean that there is a much less chance of us getting caught, but we would get along much better, and become an all around better community.

     I guess this is the end of my essay. I hope you enjoyed it, I&#39;ve been tossing these ideas around in my head for a weeks now. Yeah, I know I sounded like Hitler through some of it, but I&#39;m not talking about killing anyone, and whether or not you respect Hitler, he was a genius. So please leave feedback, and hell, let&#39;s get started. If you do not agree, please give a good reason why.

[center]Thanks for reading,[/center]

Buzzy</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 26 Jun 2007 23:36:26 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Community Suggestions</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/reconstruction-my-essay-on-us/116413.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Reconstruction -My Essay On Us =)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Buzzy Buzzy]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/buzzy">@Buzzy</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“Eh Pretty Easy, post:6, topic:116413”]Nice, I like it.</p>
<p>[quote author=Buzzy]<br>
144 RuneScape worlds.  112 Of them being free to play, and 68 of them being pay to play.<br>
[/quote]Miscalculation?[/quote]<br>
Wow yeah, it was a big miscalculation. Thanks for catching that for me. Thanks for the compliment too =).</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/reconstruction-my-essay-on-us/116413/7">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/reconstruction-my-essay-on-us/116413/7</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 26 Jun 2007 23:36:26 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-116413-7</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/reconstruction-my-essay-on-us/116413.rss">Reconstruction -My Essay On Us =)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Reconstruction -My Essay On Us =)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Eh_Pretty_Easy Eh Pretty Easy]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/eh_pretty_easy">@Eh_Pretty_Easy</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Nice, I like it.</p>
<p>[quote=“Buzzy”]144 RuneScape worlds.  112 Of them being free to play, and 68 of them being pay to play.[/quote]Miscalculation?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/reconstruction-my-essay-on-us/116413/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/reconstruction-my-essay-on-us/116413/6</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 26 Jun 2007 23:20:42 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-116413-6</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/reconstruction-my-essay-on-us/116413.rss">Reconstruction -My Essay On Us =)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Reconstruction -My Essay On Us =)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Buzzy Buzzy]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/buzzy">@Buzzy</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Thanks Fastbawlz, but you should read it all =/.  What community are you talking about that needs that though?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/reconstruction-my-essay-on-us/116413/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/reconstruction-my-essay-on-us/116413/5</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 26 Jun 2007 23:14:59 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-116413-5</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/reconstruction-my-essay-on-us/116413.rss">Reconstruction -My Essay On Us =)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Reconstruction -My Essay On Us =)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@FastBallz FastBawlz]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/fastballz">@FastBallz</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote no-group" data-post="3" data-topic="116413">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/buzzy/40/5_6259e4fa9dfe0dec282fb0955bb1974c.png" class="avatar"> Buzzy:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Honestly, it’s not really helping, it’s paving the way for us. Also it wouldn’t matter if they turned on us, each auth could be used on only one account =) Admins get to choose who has auths, and can take them away. all activity is logged. Just like autorune, except this won’t be released to leeches, because you need respect and contributions to get one =)</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Kind of like cups?</p>
<p>Well I read part of it and I can assure you that its not 1 in 20 people that contribute…Maybe 1 in 100…<br>
I dont play runescape anymore but I know its not 1 in 20…</p>
<blockquote>2.) Create New Utopia- Create a new community that has a surplus of undetectable cheating utilities, that all require authorizations that are acquired through community respect and contribution. This community would not be anti-noob, but anti-leech. I am a firm believer in the term "Don't hate, educate." That is why, I believe that we should help educate them, so that we will be able to develop more cheating utilities. At the moment, we are certainly quantity over quality. But it would be much better the other way around. Not only would this mean that there is a much less chance of us getting caught, but we would get along much better, and become an all around better community.</blockquote>
<p>This would be smart. Make a new community which require a invite code from the inside to get in. (Like Demonoid)</p>
<p>I know another cheating community that is about to do this in 1-2 Days that you need a code that you get in your User CP to activate the bots and cracks that they use…</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/reconstruction-my-essay-on-us/116413/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/reconstruction-my-essay-on-us/116413/4</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 26 Jun 2007 09:55:05 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-116413-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/reconstruction-my-essay-on-us/116413.rss">Reconstruction -My Essay On Us =)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Reconstruction -My Essay On Us =)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Buzzy Buzzy]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/buzzy">@Buzzy</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Honestly, it’s not really helping, it’s paving the way for us. Also it wouldn’t matter if they turned on us, each auth could be used on only one account =) Admins get to choose who has auths, and can take them away. all activity is logged. Just like autorune, except this won’t be released to leeches, because you need respect and contributions to get one =)</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/reconstruction-my-essay-on-us/116413/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/reconstruction-my-essay-on-us/116413/3</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 26 Jun 2007 01:34:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-116413-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/reconstruction-my-essay-on-us/116413.rss">Reconstruction -My Essay On Us =)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Reconstruction -My Essay On Us =)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@goatee goatee]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/goatee">@goatee</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Sounds good and all but did you ever thinking about the people who pretend to be good then once they gt what they wanted the would release it to the world? Also working with Jagex isn’t a good idea if we are just gonig to go behind there backs and cheat again.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/reconstruction-my-essay-on-us/116413/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/reconstruction-my-essay-on-us/116413/2</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 26 Jun 2007 01:28:06 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-116413-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/reconstruction-my-essay-on-us/116413.rss">Reconstruction -My Essay On Us =)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Reconstruction -My Essay On Us =)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Buzzy Buzzy]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/buzzy">@Buzzy</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Hello,</p>
<pre><code> Has anyone else noticed, or am I the only one, that the community of cheating has become in users, quantity over quality. Here is my essay, on how this can be fixed by showing how things used to be, how things are in present time, how we should be, and the path to that road. Please enjoy.
</code></pre>
<p>[center]<span class="bbcode-b">[size=24pt]Where We Were[/size]</span>[/center]<br>
In the beginning of the cheating era, no I am not saying I was there, as I doubt most of the people who are reading this were, was great. There were few people, who were all for the development and moving forward in the cheating world. Almost everyone had their own automation tool, or was a huge part in the development of someone else’s. Then, after using purely coordinations was no longer an option, a new big thing came out. A young man from New Zealand came out with an ingenious idea, color picking. Without going into a history lecture, this was a humongous step forward, as there was nothing like it so far. This brought more players, as the interface was user-friendly, not saying this is a bad thing. The majority of users that came after the color picking were not there to help out the community, but to just leech off of it, using it, abusing it, and bringing much attention upon us all, metaphorically speaking, the spotlight of Jagex was on us, and there was no where to run because these “leeches” refused to stop. No game as big as RuneScape ever expects there to be <span class="bbcode-b">zero</span> cheating, but they do want it to be low. But, “Leeches” don’t care about that. So, in turn Jagex was forced to take time away from development of the game to make it better, and find a fix for the cheating. In fact, if you look at every incident of a huge new leap in the cheating community and you will find every time, that leeches have ruined them by overuse and abuse. Which takes us to our next section, “Where we are now.”</p>
<p>[center]<span class="bbcode-b">[size=24pt]Where We Are Now[/size]</span>[/center]<br>
This isn’t going to be the kindest part of my essay, but it will all be fair in true. At the moment there is 144 RuneScape worlds. 73 Of them being free to play, and 71 of them being pay to play. If you were to walk around all throughout a server, you would find on average about 40-50 level 3 accounts that are using macros. They have been made for the soul purpose of gathering items to get money, or money itself. These accounts will be banned, but they still leave a lasting impression on the economy. Drops in prices and inflation is the main problem with these disposable moneymaking vessels. Another big problem with them is the fact that they take away a lot of opportunities from legit, or responsible autoers. You may be asking yourself, what the hell is a responsible autoer? Isn’t that an oxymoron? Well, it is the opposite of a leech. He/she doesn’t make dozens of accounts to make him/her money, he/she autos on one account, and contributes to the community in the best way he/she can. It’s sad to say that to my estimations, there might be one of these people in every 20 or so people who use macros. We are killing ourselves. Without rambling on, let’s go to our next section, “Where We Should Be”.</p>
<p>[center]<span class="bbcode-b">[size=24pt]Where We Should Be[/size]</span>[/center]<br>
Imagine a universal cheating forum/community utopia. Everyone gets along, we produce new cheating utilities everyday. Jagex is happy, and macro associated banning is at an all time low. You can go on a search engine, and search for RuneScape cheats, and get maybe 1-2 pages of content, which will all be either fake, or outdated cheats that ensure your account to be banned. This is the perfect cheating community. Whether or not we will ever achieve this level is entirely up to us all. Whether we can put aside our petty differences, and  use our brains. We can fight for the greater good. It will most surely tax us all with temptation, having to use your brain, and a lot of sacrifices. Along the way, it may seem like things that are impossible, but if you open your eyes, and look ahead to see what we will obtain through these acts, then whether or not we accomplish this is up to you. I know that we can do it with the great minds we all have, and the great minds we will attract on the way with our hopes for the future. But now you are asking yourself, how are we supposed to achieve this? Well, that’s what I wrote the next session for. So move on, I hope you enjoyed this part.</p>
<p>[center]<span class="bbcode-b">[size=24pt]How To Get There[/size]</span>[/center]<br>
If you read my last section, then you are probably either eager to get to that craved utopia, or you are skeptical that it is possible at all. Well, I assure you that if you have the will, I have the way. See, in my eyes, Jagex’s Anti-Cheating squad, is like the average guard. The guard is guarding a room, in the room is what we wish to accomplish. See, it would be very easy for one person to make a path to the room of accomplishment, without the guard seeing him get in. All the cheater needs to be, is smart. But let’s say that one cheater who is a good person, and believes that all people should be able to join him in the coveted room of accomplishment. So, he sends out his route (or cheating utility) on how to get in (accomplish happiness). Some people, that are like that one cheater, go into the room, and make new paths, and they too release the plans. But, then there is the people that go in, and abuse the plans(leeches). When they are in, they don’t make new plans, but become greedy. They don’t care if the guard finds the way everyone is getting in. They don’t care, if because of their greed, the room is ruined because of them. Leeches are the death of us. They are ruining the community, and the game itself. Jagex has to expect that <span class="bbcode-b">some</span> people will get in. No, of course they aren’t saying that this is ok, but they are saying that some people will get past their anti-cheating system. But right now your thinking, Buzzy, how the hell are we supposed to stop leeches? Well this is simple. On RuneScape, as your walking through, report level 3 bots. They are leeches to the community, and are killing us. Here’s an idea, let’s produce new utilities. Let’s make something <span class="bbcode-i">better</span> than SCAR. But then your saying, but Buzzy, we did that, remember AutoRune and Aryan dumbshit? Well, look what happened to them both when people found out about them. They were abused and killed. I suggest, an Authorization system. But, I do not suggest paying for them with money. I suggest instead, paying with contribution to the community. Any leech can get a few bucks, but no leech can be called just that if he/she were to contribute to the community. But still, you can be saying once again, what about the about the automation systems that are already out there. Well, here is 2 fixes to that, stop all of the development of them. Eventually, the now existing scripts and utilities will become outdated and unusable. But that can take a very long time. A faster way, but one many people will disagree with, is to contribute to the enemy, for the cause of the greater good. If we were to come up with an anti-cheat fix for all existing macros, and told Jagex, then that would mean that leeches could no longer use the systems out now, and would either have to quit cheating, or stop leeching. So, here is our to do list for achieving the top level of cheating, without being caught.</p>
<p>1.) Extinguish leeches- It’s like trying to run from the police with a 200 lb. ball chained to your ankle, good luck with that.</p>
<p>2.) Create New Utopia- Create a new community that has a surplus of undetectable cheating utilities, that all require authorizations that are acquired through community respect and contribution. This community would not be anti-noob, but anti-leech. I am a firm believer in the term “Don’t hate, educate.” That is why, I believe that we should help educate them, so that we will be able to develop more cheating utilities. At the moment, we are certainly quantity over quality. But it would be much better the other way around. Not only would this mean that there is a much less chance of us getting caught, but we would get along much better, and become an all around better community.</p>
<pre><code> I guess this is the end of my essay. I hope you enjoyed it, I've been tossing these ideas around in my head for a weeks now. Yeah, I know I sounded like Hitler through some of it, but I'm not talking about killing anyone, and whether or not you respect Hitler, he was a genius. So please leave feedback, and hell, let's get started. If you do not agree, please give a good reason why.
</code></pre>
<p>[center]Thanks for reading,[/center]</p>
<p>Buzzy</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/reconstruction-my-essay-on-us/116413/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/reconstruction-my-essay-on-us/116413/1</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 26 Jun 2007 00:30:16 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-116413-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/reconstruction-my-essay-on-us/116413.rss">Reconstruction -My Essay On Us =)</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
