<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Missing Protocol Help</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/missing-protocol-help/458965</link>
    <description>What prevents a client from disconnecting from the server protocol-wise? I&#39;m writing my own implementation of a RuneScape revision 317 emulator and I&#39;ve got the client and server through the login block and initiating an ISAAC cipher between the two.

I then send the player init and change region frames/packets and the client doesn&#39;t render the landscape, but disconnects instead. Does the server need to be reading data from the client stream to prevent this? What part of the protocol am I missing to keep the client logged in?</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 08 Sep 2012 00:39:57 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/missing-protocol-help/458965.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Missing Protocol Help</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Asteria Asteria]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/asteria">@Asteria</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>What prevents a client from disconnecting from the server protocol-wise? I’m writing my own implementation of a RuneScape revision 317 emulator and I’ve got the client and server through the login block and initiating an ISAAC cipher between the two.</p>
<p>I then send the player init and change region frames/packets and the client doesn’t render the landscape, but disconnects instead. Does the server need to be reading data from the client stream to prevent this? What part of the protocol am I missing to keep the client logged in?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/missing-protocol-help/458965/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/missing-protocol-help/458965/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 08 Sep 2012 00:39:57 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-458965-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/missing-protocol-help/458965.rss">Missing Protocol Help</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
