<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>[PI] Back to client</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/pi-back-to-client/414885</link>
    <description>I want to make my webclient back to a client. That way the cache can be downloaded with the client folders. I prefer a webclient but my cachedownloader downloads corrupt files. So if you could either tell me how to go back to a client or how to fix the corrupt cache download that would help a lot. Thanks (:

I used LostLegacy for a base. I looked at the cachedownloader.java it doesn&#39;t look to be messed up. :\

EDIT: Never mind. Anyone who can&#39;t do this is an idiot. I just gotta reverse what it tells you to do in the making webclient tutorial. It&#39;s not too easy but I can do it if I have files for another client and go through the tutorial looking at what was changed and change it back. God how could I not thing of that when it&#39;s so obvious. -_____-</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 17 Sep 2011 00:08:20 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/pi-back-to-client/414885.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>[PI] Back to client</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@belhelmiel belhelmiel]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/belhelmiel">@belhelmiel</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I want to make my webclient back to a client. That way the cache can be downloaded with the client folders. I prefer a webclient but my cachedownloader downloads corrupt files. So if you could either tell me how to go back to a client or how to fix the corrupt cache download that would help a lot. Thanks (:</p>
<p>I used LostLegacy for a base. I looked at the cachedownloader.java it doesn’t look to be messed up. :\</p>
<p>EDIT: Never mind. Anyone who can’t do this is an idiot. I just gotta reverse what it tells you to do in the making webclient tutorial. It’s not too easy but I can do it if I have files for another client and go through the tutorial looking at what was changed and change it back. God how could I not thing of that when it’s so obvious. -_____-</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/pi-back-to-client/414885/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/pi-back-to-client/414885/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 17 Sep 2011 00:08:20 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-414885-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/pi-back-to-client/414885.rss">[PI] Back to client</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
