<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Creating and managing an economy - A discussion</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/creating-and-managing-an-economy-a-discussion/549698</link>
    <description>Just feel like this is something that most RSPS overlook, even tho it can really contribute to the quality of the game.

For an economy to work you need to look at and address so many aspects, I&#39;ve listed some of them below;

When introducing a new item into the game there are a multitude of things to consider as a single item can completely ruin your economy.
1. How are you going to introduce said item? 
Jagex have used minigames/events to introduce items into the past, and have more recently (last few years) started using quests.

2. What kind of value do you want the item to have?
This one here is tricky, as it requires some thought. You will need to understand how your economy is currently sitting. What kind of price is item x sitting as, as item y (item being introduced) is an upgrade on that. 
How many will we introduce into the game, will the item degrade -if so how long will it last. The amount of an item in the game as well as the demand for it is what really determines an items value, but they aren&#39;t the only factors. If i had a whip - 200k in the game and there are 10,000 of them there, and I introduce a premium whip of which there are 10,000 then I would be forcing the price of regular whips down.


As you can see economics is a headache that no one has really grasped just yet (in the current rsps world anyway), so all discussion is really encouraged. Any ideas/something that I have left out?</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2015 08:04:03 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/creating-and-managing-an-economy-a-discussion/549698.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Creating and managing an economy - A discussion</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Ruby_Forums_Coder Ruby]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/ruby_forums_coder">@Ruby_Forums_Coder</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Something like a GE would work, yeah. It’d give you the ability to track the majority of a certain item in the game all the while giving a very attractive feature for people. When you look at it in a work load sense though, it just shows how little the people running around with these servers today rely on their players, most servers I know of and have seen have no control over what happens in their economies.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/creating-and-managing-an-economy-a-discussion/549698/7">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/creating-and-managing-an-economy-a-discussion/549698/7</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2015 08:04:03 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-549698-7</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/creating-and-managing-an-economy-a-discussion/549698.rss">Creating and managing an economy - A discussion</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Creating and managing an economy - A discussion</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@rash Rash]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/rash">@rash</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote author=Ruby link=topic=668587.msg4471426#msg4471426 date=1423202194]</p>
<p>[quote=“Rash, post:3, topic:549698”]<code>Eventually the economy question came up and it took us weeks to get our heads round it. What we eventually came up with was having dynamic pricing and full control over all items in the game. This required web panels that showed the item surge/depletion etc and allowed us to manage the economy. So the more and more of an item that was pumped into the economy (E.G Flax being picked and sold to a store) the price would go down, all within a capped price range of say roughly 15gp-55gp each or something, not exact numbers. The higher demand for flax being picked, the price would rise in the in-game store. This also left a healthy bit of growth for player to player interactions too, someone could sell it at 35gp a piece if the store was set at 55 and all this kinda stuff, it sounded really cool. So that's the first part of it, dynamic pricing. </code></p>
<p>I was thinking of something similar - but would perhaps a better way to maintain the pricing be similar to zybez’ price guide. They average out Buy/Sell offers and the price is set from there. Doing something like that would of course open the game up to manipulation (clans who want to drive prices up place ridiculous sell offers), so that would where the amount of items in circulation comes in. It would actually be quite simple, just something to read player files for an item Id.[/quote]<br>
I like it. Problem with that is how would you collect the data for the database? Players who just sell through P2P interaction wouldn’t be logged and the price could be driven higher or lower without us knowing. The data stored would be purely from people using the online sale system.</p>
<p>[quote=“Rash, post:3, topic:549698”][code]<br>
Something like the KBD dropping visages, we would make that more or less rare depending on the flow of them we’d like in the server. This allows us to control the economy in the long run. The more the players grind the more chance there is of getting a rare drop, but it requires real input from the players to get their end game goals. This was the problem that we couldn’t get by in RSPS. Players in RSPS typically want to join a server, get a party hat set and turn in for the night. Controlling an economy wouldn’t allow something like that and that was a big choke point.</p>
<p>[/code]<br>
Basically you are saying that an economy that is maintained properly where top-end items are not easy to get is very hard is a turn-off for most people playing rsps?[/quote]<br>
Yeah. It doesn’t attract the majority of players, a lot of them (or a lot of them back then) didn’t look for a private server to grind on, they wanted one to have fun on and PvP on. If they wanted to grind on something then they’d just play RuneScape. Especially now OSRS is a thing./<br>
[/quot/e]</p>
<p>Could use something like a GE - most players would use it. Maybe also use data analysis (monthly maybe?) to identify outliers and determine why they have occured and if they are affecting the price (perhaps people overpaying to get an item quicker?).</p>
<p>Something like a watchdog.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/creating-and-managing-an-economy-a-discussion/549698/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/creating-and-managing-an-economy-a-discussion/549698/6</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2015 12:08:33 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-549698-6</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/creating-and-managing-an-economy-a-discussion/549698.rss">Creating and managing an economy - A discussion</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Creating and managing an economy - A discussion</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Ruby_Forums_Coder Ruby]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/ruby_forums_coder">@Ruby_Forums_Coder</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“Rash, post:3, topic:549698”]<code>Eventually the economy question came up and it took us weeks to get our heads round it. What we eventually came up with was having dynamic pricing and full control over all items in the game. This required web panels that showed the item surge/depletion etc and allowed us to manage the economy. So the more and more of an item that was pumped into the economy (E.G Flax being picked and sold to a store) the price would go down, all within a capped price range of say roughly 15gp-55gp each or something, not exact numbers. The higher demand for flax being picked, the price would rise in the in-game store. This also left a healthy bit of growth for player to player interactions too, someone could sell it at 35gp a piece if the store was set at 55 and all this kinda stuff, it sounded really cool. So that's the first part of it, dynamic pricing. </code></p>
<p>I was thinking of something similar - but would perhaps a better way to maintain the pricing be similar to zybez’ price guide. They average out Buy/Sell offers and the price is set from there. Doing something like that would of course open the game up to manipulation (clans who want to drive prices up place ridiculous sell offers), so that would where the amount of items in circulation comes in. It would actually be quite simple, just something to read player files for an item Id.[/quote]<br>
I like it. Problem with that is how would you collect the data for the database? Players who just sell through P2P interaction wouldn’t be logged and the price could be driven higher or lower without us knowing. The data stored would be purely from people using the online sale system.</p>
<p>[quote=“Rash, post:3, topic:549698”][code]<br>
Something like the KBD dropping visages, we would make that more or less rare depending on the flow of them we’d like in the server. This allows us to control the economy in the long run. The more the players grind the more chance there is of getting a rare drop, but it requires real input from the players to get their end game goals. This was the problem that we couldn’t get by in RSPS. Players in RSPS typically want to join a server, get a party hat set and turn in for the night. Controlling an economy wouldn’t allow something like that and that was a big choke point.</p>
<p>[/code]<br>
Basically you are saying that an economy that is maintained properly where top-end items are not easy to get is very hard is a turn-off for most people playing rsps?[/quote]<br>
Yeah. It doesn’t attract the majority of players, a lot of them (or a lot of them back then) didn’t look for a private server to grind on, they wanted one to have fun on and PvP on. If they wanted to grind on something then they’d just play RuneScape. Especially now OSRS is a thing.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/creating-and-managing-an-economy-a-discussion/549698/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/creating-and-managing-an-economy-a-discussion/549698/5</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2015 05:56:34 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-549698-5</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/creating-and-managing-an-economy-a-discussion/549698.rss">Creating and managing an economy - A discussion</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Creating and managing an economy - A discussion</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Rodgerwilco Rodgerwilco]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/rodgerwilco">@Rodgerwilco</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>It’s pretty simple,</p>
<p>import &gt; export</p>
<p>release update that causes</p>
<p>export &gt; import</p>
<p>release update that causes</p>
<p>import &gt; export</p>
<p>Import = amount of items in the economy “inflated” as a constant import of item drops occur<br>
Export = amount of items being spent (food, bolts, etcetc)</p>
<p>Control your economy by managing the flow of items.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/creating-and-managing-an-economy-a-discussion/549698/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/creating-and-managing-an-economy-a-discussion/549698/4</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2015 05:08:19 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-549698-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/creating-and-managing-an-economy-a-discussion/549698.rss">Creating and managing an economy - A discussion</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Creating and managing an economy - A discussion</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@rash Rash]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/rash">@rash</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“Ruby, post:2, topic:549698”]I’ve reworded this reply about 9000 times already. Basically a few years ago me and a few guys got together to create this super amazing RSPS when we thought there was still something worth doing in here. I’ll not mention their names but it was a group of us who were all involved in massive RSPS beforehand and had closed them - for example when I had mines in circa 2009, others had theirs a little later or earlier and we thought it was going to be the likes of the big superpowers joining together, sitting down, putting our heads together and making an RSPS that could be unparalleled by any other.</p>
<p>I was going to be head of website development and community management purely because the server I had was a complete rip off of PI but I managed to keep a 700 strong playerbase happy and content with what it had. If I could do that with a bollocks shitty server think what I could’ve done with a server that had very strong content etc. Well, that was our chain of thought.</p>
<p>Eventually the economy question came up and it took us weeks to get our heads round it. What we eventually came up with was having dynamic pricing and full control over all items in the game. This required web panels that showed the item surge/depletion etc and allowed us to manage the economy. So the more and more of an item that was pumped into the economy (E.G Flax being picked and sold to a store) the price would go down, all within a capped price range of say roughly 15gp-55gp each or something, not exact numbers. The higher demand for flax being picked, the price would rise in the in-game store. This also left a healthy bit of growth for player to player interactions too, someone could sell it at 35gp a piece if the store was set at 55 and all this kinda stuff, it sounded really cool. So that’s the first part of it, dynamic pricing.</p>
<p>Onto the second part, which is the main economic control. The way it would work is the server would calculate the amount of X id upon every save and would print it to a web control panel, this would let us filter for items and see just how many were in circulation, this would, in turn, allow us to edit the drop tables to put more or less of an item into the economy.</p>
<p>Something like the KBD dropping visages, we would make that more or less rare depending on the flow of them we’d like in the server. This allows us to control the economy in the long run. The more the players grind the more chance there is of getting a rare drop, but it requires real input from the players to get their end game goals. This was the problem that we couldn’t get by in RSPS. Players in RSPS typically want to join a server, get a party hat set and turn in for the night. Controlling an economy wouldn’t allow something like that and that was a big choke point.</p>
<p>As Rash has said, economics is a massive pain in the ass.</p>
<p>Rash, I’m glad you made the thread but you seem to have the idea all wrong. The issue isn’t introducing the item to the economy and setting a price.The issue is maintaining the amount of that item in circulation. If there’s only one of that item in the game and was a rare drop by a boss, then that item truly is priceless unless someone wants to pay well over the odds. When a second one comes into circulation then people start bartering - X said he’d sell it for 20M, Y sells for 19M to undercut him. It’s all about relating to the community, finding their feedback and editing the amount in circulation as you see fit. This is the only way to truly control the economy of a server flawlessly.</p>
<p>I’ve never really discussed economics of a server publicly so this thread will be good. A lot of people just see me as an asshole who trolls a lot when in reality I’ve really looked into the fundamentals of running a successful and long living server probably more than anyone else in this community. Along with running my own pretty large server back in the day. I suppose there’s a lot of information and food for thought I can give.[/quote]</p>
<pre><code class="lang-auto"></code></pre>
<p>I was thinking of something similar - but would perhaps a better way to maintain the pricing be similar to zybez’ price guide. They average out Buy/Sell offers and the price is set from there. Doing something like that would of course open the game up to manipulation (clans who want to drive prices up place ridiculous sell offers), so that would where the amount of items in circulation comes in. It would actually be quite simple, just something to read player files for an item Id.</p>
<pre><code class="lang-auto">Something like the KBD dropping visages, we would make that more or less rare depending on the flow of them we'd like in the server. This allows us to control the economy in the long run. The more the players grind the more chance there is of getting a rare drop, but it requires real input from the players to get their end game goals. This was the problem that we couldn't get by in RSPS. Players in RSPS typically want to join a server, get a party hat set and turn in for the night. Controlling an economy wouldn't allow something like that and that was a big choke point.
</code></pre>
<p>Basically you are saying that an economy that is maintained properly where top-end items are not easy to get is very hard is a turn-off for most people playing rsps?</p>
<p>[code]Rash, I’m glad you made the thread but you seem to have the idea all wrong. The issue isn’t introducing the item to the economy and setting a price.The issue is maintaining the amount of that item in circulation. If there’s only one of that item in the game and was a rare drop by a boss, then that item truly is priceless unless someone wants to pay well over the odds. When a second one comes into circulation then people start bartering - X said he’d sell it for 20M, Y sells for 19M to undercut him. It’s all about relating to the community, finding their feedback and editing the amount in circulation as you see fit. This is the only way to truly control the economy of a server flawlessly.</p>
<p>I’ve never really discussed economics of a server publicly so this thread will be good. A lot of people just see me as an asshole who trolls a lot when in reality I’ve really looked into the fundamentals of running a successful and long living server probably more than anyone else in this community. Along with running my own pretty large server back in the day. I suppose there’s a lot of information and food for thought I can give.[/code]</p>
<p>Let the discussions begin ;)X</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/creating-and-managing-an-economy-a-discussion/549698/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/creating-and-managing-an-economy-a-discussion/549698/3</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2015 21:20:57 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-549698-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/creating-and-managing-an-economy-a-discussion/549698.rss">Creating and managing an economy - A discussion</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Creating and managing an economy - A discussion</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Ruby_Forums_Coder Ruby]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/ruby_forums_coder">@Ruby_Forums_Coder</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I’ve reworded this reply about 9000 times already. Basically a few years ago me and a few guys got together to create this super amazing RSPS when we thought there was still something worth doing in here. I’ll not mention their names but it was a group of us who were all involved in massive RSPS beforehand and had closed them - for example when I had mines in circa 2009, others had theirs a little later or earlier and we thought it was going to be the likes of the big superpowers joining together, sitting down, putting our heads together and making an RSPS that could be unparalleled by any other.</p>
<p>I was going to be head of website development and community management purely because the server I had was a complete rip off of PI but I managed to keep a 700 strong playerbase happy and content with what it had. If I could do that with a bollocks shitty server think what I could’ve done with a server that had very strong content etc. Well, that was our chain of thought.</p>
<p>Eventually the economy question came up and it took us weeks to get our heads round it. What we eventually came up with was having dynamic pricing and full control over all items in the game. This required web panels that showed the item surge/depletion etc and allowed us to manage the economy. So the more and more of an item that was pumped into the economy (E.G Flax being picked and sold to a store) the price would go down, all within a capped price range of say roughly 15gp-55gp each or something, not exact numbers. The higher demand for flax being picked, the price would rise in the in-game store. This also left a healthy bit of growth for player to player interactions too, someone could sell it at 35gp a piece if the store was set at 55 and all this kinda stuff, it sounded really cool. So that’s the first part of it, dynamic pricing.</p>
<p>Onto the second part, which is the main economic control. The way it would work is the server would calculate the amount of X id upon every save and would print it to a web control panel, this would let us filter for items and see just how many were in circulation, this would, in turn, allow us to edit the drop tables to put more or less of an item into the economy.</p>
<p>Something like the KBD dropping visages, we would make that more or less rare depending on the flow of them we’d like in the server. This allows us to control the economy in the long run. The more the players grind the more chance there is of getting a rare drop, but it requires real input from the players to get their end game goals. This was the problem that we couldn’t get by in RSPS. Players in RSPS typically want to join a server, get a party hat set and turn in for the night. Controlling an economy wouldn’t allow something like that and that was a big choke point.</p>
<p>As Rash has said, economics is a massive pain in the ass.</p>
<p>Rash, I’m glad you made the thread but you seem to have the idea all wrong. The issue isn’t introducing the item to the economy and setting a price.The issue is maintaining the amount of that item in circulation. If there’s only one of that item in the game and was a rare drop by a boss, then that item truly is priceless unless someone wants to pay well over the odds. When a second one comes into circulation then people start bartering - X said he’d sell it for 20M, Y sells for 19M to undercut him. It’s all about relating to the community, finding their feedback and editing the amount in circulation as you see fit. This is the only way to truly control the economy of a server flawlessly.</p>
<p>I’ve never really discussed economics of a server publicly so this thread will be good. A lot of people just see me as an asshole who trolls a lot when in reality I’ve really looked into the fundamentals of running a successful and long living server probably more than anyone else in this community. Along with running my own pretty large server back in the day. I suppose there’s a lot of information and food for thought I can give.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/creating-and-managing-an-economy-a-discussion/549698/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/creating-and-managing-an-economy-a-discussion/549698/2</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2015 09:00:19 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-549698-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/creating-and-managing-an-economy-a-discussion/549698.rss">Creating and managing an economy - A discussion</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Creating and managing an economy - A discussion</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@rash Rash]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/rash">@rash</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Just feel like this is something that most RSPS overlook, even tho it can really contribute to the quality of the game.</p>
<p>For an economy to work you need to look at and address so many aspects, I’ve listed some of them below;</p>
<p>When introducing a new item into the game there are a multitude of things to consider as a single item can completely ruin your economy.</p>
<ol>
<li>
<p>How are you going to introduce said item?<br>
Jagex have used minigames/events to introduce items into the past, and have more recently (last few years) started using quests.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>What kind of value do you want the item to have?<br>
This one here is tricky, as it requires some thought. You will need to understand how your economy is currently sitting. What kind of price is item x sitting as, as item y (item being introduced) is an upgrade on that.<br>
How many will we introduce into the game, will the item degrade -if so how long will it last. The amount of an item in the game as well as the demand for it is what really determines an items value, but they aren’t the only factors. If i had a whip - 200k in the game and there are 10,000 of them there, and I introduce a premium whip of which there are 10,000 then I would be forcing the price of regular whips down.</p>
</li>
</ol>
<p>As you can see economics is a headache that no one has really grasped just yet (in the current rsps world anyway), so all discussion is really encouraged. Any ideas/something that I have left out?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/creating-and-managing-an-economy-a-discussion/549698/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/creating-and-managing-an-economy-a-discussion/549698/1</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2015 02:02:50 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-549698-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/creating-and-managing-an-economy-a-discussion/549698.rss">Creating and managing an economy - A discussion</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
