<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Jagex RSC Server Rental News</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/jagex-rsc-server-rental-news/302478</link>
    <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;For those who do not know, RuneScape Classic is the name we now use to refer to the very first version of RuneScape, the original basis for RuneScape as it is today. As discussed in the RuneTek 5 blog, RuneScape Classic was RuneTek 2. When we upgraded the game engine to RuneTek 3, we renamed the first game to RuneScape Classic, and the RT3 engine took over the RuneScape moniker.
That RT3 engine has long since evolved, through RT4 (High Details) and the now all-encompassing RT5 (the version of RuneScape we all play today). But we do still run a version of RuneScape Classic on our servers for those people who have continued to play it over the years. We’re currently working on a project to revamp RuneScape Classic and open it up again to everyone who wants to play.
Introduction from Mod Mark

Baxtorian Falls, Classic-style
Mod Mark: When Mod MMG joined the company, the first thing he and I spoke about was RuneScape Classic (often just called ‘Classic’). He wanted to know more about this &quot;retro&quot; version of RuneScape, and was surprised when I told him we had closed account creation, but that the game was still running. Despite the fact we had not supported the product for years (with updates), we still had an active player base. He was keen for me to liaise with the other Classic fans in the company to work out what needed to be fixed in order for us to relaunch it.
This was the best news I had heard in ages, because Classic has always been very important to us as a company, and as individual players of the game. Without Classic, the current versions of RuneScape simply would not exist. It made us who we are today. Not supporting it was really quite painful for us, but it had just become impossible to support due to the movement in technologies in the new version of the game. I’ll hand you over to Mod Jack H, the developer for this project, to give some more details.
Over to the developer

Classic &#39;Claws of Guthix&#39;
I have to admit it was a bit of a surprise when I was told that I would now be working on RuneScape Classic! The game had not been updated for years, only a few people who had worked on it were still with the company, and nobody could really remember the details of how it worked. But Classic was about to become the basis for a totally new idea for Jagex: player-owned virtual servers. But I’m getting ahead of myself...
My first job was to get Classic into a state in which we could release it again. The Jagex systems which handle updating and releasing new content and game engine updates have moved on a long way since Classic was last released. In order to be able to make changes to the game again, I had to fit it out with the same systems that RuneScape uses to handle things like loading the game code, downloading the content (such as maps, 3D models and sprites), managing your Friends and Ignore lists, and sending abuse reports. I also had to add support for the new display names system that Mod Duncan is working on, and we got some bonuses, like the ability to private chat between Classic and RS2.
So far, we would have had to do all this anyway, because the display names project affects all our games (including Classic), so it had to be updated to support it and we had to be able to release it again. But Andrew and Mod MMG had much bigger ideas for Classic. They wanted to make it available to new players again, and solve the problems that caused it to be restricted in the first place.
The problem that needed solving was how to stop the macroing which was crippling Classic without changing the game. We didn’t want to add to Classic all the measures to stop macroing and cheating that we’ve developed for RuneScape, because that would stop Classic being Classic. We could have just enabled all the cheat codes in the game so macroing would become pointless, but that would make the game quite pointless too. So here’s what we came up with...
And then over to you...?

Demon Slayer&#39;s first incarnation
How about if players could rent and administer their own Classic servers? As a server owner, you could enable or disable any cheat codes you liked, add people to the invite list or banned list, or give individual friends any privileges you liked within your world. In this way, the activities of macroers would become pointless, as you could go on to a cheating-enabled world and get all the stuff you wanted for free if you wanted, but there would still be worlds where you’d have the satisfaction of knowing you worked for your stuff. I should explain that your character would be saved separately for each world, so you couldn’t cheat on one world then use the stuff you gained on a non-cheating world. The different rules set by the owner of each world would really make each world a different game, with different people in positions of power, wielding cheat codes and unleashing Classic’s most awesome spells and items, or making everyone work to get ahead...
Finally, to reassure our loyal Classic members who’ve stuck with the game all the way through, these new ‘player-run’ Classic worlds will be in ADDITION to the two restricted Classic worlds we already operate. We plan to leave those unchanged and not invaded by lots of newcomers or cheat codes.
We reckon this will be a lot of fun, but what do you think of the idea? It’s going to be a lot of work for us to make it a reality as we’ve never done anything like this before. Would you rent a server? How much would you be willing to pay? What sort of features would you want to see? Do you have any other comments or suggestions? Let us know.&lt;/blockquote&gt;

My impression is that Jagex is attempting to not actually release their server code to renters so they can run their own server but instead give them &quot;access&quot; to an individual world server where they pay per month. I theorize they will be given administrator rank  and granted access to a control panel in game which would let them do various administrator/pmod related tasks like spawn money, change levels, ect. (Similar to what we have seen in EasyRSC somewhat) This would involve Jagex hosting the world servers and not giving access to the actual server code unless they instead sent a binary executable which contains the world server for players to host on their own dedicated servers. That would then require an activation login in order to launch it as long as the user has paid for their rental month.

Who would play on these private rental servers? RS2 noobs and RSC lovers.
Who would run these rental servers? Every non-coding person who runs EasyRSC/related.

To me this sounds like they want to get server owners to rent from them and abandon development in return for a more complete server which has all the quests and everything working. They make profit, we loose potential coders, people stop playing these private servers, rsc development stagnates.

Win win win for Jagex, fail for RSC development. Pretty sinister.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 30 Mar 2010 01:32:09 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/jagex-rsc-server-rental-news/302478.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Jagex RSC Server Rental News</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@lothy Lothy]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/lothy">@lothy</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote no-group" data-post="31" data-topic="302478">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/icejon/40/5_513041d5f7104045db30895d3b90af16.png" class="avatar"> Icejon:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Its over they decided to not do it lol!  <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=5" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Rep-- for bumping an old topic needlessly.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/jagex-rsc-server-rental-news/302478/33">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/jagex-rsc-server-rental-news/302478/33</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 30 Mar 2010 01:32:09 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-302478-33</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/jagex-rsc-server-rental-news/302478.rss">Jagex RSC Server Rental News</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Jagex RSC Server Rental News</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@imthenull imthenull]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/imthenull">@imthenull</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote no-group" data-post="31" data-topic="302478">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/icejon/40/5_513041d5f7104045db30895d3b90af16.png" class="avatar"> Icejon:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Its over they decided to not do it lol!  <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=5" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>nice gravedig. nearly a year old thread.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/jagex-rsc-server-rental-news/302478/32">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/jagex-rsc-server-rental-news/302478/32</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 30 Mar 2010 01:31:46 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-302478-32</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/jagex-rsc-server-rental-news/302478.rss">Jagex RSC Server Rental News</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Jagex RSC Server Rental News</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Icejon Icejon]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/icejon">@Icejon</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Its over they decided to not do it lol!  <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=5" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/jagex-rsc-server-rental-news/302478/31">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/jagex-rsc-server-rental-news/302478/31</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 30 Mar 2010 01:25:40 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-302478-31</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/jagex-rsc-server-rental-news/302478.rss">Jagex RSC Server Rental News</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Jagex RSC Server Rental News</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@darscape darscape]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/darscape">@darscape</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>&lt;3 luring too!</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/jagex-rsc-server-rental-news/302478/30">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/jagex-rsc-server-rental-news/302478/30</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 26 Sep 2009 00:14:28 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-302478-30</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/jagex-rsc-server-rental-news/302478.rss">Jagex RSC Server Rental News</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Jagex RSC Server Rental News</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@nacional nacional]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/nacional">@nacional</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote no-group quote-modified" data-post="28" data-topic="302478">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/pesterd/40/5_513041d5f7104045db30895d3b90af16.png" class="avatar"> pesterd:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>RSC was made of Macroing/Looting/PJing/Pking… Bring that back and you now have the whole underground RSC community back into the game that was once made great. unless thats back I dont hink it will be a success…</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>you forgot scamming . yeah your right rsc wont be the same really with this server set up.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/jagex-rsc-server-rental-news/302478/29">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/jagex-rsc-server-rental-news/302478/29</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 24 Sep 2009 02:48:06 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-302478-29</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/jagex-rsc-server-rental-news/302478.rss">Jagex RSC Server Rental News</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Jagex RSC Server Rental News</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@pesterd pesterd]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/pesterd">@pesterd</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>RSC was made of Macroing/Looting/PJing/Pking… Bring that back and you now have the whole underground RSC community back into the game that was once made great. unless thats back I dont hink it will be a success…</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/jagex-rsc-server-rental-news/302478/28">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/jagex-rsc-server-rental-news/302478/28</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 24 Sep 2009 02:43:03 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-302478-28</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/jagex-rsc-server-rental-news/302478.rss">Jagex RSC Server Rental News</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Jagex RSC Server Rental News</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@noobsauce noobsauce]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/noobsauce">@noobsauce</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Two words.</p>
<p>HUGE FAIL.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/jagex-rsc-server-rental-news/302478/27">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/jagex-rsc-server-rental-news/302478/27</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 23 Sep 2009 15:43:47 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-302478-27</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/jagex-rsc-server-rental-news/302478.rss">Jagex RSC Server Rental News</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Jagex RSC Server Rental News</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Runes_Are_Cool Runes Are Cool?]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/runes_are_cool">@Runes_Are_Cool</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Same, I’d love to play RSC, it’d get a lot of publicity now adays.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/jagex-rsc-server-rental-news/302478/26">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/jagex-rsc-server-rental-news/302478/26</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 21 Sep 2009 03:35:55 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-302478-26</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/jagex-rsc-server-rental-news/302478.rss">Jagex RSC Server Rental News</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Jagex RSC Server Rental News</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@snoopy89 snoopy89]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/snoopy89">@snoopy89</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote no-group" data-post="19" data-topic="302478">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/slippinslide/40/5_513041d5f7104045db30895d3b90af16.png" class="avatar"> slippinslide:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>jagex sucks</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Now thats not true, idiot! If it wasn’t for Jagex We wouldn’t have RuneScape at all.<br>
If you think on other directions.<br>
How much work they spend for RS you would understand why they don’t want to release their source.</p>
<p>THINK people! Be a smart ass and code you server execly as orginal RSC.<br>
Stop complain about jagax. The only thing that sucks about them is they don’t allow new players to an old game.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/jagex-rsc-server-rental-news/302478/25">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/jagex-rsc-server-rental-news/302478/25</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 20 Sep 2009 09:30:01 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-302478-25</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/jagex-rsc-server-rental-news/302478.rss">Jagex RSC Server Rental News</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Jagex RSC Server Rental News</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@gawdz666 gawdz666]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/gawdz666">@gawdz666</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“The_AFKer, post:23, topic:302478”][quote author=vortex link=topic=398799.msg2959837#msg2959837 date=1253106566]<br>
Well, if this will indeed happen people could easily gather all the data they want for their server and WB unofficial pservs<br>
[/quote]</p>
<p>Really? I’m guessing they’re begging for lawsuits then! What makes you think they won’t just shut other servers down? Sure, you may have built the engine that runs the game, but last time I checked most if not all servers use their client and images, which are still considered intellectual property and bases for a nice civil case.[/quote]</p>
<p>It is the persons choice to download the client which isnt hosted off a website owned by the “owner of the server”</p>
<p>The player then sends packets to the server which then identifies the packet and sends a corresponding packet to preform an action that so happens to change/move/remove a sprite or image on the client.</p>
<p>But again send a packet to anything and it will respond if it is connected to the internet.</p>
<p>All bots ever made should be given “civil case” and a notice to appear in court.</p>
<p>THEN AGAIN JAGEX DOES NOT GIVE A FLYING FUCK.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/jagex-rsc-server-rental-news/302478/24">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/jagex-rsc-server-rental-news/302478/24</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 19 Sep 2009 15:21:34 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-302478-24</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/jagex-rsc-server-rental-news/302478.rss">Jagex RSC Server Rental News</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Jagex RSC Server Rental News</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@The_AFKer The_AFKer]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/the_afker">@The_AFKer</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote no-group" data-post="22" data-topic="302478">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/vortex/40/5_513041d5f7104045db30895d3b90af16.png" class="avatar"> vortex:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Well, if this will indeed happen people could easily gather all the data they want for their server and WB unofficial pservs</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Really? I’m guessing they’re begging for lawsuits then! What makes you think they won’t just shut other servers down? Sure, you may have built the engine that runs the game, but last time I checked most if not all servers use their client and images, which are still considered intellectual property and bases for a nice civil case.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/jagex-rsc-server-rental-news/302478/23">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/jagex-rsc-server-rental-news/302478/23</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 19 Sep 2009 10:20:08 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-302478-23</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/jagex-rsc-server-rental-news/302478.rss">Jagex RSC Server Rental News</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Jagex RSC Server Rental News</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@vortex vortex]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/vortex">@vortex</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Well, if this will indeed happen people could easily gather all the data they want for their server and WB unofficial pservs</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/jagex-rsc-server-rental-news/302478/22">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/jagex-rsc-server-rental-news/302478/22</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 16 Sep 2009 13:09:26 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-302478-22</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/jagex-rsc-server-rental-news/302478.rss">Jagex RSC Server Rental News</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Jagex RSC Server Rental News</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@darscape darscape]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/darscape">@darscape</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>That would be a paradise…</p>
<p>Real PKing, scamming, looting.  Ah, the good ole days.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/jagex-rsc-server-rental-news/302478/21">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/jagex-rsc-server-rental-news/302478/21</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 16 Sep 2009 13:07:53 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-302478-21</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/jagex-rsc-server-rental-news/302478.rss">Jagex RSC Server Rental News</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Jagex RSC Server Rental News</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@KO9 KO9]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/ko9">@KO9</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“Lothy, post:14, topic:302478”][quote author=Jonesy1128 link=topic=398799.msg2959371#msg2959371 date=1253060062]<br>
I’m confused about their motives. They don’t want a cheating server. And they don’t want people macroing. Their answer?</p>
<p>Allow people to make thier own servers either with “cheating” or macroing?</p>
<p>GJ Jagex…</p>
<p>Just open up RSC and make everyone happy, a much better idea.<br>
[/quote]<br>
No, they don’t want cheating and macroing that they have to take responsibility for. <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=5" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"><br>
They want to wash their hands of it.</p>
<p>I had this to say to a friend, in jest of course:</p>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p>they should have just gpl’d it like wtf why don’t they just gpl it riots varrock world 66 24/7 until jagex gpl the rsc code</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Seriously. They’re a private company; if it doesn’t line their pockets then it doesn’t happen.[/quote]</p>
<p>I don’t see why they don’t just open (new) RSC servers for paying customers only and state that there is no support for the game. If you get hacked/scammed/pissed off at botters, tough.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/jagex-rsc-server-rental-news/302478/20">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/jagex-rsc-server-rental-news/302478/20</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 16 Sep 2009 07:57:35 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-302478-20</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/jagex-rsc-server-rental-news/302478.rss">Jagex RSC Server Rental News</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Jagex RSC Server Rental News</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@slippinslide slippinslide]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/slippinslide">@slippinslide</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>jagex sucks</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/jagex-rsc-server-rental-news/302478/19">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/jagex-rsc-server-rental-news/302478/19</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 16 Sep 2009 06:10:42 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-302478-19</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/jagex-rsc-server-rental-news/302478.rss">Jagex RSC Server Rental News</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Jagex RSC Server Rental News</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@xEnt xEnt]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/xent">@xEnt</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>its shit since we can’t mod the servers.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/jagex-rsc-server-rental-news/302478/18">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/jagex-rsc-server-rental-news/302478/18</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 16 Sep 2009 03:20:45 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-302478-18</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/jagex-rsc-server-rental-news/302478.rss">Jagex RSC Server Rental News</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Jagex RSC Server Rental News</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Old_Rsc_Player Old Rsc Player]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/old_rsc_player">@Old_Rsc_Player</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote no-group" data-post="16" data-topic="302478">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/rushton88/40/5_513041d5f7104045db30895d3b90af16.png" class="avatar"> rushton88:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>no it will be for people to rent a dedi off them and the server obviously comming with it but only giving you admin somehow etc.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>you will just have a control panel. I can see how there gonna do it. Gonna be some work, but its not worth it.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/jagex-rsc-server-rental-news/302478/17">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/jagex-rsc-server-rental-news/302478/17</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 16 Sep 2009 03:13:12 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-302478-17</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/jagex-rsc-server-rental-news/302478.rss">Jagex RSC Server Rental News</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Jagex RSC Server Rental News</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@rushton88 rushton88]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/rushton88">@rushton88</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>no it will be for people to rent a dedi off them and the server obviously comming with it but only giving you admin somehow etc.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/jagex-rsc-server-rental-news/302478/16">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/jagex-rsc-server-rental-news/302478/16</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 16 Sep 2009 03:03:20 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-302478-16</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/jagex-rsc-server-rental-news/302478.rss">Jagex RSC Server Rental News</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Jagex RSC Server Rental News</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Old_Rsc_Player Old Rsc Player]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/old_rsc_player">@Old_Rsc_Player</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I believe what jagex is thinking as a server of ur own is<br>
for people to use there own computers?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/jagex-rsc-server-rental-news/302478/15">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/jagex-rsc-server-rental-news/302478/15</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 16 Sep 2009 02:13:58 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-302478-15</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/jagex-rsc-server-rental-news/302478.rss">Jagex RSC Server Rental News</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Jagex RSC Server Rental News</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@lothy Lothy]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/lothy">@lothy</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“Jonesy1128, post:12, topic:302478”]I’m confused about their motives. They don’t want a cheating server. And they don’t want people macroing. Their answer?</p>
<p>Allow people to make thier own servers either with “cheating” or macroing?</p>
<p>GJ Jagex…</p>
<p>Just open up RSC and make everyone happy, a much better idea.[/quote]<br>
No, they don’t want cheating and macroing that they have to take responsibility for. <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=5" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"><br>
They want to wash their hands of it.</p>
<p>I had this to say to a friend, in jest of course:</p>
<blockquote>they should have just gpl'd it like wtf why don't they just gpl it riots varrock world 66 24/7 until jagex gpl the rsc code</blockquote>
<p>Seriously. They’re a private company; if it doesn’t line their pockets then it doesn’t happen.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/jagex-rsc-server-rental-news/302478/14">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/jagex-rsc-server-rental-news/302478/14</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 16 Sep 2009 01:56:52 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-302478-14</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/jagex-rsc-server-rental-news/302478.rss">Jagex RSC Server Rental News</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Jagex RSC Server Rental News</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@froggie froggie]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/froggie">@froggie</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I agree with you Jonesy.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/jagex-rsc-server-rental-news/302478/13">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/jagex-rsc-server-rental-news/302478/13</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 16 Sep 2009 00:49:12 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-302478-13</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/jagex-rsc-server-rental-news/302478.rss">Jagex RSC Server Rental News</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Jagex RSC Server Rental News</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Jonesy1128 Jonesy1128]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/jonesy1128">@Jonesy1128</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I’m confused about their motives. They don’t want a cheating server. And they don’t want people macroing. Their answer?</p>
<p>Allow people to make thier own servers either with “cheating” or macroing?</p>
<p>GJ Jagex…</p>
<p>Just open up RSC and make everyone happy, a much better idea.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/jagex-rsc-server-rental-news/302478/12">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/jagex-rsc-server-rental-news/302478/12</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 16 Sep 2009 00:14:22 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-302478-12</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/jagex-rsc-server-rental-news/302478.rss">Jagex RSC Server Rental News</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Jagex RSC Server Rental News</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@lol_k lol k]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/lol_k">@lol_k</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>yes, i have tons of active rsc accs, and this would be still ruining rsc because rs2 noobs be like<br>
w0 t3s graphs r so c00l!!! jk they will hate the graphs<br>
fail</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/jagex-rsc-server-rental-news/302478/11">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/jagex-rsc-server-rental-news/302478/11</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 15 Sep 2009 23:49:08 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-302478-11</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/jagex-rsc-server-rental-news/302478.rss">Jagex RSC Server Rental News</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Jagex RSC Server Rental News</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Iron_Maiden1 Iron Maiden]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/iron_maiden1">@Iron_Maiden1</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>maybe some 1337 dude will find a way to leak the full rsc source…</p>
<p>who knows. this will mess up rsc dev though</p>
<p>what i dont get it why leave alone the last 2 remaining servers only like 60 people play its stupid</p>
<p>a much better idea for jagex to make money would be to reset rsc and make it a funorb game then just have a team of mods.</p>
<p>they will get many more funorb subs.</p>
<p>at least rsc botting will be revived with these servers<br>
i still remember the old days of Richyt</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/jagex-rsc-server-rental-news/302478/10">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/jagex-rsc-server-rental-news/302478/10</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 15 Sep 2009 23:43:08 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-302478-10</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/jagex-rsc-server-rental-news/302478.rss">Jagex RSC Server Rental News</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Jagex RSC Server Rental News</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Old_Rsc_Player Old Rsc Player]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/old_rsc_player">@Old_Rsc_Player</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>They should just allow us to run our servers instead of there bullshit.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/jagex-rsc-server-rental-news/302478/9">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/jagex-rsc-server-rental-news/302478/9</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 15 Sep 2009 23:37:33 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-302478-9</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/jagex-rsc-server-rental-news/302478.rss">Jagex RSC Server Rental News</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
