<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>RunePride || limited Spawn (will be gone by next week || friendly community || Staff needed</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/runepride-limited-spawn-will-be-gone-by-next-week-friendly-community-staff-needed/462693</link>
    <description> 1. What is RunePride and what do we strive for. Our community
RunePride has a very nice and friendly community that is always there to help you out. We strive for
direct player reflecion, this means that players are the ones that help each other out. This creates the
best gaming situation possible. Management
First I&#39;d like to start off with telling you about how our management works, we strive for the
bestgameplay for everyone - we care about what people say and we listen to them. You are what
makes us big, without players we would be close to nowhere. Players are your friends, you just need to
know how to handle them. Due to this big support of our players we have fully fixed up our wilderness,
we gave them a great platform for clans to build off to improve clan community, we have a great system that does not allow Pjing or ragging in certain zones because - let&#39;s be honest, it pisses people
off. But at the same time it improves the single clans to be more active. We are thinking of solutions,
24/7. That is what makes us #1 - We are ALWAYS ahead of the rest. RunePride fits YOU.
RunePride was designed to entertain every type of player. We have different game modes where you
can choose how you&#39;d like to play. This is your lucky day! RunePride will perfectly entertain you,You
can also choose XP modes that vary from 5,000 XP per hit to 10 XP per hit. So if you either are a
person who likes challanging gameplay or someone who just likes to enter our highly populated
wilderness straight after logging in RunePride is the place for you. Ideal (What we strive for)
Our ideal is maximum entertainment. We are not in this business for the money, we are in this to give
YOU the best entertainment. Your enjoyment of the game is what we strive for. You do not have to pay
for anything because that simply goes against our ideal. Everything is free to enjoy! You have the
option to purchase items, but you don&#39;t have to pay to wear specific items or to get privileges on other
players! That is how it&#39;s supposed to be, and that is how we do it. Market leader
RunePride is not only the market leader reaching up to 2000 players on peak time, we are also are a
highest quality RSPS out there. Our support is not only professional but they strive for the best of
every player. Without our amazing staff we would be nowhere. Our website was professionally designed
to give you maximum support, ban/mute appeals, live chat and more! RunePride Videos
In our eyes a video explains more then a thousand pictures or words. You can find our videos on
youtube.
We do not have any videos made on youtube yet, we will shortly. Change your player gender: I&#39;ve added the Make Over Mage to the home so when new players join, they can select there gender,
she is located south/west of Edgeville if needed. I&#39;ve also added brand new 728 cache because we recently had 723 cache, and we needed to update so
new players can enjoy new graphics. Earning skills, and new armor: You will need to train your player, to use Torva, Dragon etc, So we added some starter items at the
start.
To earn your starter items, you will need to finish the Start Tutorial. Which is very easy. Rules: Offensive Language
This type of language is know as F##K or N##ger etc, and if any player gets caught doing the following
above they will be banned. Account Trading or Selling
This rule is a rule that you should NOT ever do on RunePride, it will get your account muted, or this will
put your account in jail, if this rule is broken. Advertising Websites
We especially do-not allow players to advertise RS Gold sites, or any other RSPS content, if this rule
gets broken many of times, you will be banned permanently. Scamming
This is a serious rule, if any player on RunePride gets scammed, the player that scammed the other
player, will be in Jail for 30 days max. Malicious Software Sites
This is a very high risk, if somebody gives you a website url and you go to it, you could be infected. So
for your safety do NOT trust anybody with URL&#39;s unless its from the Owner/Co-Owner and its trusted sites, if any
player gives you a website link and you get any type of virus, let the Owner/co-owner know and he will do
something about it. Thank you, for reading our rules you may now download RunePride, have fun! Also, if you do not ever see the owner playing on the server, its due to the owner adding new
things to the server or the owner is editing the server. He uses other player ideas. So if you have a idea
that you want to share please leave a comment below and I will reply to it asap and I will add your idea
to the server. RunePride Staff: We are currently looking for new moderators, and donators/extreme donators, even donors. If you are
interested in the following above,
Step 1:
Please download the client and register at the login, after you have done that you will need to do the
tutorial at the start. Step 2:
Once you are done that add the owner in your friend list: *Master* or *mark* Step 3:
Then, private message him saying the following &quot; May I be a *moderator* or *donor*?&quot; Step 4:
Then I will tell you if RunePride already has moderators/donors or not, if we do not have any
moderators/donors then I will congratulate you and you will be a moderator/donor.
If you want to be a extreme donator or a regular donator you will need to donate $1 dollar for a week. You can visit our forums here: www.runepride.info/forums , please register at the forums today! We really hope to see you soon - and remember, everyone is welcome!
Sites

http://uppit.com/205uq9gwu238/RunePride.jar http://www.runepride.info/sponsor http://www.runepride.info http://www.runepride.info/game</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 01 Oct 2012 00:58:20 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/runepride-limited-spawn-will-be-gone-by-next-week-friendly-community-staff-needed/462693.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>RunePride || limited Spawn (will be gone by next week || friendly community || Staff needed</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@RunePride RunePride]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/runepride">@RunePride</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <ol>
<li>What is RunePride and what do we strive for. Our community<br>
RunePride has a very nice and friendly community that is always there to help you out. We strive for<br>
direct player reflecion, this means that players are the ones that help each other out. This creates the<br>
best gaming situation possible. Management<br>
First I’d like to start off with telling you about how our management works, we strive for the<br>
bestgameplay for everyone - we care about what people say and we listen to them. You are what<br>
makes us big, without players we would be close to nowhere. Players are your friends, you just need to<br>
know how to handle them. Due to this big support of our players we have fully fixed up our wilderness,<br>
we gave them a great platform for clans to build off to improve clan community, we have a great system that does not allow Pjing or ragging in certain zones because - let’s be honest, it pisses people<br>
off. But at the same time it improves the single clans to be more active. We are thinking of solutions,<br>
24/7. That is what makes us <span class="hashtag">#1</span> - We are ALWAYS ahead of the rest. RunePride fits YOU.<br>
RunePride was designed to entertain every type of player. We have different game modes where you<br>
can choose how you’d like to play. This is your lucky day! RunePride will perfectly entertain you,You<br>
can also choose XP modes that vary from 5,000 XP per hit to 10 XP per hit. So if you either are a<br>
person who likes challanging gameplay or someone who just likes to enter our highly populated<br>
wilderness straight after logging in RunePride is the place for you. Ideal (What we strive for)<br>
Our ideal is maximum entertainment. We are not in this business for the money, we are in this to give<br>
YOU the best entertainment. Your enjoyment of the game is what we strive for. You do not have to pay<br>
for anything because that simply goes against our ideal. Everything is free to enjoy! You have the<br>
option to purchase items, but you don’t have to pay to wear specific items or to get privileges on other<br>
players! That is how it’s supposed to be, and that is how we do it. Market leader<br>
RunePride is not only the market leader reaching up to 2000 players on peak time, we are also are a<br>
highest quality RSPS out there. Our support is not only professional but they strive for the best of<br>
every player. Without our amazing staff we would be nowhere. Our website was professionally designed<br>
to give you maximum support, ban/mute appeals, live chat and more! RunePride Videos<br>
In our eyes a video explains more then a thousand pictures or words. You can find our videos on<br>
youtube.<br>
We do not have any videos made on youtube yet, we will shortly. Change your player gender: I’ve added the Make Over Mage to the home so when new players join, they can select there gender,<br>
she is located south/west of Edgeville if needed. I’ve also added brand new 728 cache because we recently had 723 cache, and we needed to update so<br>
new players can enjoy new graphics. Earning skills, and new armor: You will need to train your player, to use Torva, Dragon etc, So we added some starter items at the<br>
start.<br>
To earn your starter items, you will need to finish the Start Tutorial. Which is very easy. Rules: Offensive Language<br>
This type of language is know as F#<span class="hashtag">#K</span> or N#<span class="hashtag">#ger</span> etc, and if any player gets caught doing the following<br>
above they will be banned. Account Trading or Selling<br>
This rule is a rule that you should NOT ever do on RunePride, it will get your account muted, or this will<br>
put your account in jail, if this rule is broken. Advertising Websites<br>
We especially do-not allow players to advertise RS Gold sites, or any other RSPS content, if this rule<br>
gets broken many of times, you will be banned permanently. Scamming<br>
This is a serious rule, if any player on RunePride gets scammed, the player that scammed the other<br>
player, will be in Jail for 30 days max. Malicious Software Sites<br>
This is a very high risk, if somebody gives you a website url and you go to it, you could be infected. So<br>
for your safety do NOT trust anybody with URL’s unless its from the Owner/Co-Owner and its trusted sites, if any<br>
player gives you a website link and you get any type of virus, let the Owner/co-owner know and he will do<br>
something about it. Thank you, for reading our rules you may now download RunePride, have fun! Also, if you do not ever see the owner playing on the server, its due to the owner adding new<br>
things to the server or the owner is editing the server. He uses other player ideas. So if you have a idea<br>
that you want to share please leave a comment below and I will reply to it asap and I will add your idea<br>
to the server. RunePride Staff: We are currently looking for new moderators, and donators/extreme donators, even donors. If you are<br>
interested in the following above,<br>
Step 1:<br>
Please download the client and register at the login, after you have done that you will need to do the<br>
tutorial at the start. Step 2:<br>
Once you are done that add the owner in your friend list: <em>Master</em> or <em>mark</em> Step 3:<br>
Then, private message him saying the following " May I be a <em>moderator</em> or <em>donor</em>?" Step 4:<br>
Then I will tell you if RunePride already has moderators/donors or not, if we do not have any<br>
moderators/donors then I will congratulate you and you will be a moderator/donor.<br>
If you want to be a extreme donator or a regular donator you will need to donate $1 dollar for a week. You can visit our forums here: www.runepride.info/forums , please register at the forums today! We really hope to see you soon - and remember, everyone is welcome!<br>
Sites</li>
</ol>
<p><a href="http://uppit.com/205uq9gwu238/RunePride.jar" rel="nofollow noopener">http://uppit.com/205uq9gwu238/RunePride.jar</a> <a href="http://www.runepride.info/sponsor" rel="nofollow noopener">http://www.runepride.info/sponsor</a> <a href="http://www.runepride.info" rel="nofollow noopener">http://www.runepride.info</a> <a href="http://www.runepride.info/game" rel="nofollow noopener">http://www.runepride.info/game</a></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/runepride-limited-spawn-will-be-gone-by-next-week-friendly-community-staff-needed/462693/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/runepride-limited-spawn-will-be-gone-by-next-week-friendly-community-staff-needed/462693/1</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 01 Oct 2012 00:58:20 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-462693-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/runepride-limited-spawn-will-be-gone-by-next-week-friendly-community-staff-needed/462693.rss">RunePride || limited Spawn (will be gone by next week || friendly community || Staff needed</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
