<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>I NEED feedback on this</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/i-need-feedback-on-this/548403</link>
    <description>Hey guys, I usually don&#39;t get much feedback but I am asking kindly, please help me with this. I am making game for Android and iOS and the character is being made the same as flappy bird (no I am not making a knock off flappy bird game) but I need some help on how to make the character look a bit better. So I made this flappy bird freehand myself..

[img]http://oi61.tinypic.com/20pcih.jpg[/img]

and yes that is the exact scale of the real flappy bird. 

Okay and then I made the character that will be in my game, but I feel like it doesn&#39;t look quite that right. Can you guys tell me what I should change on it?

[img]http://oi59.tinypic.com/es9k6u.jpg[/img]</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2014 05:03:28 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Graphics</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/i-need-feedback-on-this/548403.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>I NEED feedback on this</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@b00mz1029 b00mz1029]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/b00mz1029">@b00mz1029</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Hey guys, I usually don’t get much feedback but I am asking kindly, please help me with this. I am making game for Android and iOS and the character is being made the same as flappy bird (no I am not making a knock off flappy bird game) but I need some help on how to make the character look a bit better. So I made this flappy bird freehand myself…</p>
<p><img src="http://oi61.tinypic.com/20pcih.jpg" alt width="" height=""></p>
<p>and yes that is the exact scale of the real flappy bird.</p>
<p>Okay and then I made the character that will be in my game, but I feel like it doesn’t look quite that right. Can you guys tell me what I should change on it?</p>
<p><img src="http://oi59.tinypic.com/es9k6u.jpg" alt width="" height=""></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/i-need-feedback-on-this/548403/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/i-need-feedback-on-this/548403/1</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2014 05:03:28 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-548403-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/i-need-feedback-on-this/548403.rss">I NEED feedback on this</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
