<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>[allstar] custom minigame</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/allstar-custom-minigame/541351</link>
    <description>Hey guys, I was working on a custom minigame, (not finished though) it&#39;s called clan-wars (couldn&#39;t think of anything better lol). Anyways, let&#39;s go.

CURRENT PROGRESS: 65%

1) Entering the minigame:

You have to enter a portal which gives you 2 options, you can either go to castle wars or clan-wars.

[IMG]http://i59.tinypic.com/x1njhz.png[/img]


2) If you have entered the portal for clan-wars, you would teleport to here:

[IMG]http://i62.tinypic.com/kf0eqd.png[/img]

You will see 2 chests.

The left one is for Saradomin, and the right one for Zamorak. If you click on the chests you&#39;ll get this.

[IMG]http://i59.tinypic.com/symdl0.png[/img]

[i]Alright, now you&#39;re probably wondering, what is the purpose of the timer and the skull?[/i]

Well, if the timer hits 0 [b]and[/b] There are 5 players ready both in Saradomin and Zamorak team, they&#39;ll get teleported to their base where the actual minigame starts.

The Saradomin people will be teleported here:

[IMG]http://i62.tinypic.com/14dpoyh.png[/img]

The Zamorak people will be teleported here:

[IMG]http://i59.tinypic.com/bikv8i.png[/img]


Alright, I hear you thinking

[i]What are the killpoints for?[/i]

The killpoints are used for getting better in the minigame itself. (You actually can&#39;t bring anything with you in the minigame, I still have to add that.) For example:

[IMG]http://i57.tinypic.com/35layq8.png[/img]

You can only enter the portal when you have 10 killpoints, but however cannot attack your npcs (example: if you&#39;re in saradomin team you cannot attack the npcs in your base.) Also, if a zamorakian enters Saradomin&#39;s base, the npcs will attack the intruder. The points are also used for getting stuff (Which is really important, read 3) for more information about that)

3) The alternative of the minigame:

The saradomin team has to kill the boss of zamorak&#39;s team, the same goes for zamorak.
(Saradomin&#39;s boss is Ice Queen and Zamorak&#39;s boss is chronozon)  

But both bosses are pretty powerful and have plenty of HP, with killpoints you can get advanced armour in shops in the minigame, you get to spend killpoints in a shop for stuff.


4) Getting killpoints:

Well, getting killpoints isn&#39;t that hard. You&#39;ll have to kill non saradomin-team NPCs a lot ammount of points. Once you&#39;ve reached 10 killpoints, you&#39;ll be able to get to your victims base. If you kill their NPCs, you&#39;ll get much more points, but there is a danger. If you get killed at your victims base, you&#39;ll lose 20 points.


Let me know what you think guys, if you have questions, please post them. I&#39;d also appreciate some tips and advice.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 19 Mar 2014 18:10:43 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/allstar-custom-minigame/541351.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>[allstar] custom minigame</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@sertan8 sertan8]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/sertan8">@sertan8</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I have to admit, it a vague objective, but it’s far from done. I was also working on a book which shows you the table of contents.<br>
Thanks for the tribute!  <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=5" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/allstar-custom-minigame/541351/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/allstar-custom-minigame/541351/3</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 19 Mar 2014 18:10:43 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-541351-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/allstar-custom-minigame/541351.rss">[allstar] custom minigame</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[allstar] custom minigame</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Clawz_fury lare69]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/clawz_fury">@Clawz_fury</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>no one wants to play a complicated ass minigame with a vague objective, try simplifying it and making the actual objective more clear</p>
<p>otherwise good job and good luck</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/allstar-custom-minigame/541351/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/allstar-custom-minigame/541351/2</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 19 Mar 2014 18:06:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-541351-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/allstar-custom-minigame/541351.rss">[allstar] custom minigame</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[allstar] custom minigame</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@sertan8 sertan8]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/sertan8">@sertan8</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Hey guys, I was working on a custom minigame, (not finished though) it’s called clan-wars (couldn’t think of anything better lol). Anyways, let’s go.</p>
<p>CURRENT PROGRESS: 65%</p>
<ol>
<li>Entering the minigame:</li>
</ol>
<p>You have to enter a portal which gives you 2 options, you can either go to castle wars or clan-wars.</p>
<p><img src="http://i59.tinypic.com/x1njhz.png" alt width="" height=""></p>
<ol start="2">
<li>If you have entered the portal for clan-wars, you would teleport to here:</li>
</ol>
<p><img src="http://i62.tinypic.com/kf0eqd.png" alt width="" height=""></p>
<p>You will see 2 chests.</p>
<p>The left one is for Saradomin, and the right one for Zamorak. If you click on the chests you’ll get this.</p>
<p><img src="http://i59.tinypic.com/symdl0.png" alt width="" height=""></p>
<p><span class="bbcode-i">Alright, now you’re probably wondering, what is the purpose of the timer and the skull?</span></p>
<p>Well, if the timer hits 0 <span class="bbcode-b">and</span> There are 5 players ready both in Saradomin and Zamorak team, they’ll get teleported to their base where the actual minigame starts.</p>
<p>The Saradomin people will be teleported here:</p>
<p><img src="http://i62.tinypic.com/14dpoyh.png" alt width="" height=""></p>
<p>The Zamorak people will be teleported here:</p>
<p><img src="http://i59.tinypic.com/bikv8i.png" alt width="" height=""></p>
<p>Alright, I hear you thinking</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-i">What are the killpoints for?</span></p>
<p>The killpoints are used for getting better in the minigame itself. (You actually can’t bring anything with you in the minigame, I still have to add that.) For example:</p>
<p><img src="http://i57.tinypic.com/35layq8.png" alt width="" height=""></p>
<p>You can only enter the portal when you have 10 killpoints, but however cannot attack your npcs (example: if you’re in saradomin team you cannot attack the npcs in your base.) Also, if a zamorakian enters Saradomin’s base, the npcs will attack the intruder. The points are also used for getting stuff (Which is really important, read 3) for more information about that)</p>
<ol start="3">
<li>The alternative of the minigame:</li>
</ol>
<p>The saradomin team has to kill the boss of zamorak’s team, the same goes for zamorak.<br>
(Saradomin’s boss is Ice Queen and Zamorak’s boss is chronozon)</p>
<p>But both bosses are pretty powerful and have plenty of HP, with killpoints you can get advanced armour in shops in the minigame, you get to spend killpoints in a shop for stuff.</p>
<ol start="4">
<li>Getting killpoints:</li>
</ol>
<p>Well, getting killpoints isn’t that hard. You’ll have to kill non saradomin-team NPCs a lot ammount of points. Once you’ve reached 10 killpoints, you’ll be able to get to your victims base. If you kill their NPCs, you’ll get much more points, but there is a danger. If you get killed at your victims base, you’ll lose 20 points.</p>
<p>Let me know what you think guys, if you have questions, please post them. I’d also appreciate some tips and advice.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/allstar-custom-minigame/541351/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/allstar-custom-minigame/541351/1</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 19 Mar 2014 17:40:38 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-541351-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/allstar-custom-minigame/541351.rss">[allstar] custom minigame</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
