<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>2006scape is not happening</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/2006scape-is-not-happening/477479</link>
    <description>today i went to the 2006scape website and was redirected to www.runescape.com jagex tried to sue the owner.. so for everyone who is waiting just give up.. here is a post from the owner before it was taken down
[b][u]Hello 2006Scapers, Mod Vault here.

I have some unfortunate news to bring you; this is the end of 2006Scape. After a year of development, we are shutting down 2006Scape because of copyright infringement. The reason as to why I wasn&#39;t able to update you for the past month was because of the legal discussions I’ve been involved in. This will be my last message to you.

Following extensive legal advice, I have made the decision to permanently close 2006Scape simply because I don&#39;t want to ruin my life and that of every other individual involved. I hope you understand and respect that decision. 

What once started as a 2007 RuneScape remake made way back on April 10, 2011, 2006Scape has progressed to be one of the largest RuneScape private servers ever made. 

I wanted to thank each and every one of you. Without you we wouldn&#39;t have gotten anywhere. It&#39;s funny to think that a year and a half ago it was just me working on this project, and to see it all come together, all the while being supported by so many people, brings a tear to my eye. 

You have proven to be one of the greatest and friendliest communities to be a part of, I can&#39;t thank you all enough for being such an amazing group of people. Thank you for everything. Really, thank you. Your support has been unheard of, and I&#39;m sincerely going to miss visiting the forums and talking with you all. 

I also wanted to thank everyone who has ever been a part of the 2006Scape team. Whether you were an administrator or a moderator, I hope you all realize how I appreciate everything you have ever done for this project and also that this decision is being made to protect you as well.

It pains me to say that this really is the end. If there&#39;s one thing you should know and keep to heart, it&#39;s this: 

&quot;Don&#39;t cry because it&#39;s over, smile because it happened.&quot; 
- Dr. Seuss 

Thank you for everything. 

Head of 2006Scape 
Mod Vault[/u][/b]</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 03 Jan 2013 23:02:57 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/2006scape-is-not-happening/477479.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>2006scape is not happening</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Frell Frell]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/frell">@Frell</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>we know</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/2006scape-is-not-happening/477479/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/2006scape-is-not-happening/477479/2</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 03 Jan 2013 23:02:57 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-477479-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/2006scape-is-not-happening/477479.rss">2006scape is not happening</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>2006scape is not happening</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Blazefire_Jr Blazefire Jr]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/blazefire_jr">@Blazefire_Jr</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>today i went to the 2006scape website and was redirected to <a href="http://www.runescape.com" rel="nofollow noopener">www.runescape.com</a> jagex tried to sue the owner… so for everyone who is waiting just give up… here is a post from the owner before it was taken down<br>
[b][u]Hello 2006Scapers, Mod Vault here.</p>
<p>I have some unfortunate news to bring you; this is the end of 2006Scape. After a year of development, we are shutting down 2006Scape because of copyright infringement. The reason as to why I wasn’t able to update you for the past month was because of the legal discussions I’ve been involved in. This will be my last message to you.</p>
<p>Following extensive legal advice, I have made the decision to permanently close 2006Scape simply because I don’t want to ruin my life and that of every other individual involved. I hope you understand and respect that decision.</p>
<p>What once started as a 2007 RuneScape remake made way back on April 10, 2011, 2006Scape has progressed to be one of the largest RuneScape private servers ever made.</p>
<p>I wanted to thank each and every one of you. Without you we wouldn’t have gotten anywhere. It’s funny to think that a year and a half ago it was just me working on this project, and to see it all come together, all the while being supported by so many people, brings a tear to my eye.</p>
<p>You have proven to be one of the greatest and friendliest communities to be a part of, I can’t thank you all enough for being such an amazing group of people. Thank you for everything. Really, thank you. Your support has been unheard of, and I’m sincerely going to miss visiting the forums and talking with you all.</p>
<p>I also wanted to thank everyone who has ever been a part of the 2006Scape team. Whether you were an administrator or a moderator, I hope you all realize how I appreciate everything you have ever done for this project and also that this decision is being made to protect you as well.</p>
<p>It pains me to say that this really is the end. If there’s one thing you should know and keep to heart, it’s this:</p>
<p>“Don’t cry because it’s over, smile because it happened.”</p>
<ul>
<li>Dr. Seuss</li>
</ul>
<p>Thank you for everything.</p>
<p>Head of 2006Scape<br>
Mod Vault[/u][/b]</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/2006scape-is-not-happening/477479/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/2006scape-is-not-happening/477479/1</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 03 Jan 2013 23:02:05 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-477479-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/2006scape-is-not-happening/477479.rss">2006scape is not happening</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
