<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Couple questions about 718</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/couple-questions-about-718/470364</link>
    <description>So I got an email from a rsps forum saying my password was out of date by 2200 days and decided to get back into it.... Ive decided to host one 317 and one 718 but im pretty rusty, Im moving along smoothly with the 317 mostly from memory but the 718s giving me some problems. I decided on the matrix 718 client because it seems the most stock as far as I can tell? Is this generally considered a good client, if not opinions are welcome? If its decent, Im working on converting it to a web client but the code that handles the cache is a headache of obfuscation, can anyone provide me with information about how the 718 loads the cache? Ive deleted all of my local caches and it seems to pull some from the server but I cant find the code where it does to modify it to pull from my FTP instead. And uh... any other tips, tricks, comments about 718s/clients in general/.. anything are welcome very much,

Thanks
Hiaburi

As an afterthought. Does anyone know why I cant use my public domain name to connect to a server on my local network? Its a bit annoying trying to test code when my helper has to recompile the client every time I change it because he has to use my domain name...</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 29 Nov 2012 06:26:30 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Game Development</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/couple-questions-about-718/470364.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Couple questions about 718</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Hiaburi Hiaburi]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/hiaburi">@Hiaburi</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>So I got an email from a rsps forum saying my password was out of date by 2200 days and decided to get back into it… Ive decided to host one 317 and one 718 but im pretty rusty, Im moving along smoothly with the 317 mostly from memory but the 718s giving me some problems. I decided on the matrix 718 client because it seems the most stock as far as I can tell? Is this generally considered a good client, if not opinions are welcome? If its decent, Im working on converting it to a web client but the code that handles the cache is a headache of obfuscation, can anyone provide me with information about how the 718 loads the cache? Ive deleted all of my local caches and it seems to pull some from the server but I cant find the code where it does to modify it to pull from my FTP instead. And uh… any other tips, tricks, comments about 718s/clients in general/… anything are welcome very much,</p>
<p>Thanks<br>
Hiaburi</p>
<p>As an afterthought. Does anyone know why I cant use my public domain name to connect to a server on my local network? Its a bit annoying trying to test code when my helper has to recompile the client every time I change it because he has to use my domain name…</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/couple-questions-about-718/470364/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/couple-questions-about-718/470364/1</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 29 Nov 2012 06:26:30 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-470364-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/couple-questions-about-718/470364.rss">Couple questions about 718</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
