<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Talk about a borked system</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/talk-about-a-borked-system/429869</link>
    <description>This entire Moparcraft idea needs reworking, I may sound like a broken record when I say this because I&#39;m sick of saying it myself. Everything that is done on Moparcraft is inefficient and relies mainly on Moparisthebest, instead of adding to the list of tasks he has to do we should instead look to create an efficient system which is self running without intervention.

An inefficient system is a bad system, in short. The most annoying thing is that it&#39;s not a case of &quot;I can&#39;t think of anyways to improve the current system&quot; it&#39;s more a case of nothing getting changed to make it an efficient system. 

So I&#39;m going to spend some time going over the main issues which restrict server activity. 

[hr]

[b]Server Updating - [/b] This one is a killer, we take months to update and we rely on plugins which don&#39;t even work most the time or contain unreasonable amounts of buggy features. 

We should look for plugins which work the most effectively and review them before their use, none of us can be blamed because the author doesn&#39;t update but let us remember that MITB has a lot of sponsored server money a programmer over at MITB forums would gladly update the plugin for a small fee per time. 

If you&#39;re willing to pay for other things to help other mopar communities, why wouldn&#39;t you be willing to help MC? 

[hr]

[b]Lack of staff agreement - [/b] &quot;members of the community look up to staff members&quot; - quote from the __________ board. With a staff team which doesn&#39;t agree on much we&#39;re not exactly sending down the vibes of a popular well managed server, in short the rules need a rework to something that is universally agreed upon. 

What is said in the staff section, stays in the staff section. Drawing blood on a staff related argument outside the section itself should be stopped. I&#39;ll be the first to admit I&#39;ve probably done this before. 

[hr]

[b]The lagg - [/b] I&#39;m not going to blame this on one single factor, but we need to start taking this issue more seriously because something is causing it. If it&#39;s the 1.8.1 MC then we need to update ASAP (See previous point on Moparcraft developer). 

[hr]

[b]Completing old tasks- [/b] Uhm, we still need a W2 world map and the SSP I think they&#39;re both vital features  :rolleyes: 


[hr]
I don&#39;t want an empty thread this time, instead I want discussion. I&#39;m going to step up the pressure on agreed things until they get added. I spend huge amounts of my time trying to do positive things which will better the community but nothing ever seems to get done or even discussed most of the time. 

This isn&#39;t going to go away, and neither am I so I&#39;ll continue making these threads and reiterating myself until we have a real discussion where issues are resolved. 


UPDATE - I&#39;d also like to bring up the Tarkoff promotion nomination, is this going ahead, if so when?</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 21 Jan 2012 16:05:58 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Games</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/talk-about-a-borked-system/429869.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Talk about a borked system</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Tom Tom]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/tom">@Tom</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I’m on the IRC all day/night so if you’d like to drop by and have a chat feel free <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=5" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
<p>I’m sure Zuppers is there as well, in fact, we’re both there now. I can’t see Moparisthebest coming back on anytime soon anyway  :rolleyes:</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/talk-about-a-borked-system/429869/10">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/talk-about-a-borked-system/429869/10</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 21 Jan 2012 16:05:58 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-429869-10</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/talk-about-a-borked-system/429869.rss">Talk about a borked system</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Talk about a borked system</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@si_force Si Force]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/si_force">@si_force</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>So, I should be available for this tonight sometime. Is anybody else available, or another day?</p>
<p>edit: ah, it appears i have missed it</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/talk-about-a-borked-system/429869/9">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/talk-about-a-borked-system/429869/9</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 21 Jan 2012 16:04:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-429869-9</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/talk-about-a-borked-system/429869.rss">Talk about a borked system</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Talk about a borked system</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Tom Tom]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/tom">@Tom</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>All good, just realized it’s Friday so I can do anywhere up to 12PM GMT, Si Force.</p>
<p>I just hope MITB can make it now…</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/talk-about-a-borked-system/429869/8">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/talk-about-a-borked-system/429869/8</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jan 2012 07:47:42 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-429869-8</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/talk-about-a-borked-system/429869.rss">Talk about a borked system</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Talk about a borked system</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@zuppers zuppers]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/zuppers">@zuppers</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Alright tomorrow I’ll drop in. I’ve gotten a few new ideas as of late.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/talk-about-a-borked-system/429869/7">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/talk-about-a-borked-system/429869/7</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2012 23:26:43 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-429869-7</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/talk-about-a-borked-system/429869.rss">Talk about a borked system</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Talk about a borked system</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@si_force Si Force]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/si_force">@si_force</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I can do it tomorrow at around 10/11 pm GMT but that is not certain. I can be certain about a time on Saturday though.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/talk-about-a-borked-system/429869/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/talk-about-a-borked-system/429869/6</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2012 22:59:55 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-429869-6</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/talk-about-a-borked-system/429869.rss">Talk about a borked system</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Talk about a borked system</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Tom Tom]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/tom">@Tom</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I agree with a staff meeting, I’ll as usual specify a time slot then other staff can change it until it works for everyone!</p>
<p>Tomorrow, anywhere between 4PM GMT and 9PM GMT? Later date or?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/talk-about-a-borked-system/429869/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/talk-about-a-borked-system/429869/5</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2012 22:45:47 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-429869-5</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/talk-about-a-borked-system/429869.rss">Talk about a borked system</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Talk about a borked system</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@si_force Si Force]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/si_force">@si_force</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>If we’re going to revamp the rules of the server, then I would suggest that we all meet up in the IRC to discuss the matter and designate a person to write notes on what we agree on, and what are possibilities. We also shouldn’t be aiming to create a lot of rules, it’s off-putting to members.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/talk-about-a-borked-system/429869/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/talk-about-a-borked-system/429869/4</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2012 22:43:52 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-429869-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/talk-about-a-borked-system/429869.rss">Talk about a borked system</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Talk about a borked system</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Tom Tom]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/tom">@Tom</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I’ve brought up the VPS argument before, apparently the current server it is hosted on is very good therefore spending money would be a waste. I’ve also said before that there should be a control panel in which a certain group of people can do things themselves, he agreed with this, five months ago <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=5" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
<p>As for the staff disagreements, I agree they can be beneficial but drawing them out for everyone to see in a fighting fashion isn’t my idea of a respectable debate. My point was if a real disagreement occurs they should be handled in private rather than dragging their reputation through the dirt. Basically this:</p>
<aside class="quote quote-modified" data-post="2" data-topic="429869">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/user_avatar/forum.moparisthebest.com/davidi2/40/2579_1.png" class="avatar"> Davidi2:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Just need to make sure the playerbase doesn’t see any argument or important discussion <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/wink.png?v=5" title=":wink:" class="emoji" alt=":wink:"></p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>As for rewriting the server, I don’t think anyone would be willing to do that…</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/talk-about-a-borked-system/429869/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/talk-about-a-borked-system/429869/3</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2012 21:33:51 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-429869-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/talk-about-a-borked-system/429869.rss">Talk about a borked system</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Talk about a borked system</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@davidi2 Davidi2]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/davidi2">@davidi2</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Not sure if I should be replying but I will anyways!</p>
<p>[quote=“Tom_BETA, post:1, topic:429869”]Everything that is done on Moparcraft is inefficient and relies mainly on Moparisthebest, instead of adding to the list of tasks he has to do we should instead look to create an efficient system which is self running without intervention.[/quote]I agree. The issue is however, MITB doesn’t want to give anyone access to where the server is current hosted because it’s the same place as the website. This ties into another point, I think MITB should maybe just spend a small amount of money and get a decent VPS that some of you can have access to.</p>
<p>As for lack of staff agreement, that isn’t going to change, and I think it’s a good thing to have multiple views. Just need to make sure the playerbase doesn’t see any argument or important discussion <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/wink.png?v=5" title=":wink:" class="emoji" alt=":wink:"></p>
<p>With the lag… all I can suggest is to rewrite the server.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/talk-about-a-borked-system/429869/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/talk-about-a-borked-system/429869/2</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2012 21:29:40 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-429869-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/talk-about-a-borked-system/429869.rss">Talk about a borked system</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Talk about a borked system</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Tom Tom]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/tom">@Tom</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>This entire Moparcraft idea needs reworking, I may sound like a broken record when I say this because I’m sick of saying it myself. Everything that is done on Moparcraft is inefficient and relies mainly on Moparisthebest, instead of adding to the list of tasks he has to do we should instead look to create an efficient system which is self running without intervention.</p>
<p>An inefficient system is a bad system, in short. The most annoying thing is that it’s not a case of “I can’t think of anyways to improve the current system” it’s more a case of nothing getting changed to make it an efficient system.</p>
<p>So I’m going to spend some time going over the main issues which restrict server activity.</p>
<p>[hr]</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Server Updating - </span> This one is a killer, we take months to update and we rely on plugins which don’t even work most the time or contain unreasonable amounts of buggy features.</p>
<p>We should look for plugins which work the most effectively and review them before their use, none of us can be blamed because the author doesn’t update but let us remember that MITB has a lot of sponsored server money a programmer over at MITB forums would gladly update the plugin for a small fee per time.</p>
<p>If you’re willing to pay for other things to help other mopar communities, why wouldn’t you be willing to help MC?</p>
<p>[hr]</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Lack of staff agreement - </span> “members of the community look up to staff members” - quote from the __________ board. With a staff team which doesn’t agree on much we’re not exactly sending down the vibes of a popular well managed server, in short the rules need a rework to something that is universally agreed upon.</p>
<p>What is said in the staff section, stays in the staff section. Drawing blood on a staff related argument outside the section itself should be stopped. I’ll be the first to admit I’ve probably done this before.</p>
<p>[hr]</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">The lagg - </span> I’m not going to blame this on one single factor, but we need to start taking this issue more seriously because something is causing it. If it’s the 1.8.1 MC then we need to update ASAP (See previous point on Moparcraft developer).</p>
<p>[hr]</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Completing old tasks- </span> Uhm, we still need a W2 world map and the SSP I think they’re both vital features  :rolleyes:</p>
<p>[hr]<br>
I don’t want an empty thread this time, instead I want discussion. I’m going to step up the pressure on agreed things until they get added. I spend huge amounts of my time trying to do positive things which will better the community but nothing ever seems to get done or even discussed most of the time.</p>
<p>This isn’t going to go away, and neither am I so I’ll continue making these threads and reiterating myself until we have a real discussion where issues are resolved.</p>
<p>UPDATE - I’d also like to bring up the Tarkoff promotion nomination, is this going ahead, if so when?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/talk-about-a-borked-system/429869/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/talk-about-a-borked-system/429869/1</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2012 21:05:15 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-429869-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/talk-about-a-borked-system/429869.rss">Talk about a borked system</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
