<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Please can someone help?</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/please-can-someone-help/370211</link>
    <description>Ok I have been asking for someones help for almost a week and noone has responded in any help at all... :( Everyone says i haven&#39;t port forwarded correctly so I ask once more... Can someone please use teamviewer and show me how??? there are about 12 ip addresses that Apply to my machine and I have no idea which one To Connect. I also have a wierd router setup.. My modem connects to a router. That router connects to 1 computer and another router. the second router connects to 2 machines. So i have 2 routers in series... Do i need to port forward on both??? :confused: if so how whould i tell the first one to open to the second one?
Also I am not sure I am setting the ip up right in my client... I tried using a regualr ip instead of no-ip and i haven&#39;t gotten it to work either way... :( All the Players get back is &quot;Error connecting to server&quot; Any help??? My computer can connect if I change the clients ip to 127.0.0.1 (localhost) but as soon as i change it to anything else nothing works anymore... If someone can use teamviewer to fix this for me please! it gets really frustrating when you can&#39;t get a server to connect after 2 years! Come on, someone??? please??? no one can help me when all of you know how to do this?</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 24 Nov 2010 21:50:08 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/please-can-someone-help/370211.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Please can someone help?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Valcorex Valcorex]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/valcorex">@Valcorex</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Ok I have been asking for someones help for almost a week and noone has responded in any help at all… <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/frowning.png?v=5" title=":frowning:" class="emoji" alt=":frowning:"> Everyone says i haven’t port forwarded correctly so I ask once more… Can someone please use teamviewer and show me how??? there are about 12 ip addresses that Apply to my machine and I have no idea which one To Connect. I also have a wierd router setup… My modem connects to a router. That router connects to 1 computer and another router. the second router connects to 2 machines. So i have 2 routers in series… Do i need to port forward on both??? <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/confused.png?v=5" title=":confused:" class="emoji" alt=":confused:"> if so how whould i tell the first one to open to the second one?<br>
Also I am not sure I am setting the ip up right in my client… I tried using a regualr ip instead of no-ip and i haven’t gotten it to work either way… <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/frowning.png?v=5" title=":frowning:" class="emoji" alt=":frowning:"> All the Players get back is “Error connecting to server” Any help??? My computer can connect if I change the clients ip to 127.0.0.1 (localhost) but as soon as i change it to anything else nothing works anymore… If someone can use teamviewer to fix this for me please! it gets really frustrating when you can’t get a server to connect after 2 years! Come on, someone??? please??? no one can help me when all of you know how to do this?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/please-can-someone-help/370211/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/please-can-someone-help/370211/1</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 24 Nov 2010 21:50:08 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-370211-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/please-can-someone-help/370211.rss">Please can someone help?</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
