<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Software Engineering Degree</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/software-engineering-degree/543887</link>
    <description>Alright, I&#39;m still not 100% sure what I&#39;m wanting to major in, however I know the general area. I just can&#39;t decide what the best degree for me is, I&#39;m looking for the most options, but I don&#39;t want to close myself out of other potential options with what I pick. &quot;Software Engineering&quot; is the degree I&#39;m looking at, but there&#39;s so many different names I&#39;ve seen when I look for stuff like this. I&#39;ve seen a software development degree (Same think I&#39;m sure as engineering), but sometimes I let myself get confused. I would like to be a software engineer, good pay and a fun job for me, however, I would like the chance at game development. Game development is a much smaller market than software engineering, which is why I don&#39;t want the degree for it, I know software engineering would be the safer route, but if I get the opportunity to work for a game developer, I&#39;d like to. Mainly what I&#39;m asking is what would be the best exact degree for me to go after? Sometimes it feels like there&#39;s a lot of pressure on this topic because I hear people talking about some who get their degree and don&#39;t have anywhere to go, and I don&#39;t want to be that guy. What do you guys think?</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 12 Jun 2014 02:37:31 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>General Discussion</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/software-engineering-degree/543887.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Software Engineering Degree</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@tyb97 tyb97]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/tyb97">@tyb97</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Alright, I’m still not 100% sure what I’m wanting to major in, however I know the general area. I just can’t decide what the best degree for me is, I’m looking for the most options, but I don’t want to close myself out of other potential options with what I pick. “Software Engineering” is the degree I’m looking at, but there’s so many different names I’ve seen when I look for stuff like this. I’ve seen a software development degree (Same think I’m sure as engineering), but sometimes I let myself get confused. I would like to be a software engineer, good pay and a fun job for me, however, I would like the chance at game development. Game development is a much smaller market than software engineering, which is why I don’t want the degree for it, I know software engineering would be the safer route, but if I get the opportunity to work for a game developer, I’d like to. Mainly what I’m asking is what would be the best exact degree for me to go after? Sometimes it feels like there’s a lot of pressure on this topic because I hear people talking about some who get their degree and don’t have anywhere to go, and I don’t want to be that guy. What do you guys think?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/software-engineering-degree/543887/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/software-engineering-degree/543887/1</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jun 2014 02:37:31 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-543887-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/software-engineering-degree/543887.rss">Software Engineering Degree</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
