<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Help a little</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/help-a-little/149022</link>
    <description>Ok, I&#39;ve been trying to add specs to my server, because that seems to be what most people want, and what I want.  I have tried 3 different tuts on adding specs, and all 3 of them gave me errors.  Does anyone know a good tutorial that will help me get this accomplished?  All I really need is dds and d scimmy specs.  Dont flame is all I ask, everyone needs some help every once in a while, especially on stuff like this.  Thx, and appreciate all posts that aren&#39;t flames lol.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 05 Oct 2007 05:14:09 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/help-a-little/149022.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Help a little</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@zoltanman zoltanman]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/zoltanman">@zoltanman</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Well, once you get to know how to use java, and get to know the code, you should be able to add tutorials easier. If you get errors, and you know just a little java, you would be able to fix them. Take my advice into consideration ;). If you need a link to where you could learn, just pm me.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/help-a-little/149022/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/help-a-little/149022/2</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 05 Oct 2007 05:14:09 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-149022-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/help-a-little/149022.rss">Help a little</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Help a little</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@sp3c sp3c]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/sp3c">@sp3c</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Ok, I’ve been trying to add specs to my server, because that seems to be what most people want, and what I want.  I have tried 3 different tuts on adding specs, and all 3 of them gave me errors.  Does anyone know a good tutorial that will help me get this accomplished?  All I really need is dds and d scimmy specs.  Dont flame is all I ask, everyone needs some help every once in a while, especially on stuff like this.  Thx, and appreciate all posts that aren’t flames lol.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/help-a-little/149022/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/help-a-little/149022/1</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 05 Oct 2007 05:07:02 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-149022-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/help-a-little/149022.rss">Help a little</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
