<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Wolf Kingdom Game Concept</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/wolf-kingdom-game-concept/547221</link>
    <description>[b]Name:[/b] Wolf Kingdom
[b]Color Scheme:[/b] Resembling Diablo III
[b]Era:[/b] The medieval dark ages
[b]Basis:[/b] Rabies has driven the peaceful people of the land to become mad with blood lust.
[b]Goals:[/b] Survival as well as the accumulation of wealth and resources.
[b]Factions:[/b] Dragon Annihilators, Legionnaires, Rebels. Can attack any members only in the wilderness.
[b]Starting Location:[/b] Mystenhaven - final outpost, port town on the edge of the wilderness. Walls have NPC operated cannons to fire at nearby zombies. NPC cannon ammo is unlimited.
[b]Initial Game Engine:[/b] Hybrid of Moparscape Classic and DarkQuest
[b]Content:[/b] Eventually all original sprites once mechanics and main code are finished
[b]Financing:[/b] Owner financed, will not accept donations or use advertisements.
[b]Licencing:[/b] Open source and free to play
[b]Release Date:[/b] Q1 2015
[b]Player Support:[/b] Community provided via forum and IRC channel.
[b]PVP:[/b] All wilderness areas surrounding towns will be PVP enabled.
[b]Clans:[/b] Support for clans and temporary parties with related chat channels and mini map beacons.
[b]Experience:[/b] All players will be the same level. Armor and weaponry will degrade with use. Skills and clan support matter.
[b]Bots:[/b] Automated player bots will not survive in the wilderness against human players and zombies, grinding not needed.
[b]Skills:[/b] Leather working, smithing, crafting, tanning, hunting, woodcutting, cooking, fishing, herblaw, and beer brewing.
[b]Respawn Frequency:[/b] Ground items respawn in the wilderness every 4 hours. Resources respawn every 10 minutes (trees, rocks, fish, NPC animals) Zombies respawn every 5 minutes.
[b]Spawn Locations:[/b] Zombies, resources, and ground items spawn in set locations throughout only the wilderness.
[b]Zombies:[/b] Set to aggressive, wander distance set to &gt;= 40x40 tiles. Drops: random resources, bones. Set to poisonous.
[b]Player Death:[/b] Respawn in Mystenhaven, lose all carried items.
[b]Rabies Infection:[/b] If poisoned with rabies while in combat, death is guaranteed. Cannot consume food or potions to heal. All friendly NPCs now set aggressive and attackable. NPC operated fort wall cannons now fire upon. Able to poison/infect other players and friendly NPCs to become zombies.
[b]NPC vs NPC:[/b] Zombie NPCs can attack friendly NPCs and infect them to become zombies.
[b]Hunger, Thirst, Health:[/b] Thirst and hunger slowly increase over time. Food and drink must be consumed to replenish. 100% hunger or 100% thirst causes health to be lost quickly. Health replenishes automatically over time or with use of healing potions.
[b]Economy:[/b] Food, drinks, potions, resources, and crafted supplies can be traded between players at any price. No auction house or general store NPCs. Gold coins can be traded for beer brewing kits and other skill needed tools or between players as currency if they choose.
[b]Game Government:[/b] No moderators, no oversight, and no rules. Play any way that works best.





This should not be that difficult to set up. The Hunger and thirst numbers tied to health may take some time to figure out as well as the poison system and the faction system, but I&#39;ve played with enough of the game engine code over the last half decade to know where to get started. As development progresses and the GitHub repository is updated, I hope some will be interested in helping clean up the code and improve efficiency where possible. Working on this project to give myself a hobby where I can continue to keep learning. Intellectual stagnation while the tech world moves forward is a risk best avoided.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 11 Oct 2014 21:54:20 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/wolf-kingdom-game-concept/547221.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Wolf Kingdom Game Concept</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@cleako cleako]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/cleako">@cleako</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p><span class="bbcode-b">Name:</span> Wolf Kingdom<br>
<span class="bbcode-b">Color Scheme:</span> Resembling Diablo III<br>
<span class="bbcode-b">Era:</span> The medieval dark ages<br>
<span class="bbcode-b">Basis:</span> Rabies has driven the peaceful people of the land to become mad with blood lust.<br>
<span class="bbcode-b">Goals:</span> Survival as well as the accumulation of wealth and resources.<br>
<span class="bbcode-b">Factions:</span> Dragon Annihilators, Legionnaires, Rebels. Can attack any members only in the wilderness.<br>
<span class="bbcode-b">Starting Location:</span> Mystenhaven - final outpost, port town on the edge of the wilderness. Walls have NPC operated cannons to fire at nearby zombies. NPC cannon ammo is unlimited.<br>
<span class="bbcode-b">Initial Game Engine:</span> Hybrid of Moparscape Classic and DarkQuest<br>
<span class="bbcode-b">Content:</span> Eventually all original sprites once mechanics and main code are finished<br>
<span class="bbcode-b">Financing:</span> Owner financed, will not accept donations or use advertisements.<br>
<span class="bbcode-b">Licencing:</span> Open source and free to play<br>
<span class="bbcode-b">Release Date:</span> Q1 2015<br>
<span class="bbcode-b">Player Support:</span> Community provided via forum and IRC channel.<br>
<span class="bbcode-b">PVP:</span> All wilderness areas surrounding towns will be PVP enabled.<br>
<span class="bbcode-b">Clans:</span> Support for clans and temporary parties with related chat channels and mini map beacons.<br>
<span class="bbcode-b">Experience:</span> All players will be the same level. Armor and weaponry will degrade with use. Skills and clan support matter.<br>
<span class="bbcode-b">Bots:</span> Automated player bots will not survive in the wilderness against human players and zombies, grinding not needed.<br>
<span class="bbcode-b">Skills:</span> Leather working, smithing, crafting, tanning, hunting, woodcutting, cooking, fishing, herblaw, and beer brewing.<br>
<span class="bbcode-b">Respawn Frequency:</span> Ground items respawn in the wilderness every 4 hours. Resources respawn every 10 minutes (trees, rocks, fish, NPC animals) Zombies respawn every 5 minutes.<br>
<span class="bbcode-b">Spawn Locations:</span> Zombies, resources, and ground items spawn in set locations throughout only the wilderness.<br>
<span class="bbcode-b">Zombies:</span> Set to aggressive, wander distance set to &gt;= 40x40 tiles. Drops: random resources, bones. Set to poisonous.<br>
<span class="bbcode-b">Player Death:</span> Respawn in Mystenhaven, lose all carried items.<br>
<span class="bbcode-b">Rabies Infection:</span> If poisoned with rabies while in combat, death is guaranteed. Cannot consume food or potions to heal. All friendly NPCs now set aggressive and attackable. NPC operated fort wall cannons now fire upon. Able to poison/infect other players and friendly NPCs to become zombies.<br>
<span class="bbcode-b">NPC vs NPC:</span> Zombie NPCs can attack friendly NPCs and infect them to become zombies.<br>
<span class="bbcode-b">Hunger, Thirst, Health:</span> Thirst and hunger slowly increase over time. Food and drink must be consumed to replenish. 100% hunger or 100% thirst causes health to be lost quickly. Health replenishes automatically over time or with use of healing potions.<br>
<span class="bbcode-b">Economy:</span> Food, drinks, potions, resources, and crafted supplies can be traded between players at any price. No auction house or general store NPCs. Gold coins can be traded for beer brewing kits and other skill needed tools or between players as currency if they choose.<br>
<span class="bbcode-b">Game Government:</span> No moderators, no oversight, and no rules. Play any way that works best.</p>
<p>This should not be that difficult to set up. The Hunger and thirst numbers tied to health may take some time to figure out as well as the poison system and the faction system, but I’ve played with enough of the game engine code over the last half decade to know where to get started. As development progresses and the GitHub repository is updated, I hope some will be interested in helping clean up the code and improve efficiency where possible. Working on this project to give myself a hobby where I can continue to keep learning. Intellectual stagnation while the tech world moves forward is a risk best avoided.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/wolf-kingdom-game-concept/547221/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/wolf-kingdom-game-concept/547221/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 11 Oct 2014 21:54:20 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-547221-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/wolf-kingdom-game-concept/547221.rss">Wolf Kingdom Game Concept</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
