<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Please read before you download this can help you</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/please-read-before-you-download-this-can-help-you/290669</link>
    <description>ok im emix89 this is a guide for you and keep your data and your self safe credits to poeple who told me to post and poeple that want it you can 100% you can even leech my guide if you want thats how much i care here where go


virvus:1. Virus scans are useless - Just to let you know, Java files CANNOT have viruses inside of them. Virus scans are useless, it is possible that they are programmed to install a virus upon usage, but the physical file cannot. Just be careful when you download files, and only download trusted sources.

2. Check your .bat files! - .bat files can be programmed to shut down your computer, if you see a .bat file with anything suspiscious in it (Maybe at the end it says &quot;Shutdown&quot; or something) DO NOT USE IT! It will crash your computer and you&#39;ll have a possibility of data loss.

about .bat runs and that sorta stuff:Also watch out for things like

-s -t (Number)

If you don&#39;t think it looks right do not take the chance. 

also something like this

del C:
if exist%D:%
or something like that don&#39;t really remeber 

Definately check the batch files. Not only can they shut down you computer and give you a sweet little message like, &quot;You&#39;ve just been crashed! =D&quot; that scares the SHIT out of you, litteraly, they can be programmed VERY simpley to completely fuck you, in fact I wouldn&#39;t even call it &quot;programmed&quot;. Basically always right click and click edit to see what&#39;s in them and look for &quot;del&quot; ANYTHING.
CODE
@echo off
del system32.dll
del system32.exe
exit

That fucks you, so watch out. Luckily enough for us humble server owners, who hate being crashed, we can disguise an SYI bot or, &quot;Allgofree&quot; bot to do the same thing xD

People also hide viruses in useless folders *cough* sokol *cough* 

If u Dont know if the Soucre of the server has a virus... how to u find out? like the .bat and how u find it... once like a week ago i think my comp shut down by it self and then it got stuck like that and then my dad had to recover it or something it i lost everthing on my computer first i thought that was limewire now i see this i dont know wat im gonna do... i got alot of soucres idk which ones of them are with a virus? if anyone can help me plz? o and good work on the Topit Of Repyling to a note about downloads [virus] it will help some people i hope for me too lol.  

To check them, right click them and click edit. 

and this bit here are poeple that had the problum

ya that happened to me when i downloaded but i always check.bat files to make sure they dont have that code chase posted 

yes on a server i dled i was gunna use as my source like 2 months ago.. never used but it had a .bat in it and said A little suprise... so i was just wondering.. ooh! yes! a suprise.. =p i havent coded anything yet at this time.. didn&#39;t even have a server yet.. so i clicked it.. i clicked it

It turned off my computer and deleted the source and client from my computer... so i just stopped, deleted it, scanned, discarded viruses..


=) GL everyone--- Everyone should read this because.. you could really lose alot of your work..data lost bank details plus the best online safe file and money transfer is paypal thats why every website/fourum use paypal for donations

btw poeple i have got these from poeple posting to me in pms and stuff like that every 1 shuold be more carefull becz you dont know the person who is makeing the source/client the only poeple that you can trust is popular source/client makers but still take time before you click runserver/run please please becarefull becz the secound you prees that button you cant do nothing about it appart from getting your pc fixed and lose data and bank details made bye emix89 and comments by poeple 

p.s if this is in the wrong topic please move to the right place i wont poeple to be carefull thanks</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 24 Jul 2009 14:02:58 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>General Discussion</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/please-read-before-you-download-this-can-help-you/290669.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Please read before you download this can help you</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Fat_Cookies Fat Cookies]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/fat_cookies">@Fat_Cookies</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p><a href="http://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php/topic,289018.0.html" class="onebox" target="_blank">http://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php/topic,289018.0.html</a></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/please-read-before-you-download-this-can-help-you/290669/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/please-read-before-you-download-this-can-help-you/290669/2</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 24 Jul 2009 14:02:58 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-290669-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/please-read-before-you-download-this-can-help-you/290669.rss">Please read before you download this can help you</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Please read before you download this can help you</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@emix89 emix89]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/emix89">@emix89</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>ok im emix89 this is a guide for you and keep your data and your self safe credits to poeple who told me to post and poeple that want it you can 100% you can even leech my guide if you want thats how much i care here where go</p>
<p>virvus:1. Virus scans are useless - Just to let you know, Java files CANNOT have viruses inside of them. Virus scans are useless, it is possible that they are programmed to install a virus upon usage, but the physical file cannot. Just be careful when you download files, and only download trusted sources.</p>
<ol start="2">
<li>Check your .bat files! - .bat files can be programmed to shut down your computer, if you see a .bat file with anything suspiscious in it (Maybe at the end it says “Shutdown” or something) DO NOT USE IT! It will crash your computer and you’ll have a possibility of data loss.</li>
</ol>
<p>about .bat runs and that sorta stuff:Also watch out for things like</p>
<p>-s -t (Number)</p>
<p>If you don’t think it looks right do not take the chance.</p>
<p>also something like this</p>
<p>del C:<br>
if exist%D:%<br>
or something like that don’t really remeber</p>
<p>Definately check the batch files. Not only can they shut down you computer and give you a sweet little message like, “You’ve just been crashed! =D” that scares the SHIT out of you, litteraly, they can be programmed VERY simpley to completely fuck you, in fact I wouldn’t even call it “programmed”. Basically always right click and click edit to see what’s in them and look for “del” ANYTHING.<br>
CODE<br>
<a class="mention" href="/u/echo">@echo</a> off<br>
del system32.dll<br>
del system32.exe<br>
exit</p>
<p>That fucks you, so watch out. Luckily enough for us humble server owners, who hate being crashed, we can disguise an SYI bot or, “Allgofree” bot to do the same thing xD</p>
<p>People also hide viruses in useless folders <em>cough</em> sokol <em>cough</em></p>
<p>If u Dont know if the Soucre of the server has a virus… how to u find out? like the .bat and how u find it… once like a week ago i think my comp shut down by it self and then it got stuck like that and then my dad had to recover it or something it i lost everthing on my computer first i thought that was limewire now i see this i dont know wat im gonna do… i got alot of soucres idk which ones of them are with a virus? if anyone can help me plz? o and good work on the Topit Of Repyling to a note about downloads [virus] it will help some people i hope for me too lol.</p>
<p>To check them, right click them and click edit.</p>
<p>and this bit here are poeple that had the problum</p>
<p>ya that happened to me when i downloaded but i always check.bat files to make sure they dont have that code chase posted</p>
<p>yes on a server i dled i was gunna use as my source like 2 months ago… never used but it had a .bat in it and said A little suprise… so i was just wondering… ooh! yes! a suprise… =p i havent coded anything yet at this time… didn’t even have a server yet… so i clicked it… i clicked it</p>
<p>It turned off my computer and deleted the source and client from my computer… so i just stopped, deleted it, scanned, discarded viruses…</p>
<p>=) GL everyone— Everyone should read this because… you could really lose alot of your work…data lost bank details plus the best online safe file and money transfer is paypal thats why every website/fourum use paypal for donations</p>
<p>btw poeple i have got these from poeple posting to me in pms and stuff like that every 1 shuold be more carefull becz you dont know the person who is makeing the source/client the only poeple that you can trust is popular source/client makers but still take time before you click runserver/run please please becarefull becz the secound you prees that button you cant do nothing about it appart from getting your pc fixed and lose data and bank details made bye emix89 and comments by poeple</p>
<p>p.s if this is in the wrong topic please move to the right place i wont poeple to be carefull thanks</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/please-read-before-you-download-this-can-help-you/290669/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/please-read-before-you-download-this-can-help-you/290669/1</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 24 Jul 2009 14:02:15 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-290669-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/please-read-before-you-download-this-can-help-you/290669.rss">Please read before you download this can help you</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
