<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Telnet Server</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/telnet-server/392545</link>
    <description>Okay, so I want to create either a new server, or a different protocol handler for my server that basically acts as an administrative connection. Easiest way I thought of was to just use telnet with an SRP-6 login to ensure security (maybe an RSA key as well). Now, it won&#39;t be used for handling things like editing the source or anything like that (I&#39;d probably just SSH to the server), but it would do things like reload scripts, audit character files, etc. I&#39;ve got the framework down (since telnet is just a string based protocol), but it&#39;s the interrupts that get me messed up. For example ^C, and ^D. 

When I do ^C, the server receives
&lt;blockquote&gt;[-1, -12, -1, -3, 6]&lt;/blockquote&gt;

And when I do ^D, the server receives
&lt;blockquote&gt;[4]&lt;/blockquote&gt;

I looked up the ascii equivalents for those keys, and it doesn&#39;t make any sense. I checked the RFC for telnet, and it didn&#39;t tell me anything either. Does anyone know what those mean?</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 27 Apr 2011 16:48:33 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>General Programming</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/telnet-server/392545.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Telnet Server</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Graham Graham]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/graham">@Graham</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>For ^C, if you convert those values to the unsigned equivalents, you’ll see that they are:</p>
<p>255 244 255 253 6</p>
<p>These translate to the telnet commands:</p>
<p>IAC IP IAC DO 6</p>
<p>IAC IP means interrupt process which is kind of self-explanatory. IAC DO 6 requests that the server enables the “timing mark” option. The RFC for that option is available here: <a href="http://www.apps.ietf.org/rfc/rfc860.html" rel="nofollow noopener">http://www.apps.ietf.org/rfc/rfc860.html</a></p>
<p>The most useful point of that page for explaining what it does is this:</p>
<blockquote>It is sometimes useful for a user or process at one end of a TELNET connection to be sure that previously transmitted data has been completely processed, printed, discarded, or otherwise disposed of</blockquote>
<p>So essentially, it’s requesting that you interrupt the process and then send an indication back (you’ll need to read the RFC for the complete info on this) that it has actually been ended.</p>
<p>The IANA website has a useful list of individual options for the DO/DONT/WILL/WONT commands available here:</p>
<p><a href="http://www.iana.org/assignments/telnet-options" class="onebox" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">http://www.iana.org/assignments/telnet-options</a></p>
<p>The ^D stuff translates directly to the ASCII code “end of transmission” directly so that isn’t as hard as the sequence I’ve just explained :p.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/telnet-server/392545/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/telnet-server/392545/3</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 27 Apr 2011 16:48:33 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-392545-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/telnet-server/392545.rss">Telnet Server</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Telnet Server</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@ollie123 Ollie123]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/ollie123">@ollie123</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Why not just write your own text-based protocol?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/telnet-server/392545/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/telnet-server/392545/2</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 27 Apr 2011 14:48:54 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-392545-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/telnet-server/392545.rss">Telnet Server</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Telnet Server</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@zyle1992 Zymus]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/zyle1992">@zyle1992</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Okay, so I want to create either a new server, or a different protocol handler for my server that basically acts as an administrative connection. Easiest way I thought of was to just use telnet with an SRP-6 login to ensure security (maybe an RSA key as well). Now, it won’t be used for handling things like editing the source or anything like that (I’d probably just SSH to the server), but it would do things like reload scripts, audit character files, etc. I’ve got the framework down (since telnet is just a string based protocol), but it’s the interrupts that get me messed up. For example ^C, and ^D.</p>
<p>When I do ^C, the server receives</p>
<blockquote>[-1, -12, -1, -3, 6]</blockquote>
<p>And when I do ^D, the server receives</p>
<blockquote>[4]</blockquote>
<p>I looked up the ascii equivalents for those keys, and it doesn’t make any sense. I checked the RFC for telnet, and it didn’t tell me anything either. Does anyone know what those mean?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/telnet-server/392545/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/telnet-server/392545/1</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 25 Apr 2011 17:08:42 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-392545-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/telnet-server/392545.rss">Telnet Server</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
