<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Need help from a good/experienced coder!</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/need-help-from-a-good-experienced-coder/336664</link>
    <description>I need alot of help. I&#39;m very new to coding servers and I&#39;m only learning. (508 Server) If it matters at all, the source is a Bulby source.

 1. On my server, when you right click someone, there&#39;s an option called &quot;duel&quot; well then if the other person accepts it, it goes right to the duel. I want to make it so you could stake. Possible and if so how do I?
 
 2. How would I make the Falador Drop Party place work? I want it so when you click on the chest, you could add items and when you pull the lever, balloons come down that you could pop and possibly find objects in.

 3. Is it possible to make a lending system on my server? Not something I really need but sort of curious about this one.

 4. Whenever I make commands, they always fail. I always get a problem compiling when I do. I have several command generators/makers that will generate the code for me and help me learn how to make commands.

 5. I tried to make it so whenever I yell, it says [Server Owner &amp; Coder] (name), and for the co-owners/admins, it says [Co-Owner] (name). So I decided to change it a little bit and make it so it says [Server Owner &amp; Coder] (name) for players with the rights of 3. But of course, another problem. When I talk regularly in the regular public chat, there&#39;s no crown in front of my name because my rights are 3. I ran 2 clients at once and saw that there&#39;s no crown in front of my name in public chat, but in private chat (Pms), there was a crown in front of my name. I still have to try in the clan chat, and I&#39;ll update this whenever I found out if it works in the clans or not. Edit: It also won&#39;t let me do admin or even the mod commands, only the commands specially designed for the owner with the player rights at 3.

 6. This is an edit because I found another. I tried out pking in the wildy, and you don&#39;t get what you killed the person for. So if I make a place called &quot;dangerous pk&quot; (::dangerouspk) how would I make it so it would drop whatever the person was wearing/had in inventory?

 Probably more coming soon once I look through and find more stuff. Thanks! :)</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 13 Apr 2010 00:03:17 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/need-help-from-a-good-experienced-coder/336664.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Need help from a good/experienced coder!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@logan6305 logan6305]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/logan6305">@logan6305</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I need alot of help. I’m very new to coding servers and I’m only learning. (508 Server) If it matters at all, the source is a Bulby source.</p>
<ol>
<li>
<p>On my server, when you right click someone, there’s an option called “duel” well then if the other person accepts it, it goes right to the duel. I want to make it so you could stake. Possible and if so how do I?</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>How would I make the Falador Drop Party place work? I want it so when you click on the chest, you could add items and when you pull the lever, balloons come down that you could pop and possibly find objects in.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Is it possible to make a lending system on my server? Not something I really need but sort of curious about this one.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Whenever I make commands, they always fail. I always get a problem compiling when I do. I have several command generators/makers that will generate the code for me and help me learn how to make commands.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>I tried to make it so whenever I yell, it says [Server Owner &amp; Coder] (name), and for the co-owners/admins, it says [Co-Owner] (name). So I decided to change it a little bit and make it so it says [Server Owner &amp; Coder] (name) for players with the rights of 3. But of course, another problem. When I talk regularly in the regular public chat, there’s no crown in front of my name because my rights are 3. I ran 2 clients at once and saw that there’s no crown in front of my name in public chat, but in private chat (Pms), there was a crown in front of my name. I still have to try in the clan chat, and I’ll update this whenever I found out if it works in the clans or not. Edit: It also won’t let me do admin or even the mod commands, only the commands specially designed for the owner with the player rights at 3.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>This is an edit because I found another. I tried out pking in the wildy, and you don’t get what you killed the person for. So if I make a place called “dangerous pk” (::dangerouspk) how would I make it so it would drop whatever the person was wearing/had in inventory?</p>
</li>
</ol>
<p>Probably more coming soon once I look through and find more stuff. Thanks! <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=5" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/need-help-from-a-good-experienced-coder/336664/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/need-help-from-a-good-experienced-coder/336664/1</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 13 Apr 2010 00:03:17 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-336664-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/need-help-from-a-good-experienced-coder/336664.rss">Need help from a good/experienced coder!</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
