<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Emo Story By Goog</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/emo-story-by-goog/16538</link>
    <description>I wrote this awhile back for someone in graphics who had made a pic saying &quot;Cheer up emo kid!&quot; or something like that.


NOTE: Michael&#39;s girlfriend&#39;s name is from FFVIII, if you are wondering. And I was wearing a Misfits shirt while writing this, hence the Misfits part.
					MICHAEL THE EMO BEAR
	Michael died on June 6, 2006 from slitting his wrists after a good cry in his walk-in closet.
You see, Michael was depressed for no apparent reason, besides his obsession with stupid pop-emo/screamo
bands like &quot;My Chemical Romance&quot;, &quot;Atreyu&quot;, and &quot;Silverstein&quot;.He had become so obsessed with these bands
that he began to think that you had to be emo to fit in. This delusion had been created by the combination
of the music he listened to, the recent murder of his steady girlfriend, his best friend (an emo squirrel) 
and his incurable problem, bipolarity. He became emo slowly so his parents would hardly notice the difference,
but they wouldn&#39;t have, because they were apathetic and alcoholic. Had they been sober at least 4 hours a day,
perhaps they would have saved Michael from the evil plague of emoism. But I can&#39;t describe his life this
way. He would eat me if I did. So here&#39;s Michael&#39;s story, from the perspective of his best friend, Roger.

	Michael was 9 years old when I met him. We didn&#39;t have much in common, except for us living in the
forest together, and we were on the same food chain. We were an odd pair, and we couldn&#39;t play on the same 
playgrounds, but that didn&#39;t matter to us. We quickly became inseparable, even though he would try to eat me 
when he was very hungry and his mother was making lasagna or the like. As we grew up, I introduced him to
things like emo music, and &quot;scene&quot; clothes. I had fully evolved into my emo state by the time I was 15, but
Michael was a bit slower. It took him til he was 17, and it was a slow change. But it happened, and he was
made into a martyr when he commited suicide.

	Michael&#39;s girlfriend was named Edea, an emo to a nearly impossible extremity. She had scars all over
her arms, as the skin on her wrists had hardened after she had cut it so many times. But she was afraid of
death, and always stopped the bleeding when she felt she would pass out. However, on the eve of her 19th
birthday, she was walking to my house when she was confronted by a man in what appeared to be a mental
hospital outfit. Indeed, his clothing read &quot;5051&quot; when the light shone on it, letting Edea know that she
was dealing with a psycho. He pulled a knife and quietly said, &quot;Die, die, die, my darling...&quot; Edea screamed,
&quot;OMG!!! You&#39;re a Misfits fan! So am I!&quot; The man replied, &quot;No, I was singing the Metallica cover of the song.
The Misfits are awesome too. I especially like Teenagers From Mars. Now take this blade in your stomach!&quot;
Edea gave a soft moan as the man shoved a knife into her stomach exactly 94 times. He then cut her wrists,
as he believed it would make it appear she had commited suicide. When Edea didn&#39;t arrive after 2 hours, 
Michael panicked and ran out to the streets, only to find his dead girlfriend lying on the pavement.
&quot;Oh noes!!!&quot;, he cried in anguish, &quot;My girl has been murderz0red!&quot; Crying, he ran home and ran straight to his
closet, with me in hot pursuit. He began crying, and continued for about 2 hours. I even cried with him, for
good measure. He then told me in a soft voice, &quot;Go get me a sharp razor...&quot; I did as he said, and came quickly
back.

	He began cutting his non-existent bear wrists. Cut, cut, cut, the razor swiped in almost perfect time
with the Silverstein music that played in the background. Michael was getting frantic, as he couldn&#39;t find his 
wrists. Eventually he found them, and the razor sliced the veins like they were nothing. Blood shot everywhere,
and he quickly was dying. &quot;Ummm...should I call a paramedic?&quot;, I asked timidly. &quot;NO!!&quot;, he yelled, &quot;I&#39;m gonna
die tonight!&quot; And indeed, three minutes later, his heart stopped pumping, and he had ceased to live. I picked
up his razor and began to cut all of his fur off, for no reason that I could think of. I died too that night...
but emotionally, not physically like Michael and Edea. I softly said at his funeral, &quot;The end...&quot;</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 29 Sep 2006 20:12:12 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>General Discussion</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/emo-story-by-goog/16538.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Emo Story By Goog</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Akriam Akriam]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/akriam">@Akriam</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Yes lol, I dunno I just found that humorous that they were talking about metalica.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/emo-story-by-goog/16538/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/emo-story-by-goog/16538/6</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 29 Sep 2006 20:12:12 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-16538-6</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/emo-story-by-goog/16538.rss">Emo Story By Goog</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Emo Story By Goog</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@googlethis googlethis]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/googlethis">@googlethis</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Yes, it was intended to be humorous. And how do you know they don’t talk? I imagine some of them do, like the torture artists.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/emo-story-by-goog/16538/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/emo-story-by-goog/16538/5</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 29 Sep 2006 20:09:39 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-16538-5</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/emo-story-by-goog/16538.rss">Emo Story By Goog</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Emo Story By Goog</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@therealjdb JDB`]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/therealjdb">@therealjdb</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I also forgot to say that I found the stabbed 94 times and thought it would look like a suicide was pretty fu*king funny <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=9" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/emo-story-by-goog/16538/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/emo-story-by-goog/16538/4</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 29 Sep 2006 20:01:18 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-16538-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/emo-story-by-goog/16538.rss">Emo Story By Goog</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Emo Story By Goog</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Akriam Akriam]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/akriam">@Akriam</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Pretty good storry. Was that supposed to be funny <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=9" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"> Becasue most killers don’t make conversation with you :p[br][size=1]Posted at: September 29, 2006, 09:57:18 AM[/size][hr]now read my stories from akriam’s library <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=9" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/emo-story-by-goog/16538/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/emo-story-by-goog/16538/3</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 29 Sep 2006 19:58:17 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-16538-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/emo-story-by-goog/16538.rss">Emo Story By Goog</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Emo Story By Goog</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@therealjdb JDB`]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/therealjdb">@therealjdb</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Wow…IMO I really could care less about some emo’s dying or whatever but I got a good laugh out of it. </p><blockquote>“Oh noes!!!”, he cried in anguish, “My girl has been murderz0red!”</blockquote> that part made me lol, irl.
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/emo-story-by-goog/16538/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/emo-story-by-goog/16538/2</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 29 Sep 2006 19:55:21 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-16538-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/emo-story-by-goog/16538.rss">Emo Story By Goog</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Emo Story By Goog</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@googlethis googlethis]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/googlethis">@googlethis</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I wrote this awhile back for someone in graphics who had made a pic saying “Cheer up emo kid!” or something like that.</p>
<p>NOTE: Michael’s girlfriend’s name is from FFVIII, if you are wondering. And I was wearing a Misfits shirt while writing this, hence the Misfits part.<br>
MICHAEL THE EMO BEAR<br>
Michael died on June 6, 2006 from slitting his wrists after a good cry in his walk-in closet.<br>
You see, Michael was depressed for no apparent reason, besides his obsession with stupid pop-emo/screamo<br>
bands like “My Chemical Romance”, “Atreyu”, and “Silverstein”.He had become so obsessed with these bands<br>
that he began to think that you had to be emo to fit in. This delusion had been created by the combination<br>
of the music he listened to, the recent murder of his steady girlfriend, his best friend (an emo squirrel)<br>
and his incurable problem, bipolarity. He became emo slowly so his parents would hardly notice the difference,<br>
but they wouldn’t have, because they were apathetic and alcoholic. Had they been sober at least 4 hours a day,<br>
perhaps they would have saved Michael from the evil plague of emoism. But I can’t describe his life this<br>
way. He would eat me if I did. So here’s Michael’s story, from the perspective of his best friend, Roger.</p>
<pre><code>Michael was 9 years old when I met him. We didn't have much in common, except for us living in the
</code></pre>
<p>forest together, and we were on the same food chain. We were an odd pair, and we couldn’t play on the same<br>
playgrounds, but that didn’t matter to us. We quickly became inseparable, even though he would try to eat me<br>
when he was very hungry and his mother was making lasagna or the like. As we grew up, I introduced him to<br>
things like emo music, and “scene” clothes. I had fully evolved into my emo state by the time I was 15, but<br>
Michael was a bit slower. It took him til he was 17, and it was a slow change. But it happened, and he was<br>
made into a martyr when he commited suicide.</p>
<pre><code>Michael's girlfriend was named Edea, an emo to a nearly impossible extremity. She had scars all over
</code></pre>
<p>her arms, as the skin on her wrists had hardened after she had cut it so many times. But she was afraid of<br>
death, and always stopped the bleeding when she felt she would pass out. However, on the eve of her 19th<br>
birthday, she was walking to my house when she was confronted by a man in what appeared to be a mental<br>
hospital outfit. Indeed, his clothing read “5051” when the light shone on it, letting Edea know that she<br>
was dealing with a psycho. He pulled a knife and quietly said, “Die, die, die, my darling…” Edea screamed,<br>
“OMG!!! You’re a Misfits fan! So am I!” The man replied, “No, I was singing the Metallica cover of the song.<br>
The Misfits are awesome too. I especially like Teenagers From Mars. Now take this blade in your stomach!”<br>
Edea gave a soft moan as the man shoved a knife into her stomach exactly 94 times. He then cut her wrists,<br>
as he believed it would make it appear she had commited suicide. When Edea didn’t arrive after 2 hours,<br>
Michael panicked and ran out to the streets, only to find his dead girlfriend lying on the pavement.<br>
“Oh noes!!!”, he cried in anguish, “My girl has been murderz0red!” Crying, he ran home and ran straight to his<br>
closet, with me in hot pursuit. He began crying, and continued for about 2 hours. I even cried with him, for<br>
good measure. He then told me in a soft voice, “Go get me a sharp razor…” I did as he said, and came quickly<br>
back.</p>
<pre><code>He began cutting his non-existent bear wrists. Cut, cut, cut, the razor swiped in almost perfect time
</code></pre>
<p>with the Silverstein music that played in the background. Michael was getting frantic, as he couldn’t find his<br>
wrists. Eventually he found them, and the razor sliced the veins like they were nothing. Blood shot everywhere,<br>
and he quickly was dying. “Ummm…should I call a paramedic?”, I asked timidly. “NO!!”, he yelled, “I’m gonna<br>
die tonight!” And indeed, three minutes later, his heart stopped pumping, and he had ceased to live. I picked<br>
up his razor and began to cut all of his fur off, for no reason that I could think of. I died too that night…<br>
but emotionally, not physically like Michael and Edea. I softly said at his funeral, “The end…”</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/emo-story-by-goog/16538/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/emo-story-by-goog/16538/1</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 29 Sep 2006 10:26:28 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-16538-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/emo-story-by-goog/16538.rss">Emo Story By Goog</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
