<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Question about VPS/hosting/webhosting</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/question-about-vps-hosting-webhosting/539432</link>
    <description>Greetings to everybody. 

I have run a few servers in the past, some bigger than others. This time I kind of want to bring back a server mostly for fun, but also to see how much I can apply the knowledge I&#39;ve gained in my two year absence from private servers (I&#39;m studying networking in college, this is my last semester of a two year program). I understand a lot of the server part. I also am looking into creating a pretty decent website, and putting some forums on there- probably adding some kind of way of integrating the server with the forum database as well.

I have a few questions on how everybody recommends I do this- I&#39;m looking to have the server service 50-100 players (it&#39;s a hopeful, but not too insane). I would normally look into hosting it from my place, but for personal reasons I&#39;m looking into getting a VPS this time around. How would you guys suggest I go about doing this with handling everything else however? Does anybody have any opinions on which distro to use for the VPS itself (Linux is much cheaper than windows vps services and more hardware efficient anyway, and faster to use imo)? Should I look into getting webhosting separate from the VPS itself- would it overcomplicate things to do so (I&#39;m not that knowledgable on SQL, but I know there&#39;s a lot of apache vulnerabilities, SQL injection, xss, etc that I wouldn&#39;t really feel comfortable putting on the main server)? Also, if I wanted to set up a donation engine, how would I go about semi- automating this? I&#39;d probably run it from paypal or something, but are there any software solutions to validate a payment (donation)?

Sorry for the kind of nooby questions, had to get them out there though :)</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2014 23:41:24 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>General Discussion</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/question-about-vps-hosting-webhosting/539432.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Question about VPS/hosting/webhosting</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Mod_Whip Mod Whip]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/mod_whip">@Mod_Whip</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Greetings to everybody.</p>
<p>I have run a few servers in the past, some bigger than others. This time I kind of want to bring back a server mostly for fun, but also to see how much I can apply the knowledge I’ve gained in my two year absence from private servers (I’m studying networking in college, this is my last semester of a two year program). I understand a lot of the server part. I also am looking into creating a pretty decent website, and putting some forums on there- probably adding some kind of way of integrating the server with the forum database as well.</p>
<p>I have a few questions on how everybody recommends I do this- I’m looking to have the server service 50-100 players (it’s a hopeful, but not too insane). I would normally look into hosting it from my place, but for personal reasons I’m looking into getting a VPS this time around. How would you guys suggest I go about doing this with handling everything else however? Does anybody have any opinions on which distro to use for the VPS itself (Linux is much cheaper than windows vps services and more hardware efficient anyway, and faster to use imo)? Should I look into getting webhosting separate from the VPS itself- would it overcomplicate things to do so (I’m not that knowledgable on SQL, but I know there’s a lot of apache vulnerabilities, SQL injection, xss, etc that I wouldn’t really feel comfortable putting on the main server)? Also, if I wanted to set up a donation engine, how would I go about semi- automating this? I’d probably run it from paypal or something, but are there any software solutions to validate a payment (donation)?</p>
<p>Sorry for the kind of nooby questions, had to get them out there though <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=5" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/question-about-vps-hosting-webhosting/539432/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/question-about-vps-hosting-webhosting/539432/1</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2014 23:41:24 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-539432-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/question-about-vps-hosting-webhosting/539432.rss">Question about VPS/hosting/webhosting</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
