<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>[T_R] You Should Read This Before Advertising a Ripped/Leeched Base</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/t-r-you-should-read-this-before-advertising-a-ripped-leeched-base/527541</link>
    <description>[size=24pt][i][color=red]Why your Server is a target for criticism and flaming:[/i][/size]




Hello. Thank you very much for viewing this Thread. Please take the time to read all of It&#39;s contents so that you will have a full understanding of what is posted and do not ask questions which were already addressed within the Thread.


[size=1]NOTE: This Tutorial is aimed at audiences which have little-to-no experience in the field of RuneScape Private Server development. This Tutorial is for the MoparScape users who advertise their Servers with absolutely 0 edits or modifications made to the original Base.[/size]


[b][i]Do you find yourself posting an Advertisement Thread, only to have forum users criticize and flame what you&#39;ve posted? Do you wish you could understand why this occurs and ways to improve? This Tutorial is aimed at addressing these issues. [/b]



[size=24pt]Updates which can wait:[/size]


[b][u]Written below are several subjects which are NOT important and should wait until after vital content and other features have been implemented in-game:[/u][/b]


_____________
- Text Strings: 

     These are NOT important and can be edited at any time with no effect on a closed Server in development. The only impact if done so during the Live game would be the recognition by the community of the change. This extends to strings such as the name of Bank, Teleport names, etcetera. You have much more important things to worry about. If you&#39;re stressed over naming your Server and have no thoughts concerning stability, content, structure, features, mechanics, and more -- your project is [b]NOT[/b] ready to be advertised and accept traffic.

______________________
- Donations and Rewards: 
     
     A very sensitive issue indeed. You should NOT include Donation-specific content (content only Donors can access). A person&#39;s financial status in real life should not influence an online game. The two should not be related. If you wish, you could always create cosmetic items which are exlusive to anyone who donates $5.00 U.S.D. or more towards the continuation of the Server. Something such as adding a &#39;Donor-only Shop&#39; with end-game equipment and items is a bad idea. The community is not very fond of users who host their Server only for a quick profit.

________
- Quests: 
     
     These can be very nice to have. Quests can open up a wide variety of different features, mechanics, story-line, lore. etcetera. If designed and structured correctly -- Quests can be engaging and a change of the usual pace for Players. However, if rushed, poorly designed and executed, these Quests can become a hassle and many Players will seek any way to avoid completion of these Quests. It is not a great idea to limit equipment to Players who have completed a Quest-line and unlocked content. You should not obsess over Quests until you make vast improvements to your Server and Client Base(s) as a whole.

_______
- Home: 
     
     The location of your Server&#39;s &quot;Home&quot; is usually where the most players reside and is the very first area which Players have access to. It is usually the area to where the Player is sent during the Death method and during the creation and registry of a new account. One of my pet-peeves is to see a project with absolutely zero effort or originality put into it... consisting of only renamed strings, custom items which were ripped line-for-line, areas crowded with objects, and sometimes not even bothering to modify the minute or mundane details. This Home location can be decided and edited/implemented within 2 minutes. I&#39;m not saying that the Home location doesn&#39;t matter, because indeed it does. For example, if your Server has a theme of far-away travel via boats and ships, you should consider a location such as the Void Knight Outpost as a Home. There are several reasons this makes sense besides matching the theme. On this island, there are three Shops, a Bank and four boats. Assuming that you&#39;re using 5-line dialogue frames, that is 20 options without the need to advance dialogue for more options. If an advancement selection was added for all of the transportation offers -- it would be 38-40 different locations to choose from. You should decide your Home location once you&#39;ve improved everything your Server has to offer. Using the knowledge gained from this, you should be able to utilize many advanced features and mechanics in the Home location. For example, if you place a Cage object such as the one at Yanille (you can use debug strings to display I.D) with a N.P.C. spawned inside. One could simply reference existing factors and conditions from the N.P.C. system and modify your N.P.C. with the selected information with adjustments to create a docile N.P.C. which cannot go outside of It&#39;s Cage which it is being held in. This is a &#39;cheaphax&#39; method of doing this next step as well, but one could also add an exception into the Attack N.P.C. Packet which would prevent a Player from using melee attacks on the caged N.P.C.







[size=24pt]Updates which should be your #1 priority:[/size]


[b][u]This is the point where the subjects you SHOULD implement are listed and explained. If you follow and abide by all of the following, then you will no doubt have a successful project:[/b]


_________
- Stability:
     
     The Stability of a Server and how reliably it will maintain It&#39;s uptime without blow-back, unforeseen adverse effects, or an outright crash should be your number one goal. You should be aware of several things, including the manner in which your Listener functions, writing which might lead to a &quot;memory leak&quot; (lol), which is probably an unstable timer or piece of code, the basic structure and framework of your Server, how to include a Database Core and .ini settings file (which can store Database information, Port info, Server info, etcetera). One should also be familiar with their Client revision. In R.S.P.S. your Client is your Server&#39;s worst enemy. You need to modify, rename, document, re-write and rinse/repeat Client-to-Server communications and visa-versa. Type out the word, &quot;Muffin&quot; into your reply when you post if you&#39;re still reading. The Client once advertised and released to the public (assuming desktop Client) should be closed-source and have preventions in place against reverse engineering and decompiling. All extra items should be packed into the Client&#39;s Cache instead of externally referencing.

___________
Originality:

     A good example of having original content or gameplay is by modifying existing skills and tweaking them in a major way. An example would be creating entirely new Skill systems for Thieving and Woodcutting. If your imagination falls short, then please refer to [url=http://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php/topic,642630]this thread.[/url] Another
example of this subject would be adding additional N.P.C. Combat styles and attacks. For example, an Archer might use regular iron arrows, but as their level increases in different locations, their quality and quantity of arrows also increases. The Player receives the arrows the N.P.C. had equipped as well and may pickup the N.P.C. arrows fired from It&#39;s bow. Karil the Tainted might rapidly attack the Player with a magical attack which drains prayer even if it does not hit or splashes. The player may freeze the N.P.C. or use another tactic, but Karil resorts to firing a large magical arrow which inflicts a heavy amount of range damage if the Player moves out of his range or attempts to flee.

_____________
Modifying Skills: 

     The average Player of a RuneScape Private Server does not plan on the Server existing forever or keeping their progress for a very long period of time. This should be addressed by developers and Staff members so that this is simply not the case. An example of modifying a skill for the better would be to increase the amount of ore you may mine from a single node, drastically increasing the rate and chance of obtaining ore based upon the quality of equipment and level in use, and having a banking point at a [u]reasonable[/u] distance. You could also adjust the Mining Skill to display different text strings to the Client based on a chance which is calculated based on their outfit (Skilling Outfits would be great on a R.S.P.S). According to the single random chance, they are given a message and extra ore saying, &quot;Due to your exceptional talents in Mining, you obtain _DOUBLE_ _TRIPLE_ QUAD_ _FETCHTYPE_ Ore!&quot;, etcetera. The Mining outfit hood - Teleportation device to selected Dragon Ore spots (Dragon Smithing can
and has been done in the past). The Mining outfit Vest - Allows the Player to right-click --&gt; Store up to 20 ore of any
type inside of their Vest. The Mining outfit Leggings - Enables the Player who is a Skiller or doesn&#39;t have the require stats to wield their Pickaxe to store it inside of the Leggings. The Mining outfit Gloves - Allows the Player to right-click --&gt; Extra Sensitive Perception Blessing; on the Gloves. This once clicked sends the Locations and total amount of all Players at all ore nodes in the entire game. The Mining Chains - Chains which serve as boots worn on the Player&#39;s feet. These Chains give a bonus of +25% Sprint Energy, +50% Energy regeneration rate, and +5 Agility levels if the Player has an inventory filled with any type of ore. Their inventory must consist of 28 of the same type of ore not noted to apply the Agility bonus. Smithy&#39;s Ancient Pickaxe - This Pickaxe is the rarest and most valued piece of the Mining outfit set. It applies the following: +4 noted ore of the same type mined when Player mines 1 type of an ore, 
a right-click --&gt; Summon Ancient Mineral Demon option; which summons a N.P.C. which will bank any type of ore in the Player&#39;s inventory once every 15 minutes; this N.P.C. can only deposit ore into your bank; cannot withdraw either.

____________
Extra Content:

     After you&#39;ve molded and formed your base into the Server/Client dream team you worked so hard to achieve, you might be asking yourself, &quot;Well... What do I do now?&quot;. The answer to that question, is to have some fun and add in 
so many little things and tidbits of content that it expands upon the total items database and results in a wider variety of reasons to become interested in the exploration aspect of gameplay. You could add over 50+ different types of food, beverages, and alcoholic drinks which almost no R.S.P.S. use. Create new and unique Crafting recipes, such as the ability to craft a Robin Hood Hat at level 95 Crafting.

_________
Familiarity:

     The R.S.P.S. developer or programmer should be familiar with the base they&#39;re working with. They should know the
general structure and design of the source. The Client chosen should be as renamed as possible. I recommend that you
use a 317 revision for your first source to mess with if you&#39;re a developer. You should gain familiarity with the Client and begin your own documentation which explains code in the way you can best understand. You can worry about being objective later.



[size=24pt]Summary:[/size]

[i][size=10pt]Attempt to make edits and modify the base you downloaded before hosting. If you&#39;re hosting with the intentions of making a quick dollar, then that&#39;s your business and not mine. This informative Thread was written in an attempt to decrease the amount of users who are ignorant in regards to programming and at least editing/modifying their source before hosting their &#39;project&#39; as a short-term cancer which only seeks the currency of It&#39;s Player-base.[/size]</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2013 18:15:20 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/t-r-you-should-read-this-before-advertising-a-ripped-leeched-base/527541.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>[T_R] You Should Read This Before Advertising a Ripped/Leeched Base</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@JavaTC JavaTC]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/javatc">@JavaTC</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“Teem_Rocket, post:15, topic:527541”][quote]<br>
Type out the word, “Muffin” into your reply when you post if you’re still reading.<br>
[/quote]</p>
<p>It’s good to know that when I write up these threads, nobody actually takes the time to read all of the lines. Why should I bother?[/quote]<br>
I don’t know, why should you?  The RSPS community is 95% snot nosed brats that only care about screenshotting their max hit so they can masturbate over it.  Those who aren’t tend to be lazy, or know that the RSPS scene is a bit of a waste of time if you wish to be taken seriously as a developer, so it’s more of a side project.</p>
<p>So if you want people to take it as serious as you, you’d have to make your own community and only allow those like you, witch is a silly idea.  I didn’t see that part of it but I did read over the whole thread, skipping some lines for times sake.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/t-r-you-should-read-this-before-advertising-a-ripped-leeched-base/527541/19">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/t-r-you-should-read-this-before-advertising-a-ripped-leeched-base/527541/19</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2013 18:15:20 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-527541-19</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/t-r-you-should-read-this-before-advertising-a-ripped-leeched-base/527541.rss">[T_R] You Should Read This Before Advertising a Ripped/Leeched Base</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[T_R] You Should Read This Before Advertising a Ripped/Leeched Base</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Kidpaparoach Kidpaparoach]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/kidpaparoach">@Kidpaparoach</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I read a few lines then realized this is all based on <span class="bbcode-b">your opinion</span>. Some of your opinion is good and other parts are bad, you should reword the OP. Your opinion is not the correct way to go about things, it’s the correct way in your eyes to go about things.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/t-r-you-should-read-this-before-advertising-a-ripped-leeched-base/527541/18">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/t-r-you-should-read-this-before-advertising-a-ripped-leeched-base/527541/18</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2013 12:39:16 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-527541-18</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/t-r-you-should-read-this-before-advertising-a-ripped-leeched-base/527541.rss">[T_R] You Should Read This Before Advertising a Ripped/Leeched Base</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[T_R] You Should Read This Before Advertising a Ripped/Leeched Base</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@halflive9 halflive9]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/halflive9">@halflive9</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Because some find it interesting and do read it all.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/t-r-you-should-read-this-before-advertising-a-ripped-leeched-base/527541/17">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/t-r-you-should-read-this-before-advertising-a-ripped-leeched-base/527541/17</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2013 10:21:43 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-527541-17</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/t-r-you-should-read-this-before-advertising-a-ripped-leeched-base/527541.rss">[T_R] You Should Read This Before Advertising a Ripped/Leeched Base</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[T_R] You Should Read This Before Advertising a Ripped/Leeched Base</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@arham_4 arham 4]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/arham_4">@arham_4</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“Teem_Rocket, post:15, topic:527541”][quote]<br>
Type out the word, “Muffin” into your reply when you post if you’re still reading.<br>
[/quote]</p>
<p>It’s good to know that when I write up these threads, nobody actually takes the time to read all of the lines. Why should I bother?[/quote]<br>
I didn’t read this cuz I didnt think I was being applied <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/blush.png?v=5" title=":blush:" class="emoji" alt=":blush:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/t-r-you-should-read-this-before-advertising-a-ripped-leeched-base/527541/16">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/t-r-you-should-read-this-before-advertising-a-ripped-leeched-base/527541/16</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2013 18:07:16 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-527541-16</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/t-r-you-should-read-this-before-advertising-a-ripped-leeched-base/527541.rss">[T_R] You Should Read This Before Advertising a Ripped/Leeched Base</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[T_R] You Should Read This Before Advertising a Ripped/Leeched Base</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Teem_Rocket Teem_Rocket]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/teem_rocket">@Teem_Rocket</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <blockquote>Type out the word, "Muffin" into your reply when you post if you're still reading.</blockquote>
<p>It’s good to know that when I write up these threads, nobody actually takes the time to read all of the lines. Why should I bother?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/t-r-you-should-read-this-before-advertising-a-ripped-leeched-base/527541/15">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/t-r-you-should-read-this-before-advertising-a-ripped-leeched-base/527541/15</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2013 18:04:50 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-527541-15</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/t-r-you-should-read-this-before-advertising-a-ripped-leeched-base/527541.rss">[T_R] You Should Read This Before Advertising a Ripped/Leeched Base</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[T_R] You Should Read This Before Advertising a Ripped/Leeched Base</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Driman_Rune Driman Rune]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/driman_rune">@Driman_Rune</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Good thread mate!</p>
<p>I think rsps homes are useless.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/t-r-you-should-read-this-before-advertising-a-ripped-leeched-base/527541/14">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/t-r-you-should-read-this-before-advertising-a-ripped-leeched-base/527541/14</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2013 17:53:54 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-527541-14</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/t-r-you-should-read-this-before-advertising-a-ripped-leeched-base/527541.rss">[T_R] You Should Read This Before Advertising a Ripped/Leeched Base</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[T_R] You Should Read This Before Advertising a Ripped/Leeched Base</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Teem_Rocket Teem_Rocket]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/teem_rocket">@Teem_Rocket</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I agree that the Home location is important to Players, <span class="bbcode-b">however</span>. It should not be their main priority when they’ve done absolutely nothing to improve their emulation. I can see and understand your point of view. I’m sure that you can understand where I’m coming from as well.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/t-r-you-should-read-this-before-advertising-a-ripped-leeched-base/527541/13">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/t-r-you-should-read-this-before-advertising-a-ripped-leeched-base/527541/13</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2013 16:18:15 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-527541-13</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/t-r-you-should-read-this-before-advertising-a-ripped-leeched-base/527541.rss">[T_R] You Should Read This Before Advertising a Ripped/Leeched Base</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[T_R] You Should Read This Before Advertising a Ripped/Leeched Base</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Lin Lin]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/lin">@Lin</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I disagree with the home not being a priority. I’ve said it once and I’ll say it again. You can have the fastest, most stable, funnest and most fair server in the history of RSPS, but if your home is in edgeville I will not play it, and I probably won’t consider it if it’s in lumbridge. I’m so sick of seeing these two homes that they outweigh anything good the server has. Just something to keep in mind.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/t-r-you-should-read-this-before-advertising-a-ripped-leeched-base/527541/12">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/t-r-you-should-read-this-before-advertising-a-ripped-leeched-base/527541/12</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 11 Aug 2013 23:31:15 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-527541-12</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/t-r-you-should-read-this-before-advertising-a-ripped-leeched-base/527541.rss">[T_R] You Should Read This Before Advertising a Ripped/Leeched Base</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[T_R] You Should Read This Before Advertising a Ripped/Leeched Base</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@si_force Si Force]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/si_force">@si_force</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“arham 4, post:10, topic:527541”][quote author=Driman Rune link=topic=646296.msg4347160#msg4347160 date=1376062059]<br>
10-10!  <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/cool.png?v=5" title=":cool:" class="emoji" alt=":cool:"></p>
<p>But to tell you the truth of these “hard working” owners, who don’t have to “put server online” like players say.<br>
OR<br>
I added “shops”“fixed a dupe”. They think it’s their base, because they added 5 things, and changed the to</p>
<p>public static final String SERVER_NAME = “JoMamascape”;</p>
<p>is 70% there work.</p>
<p>I’m just saying people say they don’t or didn’t leech, but they do.<br>
[/quote]</p>
<p>*[/quote]</p>
<p>You’re not much better with the way you responded either, keep that kind of thing away please.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/t-r-you-should-read-this-before-advertising-a-ripped-leeched-base/527541/11">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/t-r-you-should-read-this-before-advertising-a-ripped-leeched-base/527541/11</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 10 Aug 2013 21:44:21 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-527541-11</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/t-r-you-should-read-this-before-advertising-a-ripped-leeched-base/527541.rss">[T_R] You Should Read This Before Advertising a Ripped/Leeched Base</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[T_R] You Should Read This Before Advertising a Ripped/Leeched Base</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@arham_4 arham 4]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/arham_4">@arham_4</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“Driman Rune, post:9, topic:527541”]10-10!  <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/cool.png?v=5" title=":cool:" class="emoji" alt=":cool:"></p>
<p>But to tell you the truth of these “hard working” owners, who don’t have to “put server online” like players say.<br>
OR<br>
I added “shops”“fixed a dupe”. They think it’s their base, because they added 5 things, and changed the to</p>
<p>public static final String SERVER_NAME = “JoMamascape”;</p>
<p>is 70% there work.</p>
<p>I’m just saying people say they don’t or didn’t leech, but they do.[/quote]</p>
<ul>
<li>
</li>
</ul>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/t-r-you-should-read-this-before-advertising-a-ripped-leeched-base/527541/10">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/t-r-you-should-read-this-before-advertising-a-ripped-leeched-base/527541/10</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2013 21:46:37 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-527541-10</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/t-r-you-should-read-this-before-advertising-a-ripped-leeched-base/527541.rss">[T_R] You Should Read This Before Advertising a Ripped/Leeched Base</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[T_R] You Should Read This Before Advertising a Ripped/Leeched Base</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Driman_Rune Driman Rune]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/driman_rune">@Driman_Rune</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>10-10!  <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/cool.png?v=5" title=":cool:" class="emoji" alt=":cool:"></p>
<p>But to tell you the truth of these “hard working” owners, who don’t have to “put server online” like players say.<br>
OR<br>
I added “shops”“fixed a dupe”. They think it’s their base, because they added 5 things, and changed the to</p>
<p>public static final String SERVER_NAME = “JoMamascape”;</p>
<p>is 70% there work.</p>
<p>I’m just saying people say they don’t or didn’t leech, but they do.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/t-r-you-should-read-this-before-advertising-a-ripped-leeched-base/527541/9">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/t-r-you-should-read-this-before-advertising-a-ripped-leeched-base/527541/9</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2013 15:27:39 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-527541-9</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/t-r-you-should-read-this-before-advertising-a-ripped-leeched-base/527541.rss">[T_R] You Should Read This Before Advertising a Ripped/Leeched Base</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[T_R] You Should Read This Before Advertising a Ripped/Leeched Base</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@JavaTC JavaTC]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/javatc">@JavaTC</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <blockquote>You should NOT include Donation-specific content (content only Donors can access). A person's financial status in real life should not influence an online game.</blockquote>
I disagree personally.  There are limits, but some people have limited time.
http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Dmtj0JyY9ac
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/t-r-you-should-read-this-before-advertising-a-ripped-leeched-base/527541/8">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/t-r-you-should-read-this-before-advertising-a-ripped-leeched-base/527541/8</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2013 14:11:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-527541-8</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/t-r-you-should-read-this-before-advertising-a-ripped-leeched-base/527541.rss">[T_R] You Should Read This Before Advertising a Ripped/Leeched Base</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[T_R] You Should Read This Before Advertising a Ripped/Leeched Base</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Int_Bauk Int Bauk]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/int_bauk">@Int_Bauk</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>do you really think people who leech will read through this lol. if they can’t even take a minute out of their day to change text, i doubt they will spend 5 minutes out of their day to read this.  ;)justsayin’</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/t-r-you-should-read-this-before-advertising-a-ripped-leeched-base/527541/7">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/t-r-you-should-read-this-before-advertising-a-ripped-leeched-base/527541/7</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2013 11:05:29 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-527541-7</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/t-r-you-should-read-this-before-advertising-a-ripped-leeched-base/527541.rss">[T_R] You Should Read This Before Advertising a Ripped/Leeched Base</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[T_R] You Should Read This Before Advertising a Ripped/Leeched Base</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@arham_4 arham 4]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/arham_4">@arham_4</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“ox random xi, post:3, topic:527541”][quote author=RandQm link=topic=646296.msg4346303#msg4346303 date=1375924734]<br>
It’s nice from yourself to write that for yourself. gj<br>
[/quote][/quote]</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/t-r-you-should-read-this-before-advertising-a-ripped-leeched-base/527541/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/t-r-you-should-read-this-before-advertising-a-ripped-leeched-base/527541/6</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2013 03:53:36 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-527541-6</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/t-r-you-should-read-this-before-advertising-a-ripped-leeched-base/527541.rss">[T_R] You Should Read This Before Advertising a Ripped/Leeched Base</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[T_R] You Should Read This Before Advertising a Ripped/Leeched Base</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Vain1 Vain_]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/vain1">@Vain1</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Just gonna go ahead and say wrong section</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/t-r-you-should-read-this-before-advertising-a-ripped-leeched-base/527541/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/t-r-you-should-read-this-before-advertising-a-ripped-leeched-base/527541/5</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2013 01:39:06 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-527541-5</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/t-r-you-should-read-this-before-advertising-a-ripped-leeched-base/527541.rss">[T_R] You Should Read This Before Advertising a Ripped/Leeched Base</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[T_R] You Should Read This Before Advertising a Ripped/Leeched Base</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Java-RSPS-Noob Java-RSPS-Noob]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/java-rsps-noob">@Java-RSPS-Noob</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>These are all very good suggestions for anybody to follow first the only two issues I have with this is:</p>
<ol>
<li>noobs will never look at this/read it</li>
<li>Some of the items you discuss such as stability would be beyond the majority of the “community”</li>
</ol>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/t-r-you-should-read-this-before-advertising-a-ripped-leeched-base/527541/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/t-r-you-should-read-this-before-advertising-a-ripped-leeched-base/527541/4</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2013 01:30:19 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-527541-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/t-r-you-should-read-this-before-advertising-a-ripped-leeched-base/527541.rss">[T_R] You Should Read This Before Advertising a Ripped/Leeched Base</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[T_R] You Should Read This Before Advertising a Ripped/Leeched Base</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@ox_random_xi ox random xi]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/ox_random_xi">@ox_random_xi</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote quote-modified" data-post="2" data-topic="527541">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/randqm/40/5_e05bb34c421432ee4d40de30c10af3e5.png" class="avatar"> RandQm:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>It’s nice from yourself to write that for yourself. gj</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/t-r-you-should-read-this-before-advertising-a-ripped-leeched-base/527541/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/t-r-you-should-read-this-before-advertising-a-ripped-leeched-base/527541/3</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2013 01:29:13 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-527541-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/t-r-you-should-read-this-before-advertising-a-ripped-leeched-base/527541.rss">[T_R] You Should Read This Before Advertising a Ripped/Leeched Base</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[T_R] You Should Read This Before Advertising a Ripped/Leeched Base</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@RandQm RandQm]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/randqm">@RandQm</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>It’s nice from yourself to write that for yourself. gj</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/t-r-you-should-read-this-before-advertising-a-ripped-leeched-base/527541/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/t-r-you-should-read-this-before-advertising-a-ripped-leeched-base/527541/2</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2013 01:18:54 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-527541-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/t-r-you-should-read-this-before-advertising-a-ripped-leeched-base/527541.rss">[T_R] You Should Read This Before Advertising a Ripped/Leeched Base</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[T_R] You Should Read This Before Advertising a Ripped/Leeched Base</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Teem_Rocket Teem_Rocket]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/teem_rocket">@Teem_Rocket</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[size=24pt]<span class="bbcode-i">[color=red]Why your Server is a target for criticism and flaming:</span>[/size]</p>
<p>Hello. Thank you very much for viewing this Thread. Please take the time to read all of It’s contents so that you will have a full understanding of what is posted and do not ask questions which were already addressed within the Thread.</p>
<p>[size=1]NOTE: This Tutorial is aimed at audiences which have little-to-no experience in the field of RuneScape Private Server development. This Tutorial is for the MoparScape users who advertise their Servers with absolutely 0 edits or modifications made to the original Base.[/size]</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">[i]Do you find yourself posting an Advertisement Thread, only to have forum users criticize and flame what you’ve posted? Do you wish you could understand why this occurs and ways to improve? This Tutorial is aimed at addressing these issues. </span></p>
<p>[size=24pt]Updates which can wait:[/size]</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b"><span class="bbcode-u">Written below are several subjects which are NOT important and should wait until after vital content and other features have been implemented in-game:</span></span></p>
<hr>
<ul>
<li>
<p>Text Strings:</p>
<p>These are NOT important and can be edited at any time with no effect on a closed Server in development. The only impact if done so during the Live game would be the recognition by the community of the change. This extends to strings such as the name of Bank, Teleport names, etcetera. You have much more important things to worry about. If you’re stressed over naming your Server and have no thoughts concerning stability, content, structure, features, mechanics, and more – your project is <span class="bbcode-b">NOT</span> ready to be advertised and accept traffic.</p>
</li>
</ul>
<hr>
<ul>
<li>
<p>Donations and Rewards:</p>
<p>A very sensitive issue indeed. You should NOT include Donation-specific content (content only Donors can access). A person’s financial status in real life should not influence an online game. The two should not be related. If you wish, you could always create cosmetic items which are exlusive to anyone who donates $5.00 U.S.D. or more towards the continuation of the Server. Something such as adding a ‘Donor-only Shop’ with end-game equipment and items is a bad idea. The community is not very fond of users who host their Server only for a quick profit.</p>
</li>
</ul>
<hr>
<ul>
<li>
<p>Quests:</p>
<p>These can be very nice to have. Quests can open up a wide variety of different features, mechanics, story-line, lore. etcetera. If designed and structured correctly – Quests can be engaging and a change of the usual pace for Players. However, if rushed, poorly designed and executed, these Quests can become a hassle and many Players will seek any way to avoid completion of these Quests. It is not a great idea to limit equipment to Players who have completed a Quest-line and unlocked content. You should not obsess over Quests until you make vast improvements to your Server and Client Base(s) as a whole.</p>
</li>
</ul>
<hr>
<ul>
<li>
<p>Home:</p>
<p>The location of your Server’s “Home” is usually where the most players reside and is the very first area which Players have access to. It is usually the area to where the Player is sent during the Death method and during the creation and registry of a new account. One of my pet-peeves is to see a project with absolutely zero effort or originality put into it… consisting of only renamed strings, custom items which were ripped line-for-line, areas crowded with objects, and sometimes not even bothering to modify the minute or mundane details. This Home location can be decided and edited/implemented within 2 minutes. I’m not saying that the Home location doesn’t matter, because indeed it does. For example, if your Server has a theme of far-away travel via boats and ships, you should consider a location such as the Void Knight Outpost as a Home. There are several reasons this makes sense besides matching the theme. On this island, there are three Shops, a Bank and four boats. Assuming that you’re using 5-line dialogue frames, that is 20 options without the need to advance dialogue for more options. If an advancement selection was added for all of the transportation offers – it would be 38-40 different locations to choose from. You should decide your Home location once you’ve improved everything your Server has to offer. Using the knowledge gained from this, you should be able to utilize many advanced features and mechanics in the Home location. For example, if you place a Cage object such as the one at Yanille (you can use debug strings to display I.D) with a N.P.C. spawned inside. One could simply reference existing factors and conditions from the N.P.C. system and modify your N.P.C. with the selected information with adjustments to create a docile N.P.C. which cannot go outside of It’s Cage which it is being held in. This is a ‘cheaphax’ method of doing this next step as well, but one could also add an exception into the Attack N.P.C. Packet which would prevent a Player from using melee attacks on the caged N.P.C.</p>
</li>
</ul>
<p>[size=24pt]Updates which should be your <span class="hashtag">#1</span> priority:[/size]</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">[u]This is the point where the subjects you SHOULD implement are listed and explained. If you follow and abide by all of the following, then you will no doubt have a successful project:</span></p>
<hr>
<ul>
<li>
<p>Stability:</p>
<p>The Stability of a Server and how reliably it will maintain It’s uptime without blow-back, unforeseen adverse effects, or an outright crash should be your number one goal. You should be aware of several things, including the manner in which your Listener functions, writing which might lead to a “memory leak” (lol), which is probably an unstable timer or piece of code, the basic structure and framework of your Server, how to include a Database Core and .ini settings file (which can store Database information, Port info, Server info, etcetera). One should also be familiar with their Client revision. In R.S.P.S. your Client is your Server’s worst enemy. You need to modify, rename, document, re-write and rinse/repeat Client-to-Server communications and visa-versa. Type out the word, “Muffin” into your reply when you post if you’re still reading. The Client once advertised and released to the public (assuming desktop Client) should be closed-source and have preventions in place against reverse engineering and decompiling. All extra items should be packed into the Client’s Cache instead of externally referencing.</p>
</li>
</ul>
<hr>
<p>Originality:</p>
<pre><code> A good example of having original content or gameplay is by modifying existing skills and tweaking them in a major way. An example would be creating entirely new Skill systems for Thieving and Woodcutting. If your imagination falls short, then please refer to [url=http://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php/topic,642630]this thread.[/url] Another
</code></pre>
<p>example of this subject would be adding additional N.P.C. Combat styles and attacks. For example, an Archer might use regular iron arrows, but as their level increases in different locations, their quality and quantity of arrows also increases. The Player receives the arrows the N.P.C. had equipped as well and may pickup the N.P.C. arrows fired from It’s bow. Karil the Tainted might rapidly attack the Player with a magical attack which drains prayer even if it does not hit or splashes. The player may freeze the N.P.C. or use another tactic, but Karil resorts to firing a large magical arrow which inflicts a heavy amount of range damage if the Player moves out of his range or attempts to flee.</p>
<hr>
<p>Modifying Skills:</p>
<pre><code> The average Player of a RuneScape Private Server does not plan on the Server existing forever or keeping their progress for a very long period of time. This should be addressed by developers and Staff members so that this is simply not the case. An example of modifying a skill for the better would be to increase the amount of ore you may mine from a single node, drastically increasing the rate and chance of obtaining ore based upon the quality of equipment and level in use, and having a banking point at a [u]reasonable[/u] distance. You could also adjust the Mining Skill to display different text strings to the Client based on a chance which is calculated based on their outfit (Skilling Outfits would be great on a R.S.P.S). According to the single random chance, they are given a message and extra ore saying, "Due to your exceptional talents in Mining, you obtain _DOUBLE_ _TRIPLE_ QUAD_ _FETCHTYPE_ Ore!", etcetera. The Mining outfit hood - Teleportation device to selected Dragon Ore spots (Dragon Smithing can
</code></pre>
<p>and has been done in the past). The Mining outfit Vest - Allows the Player to right-click --&gt; Store up to 20 ore of any<br>
type inside of their Vest. The Mining outfit Leggings - Enables the Player who is a Skiller or doesn’t have the require stats to wield their Pickaxe to store it inside of the Leggings. The Mining outfit Gloves - Allows the Player to right-click --&gt; Extra Sensitive Perception Blessing; on the Gloves. This once clicked sends the Locations and total amount of all Players at all ore nodes in the entire game. The Mining Chains - Chains which serve as boots worn on the Player’s feet. These Chains give a bonus of +25% Sprint Energy, +50% Energy regeneration rate, and +5 Agility levels if the Player has an inventory filled with any type of ore. Their inventory must consist of 28 of the same type of ore not noted to apply the Agility bonus. Smithy’s Ancient Pickaxe - This Pickaxe is the rarest and most valued piece of the Mining outfit set. It applies the following: +4 noted ore of the same type mined when Player mines 1 type of an ore,<br>
a right-click --&gt; Summon Ancient Mineral Demon option; which summons a N.P.C. which will bank any type of ore in the Player’s inventory once every 15 minutes; this N.P.C. can only deposit ore into your bank; cannot withdraw either.</p>
<hr>
<p>Extra Content:</p>
<pre><code> After you've molded and formed your base into the Server/Client dream team you worked so hard to achieve, you might be asking yourself, "Well... What do I do now?". The answer to that question, is to have some fun and add in 
</code></pre>
<p>so many little things and tidbits of content that it expands upon the total items database and results in a wider variety of reasons to become interested in the exploration aspect of gameplay. You could add over 50+ different types of food, beverages, and alcoholic drinks which almost no R.S.P.S. use. Create new and unique Crafting recipes, such as the ability to craft a Robin Hood Hat at level 95 Crafting.</p>
<hr>
<p>Familiarity:</p>
<pre><code> The R.S.P.S. developer or programmer should be familiar with the base they're working with. They should know the
</code></pre>
<p>general structure and design of the source. The Client chosen should be as renamed as possible. I recommend that you<br>
use a 317 revision for your first source to mess with if you’re a developer. You should gain familiarity with the Client and begin your own documentation which explains code in the way you can best understand. You can worry about being objective later.</p>
<p>[size=24pt]Summary:[/size]</p>
<p>[i][size=10pt]Attempt to make edits and modify the base you downloaded before hosting. If you’re hosting with the intentions of making a quick dollar, then that’s your business and not mine. This informative Thread was written in an attempt to decrease the amount of users who are ignorant in regards to programming and at least editing/modifying their source before hosting their ‘project’ as a short-term cancer which only seeks the currency of It’s Player-base.[/size]</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/t-r-you-should-read-this-before-advertising-a-ripped-leeched-base/527541/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/t-r-you-should-read-this-before-advertising-a-ripped-leeched-base/527541/1</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2013 01:17:10 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-527541-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/t-r-you-should-read-this-before-advertising-a-ripped-leeched-base/527541.rss">[T_R] You Should Read This Before Advertising a Ripped/Leeched Base</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
