<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Inventory model change</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/inventory-model-change/550127</link>
    <description>Alright, I have a cloning system that clones an item it changes the name and all its itemdefs even models. I can&#39;t seem to find the method that would update the inventory. I have tried the resetItems method but that does not work. I have tried requesting the update method nothing. All though when I change region (Teleport to new region) the models update. I have no idea were to look, I have tried implementing some methods that were used in the changeRegions.java and changeRegion.java. Is this client sided? or server sided? and what method would be the correct one to use?</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2015 00:39:20 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/inventory-model-change/550127.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Inventory model change</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Lordabyssal Lordabyssal]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/lordabyssal">@Lordabyssal</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Alright, I have a cloning system that clones an item it changes the name and all its itemdefs even models. I can’t seem to find the method that would update the inventory. I have tried the resetItems method but that does not work. I have tried requesting the update method nothing. All though when I change region (Teleport to new region) the models update. I have no idea were to look, I have tried implementing some methods that were used in the changeRegions.java and changeRegion.java. Is this client sided? or server sided? and what method would be the correct one to use?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/inventory-model-change/550127/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/inventory-model-change/550127/1</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2015 00:39:20 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-550127-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/inventory-model-change/550127.rss">Inventory model change</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
