<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>The Big bang theory</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-big-bang-theory/65491</link>
    <description>Video
http://www.allaboutscience.org/big-bang-theory-video.htm

Explanation

Big Bang Theory - The Premise
The Big Bang theory is an effort to explain what happened at the very beginning of our universe. Discoveries in astronomy and physics have shown beyond a reasonable doubt that our universe did in fact have a beginning. Prior to that moment there was nothing; during and after that moment there was something: our universe. The big bang theory is an effort to explain what happened during and after that moment.

According to the standard theory, our universe sprang into existence as &quot;singularity&quot; around 13.7 billion years ago. What is a &quot;singularity&quot; and where does it come from? Well, to be honest, we don&#39;t know for sure. Singularities are zones which defy our current understanding of physics. They are thought to exist at the core of &quot;black holes.&quot; Black holes are areas of intense gravitational pressure. The pressure is thought to be so intense that finite matter is actually squished into infinite density (a mathematical concept which truly boggles the mind). These zones of infinite density are called &quot;singularities.&quot; Our universe is thought to have begun as an infinitesimally small, infinitely hot, infinitely dense, something - a singularity. Where did it come from? We don&#39;t know. Why did it appear? We don&#39;t know.

After its initial appearance, it apparently inflated (the &quot;Big Bang&quot;), expanded and cooled, going from very, very small and very, very hot, to the size and temperature of our current universe. It continues to expand and cool to this day and we are inside of it: incredible creatures living on a unique planet, circling a beautiful star clustered together with several hundred billion other stars in a galaxy soaring through the cosmos, all of which is inside of an expanding universe that began as an infinitesimal singularity which appeared out of nowhere for reasons unknown. This is the Big Bang theory.

Big Bang Theory - Common Misconceptions
There are many misconceptions surrounding the Big Bang theory. For example, we tend to imagine a giant explosion. Experts however say that there was no explosion; there was (and continues to be) an expansion. Rather than imagining a balloon popping and releasing its contents, imagine a balloon expanding: an infinitesimally small balloon expanding to the size of our current universe.

Another misconception is that we tend to image the singularity as a little fireball appearing somewhere in space. According to the many experts however, space didn&#39;t exist prior to the Big Bang. Back in the late &#39;60s and early &#39;70s, when men first walked upon the moon, &quot;three British astrophysicists, Steven Hawking, George Ellis, and Roger Penrose turned their attention to the Theory of Relativity and its implications regarding our notions of time. In 1968 and 1970, they published papers in which they extended Einstein&#39;s Theory of General Relativity to include measurements of time and space.1, 2 According to their calculations, time and space had a finite beginning that corresponded to the origin of matter and energy.&quot;3 The singularity didn&#39;t appear in space; rather, space began inside of the singularity. Prior to the singularity, nothing existed, not space, time, matter, or energy - nothing. So where and in what did the singularity appear if not in space? We don&#39;t know. We don&#39;t know where it came from, why it&#39;s here, or even where it is. All we really know is that we are inside of it and at one time it didn&#39;t exist and neither did we.

Big Bang Theory - Evidence for the Theory
What are the major evidences which support the Big Bang theory?

    * First of all, we are reasonably certain that the universe had a beginning.
    * Second, galaxies appear to be moving away from us at speeds proportional to their distance. This is called &quot;Hubble&#39;s Law,&quot; named after Edwin Hubble (1889-1953) who discovered this phenomenon in 1929. This observation supports the expansion of the universe and suggests that the universe was once compacted.
    * Third, if the universe was initially very, very hot as the Big Bang suggests, we should be able to find some remnant of this heat. In 1965, Radioastronomers Arno Penzias and Robert Wilson discovered a 2.725 degree Kelvin (-454.765 degree Fahrenheit, -270.425 degree Celsius) Cosmic Microwave Background radiation (CMB) which pervades the observable universe. This is thought to be the remnant which scientists were looking for. Penzias and Wilson shared in the 1978 Nobel Prize for Physics for their discovery.
    * Finally, the abundance of the &quot;light elements&quot; Hydrogen and Helium found in the observable universe are thought to support the Big Bang model of origins. 

Big Bang Theory - The Only Plausible Theory?
Is the standard Big Bang theory the only model consistent with these evidences? No, it&#39;s just the most popular one. Internationally renown Astrophysicist George F. R. Ellis explains: &quot;People need to be aware that there is a range of models that could explain the observations….For instance, I can construct you a spherically symmetrical universe with Earth at its center, and you cannot disprove it based on observations….You can only exclude it on philosophical grounds. In my view there is absolutely nothing wrong in that. What I want to bring into the open is the fact that we are using philosophical criteria in choosing our models. A lot of cosmology tries to hide that.&quot;4

In 2003, Physicist Robert Gentry proposed an attractive alternative to the standard theory, an alternative which also accounts for the evidences listed above.5 Dr. Gentry claims that the standard Big Bang model is founded upon a faulty paradigm (the Friedmann-lemaitre expanding-spacetime paradigm) which he claims is inconsistent with the empirical data. He chooses instead to base his model on Einstein&#39;s static-spacetime paradigm which he claims is the &quot;genuine cosmic Rosetta.&quot; Gentry has published several papers outlining what he considers to be serious flaws in the standard Big Bang model.6 Other high-profile dissenters include Nobel laureate Dr. Hannes Alfvén, Professor Geoffrey Burbidge, Dr. Halton Arp, and the renowned British astronomer Sir Fred Hoyle, who is accredited with first coining the term &quot;the Big Bang&quot; during a BBC radio broadcast in 1950.

Big Bang Theory - What About God?
Any discussion of the Big Bang theory would be incomplete without asking the question, what about God? This is because cosmogony (the study of the origin of the universe) is an area where science and theology meet. Creation was a supernatural event. That is, it took place outside of the natural realm. This fact begs the question: is there anything else which exists outside of the natural realm? Specifically, is there a master Architect out there? We know that this universe had a beginning. Was God the &quot;First Cause&quot;? We won&#39;t attempt to answer that question in this short article. We just ask the question:

[Url=http://www.allaboutphilosophy.org/does-god-exist-c-video.htm]Does God Exist?[/url]</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 16 Mar 2007 03:30:35 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>General Discussion</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-big-bang-theory/65491.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>The Big bang theory</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@bootnecklad bootnecklad]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/bootnecklad">@bootnecklad</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>a ub3r c00l boom?<br>
i’ll go with that…<br>
sorry for this (you have your beliefs i’ll have mine) god sucks</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-big-bang-theory/65491/60">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-big-bang-theory/65491/60</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 16 Mar 2007 03:30:35 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-65491-60</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-big-bang-theory/65491.rss">The Big bang theory</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The Big bang theory</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@redragonje65 redragonje65]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/redragonje65">@redragonje65</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I thank God I’m an atheist.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-big-bang-theory/65491/59">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-big-bang-theory/65491/59</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 15 Mar 2007 08:46:14 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-65491-59</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-big-bang-theory/65491.rss">The Big bang theory</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The Big bang theory</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@bam_bam bam bam]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/bam_bam">@bam_bam</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“xxlegitxx, post:55, topic:65491”]Just because the Big Bang has no cause does not disprove it, nor is it a flaw.  Christianity and the Big Bang do not conflict, btw.<br>
And I’m Protestant, and Catholics will go to hell, so I do not pray to Saint Anthony, nor do I pray simply for personal gain.[/quote]<br>
Just because I was born Catholic does not in any way mean that I agree with them.<br>
I’m saying the that everything has at some point a beginning and if you believe in the ‘Big Bang’ theory then you also believe that this matter has always been existent, but then ask yourself where did this original matter come from?</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-post="57" data-topic="65491">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/xxlegitxx/40/5_6259e4fa9dfe0dec282fb0955bb1974c.png" class="avatar"> xxlegitxx:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Wtf, every single priest?</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I agree.  I don’t think there is more than a small percentage of priests who will tell you most of the Bible isn’t true, in fact, most will tell you they think it is.</p>
<p>How many of you disagreeing have even ever read a portion of the Bible?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-big-bang-theory/65491/58">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-big-bang-theory/65491/58</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 15 Mar 2007 06:35:11 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-65491-58</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-big-bang-theory/65491.rss">The Big bang theory</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The Big bang theory</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@xxlegitxx xxlegitxx]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/xxlegitxx">@xxlegitxx</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Wtf, every single priest?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-big-bang-theory/65491/57">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-big-bang-theory/65491/57</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 15 Mar 2007 05:21:21 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-65491-57</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-big-bang-theory/65491.rss">The Big bang theory</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The Big bang theory</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Itachi_Uchiha Itachi Uchiha]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/itachi_uchiha">@Itachi_Uchiha</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>And, what every single priest will tell you is that most of the bible isnt true, most of it is speculation based off of the first few books/chapters of it.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-big-bang-theory/65491/56">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-big-bang-theory/65491/56</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 15 Mar 2007 05:19:42 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-65491-56</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-big-bang-theory/65491.rss">The Big bang theory</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The Big bang theory</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@xxlegitxx xxlegitxx]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/xxlegitxx">@xxlegitxx</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Just because the Big Bang has no cause does not disprove it, nor is it a flaw.  Christianity and the Big Bang do not conflict, btw.<br>
And I’m Protestant, and Catholics will go to hell, so I do not pray to Saint Anthony, nor do I pray simply for personal gain.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-big-bang-theory/65491/55">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-big-bang-theory/65491/55</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 15 Mar 2007 04:50:48 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-65491-55</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-big-bang-theory/65491.rss">The Big bang theory</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The Big bang theory</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@bam_bam bam bam]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/bam_bam">@bam_bam</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>The ‘Big Bang’ theory has flaws.<br>
Everything as we know it in this universe must have a beginning, which Genesis (The first book of the Bible) explains, whether this is symbolic or fact and the theory of the so called ‘Big Bang’ does not.  Even if all the matter in this universe had been compressed to a size smaller than a pin, where did that spec of matter come from?</p>
<p>If there was no God then there would be nothing, however faith calls for you to believe God always has and always will be existent.  Have not any of you guys (and girls) seen something out of the ordinary that is no coincidence, or ever prayed to Saint Anthony then found what you were looking for in the oddest of places?  Well I have, on both counts.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-big-bang-theory/65491/54">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-big-bang-theory/65491/54</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 15 Mar 2007 03:23:17 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-65491-54</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-big-bang-theory/65491.rss">The Big bang theory</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The Big bang theory</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Itachi_Uchiha Itachi Uchiha]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/itachi_uchiha">@Itachi_Uchiha</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Some scientists on crack were studying the big bang in the 80’s and at the exact moment they heard a loud noise and one yell “It’s a second big bang!” but it turned out to be a car backfireing.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-big-bang-theory/65491/53">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-big-bang-theory/65491/53</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 15 Mar 2007 02:16:26 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-65491-53</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-big-bang-theory/65491.rss">The Big bang theory</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The Big bang theory</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@xxlegitxx xxlegitxx]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/xxlegitxx">@xxlegitxx</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote no-group" data-post="51" data-topic="65491">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 Eh Pretty Easy:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>It is possible for it to happen again. If the ozone-layer would be gone and the sun would overheat earth too much, the earth could just explode. After explosion the stuff left from the explosion will automatically create a new realm, which would take about 14 billion years for it to finish, imo.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>We’re talking about the Big Bang, not the creation of the solar system.  And btw, your 14 billion years is completely useless.  Because respected scientists aren’t even sure how long solar system formation takes, your number is a mere guess.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-big-bang-theory/65491/52">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-big-bang-theory/65491/52</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 15 Mar 2007 01:04:20 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-65491-52</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-big-bang-theory/65491.rss">The Big bang theory</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The Big bang theory</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Eh_Pretty_Easy Eh Pretty Easy]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/eh_pretty_easy">@Eh_Pretty_Easy</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>It is possible for it to happen again. If the ozone-layer would be gone and the sun would overheat earth too much, the earth could just explode. After explosion the stuff left from the explosion will automatically create a new realm, which would take about 14 billion years for it to finish, imo.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-big-bang-theory/65491/51">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-big-bang-theory/65491/51</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 13 Mar 2007 20:47:08 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-65491-51</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-big-bang-theory/65491.rss">The Big bang theory</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The Big bang theory</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@goatee goatee]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/goatee">@goatee</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote no-group quote-modified" data-post="40" data-topic="65491">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 1 dum taco:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>If the big bang theory did happen,why hasent it happend again. If there was nothing at the biggening of the univerese,how can u have something…u cant make something from nothing</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>How do you know?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-big-bang-theory/65491/50">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-big-bang-theory/65491/50</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 11 Mar 2007 14:31:01 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-65491-50</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-big-bang-theory/65491.rss">The Big bang theory</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The Big bang theory</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@redragonje65 redragonje65]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/redragonje65">@redragonje65</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote no-group quote-modified" data-post="47" data-topic="65491">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/93dcthugs93/40/5_6259e4fa9dfe0dec282fb0955bb1974c.png" class="avatar"> 93dcthugs93:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>I wanna live, since I don’t know two shits about the ‘new’ things.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Whether you live or not is not part of the choice.</p>
<blockquote>Nothing is absolutely provable, because humans' study of science is limited to our senses...who knows what lies beyond what we can sense in the world?</blockquote>
<p>Fact applies to our understanding of things. Our understanding of math tells us that 1+1 = 2. Our understanding of Science is that if we jump with enough force we can escape the range of Earth’s gravity that keeps us on the planet. Our understanding of perception tells us if we see something the way it is, it is that way to us. If we see mathematics the way we see it, we see 1+1 as 2. If we see the sky as blue, it is blue to us.[br][size=1]Posted on: March 10, 2007, 05:11:21 PM[/size][hr][quote=“BobDole81, post:48, topic:65491”][quote author=redragonje65 link=topic=95203.msg996033#msg996033 date=1173582818]<br>
if you had a choice to let the universe collapse so life can never exist again or make it possible for something in the future to have a chance to live life and maybe make the same decision, which one would you pick?<br>
[/quote]</p>
<p>But who says there won’t be life ever again?  If we do live in a closed, oscillating universe, then once the universe collapses into a singularity, it would be expected that another big bang would occur.  And who knows if life may exist in that universe?[/quote]</p>
<p>If you had a choice to let the universe collapse so life can never exist again or make it possible for something in the future to have a <span class="bbcode-u"><span class="bbcode-b">chance</span></span> to live life and maybe make the same decision, which one would you pick?</p>
<blockquote>But who says there won't be life ever again?  If we do live in a closed, oscillating universe, then once the universe collapses into a singularity, it would be expected that another big bang would occur.  And who knows if life may exist in that universe?</blockquote>
<p>I would consider the new universe that results from that big bang to be the same universe because it is the same matter. But there is the question of how the singularity of the big bang was first created. If that big bang was a result of an oscculating universe’s big crunch shouldn’t the resulting universe have the same amount of mass therefore resulting in an oscculating universe which research shows is not infact our universe?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-big-bang-theory/65491/49">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-big-bang-theory/65491/49</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 11 Mar 2007 04:14:29 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-65491-49</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-big-bang-theory/65491.rss">The Big bang theory</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The Big bang theory</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@BobDole81 BobDole81]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/bobdole81">@BobDole81</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote no-group" data-post="46" data-topic="65491">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/redragonje65/40/5_6259e4fa9dfe0dec282fb0955bb1974c.png" class="avatar"> redragonje65:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>if you had a choice to let the universe collapse so life can never exist again or make it possible for something in the future to have a chance to live life and maybe make the same decision, which one would you pick?</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Well, if the Big Crunch is to occur, we really won’t have to worry about it for at least about 30 billion years according to Stephen Hawking.</p>
<p>But who says there won’t be life ever again?  If we do live in a closed, oscillating universe, then once the universe collapses into a singularity, it would be expected that another big bang would occur.  And who knows if life may exist in that universe?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-big-bang-theory/65491/48">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-big-bang-theory/65491/48</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 11 Mar 2007 03:37:14 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-65491-48</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-big-bang-theory/65491.rss">The Big bang theory</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The Big bang theory</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@93dcthugs93 93dcthugs93]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/93dcthugs93">@93dcthugs93</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I wanna live, since I don’t know two shits about the ‘new’ things.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-big-bang-theory/65491/47">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-big-bang-theory/65491/47</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 11 Mar 2007 03:23:42 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-65491-47</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-big-bang-theory/65491.rss">The Big bang theory</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The Big bang theory</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@redragonje65 redragonje65]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/redragonje65">@redragonje65</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>if you had a choice to let the universe collapse so life can never exist again or make it possible for something in the future to have a chance to live life and maybe make the same decision, which one would you pick?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-big-bang-theory/65491/46">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-big-bang-theory/65491/46</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 11 Mar 2007 03:13:38 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-65491-46</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-big-bang-theory/65491.rss">The Big bang theory</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The Big bang theory</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@93dcthugs93 93dcthugs93]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/93dcthugs93">@93dcthugs93</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Technically, if it happened again… we would die.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-big-bang-theory/65491/45">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-big-bang-theory/65491/45</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 11 Mar 2007 00:55:57 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-65491-45</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-big-bang-theory/65491.rss">The Big bang theory</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The Big bang theory</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@xxlegitxx xxlegitxx]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/xxlegitxx">@xxlegitxx</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Of course you wouldn’t be able to see it if it did happen again…</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-big-bang-theory/65491/44">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-big-bang-theory/65491/44</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 10 Mar 2007 23:06:04 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-65491-44</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-big-bang-theory/65491.rss">The Big bang theory</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The Big bang theory</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@redragonje65 redragonje65]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/redragonje65">@redragonje65</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote no-group quote-modified" data-post="40" data-topic="65491">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 1 dum taco:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>If the big bang theory did happen,why hasent it happend again. If there was nothing at the biggening of the univerese,how can u have something…u cant make something from nothing</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>It’s theorized that it may have happened before and it may happen again in the future. What will happen is that if all the mass in the universe is strong enough to stop the constant expansion, then everything will start contracting and a “bing crunch” would occur. But if all the mass is not strong enough, then the universe will continue to expand. I think that somewhere between those two (it may be between or the one with the big crunch) there is a possibility of an oscilating universe. A universe that continues in a cycle from expanding to contracting. Which one will happen has to do with what the shape of the universe is. I.E. flat or spherical.</p>
<aside class="onebox whitelistedgeneric">
  <header class="source">
      <a href="http://www.pbs.org/program/stephen-hawkings-universe/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Retired Site: Stephen Hawking's Universe</a>
  </header>
  <article class="onebox-body">
    

<h3><a href="http://www.pbs.org/program/stephen-hawkings-universe/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Retired Site: Stephen Hawking's Universe</a></h3>

<p>Stephen Hawking's Universe was a six-part astronomical documentary series featuring the theoretical physicist Stephen Hawking.</p>


  </article>
  <div class="onebox-metadata">
    
    
  </div>
  <div style="clear: both"></div>
</aside>

<p><a href="http://www.godandscience.org/slideshow/sld012.html" class="onebox" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">http://www.godandscience.org/slideshow/sld012.html</a></p>
<p>a problem with the oscillating universe is that all the matter would lead to a big crunch. But then again, that maybe why we’re here. Maybe in a few billion years when the universe stops expanding and starts contracting and we get the news a few million years late, the human race has to find a way to eliminate some of the matter to create an oscilating universe. Meaning of life or science fiction?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-big-bang-theory/65491/43">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-big-bang-theory/65491/43</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 10 Mar 2007 21:04:10 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-65491-43</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-big-bang-theory/65491.rss">The Big bang theory</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The Big bang theory</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@BobDole81 BobDole81]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/bobdole81">@BobDole81</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote no-group quote-modified" data-post="40" data-topic="65491">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 1 dum taco:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>If the big bang theory did happen,why hasent it happend again. If there was nothing at the biggening of the univerese,how can u have something…u cant make something from nothing</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Eh…that’s questionable.  I’ll start with your last question first.</p>
<p>Obviously, matter can neither be created or destroyed, which is what I think you’re referring to.  But relativity states a relationship between mass and energy (E = mc^2).  Obviously, this works on the very small scale, but it has been shown in particle accelerators that if two particles collide at near the speed of light, they will somehow transform into a high energy photon (destroying mass, in a sense) and then revert into some particle and anti-particle (creating mass, in a sense).  So, although it is theorized that the universe was absolute nothingness before the big bang, there was still “the big bang” singularity, which is supposed to be huge amounts of energy packed into a “point” of “infinte density and zero volume.”  So, considering E=mc^2, the matter in the universe wasn’t just created from nothing (and on an off topic point, apparently all the matter in atoms we can see in our universe makes up only 4% of of the universal composition).</p>
<p>Why hasn’t be big bang happened again?  Since the initial one we know about, there hasn’t been another big bang singularity we know about to actually cause one.  There is an oscillating universe theory in which after the big bang, the size and density of the universe reaches a critical point and reverses itself into the “big crunch”…but apparently, its been “proven” that the universe is flat (in regards to the warping of time and space) and will not do that…</p>
<p>[quote=“93dcthugs93, post:41, topic:65491”]^^ Your name fits you quite well, how in the world would it happen AGAIN? Why would it happen again?</p>
<p>And the whole entire EVERYTHING the universe, the world, the planets EVERYTHING; How did they come to be? I don’t see how you people are saying how do you get something from nothing, well how did anything come to be?[/quote]<br>
Exactly…that’s actually a known (and pretty funny imo) way of thinking about it…one of the anthropic principles.  Basically, in attempt to explain why the universe formed the way it did, does it not make sense that if the universe hadn’t evolved exactly as it did, there would be no planets, and no “intelligent life” like us?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-big-bang-theory/65491/42">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-big-bang-theory/65491/42</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 10 Mar 2007 19:25:04 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-65491-42</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-big-bang-theory/65491.rss">The Big bang theory</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The Big bang theory</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@93dcthugs93 93dcthugs93]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/93dcthugs93">@93dcthugs93</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>^^ Your name fits you quite well, how in the world would it happen AGAIN? Why would it happen again?</p>
<p>And the whole entire EVERYTHING the universe, the world, the planets EVERYTHING; How did they come to be? I don’t see how you people are saying how do you get something from nothing, well how did anything come to be?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-big-bang-theory/65491/41">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-big-bang-theory/65491/41</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 10 Mar 2007 19:10:45 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-65491-41</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-big-bang-theory/65491.rss">The Big bang theory</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The Big bang theory</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@1_dum_taco 1 dum taco]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/1_dum_taco">@1_dum_taco</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>If the big bang theory did happen,why hasent it happend again. If there was nothing at the biggening of the univerese,how can u have something…u cant make something from nothing</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-big-bang-theory/65491/40">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-big-bang-theory/65491/40</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 10 Mar 2007 18:55:55 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-65491-40</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-big-bang-theory/65491.rss">The Big bang theory</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The Big bang theory</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@BobDole81 BobDole81]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/bobdole81">@BobDole81</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“Gotta Catch Them All, post:20, topic:65491”][quote author=R.I.P RSC link=topic=95203.msg988622#msg988622 date=1173464151]<br>
Well, then the universe is in something. A sample. (My samples suck I know :p)You have a pool. Imagine the pool being the universe. On the top there is a lid. Now how do you want to put more water in it. There is no space for that. So it has to expand. So you dig a bigger hole, and you can because there is the earth around it. But if there was only that pool, you couldnt dig a hole to expand the pool.</p>
<p>I hope you understand me be because when I re-read it it was a bit strange story :D.<br>
[/quote]</p>
<p>Not quite.  No new material is being formed.  The amount of energy/mass in the universe is constant.  It’s a closed system.[/quote]</p>
<p>How is that possibly known?  Our knowledge of the universe is limited to what we can see…the observable universe, which has a maximum radius of only 13.7 billion light years (since the universe is 13.7 billion years old, and nothing can travel faster than the speed of light).  Beyond this imaginary but finite border, we know nothing.  And apparently, the last estimate of the size of the entire universe (formed from the big bang as we know it, that is) is about 40 billion light years in radius.  So who knows what lies beyond the entire universe, and who knows whether the universe is a closed system.  A closed system would make logical sense, but we have no clue as to what we’re expanding into really…</p>
<p>[quote=“Gotta Catch Them All, post:25, topic:65491”][quote author=xxlegitxx link=topic=95203.msg986724#msg986724 date=1173413243]<br>
“And for all you need to know”</p>
<p>For example, when a kid asks you why the sky is blue.  You say, “For all you need to know, the sky is blue because of the way it scatters light.”</p>
<p>It isn’t completely true, nor is it completely false.<br>
[/quote]</p>
<p>Yes, but basically the sky is blue. Fact. But the Big Bang Theory is just a theory and a theory cannot be a fact at the same time. A theory can be proved and become a fact but you cannot have a theory that <span class="bbcode-i">is</span> fact (unless your theory is correct, in that case you cannot know for certain that your theory is fact). So saying a theory, no matter how widely acknowledged it is, is a fact just does not make sense.[/quote]<br>
Actually, nothing in science is fact.  Nothing is absolutely provable, because humans’ study of science is limited to our senses…who knows what lies beyond what we can sense in the world?  A great example is string theory, which in essence discusses that the universe is not 4-dimensional, but is composed up of 11-22 dimensions of strings, but “appears” to us in the 3 space dimensions and 1 time dimension (that’s my pathetic description of it for you ;))…of course, its still a mathematical hypothesis with no supporting observational evidence, but its supposed to be the best hope for solve the quantum gravity issue.  My point being that all of science depends on what we know…and for all we know, everything we think we know may be totally wrong <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=6" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"></p>
<p>Onto the topic, its interesting that this thread was formed when it was.  Actually, I just attended a lecture this past Thursday by Dr. John Mather, who won the Nobel Prize for Physics last year for pretty much confirming the Big Bang Theory.  Apparently, he and his COBE team analyzed irregularities the cosmic microwave background radiation, which was originally theorized to be kinda remanence of the big bang itself.  They were able to compare their results to theoretical predictions of the early universe, and found that the values (ie. spectra of the microwave radiation) matched perfectly…supposedly, since the publishing of that info, there has been no scientific objection to the the Big Bang Theory…obviously not verifying it as fact, but definitely making it far more credible.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-big-bang-theory/65491/39">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-big-bang-theory/65491/39</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 10 Mar 2007 09:55:04 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-65491-39</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-big-bang-theory/65491.rss">The Big bang theory</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The Big bang theory</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@xxlegitxx xxlegitxx]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/xxlegitxx">@xxlegitxx</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote no-group quote-modified" data-post="36" data-topic="65491">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/cheesehunk/40/5_6259e4fa9dfe0dec282fb0955bb1974c.png" class="avatar"> Cheesehunk:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>He’s right though… That’s the way Mathmeticians/Scientists work. They develop a theory, and build on it, trying to prove it right. It’s just like the old model of our Solar system with the earth being the center. Enough information was developed that people thought it to be true, and it just started out as a theory. Eventually it was proved wrong, and our current model has the Sun in the center. When there is enough prove something is true, its no longer a theory, but a law.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Not necessarily so.  As I was saying, there is sufficient evidence, but it isn’t complete.  The general framework is done.</p>
<blockquote>In scientific usage, a theory does not mean an unsubstantiated guess or hunch, as it can in everyday speech. A theory is a logically self-consistent model or framework for describing the behavior of a related set of natural or social phenomena. It originates from and/or is supported by experimental evidence (see scientific method). In this sense, a theory is a systematic and formalized expression of all previous observations that is predictive, logical and testable. In principle, scientific theories are always tentative, and subject to corrections or inclusion in a yet wider theory. Commonly, a large number of more specific hypotheses may be logically bound together by just one or two theories. As a general rule for use of the term, theories tend to deal with much broader sets of universals than do hypotheses, which ordinarily deal with much more specific sets of phenomena or specific applications of a theory.</blockquote>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-big-bang-theory/65491/38">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-big-bang-theory/65491/38</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 10 Mar 2007 09:03:23 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-65491-38</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-big-bang-theory/65491.rss">The Big bang theory</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The Big bang theory</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@1_dum_taco 1 dum taco]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/1_dum_taco">@1_dum_taco</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Both the theory of big bang and That God created the world(which i do belive that God created everything) cant be proven right,nor can they be proven wrong</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-big-bang-theory/65491/37">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-big-bang-theory/65491/37</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 10 Mar 2007 07:54:17 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-65491-37</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-big-bang-theory/65491.rss">The Big bang theory</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The Big bang theory</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Cheesehunk Cheesehunk]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/cheesehunk">@Cheesehunk</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“xxlegitxx, post:35, topic:65491”][quote author=YourDistracted link=topic=95203.msg988240#msg988240 date=1173444925]<br>
I was listening to some scientist on the radio and he said. That scientists have never  “prooved” anything. They just merely expand on older theories.<br>
[/quote]<br>
When was the last time <span class="bbcode-i">real</span> scientists talk on the radio?[/quote]<br>
He’s right though… That’s the way Mathmeticians/Scientists work. They develop a theory, and build on it, trying to prove it right. It’s just like the old model of our Solar system with the earth being the center. Enough information was developed that people thought it to be true, and it just started out as a theory. Eventually it was proved wrong, and our current model has the Sun in the center. When there is enough prove something is true, its no longer a theory, but a law.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-big-bang-theory/65491/36">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-big-bang-theory/65491/36</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 10 Mar 2007 04:30:12 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-65491-36</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-big-bang-theory/65491.rss">The Big bang theory</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
