<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Best Way</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/best-way/285002</link>
    <description>What&#39;s the best way to piss off my cat?</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 23 Jun 2009 20:06:02 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>General Discussion</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/best-way/285002.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Best Way</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@primadude Primadude]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/primadude">@primadude</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote no-group" data-post="5" data-topic="285002">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/zillionair1/40/5_513041d5f7104045db30895d3b90af16.png" class="avatar"> Zillionair1:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Never mind, I found a way of annoyance greater than all of these: Blowing hardly in their ear. It is hilarious! After doing this, I had scratches across my face.  ;D</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>You blew your cat? You sick bastard.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/best-way/285002/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/best-way/285002/6</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jun 2009 20:06:02 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-285002-6</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/best-way/285002.rss">Best Way</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Best Way</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Zillionair1 Zillionair1]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/zillionair1">@Zillionair1</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Never mind, I found a way of annoyance greater than all of these: Blowing hardly in their ear. It is hilarious! After doing this, I had scratches across my face.  ;D</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/best-way/285002/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/best-way/285002/5</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jun 2009 17:55:43 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-285002-5</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/best-way/285002.rss">Best Way</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Best Way</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@primadude Primadude]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/primadude">@primadude</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote no-group quote-modified" data-post="3" data-topic="285002">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 casey.:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>don’t feed it</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>^ This.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/best-way/285002/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/best-way/285002/4</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jun 2009 17:49:57 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-285002-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/best-way/285002.rss">Best Way</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Best Way</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@gothic_queen casey.]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/gothic_queen">@gothic_queen</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>don’t feed it</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/best-way/285002/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/best-way/285002/3</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jun 2009 17:44:12 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-285002-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/best-way/285002.rss">Best Way</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Best Way</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Efilite Efilite]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/efilite">@Efilite</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>kick it.</p>
<p>No don’t I’ll get in trouble for saying that :S.</p>
<p>EDIT:</p>
<ol>
<li>Forced Affection</li>
</ol>
<p>It is a bizarre aspect of their countenance. No matter how much a cat may like affection, they are absolutely repulsed by it when not on their terms. You may be able to pet little “Whiskers” all day long, but as soon as you force any sort of concern for his happiness upon him, Whiskers will immediately lose all interest in being pet. This funny quirk can be used greatly to your advantage. The primary subject of my annoyance studies, Vesuvius, has displayed high levels of aggravation during forced affection tests, and it is my belief that this is one of your greatest weapons in the war of bothering each other. Simply pick up your cat, lie down on your couch or bed, and completely envelop them in your arms, essentially “smothering” them in affection. To really enhance the obnoxiousness of this, maybe sing an extremely stupid song, replacing the majority of words with your cat’s name, or repeat a completely ridiculous sentence in a whiny, high-pitched voice, like used by the guy on that beer commercial, “Who’s got a furry little moustache?”</p>
<p>Your cat will hate you for at least ten minutes, until they forget, and will then resume all annoying activities they were previously engaged in, like missing the litter box, or lying down directly on top of whatever you happen to be reading.</p>
<ol start="2">
<li>Extreme Disappointment</li>
</ol>
<p>While my little Vesuvius has a gigantic heart, she also has a stomache to match its size. Sadly, she has been on a diet for the majority of her life, but the poor little critter’s metabolism just can’t burn away the chubbiness. Needless to say, the prime point of annoyance employed by the munchkin is based around her desire for food. Her perpetual state of hunger, coupled with her insatiable desire to vocalize every trivial, little desire is a recipe for my insanity. Fortunately, I’ve found a way to counter the effects of madness by employing concept number two: Extreme Disappointment.</p>
<p>Simply wait until one of the victim’s meal times, preferably when they are actually indicating a desire for food. Take out the source of sustenance (whether it be a bag, pouch or tupperware container), open it, feign excitement so as to increase the animal’s own zeal, and give them one piece of food. Just one. The expression on Vesuvius’s face is priceless when I employ this tactic, a mix of disbelief, desperation and utter contempt all mixed into one. Of course, I only let this go on for about a minute, but that’s all that is necessary. This speaks a message to your cat: “I’m the food master, and if you don’t like it, go eat a rodent.”</p>
<ol start="3">
<li>Refused Victory</li>
</ol>
<p>This one is simple really. If your cat likes to play (mine rarely shows interest), simply refuse to let them win. Laser pointers are perfect in this regard, since from the outset, victory is impossible; the cat cannot get the red dot. But other, more traditional toys are applicable as well, especially when attached to a string. For as long as the cat will allow, just keep the toy well out of reach. A cat will generally only fight for so long when there is no obvious reward or attainment of the target. And then, hopefully, they will ignore you for ten minutes, until they forget about the whole, painful affair and go do something obnoxious like barfing on the carpet or peeing on your $800 Turkish rug (true story, it’s a wonder she’s still alive).</p>
<p>Kittens are an exception to this rule, but I guess they really don’t apply to any of the rules, as they really can’t grasp the subtle nuances of the power struggle between man and feline. Besides, who would try to annoy a kitten? What are you, psycho?</p>
<ol start="4">
<li>Sudden Movements</li>
</ol>
<p>I know, this is extremely bratty and adolescent, but I can’t help it. When Vesuvius unsuspectingly strolls by, minding her own business and probably wrapped up in some daydream involving fresh fish and sparkly toys, I can’t help but be amused by the two foot vertical launch produced by me moving my foot a mere three inches. I refuse to grow up.</p>
<ol start="5">
<li>Complete Humiliation</li>
</ol>
<p>At risk of appearing insane, I unveil the 5th, and most powerful tool in the arsenal of annoyance: Dressing your cat up in costumes.</p>
<p>Don’t get me wrong, it’s not like I sew miniature dresses and sun hats and make her sit through tea parties with myself a host of stuffed animals (And if that sounds appealing to you, by all means, seek professional help). No, my execution of this particular tactic was motivated by a book idea. Basically, the book is a kung-fu epic, set in feudal Japan, in which the storyline is predominantly supplemented (oxymoron?) by photos of the different characters in totally awesome kung-fu costumes. My parents, who have four cats, were gracious enough to allow this complete exploitation of kitty dignity while I visited them last summer, and for the next couple hours, the photo shoot began. To no surprise, a cat hates, nay, loathes being dressed up like a ninja and having little miniature nunchuks attached to it. In fact, the whole endeavor proved to be so difficult I had to give it up. Damn prima donnas.</p>
<p>Regardless, the book shoot wasn’t a complete waste of time. I got some hilarious photos, and found that for bugging your cat, nothing else comes close to this tactic. (Oh, and don’t get any crazy ideas about stealing my phenomenal book idea, it’s copyrighted).</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/best-way/285002/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/best-way/285002/2</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jun 2009 17:38:33 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-285002-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/best-way/285002.rss">Best Way</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Best Way</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Zillionair1 Zillionair1]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/zillionair1">@Zillionair1</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>What’s the best way to piss off my cat?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/best-way/285002/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/best-way/285002/1</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jun 2009 17:03:26 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-285002-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/best-way/285002.rss">Best Way</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
