<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Multiple tutorials? (staff please read)</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/multiple-tutorials-staff-please-read/233274</link>
    <description>I was thinking about making multiple tutorials for things on 317/377 servers before I move on to 503+, but I wasn&#39;t sure how to approach them. I wasn&#39;t sure if I should make multiple threads, or just multi-post in one thread. The tutorials aren&#39;t all going to be basic, and most a lot of them are going to be different and not related to one another. Thats why I&#39;m asking if I should make multiple threads since they aren&#39;t related. And I&#39;m only asking because if i do make more than one thread, I don&#39;t want the mods to lock them one by one saying i shouldn&#39;t make so many threads.

As for why I&#39;m posting this in a thread rather than contacting a staff member, I just figured this might get my question answered quicker and more efficient without the confusion of who to PM (Some mods obviously aren&#39;t always on to answer). Lock this thread as you see needed.

Anyone that isn&#39;t a staff member, please don&#39;t post anything off topic or something that would be considered spam/flame. Although if you think you might have an answer, post it here.

Thanks,
    [i][b]The Reaper X[/b][/i]</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2008 12:02:05 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/multiple-tutorials-staff-please-read/233274.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Multiple tutorials? (staff please read)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@K_Jay K Jay]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/k_jay">@K_Jay</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Nah, Leave it we need more 503 tutorials i suggest ’ how to edit a 503 ’<br>
Second one ’ how to run a 503 ’<br>
Then a few others.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/multiple-tutorials-staff-please-read/233274/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/multiple-tutorials-staff-please-read/233274/2</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2008 12:02:05 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-233274-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/multiple-tutorials-staff-please-read/233274.rss">Multiple tutorials? (staff please read)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Multiple tutorials? (staff please read)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@The_Reaper_X The Reaper X]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/the_reaper_x">@The_Reaper_X</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I was thinking about making multiple tutorials for things on 317/377 servers before I move on to 503+, but I wasn’t sure how to approach them. I wasn’t sure if I should make multiple threads, or just multi-post in one thread. The tutorials aren’t all going to be basic, and most a lot of them are going to be different and not related to one another. Thats why I’m asking if I should make multiple threads since they aren’t related. And I’m only asking because if i do make more than one thread, I don’t want the mods to lock them one by one saying i shouldn’t make so many threads.</p>
<p>As for why I’m posting this in a thread rather than contacting a staff member, I just figured this might get my question answered quicker and more efficient without the confusion of who to PM (Some mods obviously aren’t always on to answer). Lock this thread as you see needed.</p>
<p>Anyone that isn’t a staff member, please don’t post anything off topic or something that would be considered spam/flame. Although if you think you might have an answer, post it here.</p>
<p>Thanks,<br>
<span class="bbcode-i"><span class="bbcode-b">The Reaper X</span></span></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/multiple-tutorials-staff-please-read/233274/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/multiple-tutorials-staff-please-read/233274/1</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2008 11:51:49 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-233274-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/multiple-tutorials-staff-please-read/233274.rss">Multiple tutorials? (staff please read)</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
