<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>[ZenithScape] Need Help Adding Admin Crown to Friends Chat</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/zenithscape-need-help-adding-admin-crown-to-friends-chat/460091</link>
    <description>Hello! I&#39;ve searched google and even asked some coders of other servers (some of which were not too pleasant to answer :P). I&#39;ve done searches everywhere, and I can&#39;t find it. Could someone help me find the Friends Chat ranks (for the FC interface) serverside? In regular Runescape, Jagex Moderators have a crown when they talk, and their rank is a gold crown, which is what I am attempting to do. I have the gold crown when they talk, but not as the rank. I found the sprite image for the crown, so can someone please tell me where I can find all of the ranks configurations (server-side)? By the way, the server has the base Zenithscape 721/728. I&#39;ll rep anyone who gets me to it successfully  :D.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 25 Sep 2012 04:55:49 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/zenithscape-need-help-adding-admin-crown-to-friends-chat/460091.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>[ZenithScape] Need Help Adding Admin Crown to Friends Chat</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@sundays211 sundays211]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/sundays211">@sundays211</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Not sure if it’s what you need, but the admin rank in the friends chat list is given by sending the user’s channel rank as 127 (where 0 is normally for guest, 1 for recruit, 2 for corporal, etc (7 for owner)).</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/zenithscape-need-help-adding-admin-crown-to-friends-chat/460091/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/zenithscape-need-help-adding-admin-crown-to-friends-chat/460091/2</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 25 Sep 2012 04:55:49 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-460091-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/zenithscape-need-help-adding-admin-crown-to-friends-chat/460091.rss">[ZenithScape] Need Help Adding Admin Crown to Friends Chat</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[ZenithScape] Need Help Adding Admin Crown to Friends Chat</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@mod_ap mod ap]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/mod_ap">@mod_ap</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Hello! I’ve searched google and even asked some coders of other servers (some of which were not too pleasant to answer :P). I’ve done searches everywhere, and I can’t find it. Could someone help me find the Friends Chat ranks (for the FC interface) serverside? In regular Runescape, Jagex Moderators have a crown when they talk, and their rank is a gold crown, which is what I am attempting to do. I have the gold crown when they talk, but not as the rank. I found the sprite image for the crown, so can someone please tell me where I can find all of the ranks configurations (server-side)? By the way, the server has the base Zenithscape 721/728. I’ll rep anyone who gets me to it successfully  :D.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/zenithscape-need-help-adding-admin-crown-to-friends-chat/460091/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/zenithscape-need-help-adding-admin-crown-to-friends-chat/460091/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 16 Sep 2012 14:13:28 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-460091-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/zenithscape-need-help-adding-admin-crown-to-friends-chat/460091.rss">[ZenithScape] Need Help Adding Admin Crown to Friends Chat</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
