<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Sever help please!</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/sever-help-please/337122</link>
    <description>I downloaded a server and client and also made a no-ip account and also did port forwarding. To prove this i can use the client on another computer, type in my no-ip address and it works... sorta. When i do this it logs in but shows the inventory and some stuff u start with in the inventory, but then it logs right out again. On the dos window where my server status is listed it says someone logged in and then logged out. Help please? Could this have to do with the server.ini file? Is a setting out of line? Thanks in advanced.  :)</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 17 Apr 2010 15:33:18 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/sever-help-please/337122.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Sever help please!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@osiffff osiffff]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/osiffff">@osiffff</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I downloaded a server and client and also made a no-ip account and also did port forwarding. To prove this i can use the client on another computer, type in my no-ip address and it works… sorta. When i do this it logs in but shows the inventory and some stuff u start with in the inventory, but then it logs right out again. On the dos window where my server status is listed it says someone logged in and then logged out. Help please? Could this have to do with the server.ini file? Is a setting out of line? Thanks in advanced.  <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=5" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/sever-help-please/337122/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/sever-help-please/337122/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 17 Apr 2010 15:33:18 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-337122-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/sever-help-please/337122.rss">Sever help please!</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
