<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Real Timers</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/real-timers/82467</link>
    <description>Hi,
I&#39;ve been into editing RS private servers for a while (although I can&#39;t code from scratch really, yet), and I recently decided to take a look at how the (hella glitchy) combat system works. I&#39;m using Cheez PK 78. I&#39;ve now realised just why massing in fights speeds up attacks - all because of the crappy timers in [i]public boolean process[/i]. Now, because I&#39;d want a decent combat system to be part of my server, I want to add [i]real[/i] timers to my server. I&#39;ve recently spent a couple of days trying to research timers in Java using Google but, because I don&#39;t know much about Java, i&#39;m finding it difficult. :\ I try not to usually ask for help, and do the research myself but, this time, I&#39;m sick to death of trying to find out about timers.

Here&#39;s basically what I&#39;m looking for: a timer (or something) which adds or subtracts from a public int in milliseconds. I hope i&#39;m not talking a load of crap here - I&#39;m new to this. If anyone could tell me how, or even guide me towards getting real timers set up in my server, It&#39;d [b]really[/b] appreciate it. :cool:

Thanks in advance.

[i]If there&#39;s anything wrong with this post, I apologise. Please tell me what I&#39;ve done wrong and I&#39;ll fix it. This is my first post. Thanks ;-)[/i]</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 21 Apr 2007 02:38:45 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/real-timers/82467.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Real Timers</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Evo Evo]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/evo">@Evo</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>ahh, thanks <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/smiley.png?v=6" title=":smiley:" class="emoji" alt=":smiley:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/real-timers/82467/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/real-timers/82467/3</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 21 Apr 2007 02:38:45 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-82467-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/real-timers/82467.rss">Real Timers</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Real Timers</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Javacisnotrecognized _^_]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/javacisnotrecognized">@Javacisnotrecognized</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I think System.currentTimeMillis and some basic math really is all you need :\</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/real-timers/82467/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/real-timers/82467/2</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 21 Apr 2007 02:36:12 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-82467-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/real-timers/82467.rss">Real Timers</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Real Timers</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Evo Evo]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/evo">@Evo</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Hi,<br>
I’ve been into editing RS private servers for a while (although I can’t code from scratch really, yet), and I recently decided to take a look at how the (hella glitchy) combat system works. I’m using Cheez PK 78. I’ve now realised just why massing in fights speeds up attacks - all because of the crappy timers in <span class="bbcode-i">public boolean process</span>. Now, because I’d want a decent combat system to be part of my server, I want to add <span class="bbcode-i">real</span> timers to my server. I’ve recently spent a couple of days trying to research timers in Java using Google but, because I don’t know much about Java, i’m finding it difficult. :\ I try not to usually ask for help, and do the research myself but, this time, I’m sick to death of trying to find out about timers.</p>
<p>Here’s basically what I’m looking for: a timer (or something) which adds or subtracts from a public int in milliseconds. I hope i’m not talking a load of crap here - I’m new to this. If anyone could tell me how, or even guide me towards getting real timers set up in my server, It’d <span class="bbcode-b">really</span> appreciate it. <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/cool.png?v=6" title=":cool:" class="emoji" alt=":cool:"></p>
<p>Thanks in advance.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-i">If there’s anything wrong with this post, I apologise. Please tell me what I’ve done wrong and I’ll fix it. This is my first post. Thanks <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/wink.png?v=6" title=":wink:" class="emoji" alt=":wink:"></span></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/real-timers/82467/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/real-timers/82467/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 21 Apr 2007 02:33:55 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-82467-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/real-timers/82467.rss">Real Timers</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
