<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Optional use for private chat interface</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/optional-use-for-private-chat-interface/420539</link>
    <description>Hey guys,

I was just wondering how I could use the private chat interface which says &quot;Types message you wish to send to playername&quot; for another use. For example, to make another chat system or to type commands into. I have tried opening the interface ID for the private chat (which just takes up the bottom chat box for those who didn&#39;t know) and it freezes the server. I was wondering how the server itself opened this interface, as it never includes the interface ID within its code. The private message sending packet is case 126. I have examined it and how it works. This packet processes the text information entered by the player. I was just wondering how this packet is activated though. Obviously by clicking a friends name in the list, but this has no button ID. So I cant search for that. 

All in all I just want a simple way to open the private chat interface and to stop it from activating packet 126 and possibly something I have created. For example if I found a way to display the chat interface, it would still automatically use case 126 to send the text to another player. I need to change this so I can use the inputted text for my needs within a method or command.


All help is appreciated.

Thank you :)</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 04 Nov 2011 14:25:37 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/optional-use-for-private-chat-interface/420539.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Optional use for private chat interface</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@razorback razorback]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/razorback">@razorback</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Hey guys,</p>
<p>I was just wondering how I could use the private chat interface which says “Types message you wish to send to playername” for another use. For example, to make another chat system or to type commands into. I have tried opening the interface ID for the private chat (which just takes up the bottom chat box for those who didn’t know) and it freezes the server. I was wondering how the server itself opened this interface, as it never includes the interface ID within its code. The private message sending packet is case 126. I have examined it and how it works. This packet processes the text information entered by the player. I was just wondering how this packet is activated though. Obviously by clicking a friends name in the list, but this has no button ID. So I cant search for that.</p>
<p>All in all I just want a simple way to open the private chat interface and to stop it from activating packet 126 and possibly something I have created. For example if I found a way to display the chat interface, it would still automatically use case 126 to send the text to another player. I need to change this so I can use the inputted text for my needs within a method or command.</p>
<p>All help is appreciated.</p>
<p>Thank you <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=5" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/optional-use-for-private-chat-interface/420539/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/optional-use-for-private-chat-interface/420539/1</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 04 Nov 2011 14:25:37 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-420539-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/optional-use-for-private-chat-interface/420539.rss">Optional use for private chat interface</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
