<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>In depth PHP loops</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/in-depth-php-loops/455451</link>
    <description>Hello MoparScape,

Time for yet another tutorial, I suppose :P. This one will be going further deeper into the language of PHP. Moreso than my other tutorials anyway, covering the following types of loops in depth in PHP:

For and For Each
While
Do While

[b]Part 2 - For and For Each loops:[/b]
We can loop through a set of code by keeping them inside a for each loop. We can tell what increment we want and set it, this is useful for executing larger amounts of recurring code. We will also start with some simple loops and work through to some more difficult versions. As usual, I&#39;ll give you the code then explain it.
[code=php]
&lt;?php
for($i=1; $i&lt;=10; $i++) {
echo $i.&quot;&lt;br /&gt;&quot;;
}
?&gt;
[/code]
This is the simplest form of this type of loop, as usual, your &lt;?php ?&gt; tags are opening and closing tags, your next line is initiating the for loop, declaring the $i variable as 1, then saying that if the variable of $i is lesser than or equal to 10, add the value of $i to it until it reaches that number. The next line is then echoing the data with a line break.

This next loop is advancing a little more, this is adding a parameter to the loop and telling it to stop looping at a certain condition.

[code=php]
&lt;?php
for($i=1; $i&lt;=10; $i++){
if($i &gt; 5){
break;
}
echo $i.&quot;&lt;br&gt;&quot;;
}
?&gt;
[/code]

This loop is the exact same as the before loop, with an extra line or so of code. This code is explained by the above statement, except the parameter we added in. This parameter states that if the variable of $i is greater than 5, stop looping and move on. Which can be handy if they want parameters, which people often do.

This next loop is advancing further, we will make it so that it increases the step value.

[code=php]
&lt;?php
for($i=0;$i&lt;=100;$i +=10){
echo $i.&quot;&lt;br&gt;&quot;;
}
?&gt;
[/code]

Until now, we&#39;ve merely just increased the step value by 1, this time, we&#39;re going to increase it by 10. It can be described as our before loops. Except we&#39;ve increased our values by 10 and reduced the original value of the variable $i to 0.

This next loop I&#39;m going to show you will be advancing more than you&#39;ve seen so far, this will be a foreach loop including an array, if it&#39;s too advanced, don&#39;t worry.

[code=php]
&lt;?php
$forEach = array (10, 11, 12, 13, 14, 15, 16, 17, 18, 19, 20);
foreach ($forEach as $forEach2) {
echo &quot;Current value of \$forEach: $forEach2 &lt;br /&gt; &quot;;
}
?&gt;
[/code]

So once again, if you don&#39;t understand it, read over the following explanation again and again, if you still don&#39;t get it, just come back later with fresh eyes. Obviously our &lt;?php ?&gt; are our opening and closing tags, we&#39;re then declaring that the variable $forEach is an array with the following values. We&#39;re then declaring the foreach loop itself using the $forEach variable as the aforementioned array, then the $forEach2 variable as our results, we then echo the current value of $forEach as the latest value in $forEach2.

Not too complex, but not too simple to grasp either.

[b]Part 3 - While Loops[/b]
The while loop in PHP is the condition is checked at the beginning of the loop and the statement inside is executed till the end of the loop, then again the condition is checked and loop executed. As usual, I&#39;ll give you the code then I&#39;ll talk through it:
[code=php]
&lt;?php
$i=50;
while($i &lt; 162 ) {
echo &quot; value of \$i= $i &lt;br&gt;&quot;;
$i=$i+3;
}
?&gt;
[/code]

So what this does is our &lt;?php ?&gt; tag is obviously our opening and closing tags as usual. We&#39;re then declaring the variable of $i, giving it a value of 50. We&#39;re then doing a while loop with the condition of $i being less than the value of 162. We then echo the value of $i in it&#39;s current state. Then follow up by adding 3 to our current value, therefore meeting our condition of it being below 162. I&#39;ve just used some random numbers in there, they&#39;re not really that simple, sorry, lol.

So that was a short part of the tutorial, but necessary, we&#39;ll now move on to the final part. This being Do While loops.

[b]Part 4 - Do While Loops[/b]
So a lot of you will be asking what the difference is between a while and a do while loop. Well, in a while loop, the condition is set at the beginning and if it&#39;s true the loop will begin and execute the below code, however, in do while loops the checking of the condition is done at the end of the loop, not at the start. Here&#39;s a do while loop:
[code=php]
&lt;?php
$i=50;
do {
echo $i;
echo &quot;&lt;br /&gt;&quot;;
}
while ($i &gt; 1);
?&gt;
[/code]
So as usual, our &lt;?php ?&gt; tags are opening and closing tags, we&#39;re then setting the variable of $i as 50, the same as our previous loop. I&#39;m then telling the code to echo the variable $i and echoing a line break, we&#39;re then closing our do statement and opening up a while loop, which works on while the variable $i is greater than 1.

This is rather simple, and may seem pointless but it does come in handy and is useful in certain circumstances. Here is a more advanced do while loop, with an if loop and a break in it.

[code=php]
&lt;?php
$i=5;
do{
echo $i;
echo &quot;&lt;br /&gt;&quot;;
$i=$i+1;
if($i&gt;162) {
break;
   }
} 
while ($i &lt; 15);
?&gt;
[/code]

This is once again, a do while loop.  Which is more or less the same as the last but since it&#39;s the last loop in this tutorial, I&#39;ll describe it further. As usual &lt;?php ?&gt; is our opening and closing tags, we&#39;re then setting the variable of $i as 5. We&#39;re then starting a do statement which echos the $i variable along with a line break. We&#39;re then saying that the variable $i should have 1 added to it every recurrence of the loop. We&#39;re then adding a parameter of $i being greater than 162 then we should break the loop. We then have the condition of the variable of $i being less than 15 for the while loop to initiate.

[b]Part 5 - Associative Arrays within Foreach Loops[/b]
Associative arrays will be explained further in my Arrays tutorial which will come sometime in the very near future, maybe even tonight. If you don&#39;t understand it, don&#39;t worry about it. As per usual, I&#39;ll give you the code then I&#39;ll talk you through it.
[code=php]
$moparActivity[&quot;March&quot;] = &quot;436&quot;;
$moparActivity[&quot;April&quot;] = &quot;396&quot;;
$moparActivity[&quot;May&quot;] = &quot;379&quot;;
$moparActivity[&quot;June&quot;] = &quot;586&quot;;
$moparActivity[&quot;July&quot;] = &quot;458&quot;;
$moparActivity[&quot;August&quot;] = &quot;387&quot;;

foreach( $moparActivity as $month =&gt; $activity){
	echo &quot;Month: $month &lt;br /&gt; Users Online: $activity &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&quot;;
}
[/code]

The above code is telling us the activity for MoparScape in users in the past 6 months, hence the array $moparActivity. This is what&#39;s known as an associative array and we&#39;re iterating it through a ForEach loop. We use this type of loop because it will execute the code for each piece of data. So lets talk through it, we&#39;re initiating the array with $moparActivity[&quot;month&quot;] = &quot;usersonline&quot;; Then we do this for the previous months. After doing this, we then initiate a foreach loop that is changing the data from the $moparActivity array, to holding the month in $month and the users online in $activity. This is then echoed in the next line and there we have it.

Well MoparScape, my 7th tutorial is now complete. It was done at 12:26am so there may be some mistakes, however, post below and I&#39;ll fix them. I do hope you guys enjoy that and be on the lookout for my next tutorial on PHP arrays!

Best Regards,
Ruby.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 22 Aug 2012 16:45:49 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>General Programming</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/in-depth-php-loops/455451.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>In depth PHP loops</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@management management]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/management">@management</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>No problem ^.^</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/in-depth-php-loops/455451/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/in-depth-php-loops/455451/4</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 22 Aug 2012 16:45:49 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-455451-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/in-depth-php-loops/455451.rss">In depth PHP loops</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>In depth PHP loops</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Ruby_Forums_Coder Ruby]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/ruby_forums_coder">@Ruby_Forums_Coder</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“management, post:2, topic:455451”][quote author=Ruby link=topic=558356.msg4083769#msg4083769 date=1345591663]<br>
<span class="bbcode-b">Part 1 - If/Else Loops:</span><br>
[/quote]<br>
if/else statements are <span class="bbcode-b">not</span> loops.[/quote]</p>
<p>Holy shit I just realised I done that.</p>
<p>The reason that was in there was because I had actually started this out as a general PHP tutorial again, but then I changed to putting it on Loops and I mustn’t have removed that. I had already written half of it and I wasn’t thinking since it was like 1am when I wrote it.</p>
<p>Thanks for pointing that out.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/in-depth-php-loops/455451/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/in-depth-php-loops/455451/3</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 22 Aug 2012 16:44:25 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-455451-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/in-depth-php-loops/455451.rss">In depth PHP loops</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>In depth PHP loops</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@management management]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/management">@management</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote quote-modified" data-post="1" data-topic="455451">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/ruby/40/5_e05bb34c421432ee4d40de30c10af3e5.png" class="avatar"> Ruby:</div>
<blockquote>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Part 1 - If/Else Loops:</span></p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>if/else statements are <span class="bbcode-b">not</span> loops.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/in-depth-php-loops/455451/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/in-depth-php-loops/455451/2</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 22 Aug 2012 16:20:15 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-455451-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/in-depth-php-loops/455451.rss">In depth PHP loops</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>In depth PHP loops</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Ruby_Forums_Coder Ruby]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/ruby_forums_coder">@Ruby_Forums_Coder</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Hello MoparScape,</p>
<p>Time for yet another tutorial, I suppose :P. This one will be going further deeper into the language of PHP. Moreso than my other tutorials anyway, covering the following types of loops in depth in PHP:</p>
<p>For and For Each<br>
While<br>
Do While</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Part 2 - For and For Each loops:</span><br>
We can loop through a set of code by keeping them inside a for each loop. We can tell what increment we want and set it, this is useful for executing larger amounts of recurring code. We will also start with some simple loops and work through to some more difficult versions. As usual, I’ll give you the code then explain it.</p>
<pre><code class="lang-auto">&lt;?php
for($i=1; $i&lt;=10; $i++) {
echo $i."&lt;br /&gt;";
}
?&gt;</code></pre>
<p>This is the simplest form of this type of loop, as usual, your &lt;?php ?&gt; tags are opening and closing tags, your next line is initiating the for loop, declaring the $i variable as 1, then saying that if the variable of $i is lesser than or equal to 10, add the value of $i to it until it reaches that number. The next line is then echoing the data with a line break.</p>
<p>This next loop is advancing a little more, this is adding a parameter to the loop and telling it to stop looping at a certain condition.</p>
<pre><code class="lang-auto">&lt;?php
for($i=1; $i&lt;=10; $i++){
if($i &gt; 5){
break;
}
echo $i."&lt;br&gt;";
}
?&gt;</code></pre>
<p>This loop is the exact same as the before loop, with an extra line or so of code. This code is explained by the above statement, except the parameter we added in. This parameter states that if the variable of $i is greater than 5, stop looping and move on. Which can be handy if they want parameters, which people often do.</p>
<p>This next loop is advancing further, we will make it so that it increases the step value.</p>
<pre><code class="lang-auto">&lt;?php
for($i=0;$i&lt;=100;$i +=10){
echo $i."&lt;br&gt;";
}
?&gt;</code></pre>
<p>Until now, we’ve merely just increased the step value by 1, this time, we’re going to increase it by 10. It can be described as our before loops. Except we’ve increased our values by 10 and reduced the original value of the variable $i to 0.</p>
<p>This next loop I’m going to show you will be advancing more than you’ve seen so far, this will be a foreach loop including an array, if it’s too advanced, don’t worry.</p>
<pre><code class="lang-auto">&lt;?php
$forEach = array (10, 11, 12, 13, 14, 15, 16, 17, 18, 19, 20);
foreach ($forEach as $forEach2) {
echo "Current value of \$forEach: $forEach2 &lt;br /&gt; ";
}
?&gt;</code></pre>
<p>So once again, if you don’t understand it, read over the following explanation again and again, if you still don’t get it, just come back later with fresh eyes. Obviously our &lt;?php ?&gt; are our opening and closing tags, we’re then declaring that the variable $forEach is an array with the following values. We’re then declaring the foreach loop itself using the $forEach variable as the aforementioned array, then the $forEach2 variable as our results, we then echo the current value of $forEach as the latest value in $forEach2.</p>
<p>Not too complex, but not too simple to grasp either.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Part 3 - While Loops</span><br>
The while loop in PHP is the condition is checked at the beginning of the loop and the statement inside is executed till the end of the loop, then again the condition is checked and loop executed. As usual, I’ll give you the code then I’ll talk through it:</p>
<pre><code class="lang-auto">&lt;?php
$i=50;
while($i &lt; 162 ) {
echo " value of \$i= $i &lt;br&gt;";
$i=$i+3;
}
?&gt;</code></pre>
<p>So what this does is our &lt;?php ?&gt; tag is obviously our opening and closing tags as usual. We’re then declaring the variable of $i, giving it a value of 50. We’re then doing a while loop with the condition of $i being less than the value of 162. We then echo the value of $i in it’s current state. Then follow up by adding 3 to our current value, therefore meeting our condition of it being below 162. I’ve just used some random numbers in there, they’re not really that simple, sorry, lol.</p>
<p>So that was a short part of the tutorial, but necessary, we’ll now move on to the final part. This being Do While loops.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Part 4 - Do While Loops</span><br>
So a lot of you will be asking what the difference is between a while and a do while loop. Well, in a while loop, the condition is set at the beginning and if it’s true the loop will begin and execute the below code, however, in do while loops the checking of the condition is done at the end of the loop, not at the start. Here’s a do while loop:</p>
<pre><code class="lang-auto">&lt;?php
$i=50;
do {
echo $i;
echo "&lt;br /&gt;";
}
while ($i &gt; 1);
?&gt;</code></pre>
<p>So as usual, our &lt;?php ?&gt; tags are opening and closing tags, we’re then setting the variable of $i as 50, the same as our previous loop. I’m then telling the code to echo the variable $i and echoing a line break, we’re then closing our do statement and opening up a while loop, which works on while the variable $i is greater than 1.</p>
<p>This is rather simple, and may seem pointless but it does come in handy and is useful in certain circumstances. Here is a more advanced do while loop, with an if loop and a break in it.</p>
<pre><code class="lang-auto">&lt;?php
$i=5;
do{
echo $i;
echo "&lt;br /&gt;";
$i=$i+1;
if($i&gt;162) {
break;
   }
} 
while ($i &lt; 15);
?&gt;</code></pre>
<p>This is once again, a do while loop.  Which is more or less the same as the last but since it’s the last loop in this tutorial, I’ll describe it further. As usual &lt;?php ?&gt; is our opening and closing tags, we’re then setting the variable of $i as 5. We’re then starting a do statement which echos the $i variable along with a line break. We’re then saying that the variable $i should have 1 added to it every recurrence of the loop. We’re then adding a parameter of $i being greater than 162 then we should break the loop. We then have the condition of the variable of $i being less than 15 for the while loop to initiate.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Part 5 - Associative Arrays within Foreach Loops</span><br>
Associative arrays will be explained further in my Arrays tutorial which will come sometime in the very near future, maybe even tonight. If you don’t understand it, don’t worry about it. As per usual, I’ll give you the code then I’ll talk you through it.</p>
<pre><code class="lang-auto">$moparActivity["March"] = "436";
$moparActivity["April"] = "396";
$moparActivity["May"] = "379";
$moparActivity["June"] = "586";
$moparActivity["July"] = "458";
$moparActivity["August"] = "387";

foreach( $moparActivity as $month =&gt; $activity){
	echo "Month: $month &lt;br /&gt; Users Online: $activity &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;";
}</code></pre>
<p>The above code is telling us the activity for MoparScape in users in the past 6 months, hence the array $moparActivity. This is what’s known as an associative array and we’re iterating it through a ForEach loop. We use this type of loop because it will execute the code for each piece of data. So lets talk through it, we’re initiating the array with $moparActivity[“month”] = “usersonline”; Then we do this for the previous months. After doing this, we then initiate a foreach loop that is changing the data from the $moparActivity array, to holding the month in $month and the users online in $activity. This is then echoed in the next line and there we have it.</p>
<p>Well MoparScape, my 7th tutorial is now complete. It was done at 12:26am so there may be some mistakes, however, post below and I’ll fix them. I do hope you guys enjoy that and be on the lookout for my next tutorial on PHP arrays!</p>
<p>Best Regards,<br>
Ruby.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/in-depth-php-loops/455451/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/in-depth-php-loops/455451/1</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 21 Aug 2012 23:27:43 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-455451-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/in-depth-php-loops/455451.rss">In depth PHP loops</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
