<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Red Lights</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/red-lights/534810</link>
    <description>Okay forget the plot review and all that jaz because with this movie, it&#39;s all about the end.

I couldn&#39;t but help think that the people making this film tried too hard to make it a mind fudge, by the end of the movie I was wondering wtf just happened in a sense where I actually didn&#39;t know what the fudge just happened. So it seems that Tom all along had powers and was in search for someone just like him, Silver being the most popular and well known person for doing what he does and Tom picks up on it and decides to investigate. So it turns out that Silver is a fraud and Tom shows everyone giving up his incognito to prove it but this is where I found an interest. Earlier on in the movie there was a quote Matherson said which was [i]&quot;You know, there are two kinds of people out there with a special gift - the ones who really think they have some kind of power, and the other guys who think we can&#39;t figure them out. They&#39;re both wrong.&quot; [/i]This really struck my interest and I realized that Tom may not actually have these magical powers that he thinks he does, that he thinks he has that special gift. While on the other hand Silver is the type that thinks no one can figure him out. I just thought it was an interesting theory to a movie trying to take a similar route as Shutter Island, another movie that was actually quite successful for its dozen fork in the road endings and mind fudge situations.

Would I watch again? Probably not. It&#39;s a movie you need to give your attention to every second so you don&#39;t ask questions 2 minutes later. The ending was spontanious and kind of rushed and confusing. 
I would probably rate this movie a 6/10 tabbies.
[img width=60]http://comicsgrinder.files.wordpress.com/2013/06/tabby-cat.jpg[/img][img width=60]http://comicsgrinder.files.wordpress.com/2013/06/tabby-cat.jpg[/img][img width=60]http://comicsgrinder.files.wordpress.com/2013/06/tabby-cat.jpg[/img][img width=60]http://comicsgrinder.files.wordpress.com/2013/06/tabby-cat.jpg[/img][img width=60]http://comicsgrinder.files.wordpress.com/2013/06/tabby-cat.jpg[/img][img width=60]http://comicsgrinder.files.wordpress.com/2013/06/tabby-cat.jpg[/img]</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2013 11:22:52 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>General Discussion</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/red-lights/534810.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Red Lights</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@TabbyKiller TabbyKiller]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/tabbykiller">@TabbyKiller</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Okay forget the plot review and all that jaz because with this movie, it’s all about the end.</p>
<p>I couldn’t but help think that the people making this film tried too hard to make it a mind fudge, by the end of the movie I was wondering wtf just happened in a sense where I actually didn’t know what the fudge just happened. So it seems that Tom all along had powers and was in search for someone just like him, Silver being the most popular and well known person for doing what he does and Tom picks up on it and decides to investigate. So it turns out that Silver is a fraud and Tom shows everyone giving up his incognito to prove it but this is where I found an interest. Earlier on in the movie there was a quote Matherson said which was <span class="bbcode-i">“You know, there are two kinds of people out there with a special gift - the ones who really think they have some kind of power, and the other guys who think we can’t figure them out. They’re both wrong.” </span>This really struck my interest and I realized that Tom may not actually have these magical powers that he thinks he does, that he thinks he has that special gift. While on the other hand Silver is the type that thinks no one can figure him out. I just thought it was an interesting theory to a movie trying to take a similar route as Shutter Island, another movie that was actually quite successful for its dozen fork in the road endings and mind fudge situations.</p>
<p>Would I watch again? Probably not. It’s a movie you need to give your attention to every second so you don’t ask questions 2 minutes later. The ending was spontanious and kind of rushed and confusing.<br>
I would probably rate this movie a 6/10 tabbies.<br>
<img src="http://comicsgrinder.files.wordpress.com/2013/06/tabby-cat.jpg" alt width="" height=""><img src="http://comicsgrinder.files.wordpress.com/2013/06/tabby-cat.jpg" alt width="" height=""><img src="http://comicsgrinder.files.wordpress.com/2013/06/tabby-cat.jpg" alt width="" height=""><img src="http://comicsgrinder.files.wordpress.com/2013/06/tabby-cat.jpg" alt width="" height=""><img src="http://comicsgrinder.files.wordpress.com/2013/06/tabby-cat.jpg" alt width="" height=""><img src="http://comicsgrinder.files.wordpress.com/2013/06/tabby-cat.jpg" alt width="" height=""></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/red-lights/534810/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/red-lights/534810/1</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2013 11:22:52 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-534810-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/red-lights/534810.rss">Red Lights</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
