<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Account Security [READ OR BE AT RISK FOR A BAN]</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/account-security-read-or-be-at-risk-for-a-ban/251346</link>
    <description>It seems some of our members think they are being hacked, which is sometimes true. In such a circumstance, [b]DO NOT CREATE A NEW ACCOUNT[/b]. Multiple accounts is an automatic, permanent ban to all accounts. Instead, email a staff member or ask a friend to private message a staff member in regards to the hacking. Also, you can come on IRC (irc.moparisthebest.com:6667, #moparscape) and message a staff member there as well. To avoid such a sticky situation completely, try some of the following methods to ensure your account is secure:

1. Make sure your password contains words that are not in the dictionary and which have numbers.
2. If you feel uncomfortable about your account being exploited, change your password every two weeks, or so.
3. Create a security question. Go into your Profile -&gt; Account Related Settings. Type in your security question and an answer only [b]you would know[/b]. In the circumstance you would ever forget your password or your account would be exploited, you can use this to recover your password.
4. Make sure you have full access to the email address on your account. Whenever a person changes the password on an account, they have to reverify it using an email sent to the email address. Whenever someone enters their security question, their password resets and is emailed to them to the email on their account.

Make sure you read over all four suggestions and understand them thoroughly. You can private message me or another staff member if you need help with any of the above suggestions, or if you know someone who is looking to have their account recovered. Thanks for reading and make sure you stay secure.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2008 15:04:04 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Community Suggestions</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/account-security-read-or-be-at-risk-for-a-ban/251346.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Account Security [READ OR BE AT RISK FOR A BAN]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@mod_taharok Taharok]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/mod_taharok">@mod_taharok</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>It seems some of our members think they are being hacked, which is sometimes true. In such a circumstance, <span class="bbcode-b">DO NOT CREATE A NEW ACCOUNT</span>. Multiple accounts is an automatic, permanent ban to all accounts. Instead, email a staff member or ask a friend to private message a staff member in regards to the hacking. Also, you can come on IRC (<a href="http://irc.moparisthebest.com:6667" rel="nofollow noopener">irc.moparisthebest.com:6667</a>, <span class="hashtag">#moparscape</span>) and message a staff member there as well. To avoid such a sticky situation completely, try some of the following methods to ensure your account is secure:</p>
<ol>
<li>Make sure your password contains words that are not in the dictionary and which have numbers.</li>
<li>If you feel uncomfortable about your account being exploited, change your password every two weeks, or so.</li>
<li>Create a security question. Go into your Profile -&gt; Account Related Settings. Type in your security question and an answer only <span class="bbcode-b">you would know</span>. In the circumstance you would ever forget your password or your account would be exploited, you can use this to recover your password.</li>
<li>Make sure you have full access to the email address on your account. Whenever a person changes the password on an account, they have to reverify it using an email sent to the email address. Whenever someone enters their security question, their password resets and is emailed to them to the email on their account.</li>
</ol>
<p>Make sure you read over all four suggestions and understand them thoroughly. You can private message me or another staff member if you need help with any of the above suggestions, or if you know someone who is looking to have their account recovered. Thanks for reading and make sure you stay secure.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/account-security-read-or-be-at-risk-for-a-ban/251346/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/account-security-read-or-be-at-risk-for-a-ban/251346/1</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2008 15:04:04 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-251346-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/account-security-read-or-be-at-risk-for-a-ban/251346.rss">Account Security [READ OR BE AT RISK FOR A BAN]</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
