<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>How do rs classic bots work?</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-do-rs-classic-bots-work/471787</link>
    <description>I remember rs classic bots not using mouse like the rs2 ones, I know autorune sent packets cause back then it was easy to do, now the packets are encrypted even on rs classic, but there are still some bots that interact without using any interfaces, so how is it done? I can imagine that you should be able to make the client think that you just clicked attack on some mob without actually clicking it. Someone please give me a few hints where to start and where to look at to get started with this. Like how am I going to find the &quot;switch&quot; that makes the client think I just attacked something.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 08 Dec 2012 19:51:03 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-do-rs-classic-bots-work/471787.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>How do rs classic bots work?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@rronnyv rronnyv]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/rronnyv">@rronnyv</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I remember rs classic bots not using mouse like the rs2 ones, I know autorune sent packets cause back then it was easy to do, now the packets are encrypted even on rs classic, but there are still some bots that interact without using any interfaces, so how is it done? I can imagine that you should be able to make the client think that you just clicked attack on some mob without actually clicking it. Someone please give me a few hints where to start and where to look at to get started with this. Like how am I going to find the “switch” that makes the client think I just attacked something.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-do-rs-classic-bots-work/471787/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-do-rs-classic-bots-work/471787/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 08 Dec 2012 19:51:03 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-471787-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-do-rs-classic-bots-work/471787.rss">How do rs classic bots work?</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
