<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Im ip banned from mopar?</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/im-ip-banned-from-mopar/223954</link>
    <description>   THERE IS NOWHERE ELSE TO POST OR ASK ABOUT THIS SO IM POSING IT HERE!!!!!   hey so today ive been using the mopar forums all day, and it logs me out and wont load the site again. so i wait awhile, still nothing. so i try it on another computer, and it works. so i used a proxy thing to get on mopar, and it said i was banned for posting virus links via private message.  let me get one thing straight though, I DID NOT EVEN SEND A PM IN THE LAST 2 WEEKS!!!! i NEVER even sent someone a pm that had ANY link in it. someone needs to get this straight?[br][br][size=1]Posted on: August 05, 2008, 10:55:04 am[/size][hr]is there noone that can awnser me...???? mods? admins? hello? anyone?</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 05 Aug 2008 16:32:34 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/im-ip-banned-from-mopar/223954.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Im ip banned from mopar?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@chris_lol chris lol]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/chris_lol">@chris_lol</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>THERE IS NOWHERE ELSE TO POST OR ASK ABOUT THIS SO IM POSING IT HERE!!!   hey so today ive been using the mopar forums all day, and it logs me out and wont load the site again. so i wait awhile, still nothing. so i try it on another computer, and it works. so i used a proxy thing to get on mopar, and it said i was banned for posting virus links via private message.  let me get one thing straight though, I DID NOT EVEN SEND A PM IN THE LAST 2 WEEKS!!! i NEVER even sent someone a pm that had ANY link in it. someone needs to get this straight?[br][br][size=1]Posted on: August 05, 2008, 10:55:04 am[/size][hr]is there noone that can awnser me…??? mods? admins? hello? anyone?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/im-ip-banned-from-mopar/223954/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/im-ip-banned-from-mopar/223954/1</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 05 Aug 2008 16:32:34 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-223954-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/im-ip-banned-from-mopar/223954.rss">Im ip banned from mopar?</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
