<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Trouble starting a RSPS</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/trouble-starting-a-rsps/553102</link>
    <description>I used to code private servers back in the day and had everything down, but it&#39;s been YEARS! I miss it and want to get back into to, so i looked up what to do and can not figure this out. I looked up how to portfoward and did it. No-ip and all. Go to canyouseeme.org and its having errors. Been to multiple sites to fix the erorr and still can not figure it out. Not sure if that&#39;s the problem or not, but the server of the rsps can&#39;t connect. I just need some guidance of what to do next. Please and thank you, I&#39;m not very tech savy, but Im trying to learn.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2015 10:44:12 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/trouble-starting-a-rsps/553102.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Trouble starting a RSPS</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@I_R_Fool I R Fool]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/i_r_fool">@I_R_Fool</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Try use NoobScape v3 and you wont need portforwarding and others <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=5" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/trouble-starting-a-rsps/553102/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/trouble-starting-a-rsps/553102/4</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2015 10:44:12 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-553102-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/trouble-starting-a-rsps/553102.rss">Trouble starting a RSPS</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Trouble starting a RSPS</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@top_tier top tier]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/top_tier">@top_tier</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Thanks for the advice. I tried multiple port forwarding guides/tutorials, but i guess they haven’t been successful. I’m going to keep trying! Just wanted to see what people had to say or though about the situation, but if you zoomed it down to a portforwarding issue, it makes it a whole lot easier!</p>
<p>updated*  I have tried looking more into it and Arris Modems/Routers. I went to <a href="http://portforwarding.com" rel="nofollow noopener">portforwarding.com</a> and it tells me the steps, but every arris modem has a “Virtual Servers” tab. However, my Arris settings don’t have a virtual servers tab or port forwarding tab, only a port triggering. Is there any solution to this? or advice</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/trouble-starting-a-rsps/553102/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/trouble-starting-a-rsps/553102/3</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 26 Aug 2015 14:49:46 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-553102-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/trouble-starting-a-rsps/553102.rss">Trouble starting a RSPS</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Trouble starting a RSPS</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@WarTusk-RSPS WarTusk-RSPS]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/wartusk-rsps">@WarTusk-RSPS</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>If you are having errors on <a href="http://canyouseeme.org" rel="nofollow noopener">canyouseeme.org</a> then it is a portforwarding issue.</p>
<p>There are a lot of ways to port forward.</p>
<p>Best way overall is to just get a vps for a few dollars a month. And you won’t have to worry about the port forwarding at all because the vps provider will do it for you.</p>
<p>If you do not have any money to spend right now then the easiest way to port forward for me Was to just call my internet provider and they manually will open the port for you or teach you how to do it.</p>
<p>Some router providers might not help so You can also use Uttorent. I used to use that in the past but I heard some negative reviews about it. But it still worked like a charm for when I used it.</p>
<p>And port <a href="http://forward.com" rel="nofollow noopener">forward.com</a> is the other option. I never tried to use it. But when I first tried to start my own server like 6 years ago that was like one of the only options.  And that is what most people used. But I used hamachi instead because I was a nub.</p>
<p>I suggest you do not use hamachi like I did lol.</p>
<p>There are also a lot of tutorials on google how to port forward and tutorials how to use the methods i suggested.</p>
<p>I wish you luck with your server! <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=5" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
<p>Also welcome back to the rsps club!</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/trouble-starting-a-rsps/553102/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/trouble-starting-a-rsps/553102/2</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 26 Aug 2015 14:24:59 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-553102-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/trouble-starting-a-rsps/553102.rss">Trouble starting a RSPS</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Trouble starting a RSPS</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@top_tier top tier]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/top_tier">@top_tier</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I used to code private servers back in the day and had everything down, but it’s been YEARS! I miss it and want to get back into to, so i looked up what to do and can not figure this out. I looked up how to portfoward and did it. No-ip and all. Go to <a href="http://canyouseeme.org" rel="nofollow noopener">canyouseeme.org</a> and its having errors. Been to multiple sites to fix the erorr and still can not figure it out. Not sure if that’s the problem or not, but the server of the rsps can’t connect. I just need some guidance of what to do next. Please and thank you, I’m not very tech savy, but Im trying to learn.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/trouble-starting-a-rsps/553102/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/trouble-starting-a-rsps/553102/1</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 26 Aug 2015 13:53:48 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-553102-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/trouble-starting-a-rsps/553102.rss">Trouble starting a RSPS</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
