<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Vote Points; Is their Purpose Pointless?</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/vote-points-is-their-purpose-pointless/536872</link>
    <description>As I search through the server advertisements I notice that about 95% of the servers &quot;force&quot; their players to (at some point) vote. What do I mean by force? Many servers employ a creative way to have their players vote. Some have a vote point shop with items that should be attainable within their world through what should be normal means. Some servers give cash for voting to the point where if you wish to buy anything worth while you will likely need to vote. some servers restrict their players in some way such as reduced xp amount or not being being able to trade or access shops. The latter sometimes (if rarely) can be taken to the extreme, like not allowing the players who do not vote access only to the home and no xp gained, ect ect. 

Some people may not see this as &quot;forcing&quot; the player to vote, and that&#39;s just fine. But I feel that a vote for a server should be voluntary and not used as currency. Its a vote that says &quot;I think this is a good server that is worth looking at&quot; and not &quot;Boy do I want that pernex, I better vote 25 times to get it, I dont care if I skew the vote system for it&quot;. I just feel that the point of voting for a server in no longer valid and that maybe something should change. Maybe I am wrong. Maybe that was the initial point of the server voting system. All in all I believe that a truly good server does not need any kind of incentive to have players vote for it, at most an infrequent reminder of how and where to vote is all it should need.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 14 Dec 2013 19:38:57 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/vote-points-is-their-purpose-pointless/536872.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Vote Points; Is their Purpose Pointless?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@enzo42 enzo42]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/enzo42">@enzo42</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Voting for rares or good items is stupid, something like an exp increase for 30 minutes or something sounds reasonable to me though</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/vote-points-is-their-purpose-pointless/536872/7">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/vote-points-is-their-purpose-pointless/536872/7</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 14 Dec 2013 19:38:57 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-536872-7</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/vote-points-is-their-purpose-pointless/536872.rss">Vote Points; Is their Purpose Pointless?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Vote Points; Is their Purpose Pointless?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@vManlyMan vManlyMan]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/vmanlyman">@vManlyMan</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I think the best way to set up a vote point shop would be to stock it with items that you could achieve through normal play, but could get faster through voting.  For example, put Godsword Shards or Hilts in the shop, so after a couple weeks of voting you could build an AGS.  But if you don’t feel like voting, you could just go to GWD and get the sword that way.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/vote-points-is-their-purpose-pointless/536872/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/vote-points-is-their-purpose-pointless/536872/6</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 14 Dec 2013 19:18:23 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-536872-6</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/vote-points-is-their-purpose-pointless/536872.rss">Vote Points; Is their Purpose Pointless?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Vote Points; Is their Purpose Pointless?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@runescape_sucks runescape sucks]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/runescape_sucks">@runescape_sucks</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>It would be like if they gave out coupons to people who voted irl. If they voted, they would get the bonus of having a coupon. But, if they didn’t vote, they just wouldn’t have the coupon and would live there life on normally.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/vote-points-is-their-purpose-pointless/536872/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/vote-points-is-their-purpose-pointless/536872/5</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 14 Dec 2013 03:37:19 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-536872-5</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/vote-points-is-their-purpose-pointless/536872.rss">Vote Points; Is their Purpose Pointless?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Vote Points; Is their Purpose Pointless?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@JavaTC JavaTC]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/javatc">@JavaTC</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Depends on the items you’re referring to really.  I quite like the voting systems on most servers anymore.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/vote-points-is-their-purpose-pointless/536872/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/vote-points-is-their-purpose-pointless/536872/4</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2013 23:27:16 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-536872-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/vote-points-is-their-purpose-pointless/536872.rss">Vote Points; Is their Purpose Pointless?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Vote Points; Is their Purpose Pointless?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Uncalled Uncalled]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/uncalled">@Uncalled</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>If you’re legitimately restricting your players from accessing the server unless you vote daily, then that’s wrong. Though, a little encouragement doesn’t hurt. As long as the reward for voting isn’t immense, then it’s fine. It’ll still be voluntary, but you receive a bit of appreciation for doing such actions.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/vote-points-is-their-purpose-pointless/536872/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/vote-points-is-their-purpose-pointless/536872/3</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2013 09:48:55 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-536872-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/vote-points-is-their-purpose-pointless/536872.rss">Vote Points; Is their Purpose Pointless?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Vote Points; Is their Purpose Pointless?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@arham_4 arham 4]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/arham_4">@arham_4</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I find it wrong to “force” the players to. Vote points have the purpose to encourage, but forcing decourages.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/vote-points-is-their-purpose-pointless/536872/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/vote-points-is-their-purpose-pointless/536872/2</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2013 00:34:37 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-536872-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/vote-points-is-their-purpose-pointless/536872.rss">Vote Points; Is their Purpose Pointless?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Vote Points; Is their Purpose Pointless?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Ykcud Ykcud]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/ykcud">@Ykcud</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>As I search through the server advertisements I notice that about 95% of the servers “force” their players to (at some point) vote. What do I mean by force? Many servers employ a creative way to have their players vote. Some have a vote point shop with items that should be attainable within their world through what should be normal means. Some servers give cash for voting to the point where if you wish to buy anything worth while you will likely need to vote. some servers restrict their players in some way such as reduced xp amount or not being being able to trade or access shops. The latter sometimes (if rarely) can be taken to the extreme, like not allowing the players who do not vote access only to the home and no xp gained, ect ect.</p>
<p>Some people may not see this as “forcing” the player to vote, and that’s just fine. But I feel that a vote for a server should be voluntary and not used as currency. Its a vote that says “I think this is a good server that is worth looking at” and not “Boy do I want that pernex, I better vote 25 times to get it, I dont care if I skew the vote system for it”. I just feel that the point of voting for a server in no longer valid and that maybe something should change. Maybe I am wrong. Maybe that was the initial point of the server voting system. All in all I believe that a truly good server does not need any kind of incentive to have players vote for it, at most an infrequent reminder of how and where to vote is all it should need.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/vote-points-is-their-purpose-pointless/536872/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/vote-points-is-their-purpose-pointless/536872/1</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2013 17:50:56 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-536872-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/vote-points-is-their-purpose-pointless/536872.rss">Vote Points; Is their Purpose Pointless?</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
