<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>The Warrior</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-warrior/138600</link>
    <description>The Warrior
~VB6 FTW~
Genre: Science/Fiction

@#-Chapter 1
Runescape. The game filled with daggers, magic and ownage. This story will tell you how 1 boy turned into a sucess. The boy, which screenname is Bong Boy, is walking down the street. Then he finds a guard to kill. One by one, his blood-lashing sword curdles in the guards skin puncturing it. Then he finally kills the guard. &quot;Another success by Bong Boy&quot; he shouts. Walking down, he finds the back. Then, he meets somebody selling a addy dagger. &quot;Ill buy&quot; he says with triumph. Walking up to the man, he opens the trade screen. Up goes the dagger, and up goes 800gp. &quot;Boy, this is a deal&quot; He says happily. Huh? The dagger changed color. As the boy puts his cursor on it, it is now iron. Currently, IRL, he screams, slamming his keyboard on the desk like the Angry German Kid (AGK) some of you might have seen on youtube. Putting his keyboard in position, he exits the bank. Now, as he is walking, he finds a castle he&#39;s never been to before. &quot;Wow, another thing to hopefully NOT be a scam lol&quot; He says chuckling. Up he goes and yet, he finds another pathway. &quot;My lucky day&quot; he says.


@#-Chapter 2
Up he goes, and finds a pathway. Up he goes and a sign pops up in front of him. IRL, he jumps so high, he banged his head against the ceiling. He takes the risk, and walks 2 steps. Then, as he looks ahead, he can see many, many, MANY people fighting for their lives. &quot;Cool!&quot; he says walking in. So, he sees someone attacking him. Like that guard on chapter 1, he basically whacks him with his Adamant Longsword. The swords lashing through that enemy&#39;s skull (and the skull above his skull) made that stupid little ranger run like hell. &quot;COOL!&quot; he says, mixing chuckling with happiness. Next, he finds someone with full rune. Carrying a Rune Scimitar. He doesn&#39;t look happy.


TUNE IN FOR MORE OF THIS STORY!
[br][size=1]Posted on: August 30, 2007, 10:36:56 AM[/size][hr]RESERVED[br][size=1]Posted on: August 30, 2007, 10:37:50 AM[/size][hr]RESERVED[br][size=1]Posted on: August 30, 2007, 10:38:49 AM[/size][hr]RESERVED</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 31 Aug 2007 12:24:55 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>General Discussion</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-warrior/138600.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>The Warrior</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@goatee goatee]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/goatee">@goatee</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Whats the point of reserving? It just merges with your post. Ummm also you try to describe the fights too much and it sounds a bit wierd. Anjd at the end of chapter to i read “mixing chuckling with happiness” Do you chuckle when your said. It should just be chuckling happily tbh.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-warrior/138600/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-warrior/138600/2</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 31 Aug 2007 12:24:55 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-138600-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-warrior/138600.rss">The Warrior</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The Warrior</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@VB6_FTW VB6 FTW]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/vb6_ftw">@VB6_FTW</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>The Warrior<br>
~VB6 FTW~<br>
Genre: Science/Fiction</p>
<p>@<span class="hashtag">#-Chapter</span> 1<br>
Runescape. The game filled with daggers, magic and ownage. This story will tell you how 1 boy turned into a sucess. The boy, which screenname is Bong Boy, is walking down the street. Then he finds a guard to kill. One by one, his blood-lashing sword curdles in the guards skin puncturing it. Then he finally kills the guard. “Another success by Bong Boy” he shouts. Walking down, he finds the back. Then, he meets somebody selling a addy dagger. “Ill buy” he says with triumph. Walking up to the man, he opens the trade screen. Up goes the dagger, and up goes 800gp. “Boy, this is a deal” He says happily. Huh? The dagger changed color. As the boy puts his cursor on it, it is now iron. Currently, IRL, he screams, slamming his keyboard on the desk like the Angry German Kid (AGK) some of you might have seen on youtube. Putting his keyboard in position, he exits the bank. Now, as he is walking, he finds a castle he’s never been to before. “Wow, another thing to hopefully NOT be a scam lol” He says chuckling. Up he goes and yet, he finds another pathway. “My lucky day” he says.</p>
<p>@<span class="hashtag">#-Chapter</span> 2<br>
Up he goes, and finds a pathway. Up he goes and a sign pops up in front of him. IRL, he jumps so high, he banged his head against the ceiling. He takes the risk, and walks 2 steps. Then, as he looks ahead, he can see many, many, MANY people fighting for their lives. “Cool!” he says walking in. So, he sees someone attacking him. Like that guard on chapter 1, he basically whacks him with his Adamant Longsword. The swords lashing through that enemy’s skull (and the skull above his skull) made that stupid little ranger run like hell. “COOL!” he says, mixing chuckling with happiness. Next, he finds someone with full rune. Carrying a Rune Scimitar. He doesn’t look happy.</p>
<p>TUNE IN FOR MORE OF THIS STORY!<br>
[br][size=1]Posted on: August 30, 2007, 10:36:56 AM[/size][hr]RESERVED[br][size=1]Posted on: August 30, 2007, 10:37:50 AM[/size][hr]RESERVED[br][size=1]Posted on: August 30, 2007, 10:38:49 AM[/size][hr]RESERVED</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-warrior/138600/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-warrior/138600/1</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 30 Aug 2007 21:39:25 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-138600-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-warrior/138600.rss">The Warrior</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
