<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Myers-Briggs Personality Types?</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/myers-briggs-personality-types/405487</link>
    <description>What is your Myers-Briggs personality type?

I&#39;m curious as to what this community is made up of. If you don&#39;t know your personality type, you can take a test [b][url=http://www.humanmetrics.com/cgi-win/jtypes2.asp]HERE[/url][/b] and find out.

I myself am very skeptical on how authentic this science is, but I find it interesting to read about. As for my type, I am an INTJ.

Also, tell me what you think about the Myers-Briggs personality test, and any experiences you have had with it before.


Just as a reference, according to Keirsey there are 4 temperments:

[b][size=10pt]Guardians (ESTJ, ISTJ, ESFJ, ISFJ)
[/size][/b]
[i][b]Guardians (SJs) [/b][/i]are the cornerstone of society, for they are the temperament given to serving and preserving our most important social institutions. Guardians have natural talent in managing goods and services--from supervision to maintenance and supply -- and they use all their skills to keep things running smoothly in their families, communities, schools, churches, hospitals, and businesses.

All Guardians share the following core characteristics:


[ul][li]Guardians pride themselves on being dependable, helpful, and hard-working.[/li]
[li]Guardians make loyal mates, responsible parents, and stabilizing leaders.[/li]
[li]Guardians tend to be dutiful, cautious, humble, and focused on credentials and traditions.[/li]
[li]Guardians are concerned citizens who trust authority, join groups, seek security, prize gratitude, and dream of meting out justice.[/li][/ul]


[b][size=10pt]Artisans (ISFP, ESFP, ISTP, ESTP)[/size][/b]

[i][b]Artisans[/b][/i] are the temperament with a natural ability to excel in any of the arts, not only the fine arts such as painting and sculpting, or the performing arts such as music, theater, and dance, but also the athletic, military, political, mechanical, and industrial arts, as well as the &quot;art of the deal&quot; in business.

All Artisans share the following core characteristics:

[ul][li]
Artisans tend to be fun-loving, optimistic, realistic, and focused on the here and now.[/li]

[li]Artisans pride themselves on being unconventional, bold, and spontaneous.[/li]

[li]Artisans make playful mates, creative parents, and troubleshooting leaders.[/li]

[li]Artisans are excitable, trust their impulses, want to make a splash, seek stimulation, prize freedom, and dream of mastering action skills.[/li][/ul]

[size=10pt]
[b]Idealists (ENFJ, INFJ, ENFP, INFP)[/b][/size]

[i][b]Idealists (NFs)[/b][/i], as a temperament, are passionately concerned with personal growth and development. Idealists strive to discover who they are and how they can become their best possible self -- always this quest for self-knowledge and self-improvement drives their imagination. And they want to help others make the journey. Idealists are naturally drawn to working with people, and whether in education or counseling, in social services or personnel work, in journalism or the ministry, they are gifted at helping others find their way in life, often inspiring them to grow as individuals and to fulfill their potentials.

All Idealists share the following core characteristics:


[ul][li]Idealists are enthusiastic, they trust their intuition, yearn for romance, seek their true self, prize meaningful relationships, and dream of attaining wisdom.[/li]
[li]Idealists pride themselves on being loving, kindhearted, and authentic.[/li]
[li]Idealists tend to be giving, trusting, spiritual, and they are focused on personal journeys and human potentials.[/li]
[li]Idealists make intense mates, nurturing parents, and inspirational leaders.[/li][/ul]


[b][size=10pt]Rationals (ENTP, ENTJ, INTP, INTJ)[/size][/b]

[b][i]Rationals (NTs)[/i][/b] are the problem solving temperament, particularly if the problem has to do with the many complex systems that make up the world around us. Rationals might tackle problems in organic systems such as plants and animals, or in mechanical systems such as railroads and computers, or in social systems such as families and companies and governments. But whatever systems fire their curiosity, Rationals will analyze them to understand how they work, so they can figure out how to make them work better.

All Rationals share the following core characteristics:


[ul][li]Rationals tend to be pragmatic, skeptical, self-contained, and focused on problem-solving and systems analysis.[/li]
[li]Rationals pride themselves on being ingenious, independent, and strong willed.[/li]
[li]Rationals make reasonable mates, individualizing parents, and strategic leaders.[/li]
[li]Rationals are even-tempered, they trust logic, yearn for achievement, seek knowledge, prize technology, and dream of understanding how the world works.[/li][/ul]




Be sure to check out the profile of your type, check it out here [select your type on the right]:

http://www.keirsey.com/4temps/overview_temperaments.asp</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 27 Jul 2011 00:26:11 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>General Discussion</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/myers-briggs-personality-types/405487.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Myers-Briggs Personality Types?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Squirt_Ltd Squirt Ltd]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/squirt_ltd">@Squirt_Ltd</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>You are:<br>
moderately expressed extravert<br>
slightly expressed intuitive personality<br>
moderately expressed feeling personality<br>
slightly expressed perceiving personality</p>
<p>Famous people of your particular type<br>
Mark Twain, Bill Cosby, Oprah Winfrey, Betty Friedan</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/myers-briggs-personality-types/405487/32">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/myers-briggs-personality-types/405487/32</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 27 Jul 2011 00:26:11 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-405487-32</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/myers-briggs-personality-types/405487.rss">Myers-Briggs Personality Types?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Myers-Briggs Personality Types?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@the_wanderer The Wanderer]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/the_wanderer">@the_wanderer</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote quote-modified" data-post="1" data-topic="406554">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
</div>
<blockquote>
<p>I find it odd that (as of right now) INTJ takes up 38% of this community however it is only seen in 2% of the population…</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I found that odd too.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/myers-briggs-personality-types/405487/31">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/myers-briggs-personality-types/405487/31</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 26 Jul 2011 23:01:50 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-405487-31</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/myers-briggs-personality-types/405487.rss">Myers-Briggs Personality Types?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Myers-Briggs Personality Types?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Mack_n_cheese Mack n cheese]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/mack_n_cheese">@Mack_n_cheese</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>tl;dr</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/myers-briggs-personality-types/405487/30">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/myers-briggs-personality-types/405487/30</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 26 Jul 2011 22:34:29 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-405487-30</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/myers-briggs-personality-types/405487.rss">Myers-Briggs Personality Types?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Myers-Briggs Personality Types?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@the_wanderer The Wanderer]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/the_wanderer">@the_wanderer</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote" data-post="15" data-topic="405487">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 T4_:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>INTJ.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Your Type is<br>
INTJ<br>
Introverted	Intuitive	Thinking	Judging<br>
Strength of the preferences %<br>
67	75	75	33</p>
<p>You are:<br>
distinctively expressed introvert<br>
distinctively expressed intuitive personality<br>
distinctively expressed thinking personality<br>
moderately expressed judging personality</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/myers-briggs-personality-types/405487/29">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/myers-briggs-personality-types/405487/29</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 26 Jul 2011 22:05:08 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-405487-29</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/myers-briggs-personality-types/405487.rss">Myers-Briggs Personality Types?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Myers-Briggs Personality Types?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Eh_Pretty_Easy Eh Pretty Easy]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/eh_pretty_easy">@Eh_Pretty_Easy</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>The psychological basis for this test is quite loose, it relies heavily on generalised traits of the human character - things which people already know, or at least should know about themselves - and it doesn’t really provide the individual with what it should, an objective look at one’s personality.</p>
<blockquote>There are six billion people on earth. All of their psychological states, tendencies, and personalities are so vastly different, which means that there are six billion kinds of psychological states, tendencies, and personalities. All humans are unique.  In truth, that is just six billion ways of expressing a person. Humans are all the same.</blockquote> 
A quote I like.
<p>EDIT: Just did the test, mine is ESTJ.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/myers-briggs-personality-types/405487/28">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/myers-briggs-personality-types/405487/28</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 25 Jul 2011 20:40:50 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-405487-28</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/myers-briggs-personality-types/405487.rss">Myers-Briggs Personality Types?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Myers-Briggs Personality Types?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Svitkona Svitkona]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/svitkona">@Svitkona</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>yeah kind of</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/myers-briggs-personality-types/405487/27">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/myers-briggs-personality-types/405487/27</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jul 2011 23:50:19 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-405487-27</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/myers-briggs-personality-types/405487.rss">Myers-Briggs Personality Types?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Myers-Briggs Personality Types?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@jc22493 Jc22493]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/jc22493">@jc22493</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>So you’re basically saying that Jung was wrong in attempting to ‘categorize’ human beings into x amount of categories?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/myers-briggs-personality-types/405487/26">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/myers-briggs-personality-types/405487/26</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jul 2011 23:36:50 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-405487-26</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/myers-briggs-personality-types/405487.rss">Myers-Briggs Personality Types?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Myers-Briggs Personality Types?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Svitkona Svitkona]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/svitkona">@Svitkona</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Ah, that’s much better. Let me take this one by one:</p>
<p>First paragraph says how an INTJ projects an aura of definiteness which can be perceived as arrogance. Imo. however, I like to keep all attention away from me, and therefore like to look like I don’t know what I’m talking about while actually laughing inwardly at those who think they do. However, if someone comes to me with help on a problem, I definitely will tell them if I can solve it or not - though if I can’t solve it, I’ll attempt to find a way for them and say so as well.</p>
<p>Next it says an INTJ is a perfectionist. That is accurate for the most part. No comments there. However one thing I did notice was how an INTJ apparently has little regard to authority if it comes to something they are working on. That is not exactly true in my case. I like to make sure a decision is ok with the group, but once it is going I don’t like to stop working on that.</p>
<p>Finally it talks about personal relations. I personally have no time for personal relations. I’ve never seen the value in talking to someone who only ends up using me for something then abandoning me later. I am not a complete social dunce however (or that’s what I like to think at any rate! Whether that is true or not is up to the people I am actually friends with!). I like to say I have a good ability to read people and treat them accordingly. So that part was not extremely accurate.</p>
<p>I still stand by my argument. You can’t categorize a human being. So you see, even though it can get the broad idea correct (yes I admit that it did that :p) it can never get the intricate details because every human is defined by the experiences he has lied through in life, and those experiences are different for every one of us.</p>
<p>Also I looked at the famous INTJ people and look who I found:</p>
<blockquote>Gandalf the Grey (J. R. R. Tolkein's Middle Earth books)</blockquote>
guys I am going to be a vvizard :3
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/myers-briggs-personality-types/405487/25">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/myers-briggs-personality-types/405487/25</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jul 2011 22:26:04 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-405487-25</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/myers-briggs-personality-types/405487.rss">Myers-Briggs Personality Types?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Myers-Briggs Personality Types?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@meiscooldude meiscooldude]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/meiscooldude">@meiscooldude</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>ytuio9, have a look here: <a href="http://typelogic.com/intj.html" rel="nofollow noopener">http://typelogic.com/intj.html</a></p>
<p>Does that describe you in the slightest?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/myers-briggs-personality-types/405487/24">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/myers-briggs-personality-types/405487/24</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jul 2011 22:12:16 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-405487-24</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/myers-briggs-personality-types/405487.rss">Myers-Briggs Personality Types?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Myers-Briggs Personality Types?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Svitkona Svitkona]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/svitkona">@Svitkona</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <blockquote>The original developers of the personality inventory were Katharine Cook Briggs and her daughter, Isabel Briggs Myers. They began creating the indicator during World War II, believing that a knowledge of personality preferences would [b]help women who were entering the industrial workforce for the first time to identify the sort of war-time jobs[/b] where they would be "most comfortable and effective"</blockquote>
Also iirc they were talking about people measuring their own success rate.
@JC: Maybe I'm just critical because somehow their results always turn out inaccurate for me. At best, they portray one part of whatever the test was supposed to predict. They're never completely accurate though.
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/myers-briggs-personality-types/405487/23">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/myers-briggs-personality-types/405487/23</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jul 2011 22:11:03 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-405487-23</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/myers-briggs-personality-types/405487.rss">Myers-Briggs Personality Types?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Myers-Briggs Personality Types?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@xxxtilllyxxx xxxtilllyxxx]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/xxxtilllyxxx">@xxxtilllyxxx</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>ENFJ</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/myers-briggs-personality-types/405487/22">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/myers-briggs-personality-types/405487/22</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jul 2011 22:08:48 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-405487-22</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/myers-briggs-personality-types/405487.rss">Myers-Briggs Personality Types?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Myers-Briggs Personality Types?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@meiscooldude meiscooldude]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/meiscooldude">@meiscooldude</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“ytuio9, post:19, topic:405487”][quote]<br>
he use of the Myers-Briggs Type Indicator as a predictor of job success has not been supported in studies,[15][16] and its use for this purpose is expressly discouraged in the Manual.<br>
[/quote]<br>
In other words, it failed at doing what the original inventors wanted it to do.[/quote]</p>
<p>Actually, the Myers-Briggs test was based off of Carl Jung’s research in Analytical Psychology. [Carl Jung was greatly influence by sigmund freud who was a very famous nurologist, who invented phycoanalysis]. The Myers-Briggs test wasn’t developed as a predictor of job success, and is actually discouraged in the Myers-Briggs moral use section of their original publication.</p>
<p>A quote:</p>
<p>“Whether people first hear about the two kinds of perception and two kinds of judgment as children, high school students, parents or grandparents, the richer development of their own type can be a rewarding adventure for the rest of their lives.”</p>
<p>–Isabel Myers</p>
<p>The point of this was to be able to tell people how to improve themselves and lead a more fulfilling life. Not to give companies a ‘possible success meter’ on interviewees.</p>
<p>In-fact the reason its so discouraged as a success meter for jobs is plain and simple: If a job candidate knows what job they are applying for, and is asked to take this test, he/she can [attempt to] answer questions best suited towards that job.</p>
<p>This is honestly only for personal enrichment.</p>
<p>Also, ytuio9, I think you may have a different understanding of Judging vs. Perceiving than the myers-briggs tests means to convey.</p>
<p>Judging means you use your best judgment in a given situation, not necessarily judge others.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/myers-briggs-personality-types/405487/21">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/myers-briggs-personality-types/405487/21</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jul 2011 22:00:12 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-405487-21</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/myers-briggs-personality-types/405487.rss">Myers-Briggs Personality Types?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Myers-Briggs Personality Types?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@jc22493 Jc22493]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/jc22493">@jc22493</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>…predictors don’t always succeed. In your case, it failed, because your results were not representative of your personality. However, as you can see, most of the members who took the questionnaire received results that <span class="bbcode-b">were</span> representative of their actual personalities.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/myers-briggs-personality-types/405487/20">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/myers-briggs-personality-types/405487/20</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jul 2011 21:52:27 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-405487-20</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/myers-briggs-personality-types/405487.rss">Myers-Briggs Personality Types?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Myers-Briggs Personality Types?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Svitkona Svitkona]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/svitkona">@Svitkona</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <blockquote>he use of the Myers-Briggs Type Indicator as a predictor of job success has not been supported in studies,[15][16] and its use for this purpose is expressly discouraged in the Manual.</blockquote>
In other words, it failed at doing what the original inventors wanted it to do.
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/myers-briggs-personality-types/405487/19">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/myers-briggs-personality-types/405487/19</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jul 2011 21:44:10 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-405487-19</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/myers-briggs-personality-types/405487.rss">Myers-Briggs Personality Types?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Myers-Briggs Personality Types?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@jc22493 Jc22493]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/jc22493">@jc22493</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p><span class="mention">@ytuio</span>: These tests aren’t exactly bullshit. Please read up on the test itself before making such comments…</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/myers-briggs-personality-types/405487/18">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/myers-briggs-personality-types/405487/18</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jul 2011 21:40:18 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-405487-18</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/myers-briggs-personality-types/405487.rss">Myers-Briggs Personality Types?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Myers-Briggs Personality Types?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Svitkona Svitkona]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/svitkona">@Svitkona</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>A complete load of bull. I am apparently INTJ but the results do not reflect my current personality at all. Also do note that imo, tests such as these yield little results. People cannot just be categorized in a manner of “The Africans are black and usually stick to primal ways”. Every human being is different than the other, and each has their own layer of feelings, experiences and thoughts that create his personality and shape it to what it is. This personality is ever-changing, because as you grow you see more of life and either learn to face it or just run away from it forever. This obviously affects your way of thinking, as well as the experiences you will live through in your life.<br>
/rant</p>
<blockquote>You are:
<pre><code>very expressed introvert
moderately expressed intuitive personality
slightly expressed thinking personality
slightly expressed judging personality&lt;/blockquote&gt;
</code></pre>
<p>“Do you situate yourself near the side of the room in a social gathering?” obviously a yes to this might mean I’m shy but it might also mean I just prefer to keep to myself… This is why I say people can’t just be cataloged in different groups. This reminds me of an article I once read about how the shape of a woman’s breasts affects her personality.</p>
<blockquote>Introverted	Intuitive	Thinking	Judging
Strength of the preferences %
78	50	1	22</blockquote>
I kind of find the first one true but the rest is definitely not accurate. I find myself highly judging even if I keep it to myself most of the times (hence the high introverted score). Also I like to think a lot before doing anything. A lot of things come to me intuitively as well, but this does not mean that I am an expert at everything all of a sudden. Most of the times it's things to do with numbers, words and graphs (basically stuff that can be represented on paper [or computer for the [i]jokers[/i] out there]) that are intuitive to me. I also seem to have a knack for understanding sports and why a player might do better in a given situation than another player. That is all of it, however. Again, this is why I believe these tests can not reflect on your true personality. Perhaps in a star wars movie where they just clone the shit out of anyone who is powerful but not in the real world for certain.</blockquote>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/myers-briggs-personality-types/405487/17">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/myers-briggs-personality-types/405487/17</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jul 2011 21:32:22 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-405487-17</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/myers-briggs-personality-types/405487.rss">Myers-Briggs Personality Types?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Myers-Briggs Personality Types?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@John459 John459]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/john459">@John459</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote" data-post="15" data-topic="405487">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 T4_:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>INTJ.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/myers-briggs-personality-types/405487/16">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/myers-briggs-personality-types/405487/16</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jul 2011 21:14:27 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-405487-16</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/myers-briggs-personality-types/405487.rss">Myers-Briggs Personality Types?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Myers-Briggs Personality Types?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@T41 t4]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/t41">@T41</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>INTJ.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/myers-briggs-personality-types/405487/15">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/myers-briggs-personality-types/405487/15</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jul 2011 21:09:15 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-405487-15</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/myers-briggs-personality-types/405487.rss">Myers-Briggs Personality Types?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Myers-Briggs Personality Types?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@meiscooldude meiscooldude]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/meiscooldude">@meiscooldude</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Really, you guys should read into more about the personality type you are.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/myers-briggs-personality-types/405487/14">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/myers-briggs-personality-types/405487/14</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jul 2011 21:04:35 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-405487-14</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/myers-briggs-personality-types/405487.rss">Myers-Briggs Personality Types?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Myers-Briggs Personality Types?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@reyx7 reyx7]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/reyx7">@reyx7</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <blockquote>Rationals tend to be pragmatic, skeptical, self-contained, and focused on problem-solving and systems analysis.</blockquote>
<p>Never mind then, mine was pretty accurate.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/myers-briggs-personality-types/405487/13">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/myers-briggs-personality-types/405487/13</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jul 2011 19:59:49 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-405487-13</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/myers-briggs-personality-types/405487.rss">Myers-Briggs Personality Types?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Myers-Briggs Personality Types?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Ix_Soulcist_xI Soulcist]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/ix_soulcist_xi">@Ix_Soulcist_xI</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>That is nice to know.<br>
ESFJ</p>
<p>[QUOTE]You are:<br>
slightly expressed extravert<br>
moderately expressed sensing personality<br>
moderately expressed feeling personality<br>
slightly expressed judging personality[/QUOTE]</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/myers-briggs-personality-types/405487/12">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/myers-briggs-personality-types/405487/12</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jul 2011 19:47:40 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-405487-12</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/myers-briggs-personality-types/405487.rss">Myers-Briggs Personality Types?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Myers-Briggs Personality Types?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@jc22493 Jc22493]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/jc22493">@jc22493</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Took one of these tests (not online) a while ago; forgot what my results were though.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/myers-briggs-personality-types/405487/11">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/myers-briggs-personality-types/405487/11</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jul 2011 19:44:15 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-405487-11</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/myers-briggs-personality-types/405487.rss">Myers-Briggs Personality Types?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Myers-Briggs Personality Types?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@meiscooldude meiscooldude]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/meiscooldude">@meiscooldude</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I’m actually curious as to how many of each type is on this forum. Right now its a decent amount of Rationals [which makes sense, being as the topics on this forum]</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/myers-briggs-personality-types/405487/10">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/myers-briggs-personality-types/405487/10</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jul 2011 19:39:42 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-405487-10</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/myers-briggs-personality-types/405487.rss">Myers-Briggs Personality Types?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Myers-Briggs Personality Types?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@IlikeArrays IlikeArrays]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/ilikearrays">@IlikeArrays</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>72 questions… meh</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/myers-briggs-personality-types/405487/9">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/myers-briggs-personality-types/405487/9</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jul 2011 19:07:16 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-405487-9</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/myers-briggs-personality-types/405487.rss">Myers-Briggs Personality Types?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Myers-Briggs Personality Types?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@reyx7 reyx7]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/reyx7">@reyx7</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“n10si t, post:7, topic:405487”]INFJ</p>
<aside class="quote">
<blockquote>
<p>You are:</p>
<pre><code>slightly expressed introvert
moderately expressed intuitive personality
moderately expressed feeling personality
moderately expressed judging personality
</code></pre>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Famous people like me: <span class="bbcode-b">Nelson Mandela</span>[/quote]</p>
<p>Oh nice.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/myers-briggs-personality-types/405487/8">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/myers-briggs-personality-types/405487/8</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jul 2011 18:34:47 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-405487-8</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/myers-briggs-personality-types/405487.rss">Myers-Briggs Personality Types?</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
