<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Connecting to update server</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/connecting-to-update-server/376985</link>
    <description>Hey.
My 508 client, seems to be... retarded, to be frank. I have added the cache to my C: drive, so that&#39;s not the problem. Also, my Runserver batch file is showing that it is accepting connections from 127.0.0.1 (which is to say, me...)
Despite this, my client won&#39;t move past the &#39;connecting to update server&#39;.
I&#39;m stumped; I&#39;ve tried multiple different caches, I&#39;ve got about four different 508 caches just due to my failed attempts to fix it...

If it isn&#39;t the cache&#39;s fault, it must be the mine, or the client&#39;s... right?

Halp? :D

Edit: OH, by the way, I forgot to mention that my client is suffering from the js5connect error, which surely makes no sense? After all, my server IS accepting my connections, according to the runserver batch... The only other thing on the client&#39;s run batch file is &#39;Loaded 10 custom sprites&#39;...

I&#39;m pretty sure i&#39;m missing the obvious here. I swear, i&#39;m gonna stab something if I&#39;ve just forgotten to but a bracket somewhere...</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 05 Jan 2011 16:53:52 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Game Development</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/connecting-to-update-server/376985.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Connecting to update server</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Retard_Monkey Retard Monkey]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/retard_monkey">@Retard_Monkey</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Hey.<br>
My 508 client, seems to be… retarded, to be frank. I have added the cache to my C: drive, so that’s not the problem. Also, my Runserver batch file is showing that it is accepting connections from 127.0.0.1 (which is to say, me…)<br>
Despite this, my client won’t move past the ‘connecting to update server’.<br>
I’m stumped; I’ve tried multiple different caches, I’ve got about four different 508 caches just due to my failed attempts to fix it…</p>
<p>If it isn’t the cache’s fault, it must be the mine, or the client’s… right?</p>
<p>Halp? <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/smiley.png?v=5" title=":smiley:" class="emoji" alt=":smiley:"></p>
<p>Edit: OH, by the way, I forgot to mention that my client is suffering from the js5connect error, which surely makes no sense? After all, my server IS accepting my connections, according to the runserver batch… The only other thing on the client’s run batch file is ‘Loaded 10 custom sprites’…</p>
<p>I’m pretty sure i’m missing the obvious here. I swear, i’m gonna stab something if I’ve just forgotten to but a bracket somewhere…</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/connecting-to-update-server/376985/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/connecting-to-update-server/376985/1</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 05 Jan 2011 16:53:52 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-376985-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/connecting-to-update-server/376985.rss">Connecting to update server</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
