<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Need Some Help Deciding On A Server/Client</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/need-some-help-deciding-on-a-server-client/287844</link>
    <description>Okay,
  Thanks to the help from alot of you I FINALLY got the port forward and I can host servers 24/7/365 and welcome other people to come play on them. Thanks everyone I really appreciate it. There IS one last thing though, HaHa, there always is ;) Okay I need your help deciding on a server to host keep in mind I am a total newbie. When I think about it, I want it to be realistic like RuneScape, Kinda Simple For A Newbie, I have a buddy who&#39;s a coder so a little challenge won&#39;t hurt. Basically, I wanna be able to give mod, admin, and owner/co-owner rights to people, but I don&#39;t want everyone in the game to be using Item ID&#39;s to rezz things for themselves, Nuh-Uh, just the administration and staff. So, I need a Server/Client if you guys have any recommendations or &quot;any for-sure&quot; choices throw them down at the bottom, appreciate all the help!

               Thanks,
                   :cool: Captain :cool:</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 09 Jul 2009 08:54:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/need-some-help-deciding-on-a-server-client/287844.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Need Some Help Deciding On A Server/Client</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@CaptainNegatory CaptainNegatory]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/captainnegatory">@CaptainNegatory</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Okay,<br>
Thanks to the help from alot of you I FINALLY got the port forward and I can host servers 24/7/365 and welcome other people to come play on them. Thanks everyone I really appreciate it. There IS one last thing though, HaHa, there always is <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/wink.png?v=5" title=":wink:" class="emoji" alt=":wink:"> Okay I need your help deciding on a server to host keep in mind I am a total newbie. When I think about it, I want it to be realistic like RuneScape, Kinda Simple For A Newbie, I have a buddy who’s a coder so a little challenge won’t hurt. Basically, I wanna be able to give mod, admin, and owner/co-owner rights to people, but I don’t want everyone in the game to be using Item ID’s to rezz things for themselves, Nuh-Uh, just the administration and staff. So, I need a Server/Client if you guys have any recommendations or “any for-sure” choices throw them down at the bottom, appreciate all the help!</p>
<pre><code>           Thanks,
               :cool: Captain :cool:</code></pre>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/need-some-help-deciding-on-a-server-client/287844/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/need-some-help-deciding-on-a-server-client/287844/1</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 09 Jul 2009 08:54:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-287844-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/need-some-help-deciding-on-a-server-client/287844.rss">Need Some Help Deciding On A Server/Client</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
