<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Possible scar bug?</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/possible-scar-bug/3523</link>
    <description>Ok in the picture bellow i have 2 functions. Straight forward enough really. The top one is called &quot;TryFinish()&quot; and the bottom one is called &quot;TryUpgrade&quot; If you look at my large comment in the function TryUpgrade() you&#39;l see that i&#39;m starting a while loop which wont EVER finish until the procedure aboce TryFinish returns TRUE. This should go on and on forever. 

What hapens is that Upgrade(); clicks on a link that says &quot;upgrade&quot; and then i have to wait so many minutes until the upgrade finishes and the text &quot;continue&quot; appears which i then need to click on. It keeps checkings the screen for the text &quot;complete&quot; and it will only return true when its found, has been clicked on and then displays the message &quot;Completed Upgrade&quot;. If it doesn&#39;t find it then it displays &quot;Not Complete Yet, Tries 1/2/3/4/5....&quot; for however many times its tried it. 

If you look down at the bottom in the debug box everything is going fine for a while. It Sucessfully clicks the upgrade button and enters the loop to find the &quot;continue&quot; text. Then the script seems To MAGICALY FINISH!!!! This is impossible! It HAS to display the message &quot;Completed Upgrade&quot; if its going to exit that loop because it has to be true to exit. Even if it somehow manages to fuck up and find the text in the wrong place it should still display this anyway so thats not the problem.

In the TryUpgrade procedure just after the while loop thats being a bitch i have it say &quot;Managed To Click Finish Apparently&quot; Now the fact that it doesnt even print that out is PROOF that the script is just deciding to finish in the middle of my while loop. I don&#39;t have a fucking clue whats going and need some help. Could this be a glitch in Scar or have i been a complete twat and missed out something really obvious? Ths is NOT a syntax error or a case of missing brackers because the code DOES work. I have tested each function individually and have had it work several times. Its being a dick and decides that somtimes it just won&#39;t even bother finishing the script and kills itself.

If anybody can give me answer to this i&#39;d be really really thankfull... You might have to save the picture and zoom in a bit to see the text beter.

[IMG]http://i3.photobucket.com/albums/y55/mush666/omfggay.jpg[/img]</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 02 Jun 2006 23:56:27 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/possible-scar-bug/3523.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Possible scar bug?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Chrisface Chrisface]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/chrisface">@Chrisface</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I asked mopar and he said that the wait() procedure sometimes crashes the script when using mathematical operators as a value in the function. Thats pretty annoying and im suprised it messes up over something like that. Beware using waits in the future!</p>
<p>Never do this wait(5*1000);</p>
<p>Do this! wait(5000);</p>
<p>Apparently it just doesnt feel like working some of the time if you do it the first way lol.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/possible-scar-bug/3523/7">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/possible-scar-bug/3523/7</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jun 2006 23:56:27 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-3523-7</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/possible-scar-bug/3523.rss">Possible scar bug?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Possible scar bug?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@doomsday doomsday]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/doomsday">@doomsday</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>so then set the wait for lower try 10 seconds…</p>
<p>or better yet, try what i said <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/smiley.png?v=9" title=":smiley:" class="emoji" alt=":smiley:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/possible-scar-bug/3523/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/possible-scar-bug/3523/6</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jun 2006 23:40:58 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-3523-6</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/possible-scar-bug/3523.rss">Possible scar bug?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Possible scar bug?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Chrisface Chrisface]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/chrisface">@Chrisface</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote no-group" data-post="4" data-topic="3523">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/traitors/40/5_8504b32b4165840149d2c3dd52eb0686.png" class="avatar"> traitors:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>omg OGAME BREED!</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>OMGZ! that was it! thanks you just fixed my problem!</p>
<p>But seriously, i managed to track this down to the wait() procedure. I stepped through the program line by line and on the 47th!!! attempt when it went over the wait() procedure the script ended. I can tell its not the function im calling because i had it display a message at the start which it never did. I can tell its not from the previous loop because it displays a message at the end of it. Also i did WATCH it terminate my script when it did the pause.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/possible-scar-bug/3523/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/possible-scar-bug/3523/5</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jun 2006 17:21:29 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-3523-5</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/possible-scar-bug/3523.rss">Possible scar bug?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Possible scar bug?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@traitors traitors]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/traitors">@traitors</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>omg OGAME BREED!</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/possible-scar-bug/3523/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/possible-scar-bug/3523/4</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jun 2006 10:39:43 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-3523-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/possible-scar-bug/3523.rss">Possible scar bug?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Possible scar bug?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Chrisface Chrisface]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/chrisface">@Chrisface</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Nope thats definitly not it. Im pretty you can’t have a while AND an until in the same loop anyway because it could mean two conflicting terminating states. It’s just the same term anyway so i could use either one or the other but not both.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/possible-scar-bug/3523/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/possible-scar-bug/3523/3</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jun 2006 07:05:11 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-3523-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/possible-scar-bug/3523.rss">Possible scar bug?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Possible scar bug?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@doomsday doomsday]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/doomsday">@doomsday</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>umm yeah try this</p>
<p>while (not tryfinish() ) do<br>
begin<br>
repeat<br>
wait(180<em>1000)+random(30</em>1000)<br>
until(tryfinish()<br>
end;</p>
<p>thats my best bet…</p>
<p>or something close to that lol</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/possible-scar-bug/3523/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/possible-scar-bug/3523/2</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jun 2006 06:43:16 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-3523-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/possible-scar-bug/3523.rss">Possible scar bug?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Possible scar bug?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Chrisface Chrisface]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/chrisface">@Chrisface</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Ok in the picture bellow i have 2 functions. Straight forward enough really. The top one is called “TryFinish()” and the bottom one is called “TryUpgrade” If you look at my large comment in the function TryUpgrade() you’l see that i’m starting a while loop which wont EVER finish until the procedure aboce TryFinish returns TRUE. This should go on and on forever.</p>
<p>What hapens is that Upgrade(); clicks on a link that says “upgrade” and then i have to wait so many minutes until the upgrade finishes and the text “continue” appears which i then need to click on. It keeps checkings the screen for the text “complete” and it will only return true when its found, has been clicked on and then displays the message “Completed Upgrade”. If it doesn’t find it then it displays “Not Complete Yet, Tries 1/2/3/4/5…” for however many times its tried it.</p>
<p>If you look down at the bottom in the debug box everything is going fine for a while. It Sucessfully clicks the upgrade button and enters the loop to find the “continue” text. Then the script seems To MAGICALY FINISH!!! This is impossible! It HAS to display the message “Completed Upgrade” if its going to exit that loop because it has to be true to exit. Even if it somehow manages to fuck up and find the text in the wrong place it should still display this anyway so thats not the problem.</p>
<p>In the TryUpgrade procedure just after the while loop thats being a bitch i have it say “Managed To Click Finish Apparently” Now the fact that it doesnt even print that out is PROOF that the script is just deciding to finish in the middle of my while loop. I don’t have a fucking clue whats going and need some help. Could this be a glitch in Scar or have i been a complete twat and missed out something really obvious? Ths is NOT a syntax error or a case of missing brackers because the code DOES work. I have tested each function individually and have had it work several times. Its being a dick and decides that somtimes it just won’t even bother finishing the script and kills itself.</p>
<p>If anybody can give me answer to this i’d be really really thankfull… You might have to save the picture and zoom in a bit to see the text beter.</p>
<p><img src="http://i3.photobucket.com/albums/y55/mush666/omfggay.jpg" alt width="" height=""></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/possible-scar-bug/3523/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/possible-scar-bug/3523/1</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2006 22:21:42 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-3523-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/possible-scar-bug/3523.rss">Possible scar bug?</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
