<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Okay, uhmm need help with a few things, if u can help that would be great ty</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/okay-uhmm-need-help-with-a-few-things-if-u-can-help-that-would-be-great-ty/219694</link>
    <description>okay uhmmm for onee forgot what i was gunna ask.. OH anyone have a &quot;silab&quot; related server 100% like silabs but like not the silab client from her website.. but like has all silab items and is open source so i can add my own items in there. annnd what was it.. grr i forgot... but ya does anyone have a client like that? if they can post a download link id greatly appreciate it.. but i dont want anotehr one of her client just with the items just like hers and stuff like that but i can add my own.. ty for whoever posts.. if anyone does.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 13 Jul 2008 00:37:09 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/okay-uhmm-need-help-with-a-few-things-if-u-can-help-that-would-be-great-ty/219694.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Okay, uhmm need help with a few things, if u can help that would be great ty</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@BACON555 BACON555]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/bacon555">@BACON555</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>okay uhmmm for onee forgot what i was gunna ask… OH anyone have a “silab” related server 100% like silabs but like not the silab client from her website… but like has all silab items and is open source so i can add my own items in there. annnd what was it… grr i forgot… but ya does anyone have a client like that? if they can post a download link id greatly appreciate it… but i dont want anotehr one of her client just with the items just like hers and stuff like that but i can add my own… ty for whoever posts… if anyone does.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/okay-uhmm-need-help-with-a-few-things-if-u-can-help-that-would-be-great-ty/219694/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/okay-uhmm-need-help-with-a-few-things-if-u-can-help-that-would-be-great-ty/219694/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 13 Jul 2008 00:37:09 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-219694-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/okay-uhmm-need-help-with-a-few-things-if-u-can-help-that-would-be-great-ty/219694.rss">Okay, uhmm need help with a few things, if u can help that would be great ty</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
