<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>My grandma</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-grandma/462593</link>
    <description>Please note, I am not wanting sympathy. This thread is going to be about my grandmother, Linda. So, all I ask of you all is no-flaming/inconsiderate posts. I know how some of you are here, and I respect that. It&#39;s just, this is going to be somewhat of a diary for me, I just want people to hear about what i&#39;m going through, and how hard it is for me to continue my day-to-day life. Hell, maybe some are you are going through what I am, so if you are, don&#39;t be afraid to comment.

Here we go. Well, about 3 years ago I moved to Florida. We began having family problems so my step-dad moved back and my mom, sister, brother, and myself stayed. Two months later, we followed because my step-dad obtained a decent job, but unfortunately it didn&#39;t pay enough to support a family of four. After we moved back, we had to live with my grandmother for about four months, in her 2 bedroom apartment. 

Before I continue any further, I would like to let you all into my past a bit. When I was about 11 years old, my grandma found out she had diabetes. Soon after, she began having heart problems and a hard time breathing. One night she woke up and could hardly breathe. That night she was admitted to the hospital in which she stayed for 3 weeks. Soon after, my sister and I went to visit her over the weekend. On the first day that we visited her, she got real dizzy and collapsed. We had no clue what to do, so we called my mom, and my mom called 9-1-1. Later that day, she was admitted into the hospital and stayed for over a month.

Back to us moving in with her. After a little over four months, my mom and her began arguing over bills and such. See, my grandma can&#39;t work because of her health issues, so she lives off food stamps and social security checks. Anyways, she ended up kicking us out. We had no clue what we were going to do, so my step-dads mom insisted we live with her, until we get back on our feet. Well, she ended up kicking us out for the exact same shit. 

So, my mom won&#39;t let me speak to my grandmother for what she did to us. Which honestly, I didn&#39;t blame her. If we lived with her, rent-free, the least my parents could have done was help her with the light bill and buying food. Everyday I think about my grandmother, and I try persuading my mom into taking me over there to see her. The last time I asked her, she replied with &quot;your nana is nothing but a greedy bitch. She kicked us out and we had nowhere to go. You still want to talk to her after that? I hope she burns in hell&quot; After that, I lost all the respect I had for my mom that I had left. How could you say that about your own mother? It beats me.

Today was the first day I got to see her after that incident. This was only because my sister recently got her intermediate on Wednesday. When I knocked on the door, you could see her face light up. She began crying and hugging me. The words that followed will live with me for the rest of my life. &quot;I thought I was never going to get to see you again&quot;. She sat there and hugged me for a good 15 minutes. My sister and I then stayed for about 30 minutes to catch up, the whole time she was crying. Right before we left, she cried even harder. It broke my heart to leave, but we had a curfew.

After I got home, I attempted to speak with my mom again, regarding my nana. She still replied the same thing, but this time it was more vulgar. &quot;Fuck your Nana, if I found out you&#39;ve been speaking to her, you will never see the light of day again&quot;. I then asked, &quot;so, you wouldn&#39;t even go to her funeral&quot; you can obviously guess what her response was. Now don&#39;t get me wrong, i&#39;m not trying to act like a hard-ass, but after she told me no, I told her straight up. &quot;If I don&#39;t get to go to her funeral, I put it on everyone I loves life, I will never speak or look at you again. You&#39;re an inconsiderate bitch&quot; If she dies before I get to see her again, I will go absolutely ballistic. It will take physical restraint to even get me to remotely calm down. I would rather go to Juvie until i&#39;m 18 than continue living here with my parents.

And that is that. If you took the time to read this entire thread, I want to thank you. If you are having a problem similar to mine, shoot me a PM and we will talk. I know how it feels, it hurts.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 02 Oct 2012 03:16:15 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>General Discussion</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-grandma/462593.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>My grandma</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@sour sour]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/sour">@sour</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote quote-modified" data-post="32" data-topic="462593">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 the elve age:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>I stand corrected. I’m giving you legitimate criticism by telling you to <span class="bbcode-b">grow up</span>, you need to mature more. You’ve argued almost <span class="bbcode-b">every</span> single post which shows no sign of change or sympathy towards others’ posts, then why should we care about yours? The moment you call someone <span class="bbcode-i"><span class="bbcode-b">fucking</span> ignorant</span> shows your true colors. Saying <span class="bbcode-b">no one</span> cares was a bit exaggerated but not far off, from this thread you’ve gotten 2 “supporters”. Have fun flaming back to this post, as you will most likely take this offensively and bitch :). Hope everything goes better.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I don’t believe I argued with anyone but you. If you would read my previous comments, you’d know I don’t get offended to easily. Anyways, finally you gave some criticism. <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/wink.png?v=5" title=":wink:" class="emoji" alt=":wink:"> I misinterpreted you at first I believe. I thought you telling me no one cared and to grow up <span class="bbcode-i">was</span> your criticism, my apologies. Also, i’m not looking for any ‘supporters’, I just needed a place to post this, so why not here? Oh, and I called you <span class="bbcode-i">fucking ignorant</span> because you were stating your opinions as facts. Sorry.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-grandma/462593/33">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-grandma/462593/33</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 02 Oct 2012 03:16:15 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-462593-33</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-grandma/462593.rss">My grandma</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>My grandma</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@the_elve_age the elve age]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/the_elve_age">@the_elve_age</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“the elve age, post:29, topic:462593”]This is what I mean, you take way too much time to respond so you “win” the argument.[/quote]I stand corrected. I’m giving you legitimate criticism by telling you to <span class="bbcode-b">grow up</span>, you need to mature more. You’ve argued almost <span class="bbcode-b">every</span> single post which shows no sign of change or sympathy towards others’ posts, then why should we care about yours? The moment you call someone <span class="bbcode-i"><span class="bbcode-b">fucking</span> ignorant</span> shows your true colors. Saying <span class="bbcode-b">no one</span> cares was a bit exaggerated but not far off, from this thread you’ve gotten 2 “supporters”. Have fun flaming back to this post, as you will most likely take this offensively and bitch :). Hope everything goes better.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-grandma/462593/32">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-grandma/462593/32</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 02 Oct 2012 03:01:14 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-462593-32</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-grandma/462593.rss">My grandma</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>My grandma</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@sour sour]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/sour">@sour</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote quote-modified" data-post="29" data-topic="462593">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 the elve age:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>]his is what I mean, you take way too much time to respond so you “win” the argument. I’m giving you legitimate criticism but you can’t take it, you have to be right in the instance. <span class="bbcode-b">Posting something no one cares about</span>? Go for it.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>For a sectional mod (please excuse my language) you’re pretty fucking ignorant, creating false assumptions and such. Who are you to say <span class="bbcode-b">no one</span> cares? Sure, you may not care and in all honesty, I could care less. Also, how are you giving me ‘legitimate’ criticism when you are attempting to make <span class="bbcode-b">your opinions</span> <span class="bbcode-i">facts</span>? Again, you’re fucking ignorant.</p>
<p>[quote=“Jc22493, post:30, topic:462593”]at least op tries to use correct grammar, though his writing isn’t too fluid.</p>
<p>your retaliation is a form of immaturity imo, i would never disrespect my mother no matter the circumstances. you’d die before your grandmother if it weren’t for your mother, and don’t start with ‘i can take care of myself’. i see your attempt to vent, but this also isn’t the ‘post your problems’ section even though there’s nothing that prevents you from posting this here. i think you just need to mature and literally grow up a bit (not trying to be offensive) as this is something you need to deal with without the aid of ‘internet buddies’ etc.[/quote]<br>
Alright, that’s your opinion. I just wanted a place to write about this, thus I decided to post it here. Some of you may think I’m immature or childish because I will not forgive my mom, and well, that’s something i’m going to have to live with.</p>
<p>Thanks for the criticism.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-grandma/462593/31">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-grandma/462593/31</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 02 Oct 2012 02:39:32 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-462593-31</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-grandma/462593.rss">My grandma</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>My grandma</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@jc22493 Jc22493]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/jc22493">@jc22493</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>at least op tries to use correct grammar, though his writing isn’t too fluid.</p>
<p>your retaliation is a form of immaturity imo, i would never disrespect my mother no matter the circumstances. you’d die before your grandmother if it weren’t for your mother, and don’t start with ‘i can take care of myself’. i see your attempt to vent, but this also isn’t the ‘post your problems’ section even though there’s nothing that prevents you from posting this here. i think you just need to mature and literally grow up a bit (not trying to be offensive) as this is something you need to deal with without the aid of ‘internet buddies’ etc.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-grandma/462593/30">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-grandma/462593/30</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 01 Oct 2012 16:39:13 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-462593-30</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-grandma/462593.rss">My grandma</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>My grandma</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@the_elve_age the elve age]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/the_elve_age">@the_elve_age</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“sour, post:26, topic:462593”][quote author=the elve age link=topic=565774.msg4116203#msg4116203 date=1349059658]<br>
The thing is… Kronikz was being serious… We don’t want to hear this, go get a best friend and tell them, not us. If can’t take any criticism (so far you haven’t) then you still have some growing up to do <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=5" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"><br>
[/quote]<br>
Just because you don’t want to hear it means I can’t post it here? I don’t believe so. I can handle criticism, hence why I haven’t raged, so your argument is rather invalid. Also, I don’t think i’m the one who has growing up to do, I have no clue why you’re assuming this, but it’s whatever. All of this relating back to KroniKz_ comment, he could have written it in a mature manner, such as “We don’t want to hear about this” or something of the sort.</p>
<p>Moving back to the “we don’t want to hear this”, you sir, have some growing up to do. Speak for yourself, not others. Sure, half the people on the forum don’t want to hear about it, but that doesn’t mean <span class="bbcode-b">no one</span> wants to hear. Assuming you used “we” as in the community as a whole.</p>
<p>Thanks for your rather invalid comment. :)[/quote]This is what I mean, you take way too much time to respond so you “win” the argument. I’m giving you legitimate criticism but you can’t take it, you have to be right in the instance. Posting something no one cares about? Go for it.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-grandma/462593/29">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-grandma/462593/29</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 01 Oct 2012 12:05:43 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-462593-29</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-grandma/462593.rss">My grandma</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>My grandma</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Team_Rocket Team_Rocket]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/team_rocket">@Team_Rocket</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Once a person realizes that parents aren’t perfect and make mistakes, they become an adolescent. Once a person forgives them for their mistakes, they become an adult.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-grandma/462593/28">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-grandma/462593/28</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 01 Oct 2012 09:23:45 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-462593-28</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-grandma/462593.rss">My grandma</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>My grandma</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@krackkid Krackkid]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/krackkid">@krackkid</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>oh yeah me how I use to be I am no longer a troll! well…</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-grandma/462593/27">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-grandma/462593/27</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 01 Oct 2012 03:18:51 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-462593-27</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-grandma/462593.rss">My grandma</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>My grandma</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@sour sour]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/sour">@sour</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote quote-modified" data-post="25" data-topic="462593">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 the elve age:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>The thing is… Kronikz was being serious… We don’t want to hear this, go get a best friend and tell them, not us. If can’t take any criticism (so far you haven’t) then you still have some growing up to do <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=5" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Just because you don’t want to hear it means I can’t post it here? I don’t believe so. I can handle criticism, hence why I haven’t raged, so your argument is rather invalid. Also, I don’t think i’m the one who has growing up to do, I have no clue why you’re assuming this, but it’s whatever. All of this relating back to KroniKz_ comment, he could have written it in a mature manner, such as “We don’t want to hear about this” or something of the sort.</p>
<p>Moving back to the “we don’t want to hear this”, you sir, have some growing up to do. Speak for yourself, not others. Sure, half the people on the forum don’t want to hear about it, but that doesn’t mean <span class="bbcode-b">no one</span> wants to hear. Assuming you used “we” as in the community as a whole.</p>
<p>Thanks for your rather invalid comment. <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=5" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-grandma/462593/26">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-grandma/462593/26</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 01 Oct 2012 03:16:55 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-462593-26</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-grandma/462593.rss">My grandma</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>My grandma</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@the_elve_age the elve age]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/the_elve_age">@the_elve_age</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>The thing is… Kronikz was being serious… We don’t want to hear this, go get a best friend and tell them, not us. If can’t take any criticism (so far you haven’t) then you still have some growing up to do <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=5" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-grandma/462593/25">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-grandma/462593/25</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 01 Oct 2012 02:47:38 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-462593-25</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-grandma/462593.rss">My grandma</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>My grandma</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@sour sour]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/sour">@sour</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote quote-modified" data-post="22" data-topic="462593">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/krackkid/40/5_e05bb34c421432ee4d40de30c10af3e5.png" class="avatar"> Krackkid:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Just what I said is actually true…So if he is being like me he isn’t doing a very good job.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I wasn’t referring to what we spoke about last night, but you in general. Sure, you can be serious at times, but over half the time, you’re just funny as fuck. That’s exactly what I was referring to… you being you, when you’re not serious. He’s attempting to become a troll, but is failing miserably. Maybe you should give him a few pointers, eh? <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/wink.png?v=5" title=":wink:" class="emoji" alt=":wink:"></p>
<p>Casey., I’m not 12, but thanks for the comment! Yours was more funny than KroniKz. You and Krackkid are a lot alike, more then you all may think. <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/wink.png?v=5" title=":wink:" class="emoji" alt=":wink:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-grandma/462593/24">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-grandma/462593/24</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 01 Oct 2012 02:40:48 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-462593-24</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-grandma/462593.rss">My grandma</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>My grandma</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@gothic_queen casey.]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/gothic_queen">@gothic_queen</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>breaking news: another 12 year old comes seeking attention for some sob story</p>
<p>in other news: <span class="hashtag">#care</span></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-grandma/462593/23">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-grandma/462593/23</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 01 Oct 2012 02:39:10 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-462593-23</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-grandma/462593.rss">My grandma</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>My grandma</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@krackkid Krackkid]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/krackkid">@krackkid</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Just what I said is actually true…So if he is being like me he isn’t doing a very good job.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-grandma/462593/22">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-grandma/462593/22</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 01 Oct 2012 02:36:29 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-462593-22</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-grandma/462593.rss">My grandma</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>My grandma</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@sour sour]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/sour">@sour</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote" data-post="20" data-topic="462593">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 KroniKz_:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Yo we are not therapists, none of us want to hear your life story, if you are looking for help see a therapist. Not trollapist.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Aww, what a cute attempt at a troll :). Also, before you even think about commenting, you must think before doing so. First of all, this isn’t my life story, this is about my grandmother. Second of all, ‘not trollapist’ makes no sense. I think you mean “Not a trollapist” or “Not Trollapist<span class="bbcode-b">s</span>” Moving on. Did I once insinuate you all were therapists, if so, would you be as kind to point me toward the particular comment that this insinuation was mentioned in? I’d be so grateful!</p>
<p>Alright, moving on, again. You are obviously trying to ‘impress’ everyone who reads this thread in the future. You’re attempting to be humorous, which in reality, you’re not. Well that, or you’re trying to be like Kracky. In whichever case, you fail. So, if you would like to try again, i’m all ears! <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=5" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"> Thanks, babe.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-grandma/462593/21">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-grandma/462593/21</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 01 Oct 2012 02:19:14 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-462593-21</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-grandma/462593.rss">My grandma</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>My grandma</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@kronixz kronikz]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/kronixz">@kronixz</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Yo we are not therapists, none of us want to hear your life story, if you are looking for help see a therapist. Not trollapist.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-grandma/462593/20">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-grandma/462593/20</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 01 Oct 2012 01:33:39 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-462593-20</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-grandma/462593.rss">My grandma</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>My grandma</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Kidpaparoach Kidpaparoach]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/kidpaparoach">@Kidpaparoach</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I read a few paragraphs then decided to read no more of it because of how naive the OP is.<br>
You claim your not attention seeking but you post a ‘diary’ on a forums for people to read. You lost all respect for your mum cause she said mean things because she most likely felt abonded in a time of need.</p>
<p>Of all people you should understand the pain of feeling abandoned by the person you love of course its going to make you angry at them, almost even hate. You put your heart into someone else just for them to stomp on it when you need them most. And that’s where I stopped reading, please correct me if I’m wrong in saying the OP is naive.<br>
But I hope everything works out for you either way.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-grandma/462593/19">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-grandma/462593/19</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 30 Sep 2012 14:22:49 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-462593-19</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-grandma/462593.rss">My grandma</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>My grandma</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@system system]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/system">@system</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Wait. I Dont Get it, if you cant live with your grandma, why not go to your step-dad? Gl with Life (not saying in a bad way)</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-grandma/462593/18">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-grandma/462593/18</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 30 Sep 2012 08:30:46 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-462593-18</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-grandma/462593.rss">My grandma</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>My grandma</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@sour sour]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/sour">@sour</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote quote-modified" data-post="16" data-topic="462593">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/user_avatar/forum.moparisthebest.com/davidi2/40/2579_1.png" class="avatar"> Davidi2:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>This is the longest tl;dr I’ve ever seen!</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>It is quite lengthy, isn’t it? It’s quite hard to right about complications regarding serious family issues in 1-2 sentences. I know this is Mopar and all, but I decided to pour my heart out on this post. Yes, I know, I may sound like a giant ‘pussy’ but I couldn’t care less. If people want to read it and relate it to their life, well then, i’d be more than interested in hearing about it. If they don’t read any of it, well, so be it. It’s hard reading a lengthy post, especially about someone else’s situations. Most people don’t care about people over the internet whatsoever, and I totally respect that. But then again, there are those select few that take interest in others, I have yet to find one, but I know they’re out there <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=5" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"> Anyway, thanks for taking a look at it, I guess.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-grandma/462593/17">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-grandma/462593/17</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 30 Sep 2012 07:35:32 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-462593-17</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-grandma/462593.rss">My grandma</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>My grandma</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@davidi2 Davidi2]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/davidi2">@davidi2</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>This is the longest tl;dr I’ve ever seen!</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-grandma/462593/16">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-grandma/462593/16</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 30 Sep 2012 07:07:59 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-462593-16</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-grandma/462593.rss">My grandma</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>My grandma</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@sour sour]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/sour">@sour</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote" data-post="13" data-topic="462593">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/spades/40/5_e05bb34c421432ee4d40de30c10af3e5.png" class="avatar"> Spades:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Wait 2 years(Guessing you are 16 based on your profile) and go live with your Grandma. Sounds like your Mom never grew up.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>In all honesty, in the state of health she is currently in, she won’t live another year. That’s my problem. Do you think I’ve never told my mom I would move in with her when I was of age? Well, I did, and she told me the exact same thing I just told you. When I say “the state of health she is currently in” I mean, it’s pretty bad. She has to inject herself with insulin because her body doesn’t produce it itself. She barely has enough money to feed herself. I shit you not, when I walked into her apartment she had two boxes of Frosted Flakes on the shelf and left-over spaghetti in the fridge. When I asked her about it, she replied with “Don’t worry about me, i’ll be fine”. What happens if her blood-sugar runs low? I’ll tell you what, either she’ll be admitted into the hospital or she’ll just give up.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-grandma/462593/15">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-grandma/462593/15</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 30 Sep 2012 07:02:40 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-462593-15</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-grandma/462593.rss">My grandma</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>My grandma</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@yoder yoder]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/yoder">@yoder</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote" data-post="13" data-topic="462593">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/spades/40/5_e05bb34c421432ee4d40de30c10af3e5.png" class="avatar"> Spades:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Wait 2 years(Guessing you are 16 based on your profile) and go live with your Grandma. Sounds like your Mom never grew up.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I’m not sure if you read the whole thing or not, but he is not sure if his grandmother has 2 years left.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-grandma/462593/14">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-grandma/462593/14</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 30 Sep 2012 06:59:05 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-462593-14</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-grandma/462593.rss">My grandma</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>My grandma</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Spades Spades]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/spades">@Spades</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Wait 2 years(Guessing you are 16 based on your profile) and go live with your Grandma. Sounds like your Mom never grew up.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-grandma/462593/13">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-grandma/462593/13</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 30 Sep 2012 06:55:30 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-462593-13</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-grandma/462593.rss">My grandma</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>My grandma</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@sour sour]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/sour">@sour</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote" data-post="10" data-topic="462593">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 AtomicInt_:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>counselors suck, especially school ones, if you say one misleading thing, they will go tell your parents.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Exactly. That’s what i’m trying to prevent. So I had no choice left but to turn to the internet. If my parents found out I went to see her, let alone speak to her, I would be in deep shit. My life would be over, and when I say this, i’m not exaggerating one bit. What social life I have now will be terminated, not that I have that many ‘good’ friends, but still. I have no clue how I will end up in the future, or if I even have a future. My grandma is the only one that I care about, aside from my 2 sisters and little brother. I could go to her and tell her anything and would not be judged. Before she answered my question(s) she would put herself in my shoes and answer them that way. However, I can’t talk to her about this problem because she is the problem.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-grandma/462593/12">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-grandma/462593/12</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 30 Sep 2012 06:48:41 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-462593-12</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-grandma/462593.rss">My grandma</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>My grandma</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@krackkid Krackkid]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/krackkid">@krackkid</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Well I kind of know what you mean, my grandma is a hardcore christian and my mom is a lesbian…SO yeah</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-grandma/462593/11">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-grandma/462593/11</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 30 Sep 2012 06:48:09 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-462593-11</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-grandma/462593.rss">My grandma</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>My grandma</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@ExtremeX-Scape Ryley]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/extremex-scape">@ExtremeX-Scape</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>counselors suck, especially school ones, if you say one misleading thing, they will go tell your parents.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-grandma/462593/10">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-grandma/462593/10</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 30 Sep 2012 06:43:34 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-462593-10</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-grandma/462593.rss">My grandma</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>My grandma</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@sour sour]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/sour">@sour</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“AtomicInt_, post:7, topic:462593”]I’ve been through a lot too, but nothing recently.</p>
<p>I never thought to vent to the internet, I have my dad for that.[/quote]<br>
Consider yourself lucky. My step-dad feels the same way about my grandma as my so-called mom does, other than them, I don’t have much of a family. I know I will get a lot of ‘troll’ comments, and in all honesty, I’m completely fine with it. I’m just glad people actually took the time to read this, as I stated previously. Anyways, I have considered going to see my school counselor, but I’m not real sure. My grades have declined a great deal because of this incident, and I just don’t seem to care anymore. I hate going through this, but i’m going to stick it out for the next few years until I am able to move. I say that with the current amount of confidence I have, which isn’t much at all.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-grandma/462593/9">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-grandma/462593/9</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 30 Sep 2012 06:41:19 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-462593-9</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-grandma/462593.rss">My grandma</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
