<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Need help on webclients</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/need-help-on-webclients/295947</link>
    <description>Hey i need someone that has information about webclients and that stuff i have been trying to find out for about one straight year.
i would apprecheat if someone pm&#39;s me and ill pm him ip for my Game and give him owner or create him his own game.
Thanks</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 19 Aug 2009 01:53:12 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Game Development</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/need-help-on-webclients/295947.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Need help on webclients</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Da_0wnz Da 0wnz]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/da_0wnz">@Da_0wnz</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote no-group" data-post="3" data-topic="295947">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 ~~the pk68~~:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>omfg nice tut lol</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>He copy-pasted it. Idk where from but I’ve seen it somewhere.</p>
<p>By the way. Here is the answer to all your problems! Hope this helps!</p>
<p><a href="http://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php?action=search;advanced" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">Advanced Tutorial on Webclients</a></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/need-help-on-webclients/295947/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/need-help-on-webclients/295947/4</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 19 Aug 2009 01:53:12 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-295947-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/need-help-on-webclients/295947.rss">Need help on webclients</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Need help on webclients</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@_the_pk68 ~~the pk68~~]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/_the_pk68">@_the_pk68</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>omfg nice tut lol</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/need-help-on-webclients/295947/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/need-help-on-webclients/295947/3</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 18 Aug 2009 20:32:38 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-295947-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/need-help-on-webclients/295947.rss">Need help on webclients</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Need help on webclients</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@ug1yw4t3rm3l0n ug1yw4t3rm3l0n]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/ug1yw4t3rm3l0n">@ug1yw4t3rm3l0n</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Credit to into the sun</p>
<p>The first thing you need to do is get winRar. (most people have it by now, but just to be sure).<br>
You can download it at<br>
<a href="http://www.rarlab.com/download.htm" class="onebox" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">http://www.rarlab.com/download.htm</a><br>
Get the first one (WinRar 3.71)</p>
<p>For those of you who do not know what WinRar is, here is a definition i got at<br>
<a href="http://kb.iu.edu/data/anny.html" class="onebox" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">http://kb.iu.edu/data/anny.html</a><br>
Code:</p>
<p>WinRAR is a competing product to WinZip; both products compress/decompress and archive files. Files compressed with WinRAR typically have the .rar extension, as opposed to .zip for WinZip archives. WinRAR can also create and decompress a WinZip archived file.</p>
<p>Like later versions of WinZip, WinRAR has the ability to create archives in multiple parts; that is, it not only can compress a file but can split it up into smaller parts. In WinZip, this is called a “split Zip file”; in WinRAR, this is called a “multipart” or “multivolume” archive. When this is done, the extensions for the smaller RAR files end up being .r00, .r01, and so forth, with the first file just having the .rar extension. To decompress a multipart archive, you simply have to ensure that all the component files (.rar, .r00, .r01, etc.) are in the same directory. When you double-click the .rar file, all other files are automatically found by WinRAR without you having to select them, and the final decompressed file is automatically assembled from all those files.</p>
<p>In many Usenet newsgroups, .rar files are favored over .zip files; many FAQs for newsgroups, especially the binary ones, mention and openly push .rar over .zip. Many posters to various groups have said that they prefer the way WinRAR creates multipart archives. Multipart archives are important on Usenet, as a majority of newsgroup servers have strict size limitations for binary groups, and many foreign newsgroup users tend to be on Internet service providers (ISPs) that have strict megabyte limitations on downloads. Because of these limitations, it is actually considered impolite to post very large files, as many people won’t be able to download them all at once due to the restrictions. Posting multipart archives solves this problem, as users can download as much as they’re able to at one time and still eventually end up with the complete file.</p>
<p>The next thing you need is a client.<br>
Here are some ones I have found.<br>
EyreScape<br>
<a href="http://www.megaupload.com/?d=01SH1FJJ" class="onebox" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">http://www.megaupload.com/?d=01SH1FJJ</a><br>
<a href="http://rapidshare.com/files/14966631/EyreScape_OpenSource.rar" class="onebox" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">http://rapidshare.com/files/14966631/EyreScape_OpenSource.rar</a><br>
Credits-Skating On Java<br>
ScapeRune<br>
<a href="http://www.megaupload.com/?d=3G8V80W1" class="onebox" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">http://www.megaupload.com/?d=3G8V80W1</a><br>
ScapePlayer<br>
<a href="http://www.megaupload.com/?d=3G8V80W1" class="onebox" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">http://www.megaupload.com/?d=3G8V80W1</a><br>
Credits-billygotshot<br>
JehanScape Client<br>
<a href="http://www.megaupload.com/?d=W1XZYHYQ" class="onebox" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">http://www.megaupload.com/?d=W1XZYHYQ</a><br>
(link broken)<br>
JehanScape Client V2<br>
<a href="http://www.megaupload.com/?d=CW59X5KW" class="onebox" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">http://www.megaupload.com/?d=CW59X5KW</a><br>
credits-jehanne<br>
(please report any broken links, and I will remove them).</p>
<p>Just unzip the rar/zip file with WinRar (downloaded earlier).</p>
<p>But enough of all the preparing, now lets talk about how to turn a client, into a web client.</p>
<p>Getting A Web Site<br>
This can be one of the hardest parts of this whole tutorial (to your wallet), but also one of the most important. I will be telling you how to get a web site. Free web-sites are not what you want to use (unless it is nationvoice)! If you want to buy a web site (domain &amp; hosting) I suggest buying it all through GoDaddy But there are many other places to buy your web site. If you don’t want to buy a web site then use Nationvoice</p>
<p>Getting your client to look for images on the web<br>
After you sign up for a website you must edit the file Class30_sub2_sub1_sub1 so it looks on the web for all the images. Sadly costom sprites will not work with web-clients.<br>
Download the new Class30_Sub2_Sub1_Sub1.java Here (<a href="http://www.megaupload.com/?d=UN7FFFZP" rel="nofollow noopener">http://www.megaupload.com/?d=UN7FFFZP</a>)<br>
Save that file to the clients folder (if it asks to replace, which it will, hit yes).</p>
<p>Now you must upload the clients background image, to a image host. Here are some good ones.</p>
<p><a href="http://imageshack.us/" class="onebox" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">http://imageshack.us/</a><br>
<aside class="onebox whitelistedgeneric">
  <header class="source">
      <img src="http://pic2.pbsrc.com/common/favicon.ico" class="site-icon" width="16" height="16">
      <a href="http://photobucket.com/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Photobucket</a>
  </header>
  <article class="onebox-body">
    <div class="aspect-image" style="--aspect-ratio:600/315;"><img src="http://pic2.pbsrc.com/common/FB_OG_default_600x315.jpg" class="thumbnail"></div>

<h3><a href="http://photobucket.com/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Photobucket - Photo and image hosting, free photo galleries, photo editing.</a></h3>

<p>Get free image hosting, easy photo sharing, and photo editing. Upload pictures and videos, create with the online photo editor, or browse a photo gallery or album and create custom print products.</p>


  </article>
  <div class="onebox-metadata">
    
    
  </div>
  <div style="clear: both"></div>
</aside>
</p>
<p>Next open up the NEW Class_30_Sub2_Sub1_Sub1.java and search for</p>
<p>Code:<br>
“Image image = ”<br>
Replace That Whole Line With</p>
<p>Image image =<br>
Code:<br>
Toolkit.getDefaultToolkit().getImage(new URL(“imageurlhere”));Change the imageurlhere to the url of your client background.</p>
<p>Then Compile the client.</p>
<p>Jaring &amp; Signing The Client<br>
The first thing you must do is download the jar maker/signer Here (<a href="http://www.megaupload.com/?d=0HMWFH7F" rel="nofollow noopener">http://www.megaupload.com/?d=0HMWFH7F</a>)</p>
<p>Then clear EVERY thing out of the manifest folder.<br>
If you don’t have anything in your manifest folder then skip that step.</p>
<p>Next run the jar maker/signer, and open the JarMaker tab.<br>
Set the output directory to your client folder. change the application.jar to anything you want. BUT KEEP THE .JAR PART!!!<br>
Set the input directory to your clients folder.<br>
Then hit the manifest template button, for the main class put client<br>
Then hit the set manifest button, then hit the Create Jar! button</p>
<p>Congrats! You just made a jar!<br>
Now to Sign it.<br>
Signing the jar, basicly tells who made the jar, and what the jars name is.</p>
<p>Signing the Jar<br>
Hit the Jar Signer tab.<br>
For the out put file put the path to your clients folder, and change the application.jar to whateveryouwant.jar<br>
For the signed Jar file put signed_JARNAME<br>
For The Jarsigner path, put the path to your jarsigner.<br>
It should be something like what is allready there.<br>
Then hit the Generate Keystore button/<br>
For keytool location put the path to keytool.exe (should be something like what they have).<br>
For output keystore file put the path to your client folder, and put Keystore as the file name.<br>
Fill in all of the other boxes (self explained). Except the City, Province, country (unless you want to).<br>
And hit generate keystore.<br>
Then for the Keystore file, put the path to the one you just made (should be in clients folder).<br>
And fill out the Keystore alias, Public key, and private key (there what ever you set them as).<br>
And hit Sign Jar!</p>
<p>If that appears when you run the jar (online), then the jar is signed correctly</p>
<p>Your almost done!<br>
Now, upload the jar file to the website you got earlier.</p>
<p>Open up a blank notepad document and put this in.</p>
<p>Code:</p>

WEBCLIENT NAME


Change the WEBCLIEBT NAME to the name of the webclient (or what ever you want the pages name to be)
and the JAR URL to the url to the jar.
<p>That is just basic html. You can get more html help at <a href="http://w3schools.com/html/default.asp" rel="nofollow noopener">http://w3schools.com/html/default.asp</a>.</p>
<p>Save that as client.html and upload it to your site.</p>
<p>Congrats you have just turned your downloadable client into a webclient!</p>
<p>Credits: %1 me (for reposting), %1 to all the client makers, and %98 to whoever wrote the tut.</p>
<p>There are some updates that you should use to enhance your webclient. Perform these BEFORE you jar and sign your client. If you need to “unjar” the client right-click on the .jar file and hit “Extract”. It will extract all the class files.</p>
<p>Update <span class="hashtag">#1</span><br>
This should stop the connection problems. The connection error “Error connecting, retrying in 10 seconds, 20 seconds, ect.” is just an error while connecting to the cache. The easiest way to fix this is to get the client to look for the moparscape cache, because most people have this in their computer and it is always in the same place.</p>
<p>Step 1:<br>
Open your signlink.java file.<br>
If you scoll about half way through the file (it could be different on yours) you should see the following line.</p>
<p>Code:<br>
String string_0_ = “.file_store_32”;Change the .file_store_32 part to C:\WINDOWS.mpr_file_store_32\</p>
<p>There is an alternative way to fix this.<br>
If you have a line below that line that says</p>
<p>Code:<br>
String string_1_ = “./cache/”;Then you can do it this way.<br>
Make a directory called “cache” (without quotation warks) on your website. Upload all the contents of any of the private server cache folders (like .mpr_file_store_32) to that folder.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/need-help-on-webclients/295947/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/need-help-on-webclients/295947/2</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 18 Aug 2009 20:26:20 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-295947-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/need-help-on-webclients/295947.rss">Need help on webclients</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Need help on webclients</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@123kdd100 123kdd100]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/123kdd100">@123kdd100</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Hey i need someone that has information about webclients and that stuff i have been trying to find out for about one straight year.<br>
i would apprecheat if someone pm’s me and ill pm him ip for my Game and give him owner or create him his own game.<br>
Thanks</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/need-help-on-webclients/295947/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/need-help-on-webclients/295947/1</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 18 Aug 2009 16:00:55 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-295947-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/need-help-on-webclients/295947.rss">Need help on webclients</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
