<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>RSPS 575 / How to host it so other users can play? (Hamachi)</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rsps-575-how-to-host-it-so-other-users-can-play-hamachi/548333</link>
    <description>So I looked through countless Youtube videos, and they all show me how to get and make my own RsPs but I want to know how I can put a web-client or just a download client on my website and have the source running on my pc and let other users be able to join my game either the web-client or the client they download. First off I do not know how to make a web-client I really want to know but I don&#39;t. I am using [url=https://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php/topic,662648.0.html]https://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php/topic,662648.0.html[/url] this source and client, but I do not know how to be able to let other users play it etc I don&#39;t even know what client to give them? do I give them my client folder or what?? that doesn&#39;t seem right but I am a noob back in maybe 2006 or 2007 I use to have a 317 RsPs or older can&#39;t remember and was able to let other users play it but its 2014 now and all memory of that time is lost  :( I want to be able to host it from hamachi since I already am using it for other things etc. If anyone can help me that would be great you will get Co-Owner within my RsPs for sure and I would love to talk about what we should fix or add next etc but as of right now I need to know how to even put it online for other users and what how do I give users a client to use for my RsPs without letting them change the background etc and how to also make a web-client since I really would like to just post a .java code into a page of mine and have it be on my website.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 08 Dec 2014 15:43:07 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rsps-575-how-to-host-it-so-other-users-can-play-hamachi/548333.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>RSPS 575 / How to host it so other users can play? (Hamachi)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Kyle-Billni Kyle-Billni]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/kyle-billni">@Kyle-Billni</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>So I looked through countless Youtube videos, and they all show me how to get and make my own RsPs but I want to know how I can put a web-client or just a download client on my website and have the source running on my pc and let other users be able to join my game either the web-client or the client they download. First off I do not know how to make a web-client I really want to know but I don’t. I am using <a href="https://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php/topic,662648.0.html" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">https://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php/topic,662648.0.html</a> this source and client, but I do not know how to be able to let other users play it etc I don’t even know what client to give them? do I give them my client folder or what?? that doesn’t seem right but I am a noob back in maybe 2006 or 2007 I use to have a 317 RsPs or older can’t remember and was able to let other users play it but its 2014 now and all memory of that time is lost  <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/frowning.png?v=5" title=":frowning:" class="emoji" alt=":frowning:"> I want to be able to host it from hamachi since I already am using it for other things etc. If anyone can help me that would be great you will get Co-Owner within my RsPs for sure and I would love to talk about what we should fix or add next etc but as of right now I need to know how to even put it online for other users and what how do I give users a client to use for my RsPs without letting them change the background etc and how to also make a web-client since I really would like to just post a .java code into a page of mine and have it be on my website.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rsps-575-how-to-host-it-so-other-users-can-play-hamachi/548333/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rsps-575-how-to-host-it-so-other-users-can-play-hamachi/548333/1</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 08 Dec 2014 15:43:07 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-548333-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rsps-575-how-to-host-it-so-other-users-can-play-hamachi/548333.rss">RSPS 575 / How to host it so other users can play? (Hamachi)</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
