<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Help to make free items from shop (delta)</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/help-to-make-free-items-from-shop-delta/368973</link>
    <description>I need help with this please. I want to make some items available in shops for 0gp (i.e. free), I have changed the item values correctly in item.cfg and when I value them in shop it shows 0gp.

But when i try to buy it says &quot;you don&#39;t have enough coins&quot;, when I carry 1gp I can buy the stuff free (it doesn&#39;t use the money) but I have to have it on me or it won&#39;t let me buy. 

I have searched client.java and tried to modify the bit where it says something like: if you don&#39;t have any coins with you it sends that message and tried to make so it doesn&#39;t check that, and what happened is now if you try to buy free item you get dc.

So my question, if you can understand the above is, how could I make it so shop stuff can be free and you don&#39;t need money to buy? Reason is I&#39;m making a sort of &#39;semi-spawn&#39; server but remembering item IDs is stupid so I&#39;d rather do it this way for weapons, and spawning via quest tab for runes/arrows/food.

Also I intentionally put delta in title so if you&#39;re just going to flame me for using this source then you&#39;re not helping, and if you&#39;re not going to help then don&#39;t click on threads with delta in the title in the help section. Ty</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 16 Nov 2010 21:38:02 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/help-to-make-free-items-from-shop-delta/368973.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Help to make free items from shop (delta)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@rova1 rova1]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/rova1">@rova1</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I need help with this please. I want to make some items available in shops for 0gp (i.e. free), I have changed the item values correctly in item.cfg and when I value them in shop it shows 0gp.</p>
<p>But when i try to buy it says “you don’t have enough coins”, when I carry 1gp I can buy the stuff free (it doesn’t use the money) but I have to have it on me or it won’t let me buy.</p>
<p>I have searched client.java and tried to modify the bit where it says something like: if you don’t have any coins with you it sends that message and tried to make so it doesn’t check that, and what happened is now if you try to buy free item you get dc.</p>
<p>So my question, if you can understand the above is, how could I make it so shop stuff can be free and you don’t need money to buy? Reason is I’m making a sort of ‘semi-spawn’ server but remembering item IDs is stupid so I’d rather do it this way for weapons, and spawning via quest tab for runes/arrows/food.</p>
<p>Also I intentionally put delta in title so if you’re just going to flame me for using this source then you’re not helping, and if you’re not going to help then don’t click on threads with delta in the title in the help section. Ty</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/help-to-make-free-items-from-shop-delta/368973/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/help-to-make-free-items-from-shop-delta/368973/1</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 16 Nov 2010 21:38:02 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-368973-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/help-to-make-free-items-from-shop-delta/368973.rss">Help to make free items from shop (delta)</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
