<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Fallian, Inc. is searching for talented and aspiring programmers - Worth Reading</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/fallian-inc-is-searching-for-talented-and-aspiring-programmers-worth-reading/555587</link>
    <description>[center][size=27px]~~ Preface Disclaimer ~~[/size][/center]
[size=14px]Disclaimer: In order to avoid future legal issues, specific information has been [I]withhold[/I] from this forum post. Any and all details will, however, be available for full disclosure on our enterprise chat and/or our private confluence space. This information will typically be accessible immediately after having your [u]VIONOX Account[/u] upgraded to a [u][i]Corporate[/i] VIONOX Account[/u].
Thank you for understanding.[/size]

[center][size=27px]~~ Introduction ~~[/size][/center]
[size=14px]Hello, I&#39;m Brandon. I am the Chairman and CEO of VIONOX, Inc. and Fallian, Inc.
First let me personally thank you for taking the time to look at my thread. I hope that if this project is of interest, you follow-up with us. We would love to work with you.
[/size]

[center][size=27px]~~ Project Description ~~[/size][/center]
[size=14px]Our goal is to professionally recreate Runescape though, while doing so, we will be optimizing the game, improving &quot;Bad&quot; aspects of the game, and ultimately building it into a truly great game. [u]Please note[/u], that this is just a brief explanation of our project. For more details, please contact me or one of our team members.
[/size]

[center][size=27px]~~ Our Sexy Infrastructure ~~[/size][/center]
[size=14px][b]Our Servers[/b]
We have a cluster of 4 machines in total which we utilize to offer globalized, and locally redundant, lag-free experience for everybody.
Our machines are located in the following locations:
Server-0001 - Buffalo, NY
Server-0002 - Chicago, IL
Server-0005 - Amsterdam, Netherlands
Server-0006 - Singapore

[b]Local Development Resources[/b]
Depending on the development area(s) you sign up for, the following IDE&#39;s are offered and fully licensed to you under Fallian, Inc.:

[ul][li]IntelliJ IDEA[/li]
[li]PhpStorm IDE[/li]
[li]WebStorm[/li]
[li]Visual Studio 2015 Enterprise (We have licenses supporting all versions, though this is the one we would prefer you use)[/li]
[li]Xamarin Studio[/li]
[li]Expression Studio 4 Ultimate[/li]
[li]Expression Blend[/li]
[li]Expression Web[/li]
[li]We will soon be offering Adobe products in addition to our others[/li][/ul]

[b]Development/Collaboration Resources[/b]
* Please note that all of these resources are hosted in-house and accessed using your Corporate VIONOX Account

[ul][li]Document Collaboration/Enterprise Wiki/Knowledgebase - Atlassian Confluence
[list]
[li]Confluence Diagramming by Creately - Add UML, Flowcharts, Wireframes / UI Mockups, Mind-Maps and more to your wiki pages and blog posts[/li]
[li]Discussion - Gives Confluence features to allow team members to have discussions that get indexed and organized into our records[/li]
[li]Gliffy Diagrams for Confluence - Adds more diagram/flowchart content to use in conjunction or place-of the first extension[/li]
[li]Ideation - (My favourite) This extension gives everyone a place to write their own ideas and is used as a starting point of the [u]workflow[/u][/li]
[li]IT System and Application Catalogue - Adds extra tools to monitor and visualize the infrastructure. (Useful for quick reference or info)[/li]
[li]Questions for Confluence Plugin - It&#39;s similar to stack overflow or yahoo! answers, though it indexes the questions/answers into the search engine[/li]
[li]RefinedMobile for Confluence - An optional extension to be used for easier access to confluence on a mobile device. (Personally, I just like the default Confluence layout on my Note 4)[/li]
[li]RefinedTheme for Confluence - Adds a few extra easy navigation features, makes confluence also look prettier[/li]
[li]Team Calendars - We use this extension to map out events and due dates on sprints mostly[/li]
[/list][/li]

[li]Project and Issue Tracking - Atlassian JIRA
[list]
[li]JIRA Client - Desktop client to access JIRA without the need for a web-browser. (Very useful for those with slow connections and need local caching)[/li]
[li]JIRA Connect Enterprise - Mobile application for accessing JIRA on the go[/li]
[li]JIRA Portfolio - Used to help plan out goals, and track them (For the most part)[/li]
[/list][/li]
[li]Version Control System - Atlassian Bitbucket Server (Formally Stash)[/li]
[li]Artifactory - Artifact Repository Management[/li]
[li]TeamSpeak 3 - Communication/Meetings/Customer Interaction[/li]
[li]Atlassian Bamboo - Continuous integration System[/li]
[li](Soon to be using) Atlassian Crucible - Collaborative code review system[/li][/ul]


[center][size=27px]~~ Qualifications ~~[/size][/center]
[size=14px]To qualify, you only are required to be interested, determined, and dedicated to our project. We welcome anybody who meets those, regardless of programming experience. We believe that anyone who is [u]truly[/u] interested and dedicated, will be able to quickly learn how to work with Java and our infrastructure within a reasonable amount of time.

Please do not be deterred by the complexity of the project, tools we use, workflow, or anything else. We are happy to teach you everything you want to know. All we ask is a willingness and motivation to learn. We are asking you for a time investment, the least we can do is offer you the same. Everything in our infrastructure is thought out and scalable. Once you have it down, you will be able to continue using the same workflow regardless of how many members are working on this project. May it be 10 people to 200,000 people. It&#39;s still the exact same, if not easier. Everything is also developed to a specific standard, though your code reviewer&#39;s responsibility is to make sure that it&#39;s written to standard before it gets merged into production (They will let you know what&#39;s off and how it can be improved).

[b]Bonuses[/b] - It is a major plus if you have experience working with any/all of the following:
[/size]

[ul][li]Agile Workflow[/li]
[li]Git[/li]
[li]Bitbucket/GitHub[/li]
[li]JIRA/Issue Trackers[/li]
[li]Confluence/SharePoint[/li]
[li]HipChat/XMPP/SIP[/li]
[li]PostgreSQL/Microsoft SQL/MySQL/MariaDB[/li]
[li]AMQP[/li]
[li]Artifactory[/li]
[li]Laravel PHP Framework[/li]
[li]Composer[/li][/ul]


[size=14px]
[b]Programming/Markup/Misc Languages that apply to development positions[/b]
[/size]

[ul][li]Java[/li]
[li]C#[/li]
[li]C/C++[/li]
[li]SQL[/li]
[li]PHP[/li]
[li]HTML(5)[/li]
[li]CSS[/li]
[li]JavaScript[/li]
[li]Bash[/li][/ul]

[size=14px]
If any information above is incorrect or information is missing, that&#39;s my failure to remember and I apologize in advance. 

[/size]
[center][size=27px]~~ Contact ~~[/size][/center]
[size=14px]Please contact me through one of the methods listed below. 
Skype: Xversial
E-Mail: Xversial@vionox.com
TeamSpeak 3: fallian.com (Look for Xversial)

[/size]</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 09 Jun 2016 01:44:33 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/fallian-inc-is-searching-for-talented-and-aspiring-programmers-worth-reading/555587.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Fallian, Inc. is searching for talented and aspiring programmers - Worth Reading</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Pwn3rxx Pwn3rxx]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/pwn3rxx">@Pwn3rxx</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I have been apart of this project for a few weeks now and this project is one of the best ones I have seen so far. The progress it has made since my arrival has been slow but that is because Brandon has done everything by himself. Brandon is in dire need of other people with knowledge of programming to help him continue the project until it is ready for release. If you have knowledge in anything list above please DO NOT hesitate to contact or reply and try to join the team. Any help is definitely appreciated.</p>
<p>PS : If you are interested in this idea of a project please also reply or contact Brandon because there are also positions available to people without programming knowledge.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/fallian-inc-is-searching-for-talented-and-aspiring-programmers-worth-reading/555587/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/fallian-inc-is-searching-for-talented-and-aspiring-programmers-worth-reading/555587/2</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 09 Jun 2016 01:44:33 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-555587-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/fallian-inc-is-searching-for-talented-and-aspiring-programmers-worth-reading/555587.rss">Fallian, Inc. is searching for talented and aspiring programmers - Worth Reading</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Fallian, Inc. is searching for talented and aspiring programmers - Worth Reading</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Xversial Xversial]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/xversial">@Xversial</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[center][size=27px]~~ Preface Disclaimer ~~[/size][/center]<br>
[size=14px]Disclaimer: In order to avoid future legal issues, specific information has been [I]withhold[/I] from this forum post. Any and all details will, however, be available for full disclosure on our enterprise chat and/or our private confluence space. This information will typically be accessible immediately after having your <span class="bbcode-u">VIONOX Account</span> upgraded to a <span class="bbcode-u"><span class="bbcode-i">Corporate</span> VIONOX Account</span>.<br>
Thank you for understanding.[/size]</p>
<p>[center][size=27px]~~ Introduction ~~[/size][/center]<br>
[size=14px]Hello, I’m Brandon. I am the Chairman and CEO of VIONOX, Inc. and Fallian, Inc.<br>
First let me personally thank you for taking the time to look at my thread. I hope that if this project is of interest, you follow-up with us. We would love to work with you.<br>
[/size]</p>
<p>[center][size=27px]~~ Project Description ~~[/size][/center]<br>
[size=14px]Our goal is to professionally recreate Runescape though, while doing so, we will be optimizing the game, improving “Bad” aspects of the game, and ultimately building it into a truly great game. <span class="bbcode-u">Please note</span>, that this is just a brief explanation of our project. For more details, please contact me or one of our team members.<br>
[/size]</p>
<p>[center][size=27px]~~ Our Sexy Infrastructure ~~[/size][/center]<br>
[size=14px]<span class="bbcode-b">Our Servers</span><br>
We have a cluster of 4 machines in total which we utilize to offer globalized, and locally redundant, lag-free experience for everybody.<br>
Our machines are located in the following locations:<br>
Server-0001 - Buffalo, NY<br>
Server-0002 - Chicago, IL<br>
Server-0005 - Amsterdam, Netherlands<br>
Server-0006 - Singapore</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Local Development Resources</span><br>
Depending on the development area(s) you sign up for, the following IDE’s are offered and fully licensed to you under Fallian, Inc.:</p>
<p>[ul][li]IntelliJ IDEA[/li]<br>
[li]PhpStorm IDE[/li]<br>
[li]WebStorm[/li]<br>
[li]Visual Studio 2015 Enterprise (We have licenses supporting all versions, though this is the one we would prefer you use)[/li]<br>
[li]Xamarin Studio[/li]<br>
[li]Expression Studio 4 Ultimate[/li]<br>
[li]Expression Blend[/li]<br>
[li]Expression Web[/li]<br>
[li]We will soon be offering Adobe products in addition to our others[/li][/ul]</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Development/Collaboration Resources</span></p>
<ul>
<li>Please note that all of these resources are hosted in-house and accessed using your Corporate VIONOX Account</li>
</ul>
<p>[ul][li]Document Collaboration/Enterprise Wiki/Knowledgebase - Atlassian Confluence<br>
[list]<br>
[li]Confluence Diagramming by Creately - Add UML, Flowcharts, Wireframes / UI Mockups, Mind-Maps and more to your wiki pages and blog posts[/li]<br>
[li]Discussion - Gives Confluence features to allow team members to have discussions that get indexed and organized into our records[/li]<br>
[li]Gliffy Diagrams for Confluence - Adds more diagram/flowchart content to use in conjunction or place-of the first extension[/li]<br>
[li]Ideation - (My favourite) This extension gives everyone a place to write their own ideas and is used as a starting point of the <span class="bbcode-u">workflow</span>[/li]<br>
[li]IT System and Application Catalogue - Adds extra tools to monitor and visualize the infrastructure. (Useful for quick reference or info)[/li]<br>
[li]Questions for Confluence Plugin - It’s similar to stack overflow or yahoo! answers, though it indexes the questions/answers into the search engine[/li]<br>
[li]RefinedMobile for Confluence - An optional extension to be used for easier access to confluence on a mobile device. (Personally, I just like the default Confluence layout on my Note 4)[/li]<br>
[li]RefinedTheme for Confluence - Adds a few extra easy navigation features, makes confluence also look prettier[/li]<br>
[li]Team Calendars - We use this extension to map out events and due dates on sprints mostly[/li]<br>
[/list][/li]</p>
<p>[li]Project and Issue Tracking - Atlassian JIRA<br>
[list]<br>
[li]JIRA Client - Desktop client to access JIRA without the need for a web-browser. (Very useful for those with slow connections and need local caching)[/li]<br>
[li]JIRA Connect Enterprise - Mobile application for accessing JIRA on the go[/li]<br>
[li]JIRA Portfolio - Used to help plan out goals, and track them (For the most part)[/li]<br>
[/list][/li]<br>
[li]Version Control System - Atlassian Bitbucket Server (Formally Stash)[/li]<br>
[li]Artifactory - Artifact Repository Management[/li]<br>
[li]TeamSpeak 3 - Communication/Meetings/Customer Interaction[/li]<br>
[li]Atlassian Bamboo - Continuous integration System[/li]<br>
[li](Soon to be using) Atlassian Crucible - Collaborative code review system[/li][/ul]</p>
<p>[center][size=27px]~~ Qualifications ~~[/size][/center]<br>
[size=14px]To qualify, you only are required to be interested, determined, and dedicated to our project. We welcome anybody who meets those, regardless of programming experience. We believe that anyone who is <span class="bbcode-u">truly</span> interested and dedicated, will be able to quickly learn how to work with Java and our infrastructure within a reasonable amount of time.</p>
<p>Please do not be deterred by the complexity of the project, tools we use, workflow, or anything else. We are happy to teach you everything you want to know. All we ask is a willingness and motivation to learn. We are asking you for a time investment, the least we can do is offer you the same. Everything in our infrastructure is thought out and scalable. Once you have it down, you will be able to continue using the same workflow regardless of how many members are working on this project. May it be 10 people to 200,000 people. It’s still the exact same, if not easier. Everything is also developed to a specific standard, though your code reviewer’s responsibility is to make sure that it’s written to standard before it gets merged into production (They will let you know what’s off and how it can be improved).</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Bonuses</span> - It is a major plus if you have experience working with any/all of the following:<br>
[/size]</p>
<p>[ul][li]Agile Workflow[/li]<br>
[li]Git[/li]<br>
[li]Bitbucket/GitHub[/li]<br>
[li]JIRA/Issue Trackers[/li]<br>
[li]Confluence/SharePoint[/li]<br>
[li]HipChat/XMPP/SIP[/li]<br>
[li]PostgreSQL/Microsoft SQL/MySQL/MariaDB[/li]<br>
[li]AMQP[/li]<br>
[li]Artifactory[/li]<br>
[li]Laravel PHP Framework[/li]<br>
[li]Composer[/li][/ul]</p>
<p>[size=14px]<br>
<span class="bbcode-b">Programming/Markup/Misc Languages that apply to development positions</span><br>
[/size]</p>
<p>[ul][li]Java[/li]<br>
[li]C#[/li]<br>
[li]C/C++[/li]<br>
[li]SQL[/li]<br>
[li]PHP[/li]<br>
[li]HTML(5)[/li]<br>
[li]CSS[/li]<br>
[li]JavaScript[/li]<br>
[li]Bash[/li][/ul]</p>
<p>[size=14px]<br>
If any information above is incorrect or information is missing, that’s my failure to remember and I apologize in advance.</p>
<p>[/size]<br>
[center][size=27px]~~ Contact ~~[/size][/center]<br>
[size=14px]Please contact me through one of the methods listed below.<br>
Skype: Xversial<br>
E-Mail: <a href="mailto:Xversial@vionox.com">Xversial@vionox.com</a><br>
TeamSpeak 3: <a href="http://fallian.com" rel="nofollow noopener">fallian.com</a> (Look for Xversial)</p>
<p>[/size]</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/fallian-inc-is-searching-for-talented-and-aspiring-programmers-worth-reading/555587/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/fallian-inc-is-searching-for-talented-and-aspiring-programmers-worth-reading/555587/1</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 09 Jun 2016 01:33:40 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-555587-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/fallian-inc-is-searching-for-talented-and-aspiring-programmers-worth-reading/555587.rss">Fallian, Inc. is searching for talented and aspiring programmers - Worth Reading</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
