<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Trisidiax v3 summoning?</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/trisidiax-v3-summoning/536090</link>
    <description>So ive got the majority of broken skills and interfaces fixed for this source but one thing i cant quite wrap my head around is the summoning. When i dl&#39;d the source a wile back i noticed it has working summoning and some shops sell charms an stuff, ive looked in practialy every folder i can think of an i cant for the love of god find a way to make summoning actualy work (like bringing up the proper interface 672 for the pouch creation thing, and everything else summoning related) needless to say there is just no way i can see of summoning working, theres nothing in the folders or files that bring up the interface, is there any1 who has used trisidias source and would be willing to share with me how to get the darn summoning to work. Thanks :)

O.T: or Even if you could specify how you got the crafting to work (gem cutting etc)</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2013 22:16:14 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/trisidiax-v3-summoning/536090.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Trisidiax v3 summoning?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@gimpie gimpie]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/gimpie">@gimpie</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>So ive got the majority of broken skills and interfaces fixed for this source but one thing i cant quite wrap my head around is the summoning. When i dl’d the source a wile back i noticed it has working summoning and some shops sell charms an stuff, ive looked in practialy every folder i can think of an i cant for the love of god find a way to make summoning actualy work (like bringing up the proper interface 672 for the pouch creation thing, and everything else summoning related) needless to say there is just no way i can see of summoning working, theres nothing in the folders or files that bring up the interface, is there any1 who has used trisidias source and would be willing to share with me how to get the darn summoning to work. Thanks <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=5" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
<p>O.T: or Even if you could specify how you got the crafting to work (gem cutting etc)</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/trisidiax-v3-summoning/536090/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/trisidiax-v3-summoning/536090/1</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2013 22:16:14 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-536090-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/trisidiax-v3-summoning/536090.rss">Trisidiax v3 summoning?</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
