<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Issues</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/issues/217266</link>
    <description>I need to be able to work out a few things before my server is playable..

Ok first off, spawning npc&#39;s to work as shops. YES I have checked guides and following tuts. And i get to the point where the shops are trade able, but then, the items do not show up in the shops. Anyone else have this issue? Maybe with issue #7?

Second, when my beta tester dies, the client freezes. Then when logged back in he is at the re-spawn point. I have looked through alot of files and can&#39;t find anything that would be the cause of this problem. Help?

Third, i can&#39;t seem to change magic xp rate. I have successfully changed melee/range. Do I need to go to a different file for mage?

Fourth, when attacking somebody and they run, i stay in one place and do not follow. I&#39;m thinking there is a simple fix for that one.

Fifth, I have tried changing the skill req&#39;s for dhide, and still it says 60 defence needed. I have went into my defCL and added it and everything still no luck. Might have to do with problem #7?

And sixth, I wish to make the ENTIRE map, or at least as much as possible, wild. I have looked in client.java, and seen some things about PvP coords, and wildy coords. Is this where i change that? And could somebody help me with what order/places, i put in the coords?

Finally seventh, now this one is strange. For example i changed the bank command to &quot;shit&quot; from &quot;bank&quot;. And when i compile, and login, the &quot;bank&quot; command works, when i clearly took out &quot;bank&quot;. Any ideas on what might be causing some original files/commands to ge referenced  when they are not even there? This is the most urgent issue at the moment. It&#39;s like the server won&#39;t save/compile changes i make.

Thanks to anyone that can help me.

~jAnDa</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 04 Jul 2008 03:58:24 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/issues/217266.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Issues</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@hootywooty hootywooty]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/hootywooty">@hootywooty</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>ooo srry about that when i said this code <code>if (playerLevel[6]</code> change the 6 to the requirments of the dhide. So if the requirments were like 70 then swith out the 6 witha 70. Sorry that is my bad i just copyied and pasted right out of my client.java<br>
Hope you understand my mistake</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/issues/217266/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/issues/217266/5</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 04 Jul 2008 03:58:24 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-217266-5</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/issues/217266.rss">Issues</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Issues</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@OMG_its_NICK OMG its NICK]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/omg_its_nick">@OMG_its_NICK</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>For the bank one, keep searching you probably have 2 commands for bank.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/issues/217266/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/issues/217266/4</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 04 Jul 2008 03:49:32 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-217266-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/issues/217266.rss">Issues</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Issues</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@jandascape90 jandascape90]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/jandascape90">@jandascape90</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“hootywooty, post:2, topic:217266”]this might help with the dhide see if you can find this code around it somewhere</p>
<pre><code class="lang-auto"> if (playerLevel[6]</code></pre>
<p>Couldn’t find in client. Anywhere else i should search at?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/issues/217266/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/issues/217266/3</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 04 Jul 2008 03:41:53 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-217266-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/issues/217266.rss">Issues</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Issues</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@hootywooty hootywooty]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/hootywooty">@hootywooty</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>this might help with the dhide see if you can find this code around it somewhere</p>
<pre><code class="lang-auto"> if (playerLevel[6]</code></pre>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/issues/217266/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/issues/217266/2</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 04 Jul 2008 03:28:46 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-217266-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/issues/217266.rss">Issues</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Issues</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@jandascape90 jandascape90]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/jandascape90">@jandascape90</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I need to be able to work out a few things before my server is playable…</p>
<p>Ok first off, spawning npc’s to work as shops. YES I have checked guides and following tuts. And i get to the point where the shops are trade able, but then, the items do not show up in the shops. Anyone else have this issue? Maybe with issue <span class="hashtag">#7</span>?</p>
<p>Second, when my beta tester dies, the client freezes. Then when logged back in he is at the re-spawn point. I have looked through alot of files and can’t find anything that would be the cause of this problem. Help?</p>
<p>Third, i can’t seem to change magic xp rate. I have successfully changed melee/range. Do I need to go to a different file for mage?</p>
<p>Fourth, when attacking somebody and they run, i stay in one place and do not follow. I’m thinking there is a simple fix for that one.</p>
<p>Fifth, I have tried changing the skill req’s for dhide, and still it says 60 defence needed. I have went into my defCL and added it and everything still no luck. Might have to do with problem <span class="hashtag">#7</span>?</p>
<p>And sixth, I wish to make the ENTIRE map, or at least as much as possible, wild. I have looked in client.java, and seen some things about PvP coords, and wildy coords. Is this where i change that? And could somebody help me with what order/places, i put in the coords?</p>
<p>Finally seventh, now this one is strange. For example i changed the bank command to “shit” from “bank”. And when i compile, and login, the “bank” command works, when i clearly took out “bank”. Any ideas on what might be causing some original files/commands to ge referenced  when they are not even there? This is the most urgent issue at the moment. It’s like the server won’t save/compile changes i make.</p>
<p>Thanks to anyone that can help me.</p>
<p>~jAnDa</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/issues/217266/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/issues/217266/1</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 04 Jul 2008 02:53:09 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-217266-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/issues/217266.rss">Issues</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
