<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>An Update</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/an-update/113742</link>
    <description>Well, it&#39;s been a while since any of you have heard an update on #64 (Jake McCullum).
For those of you who don&#39;t know, Jake McCullum was a 13 year old kid, with a best friend of a dirtbike. He was racing his 85 when he fell off. He went up a jump and was kicked sideways. Onto his head. Fracturing 3 vertebrates in his neck. He is now fighting for his future of walking, and whether or not he will be deemed a paraplegic.

So, here&#39;s the update.
So far Jake has made extreme progress over the last 4 weeks. He is able to twitch his right foot, and nearly turn his left ankle to 90 degrees.
He has full movement in his arms. Docter&#39;s say he will walk again.
Jake says he can&#39;t wait to be back on his bike an racing with his fellow motocrossers.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 20 Jun 2007 05:22:37 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>General Discussion</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/an-update/113742.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>An Update</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Yz85Racer Yz85Racer]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/yz85racer">@Yz85Racer</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Well, it’s been a while since any of you have heard an update on <span class="hashtag">#64</span> (Jake McCullum).<br>
For those of you who don’t know, Jake McCullum was a 13 year old kid, with a best friend of a dirtbike. He was racing his 85 when he fell off. He went up a jump and was kicked sideways. Onto his head. Fracturing 3 vertebrates in his neck. He is now fighting for his future of walking, and whether or not he will be deemed a paraplegic.</p>
<p>So, here’s the update.<br>
So far Jake has made extreme progress over the last 4 weeks. He is able to twitch his right foot, and nearly turn his left ankle to 90 degrees.<br>
He has full movement in his arms. Docter’s say he will walk again.<br>
Jake says he can’t wait to be back on his bike an racing with his fellow motocrossers.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/an-update/113742/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/an-update/113742/1</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 20 Jun 2007 05:22:37 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-113742-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/an-update/113742.rss">An Update</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
