<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Moderator discretion and the rules</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/moderator-discretion-and-the-rules/312301</link>
    <description>After reading [url=http://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php/topic,408682.0.html]this topic[/url], I saw a real need to post. That topic is the eighth topic we&#39;ve had regarding how we do things around here. Now in my opinion, that is both a good and bad thing. It&#39;s good that the community cares enough to try and show us what we are doing wrong, and it also shows we [i]are[/i] doing something wrong. We need to have parallel discretion. The current system is flawed and it really shouldn&#39;t be going on any longer.

There are a few rules I find either vague or impossible. These would include:

&lt;blockquote&gt;[b]Rule 1:[/b]
Moderators lock topics/remove posts and topics/hand infractions to users at their own discretion as required to foster a positive community. Any disagreement with a staff member&#39;s decision is to be resolved through the use of the PM system. Any public disputes are unacceptable and punishable.

[b]Rule 2:[/b]
Everybody is equal, don&#39;t treat people worse than you do others(E.G., don&#39;t isolate someone and flame them).

[b]Rule 5:[/b]
Do not advertise without permission from a Global Moderator or an Administrator. Anyone advertising maliciously will be permanently banned.

[b]Rule 7:[/b]
A moderators decision is final, if you have a problem with it, pm an administrator. Trying to resolve it through a thread will result in a heavier punishment.

[b]Rule 10:[/b]
We never advertise via the PM system whether the site is approved or not. If your site is approved than you must advertise through appropriate means.

[b]Rule 11:[/b]
Never ask for reputation(rep). Reputation is to be handed out, at the forum members digression, as a reward for adding quality content to a thread, or the forum in general. Reputation abuse is punished. 

[b]Rule 12:[/b]
We respect each other and other communities. We do [b]not[/b] flame. There is to be no fighting on the forums.&lt;/blockquote&gt;

That would be 7/12 of the rules. I can explain my reasons on why I listed any of those seven (I won&#39;t for the sake of keeping a small post :P). But anyway, we are coming on too strictly. This forum&#39;s user base is gradually maturing, thus the rules should follow.

What are our ideals? Let&#39;s look at what&#39;s listed:

&lt;blockquote&gt;[u][b]Ideals:[/b][/u]
[ul][li]We are not anti-leech. If you respect our community and our ideas, feel free to ask questions and they will be kindly answered if you follow the rules. Answer to questions that others ask if you know the answer or offer useful content, otherwise remain silent.[/li]
[li]We don&#39;t talk about things we don&#39;t know. This is an informative community.[/li]
[li]We do not care about post count alone. If someone has high post count but most of it is spam, we hate them. If someone has a high post count with informative posts, we love them. The higher count, the more we hate/love them.[/li]
[li]We do not make spelling mistakes on purpose. We use &quot;you&quot; not &quot;u&quot;, we use &quot;why&quot; not &quot;y&quot; etc.[/li][/ul]&lt;/blockquote&gt;

In my opinion, the only worthwhile one in that list is the post count one. It is somewhat specific, though. This community should have specific ideologies that we believe in, &#39;we&#39; referring to this entire community. The rules should be designed to follow those ideologies and to protect the integrity of this forum (in some cases, the legal status as well).

[hr]

I&#39;m going to get a start on listing some of our apparent ideologies. I&#39;ll then reform the rules according to those. If we can come to some sort of agreement on a new set of rules, then we should ask the community whether they like them.

These are our apparent ideologies:

&lt;blockquote&gt;[ul][li]We, as a community, care about the quality of the content on this site. We prefer to have very informative content over a large amount of content. We prefer quality over quantity. We do not look lightly upon those who steal other&#39;s work or take credit for something someone else did.[/li]
[li]We, as a community, believe in the informative nature of the community members. We believe that a community member is both mature, and intelligent, in nature.[/li]
[li]We, as a community, support all open discussions about related programming content, site discussions, graphical content, and any general question or discussion which is useful to this community.[/li]
[li]We, as a community, wish to continually strive for a better community. We will analyze our current problems in order to construct new implementations to better fit the community to ensure the survival of the community for years to come.[/li][/ul]&lt;/blockquote&gt;

Like I said above, the rules should primarily be built around keeping this forum&#39;s ideologies. But in some special cases, they also need to protect the integrity and legal status of the forum (especially on this one :rolleyes:). With both of these things in mind, here is my suggested rules list:

&lt;blockquote&gt;[b]Rule 1:[/b]
Put effort in your posts. Don&#39;t make effortless posts or topics that do not contribute to the overall wellbeing of this community. Whether a post/topic is considered useful to the community depends on the community response to the topic.

[b]Rule 2:[/b]
When posting any sort of work, be sure that the work is your own. If you are posting an article or a blog, be sure to to cite where the content came from. If you have explicit permission from the author of any work, article, or blog to post the content (without citations in the latter case), then you may post the content as long as the author is still accredited for their efforts.

[b]Rule 3:[/b]
Your role in this community should reflect your level of maturity. If you are a higher rank or are prized for being particularly gifted in a certain area, then you have the responsibility to represent this community through that rank or prize through your maturity, or lack thereof. A poor representation of the community may result in a removal from the rank or a loss of the prize.

[b]Rule 4:[/b]
All topics posted should belong in the correct section. If a member is confused on where a topic should be posted, then the community and staff members are responsible for pointing them in the correct direction. Don&#39;t post multiple topics for a particular subject or question. Multiple topics [i]will[/i] give you more publicity, but they will also give you more negativity from the community.

Furthermore, all posts should be on-topic. The subject of a topic is based around the first post of that topic. If this post is changed throughout the course of the topic, then the posts up until the time of the change are considered on-topic by default.

[b]Rule 5:[/b]
When judging someone else&#39;s topic, be sure to be a constructive critic. No one likes put-downs, so try to be kind when pointing out someone&#39;s error in anything they have done on the forum. Community members reserve extra rights of criticism due to their intellectual nature. These extra rights are also applied to specific gurus in subject a person has posted.

This rule is general: criticism must be constructive. Sometimes a member may be somewhat negative or cruel when criticizing a particular topic, but it will be judged on its constructiveness, not on its niceties.

[b]Rule 6:[/b]
You are only allowed to have one account on this website. There are special circumstances where staff members have granted an account switch or a similar situation. These circumstances are determined by the staff members which have banning privileges. If you do have more than one account, messaging a staff member will allow you to stay at this site. Having multiple accounts but not mentioning them will result in a punishment, and possible a ban. Continuing to be active on multiple accounts may result in a permanent ban.

Never evade a punishment of any kind. Evasion will almost always result in a ban from the website.

[b]Rule 7:[/b]
Respect the staff and the decisions the staff have made. We aren&#39;t asking you to like us, but we are asking you to respect us. As a staff body, we put forth our volunteered time to enforce these rules and foster the ideologies of this community.

If you do not like the decision a particular staff member made, then you should bring up the issue with them, or an equal or higher member of staff. We have our own guidelines we must follow and not doing so is being abusive. We want to know what we are doing wrong.

If you do not like the decision of the staff in general, please post a topic in &#39;General site discussions&#39;. We are here to ensure the rules and ideologies of the community are kept, not to pick on any particular people in general. We want to know what we are doing wrong.&lt;/blockquote&gt;

I think the above rules are acceptable. They cover nearly everything the current rules cover, and then some. I don&#39;t think any are particularly vague and need extra explaining, but I may be wrong.

I started this topic talking about moderator discretion. Now I will list out the rule numbers of the rules I just created and show guidelines that we, the staff, need to follow in order to have parallel discretion.

&lt;blockquote&gt;Members should only receive infractions when they repeatedly break any of these rules, or they danger the integrity or legal status of this site. If you are unsure about either of these, message another member of staff. Never let a rule-breaker go unnoticed by the staff in general. You may not know whether the person should receive an infraction, but another staff member may.

[i]Note: The below rules are intended specifically for Moparisthebest.com. A new set of rules and respective guidelines needs to be written for MoparScape.[/i]

[b]Rule 1 Guidelines:[/b]
Unless blatantly obvious (beyond the explanation covered here), you shouldn&#39;t deal with a topic that is considered spam unless the community also thinks so. Whether the community wants the topic/post dealt with depends on private messages, reports, forum discussion, or other communication (internet relay chat, instant messaging, telephone, etc).

[b]Rule 2 Guidelines:[/b]
There should be general techniques we follow to check whether work is stolen. However, most of the time other members of the community will post about it. If no members have direct proof (such as a link) that the work is stolen, then whether the topic or post stays depends on the amount of members that rise against it. If ten people say it&#39;s stolen, then likely it&#39;s stolen (even if it wasn&#39;t proven).

[b]Rule 3 Guidelines:[/b]
Maturity is initially vague in this rule, yet should be easy to measure. A particular member&#39;s maturity should be compared to the overall maturity of the community. If the community is generally immature on a particular subject, then a member&#39;s maturity should be equal, slightly lower, or greater than that general immaturity.

Immaturity is initially a low-level infraction. However, since there are multiple degrees to this rule, the severity of the punishment can start to rise (esp. in cases where a member is abusing another member).

[b]Rule 4 Guidelines:[/b]
Topics should be moved to the correct section. Multiple topics should be removed, and the topic owner should be notified that multiple topics aren&#39;t allowed.

Make sure you always post when making a moderator operation on someone else&#39;s topic or post. We believe in accountability, to a certain extent.

[b]Rule 5 Guidelines:[/b]
This rule requires the most discretion of any of the rules. Members are punished for negative criticism based on the topic at hand, not on this rule. If the general topic is implying a certain level of negativity, then a lower infraction may be given out to particular members. We are looking for people who are downright nasty, not for people who are just slightly rude.

We want everyone to respect each other, but that isn&#39;t always going to happen. Be very mature when enforcing this rule. This is the touchiest subject on the website and needs to be dealt with very cautiously. Make sure you realize that this community can be expected to be mature in any scenario, even in criticism.

[b]Rule 6 Guidelines:[/b]
[url=http://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php/topic,373331.0.html]Please refer to the standard of banning[/url]. I feel it&#39;s time to start using this standard, assuming we can agree on that particular standard.

[b]Rule 7 Guidelines:[/b]
This rule may only be enforced by a member of staff with a higher rank than the person being disrespected. For the sake of preventing major fighting, don&#39;t punish people if they don&#39;t respect you (directed at non-administrators). This is considered abuse on both ends, and does not have a very pretty result.&lt;/blockquote&gt;

There it is-- a new direction for the staff, and a new direction for the community.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 10 Nov 2009 11:47:57 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Community Suggestions</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/moderator-discretion-and-the-rules/312301.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Moderator discretion and the rules</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Speljohan Speljohan]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/speljohan">@Speljohan</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“casey., post:9, topic:312301”]You can write a big long topic to try to make a point, but will all staff actually follow it?[/quote]When it’s very enforced yes. Needs moar sLothybans</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/moderator-discretion-and-the-rules/312301/10">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/moderator-discretion-and-the-rules/312301/10</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 10 Nov 2009 11:47:57 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-312301-10</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/moderator-discretion-and-the-rules/312301.rss">Moderator discretion and the rules</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Moderator discretion and the rules</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@gothic_queen casey.]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/gothic_queen">@gothic_queen</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>You can write a big long topic to try to make a point, but will all staff actually follow it?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/moderator-discretion-and-the-rules/312301/9">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/moderator-discretion-and-the-rules/312301/9</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 10 Nov 2009 11:46:45 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-312301-9</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/moderator-discretion-and-the-rules/312301.rss">Moderator discretion and the rules</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Moderator discretion and the rules</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Speljohan Speljohan]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/speljohan">@Speljohan</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Cool now the public can see this. GIVE US INPUT ON THESE AWESOME RULES</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/moderator-discretion-and-the-rules/312301/8">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/moderator-discretion-and-the-rules/312301/8</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 10 Nov 2009 04:03:44 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-312301-8</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/moderator-discretion-and-the-rules/312301.rss">Moderator discretion and the rules</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Moderator discretion and the rules</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@lothy Lothy]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/lothy">@lothy</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I agree with Niall about 5. I think he’s on the money with the 4th one too.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/moderator-discretion-and-the-rules/312301/7">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/moderator-discretion-and-the-rules/312301/7</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 09 Nov 2009 00:24:40 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-312301-7</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/moderator-discretion-and-the-rules/312301.rss">Moderator discretion and the rules</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Moderator discretion and the rules</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@The_Un-Named The Un-Named]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/the_un-named">@The_Un-Named</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>“Rule 4:<br>
All topics posted should belong in the correct section. If a member is confused on where a topic should be posted, then the community and staff members are responsible for pointing them in the correct direction.”</p>
<p>That’s just askinnnnnnnng for trouble. In fact the whole rule 4 is just awful, rule 5 is just sucking up to the cms, and rule 7 is pretty bad too. I’m too tired to post anything constructive(and I’m skipping the guidelines for now) but tomorrow I will post again regarding rule 4, 5 7 and anything else that may have been missed.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/moderator-discretion-and-the-rules/312301/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/moderator-discretion-and-the-rules/312301/6</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 08 Nov 2009 23:09:42 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-312301-6</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/moderator-discretion-and-the-rules/312301.rss">Moderator discretion and the rules</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Moderator discretion and the rules</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Speljohan Speljohan]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/speljohan">@Speljohan</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“Taharok, post:4, topic:312301”]Does everyone else agree this should be made public? No point in publicizing it if the staff don’t agree with it.[/quote]As we are obviously the only ones who care (since no other mods have cared to post) yes, we agree.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/moderator-discretion-and-the-rules/312301/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/moderator-discretion-and-the-rules/312301/5</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 08 Nov 2009 22:15:13 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-312301-5</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/moderator-discretion-and-the-rules/312301.rss">Moderator discretion and the rules</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Moderator discretion and the rules</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@mod_taharok Taharok]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/mod_taharok">@mod_taharok</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Does everyone else agree this should be made public? No point in publicizing it if the staff don’t agree with it.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/moderator-discretion-and-the-rules/312301/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/moderator-discretion-and-the-rules/312301/4</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 08 Nov 2009 20:59:41 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-312301-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/moderator-discretion-and-the-rules/312301.rss">Moderator discretion and the rules</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Moderator discretion and the rules</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Speljohan Speljohan]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/speljohan">@Speljohan</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I like alot. Now let the public see this so you might get some more input.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/moderator-discretion-and-the-rules/312301/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/moderator-discretion-and-the-rules/312301/3</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 03 Nov 2009 16:42:38 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-312301-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/moderator-discretion-and-the-rules/312301.rss">Moderator discretion and the rules</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Moderator discretion and the rules</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Fat_Cookies Fat Cookies]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/fat_cookies">@Fat_Cookies</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>+1 to your collection of really long posts.</p>
<p>Only problem with the rules is that not many people actually bother to read them (especially in moparscape) therefore, instead of changing the rules we need to put more time into presenting them to every single member of both sides of the community.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/moderator-discretion-and-the-rules/312301/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/moderator-discretion-and-the-rules/312301/2</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 03 Nov 2009 16:42:24 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-312301-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/moderator-discretion-and-the-rules/312301.rss">Moderator discretion and the rules</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Moderator discretion and the rules</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@mod_taharok Taharok]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/mod_taharok">@mod_taharok</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>After reading <a href="http://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php/topic,408682.0.html" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">this topic</a>, I saw a real need to post. That topic is the eighth topic we’ve had regarding how we do things around here. Now in my opinion, that is both a good and bad thing. It’s good that the community cares enough to try and show us what we are doing wrong, and it also shows we <span class="bbcode-i">are</span> doing something wrong. We need to have parallel discretion. The current system is flawed and it really shouldn’t be going on any longer.</p>
<p>There are a few rules I find either vague or impossible. These would include:</p>
<blockquote>[b]Rule 1:[/b]
Moderators lock topics/remove posts and topics/hand infractions to users at their own discretion as required to foster a positive community. Any disagreement with a staff member's decision is to be resolved through the use of the PM system. Any public disputes are unacceptable and punishable.
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Rule 2:</span><br>
Everybody is equal, don’t treat people worse than you do others(E.G., don’t isolate someone and flame them).</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Rule 5:</span><br>
Do not advertise without permission from a Global Moderator or an Administrator. Anyone advertising maliciously will be permanently banned.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Rule 7:</span><br>
A moderators decision is final, if you have a problem with it, pm an administrator. Trying to resolve it through a thread will result in a heavier punishment.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Rule 10:</span><br>
We never advertise via the PM system whether the site is approved or not. If your site is approved than you must advertise through appropriate means.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Rule 11:</span><br>
Never ask for reputation(rep). Reputation is to be handed out, at the forum members digression, as a reward for adding quality content to a thread, or the forum in general. Reputation abuse is punished.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Rule 12:</span><br>
We respect each other and other communities. We do <span class="bbcode-b">not</span> flame. There is to be no fighting on the forums.</p>
</blockquote>
<p>That would be 7/12 of the rules. I can explain my reasons on why I listed any of those seven (I won’t for the sake of keeping a small post :P). But anyway, we are coming on too strictly. This forum’s user base is gradually maturing, thus the rules should follow.</p>
<p>What are our ideals? Let’s look at what’s listed:</p>
<blockquote>[u][b]Ideals:[/b][/u]
[ul][li]We are not anti-leech. If you respect our community and our ideas, feel free to ask questions and they will be kindly answered if you follow the rules. Answer to questions that others ask if you know the answer or offer useful content, otherwise remain silent.[/li]
[li]We don't talk about things we don't know. This is an informative community.[/li]
[li]We do not care about post count alone. If someone has high post count but most of it is spam, we hate them. If someone has a high post count with informative posts, we love them. The higher count, the more we hate/love them.[/li]
[li]We do not make spelling mistakes on purpose. We use "you" not "u", we use "why" not "y" etc.[/li][/ul]</blockquote>
<p>In my opinion, the only worthwhile one in that list is the post count one. It is somewhat specific, though. This community should have specific ideologies that we believe in, ‘we’ referring to this entire community. The rules should be designed to follow those ideologies and to protect the integrity of this forum (in some cases, the legal status as well).</p>
<p>[hr]</p>
<p>I’m going to get a start on listing some of our apparent ideologies. I’ll then reform the rules according to those. If we can come to some sort of agreement on a new set of rules, then we should ask the community whether they like them.</p>
<p>These are our apparent ideologies:</p>
<blockquote>[ul][li]We, as a community, care about the quality of the content on this site. We prefer to have very informative content over a large amount of content. We prefer quality over quantity. We do not look lightly upon those who steal other's work or take credit for something someone else did.[/li]
[li]We, as a community, believe in the informative nature of the community members. We believe that a community member is both mature, and intelligent, in nature.[/li]
[li]We, as a community, support all open discussions about related programming content, site discussions, graphical content, and any general question or discussion which is useful to this community.[/li]
[li]We, as a community, wish to continually strive for a better community. We will analyze our current problems in order to construct new implementations to better fit the community to ensure the survival of the community for years to come.[/li][/ul]</blockquote>
<p>Like I said above, the rules should primarily be built around keeping this forum’s ideologies. But in some special cases, they also need to protect the integrity and legal status of the forum (especially on this one :rolleyes:). With both of these things in mind, here is my suggested rules list:</p>
<blockquote>[b]Rule 1:[/b]
Put effort in your posts. Don't make effortless posts or topics that do not contribute to the overall wellbeing of this community. Whether a post/topic is considered useful to the community depends on the community response to the topic.
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Rule 2:</span><br>
When posting any sort of work, be sure that the work is your own. If you are posting an article or a blog, be sure to to cite where the content came from. If you have explicit permission from the author of any work, article, or blog to post the content (without citations in the latter case), then you may post the content as long as the author is still accredited for their efforts.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Rule 3:</span><br>
Your role in this community should reflect your level of maturity. If you are a higher rank or are prized for being particularly gifted in a certain area, then you have the responsibility to represent this community through that rank or prize through your maturity, or lack thereof. A poor representation of the community may result in a removal from the rank or a loss of the prize.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Rule 4:</span><br>
All topics posted should belong in the correct section. If a member is confused on where a topic should be posted, then the community and staff members are responsible for pointing them in the correct direction. Don’t post multiple topics for a particular subject or question. Multiple topics <span class="bbcode-i">will</span> give you more publicity, but they will also give you more negativity from the community.</p>
<p>Furthermore, all posts should be on-topic. The subject of a topic is based around the first post of that topic. If this post is changed throughout the course of the topic, then the posts up until the time of the change are considered on-topic by default.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Rule 5:</span><br>
When judging someone else’s topic, be sure to be a constructive critic. No one likes put-downs, so try to be kind when pointing out someone’s error in anything they have done on the forum. Community members reserve extra rights of criticism due to their intellectual nature. These extra rights are also applied to specific gurus in subject a person has posted.</p>
<p>This rule is general: criticism must be constructive. Sometimes a member may be somewhat negative or cruel when criticizing a particular topic, but it will be judged on its constructiveness, not on its niceties.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Rule 6:</span><br>
You are only allowed to have one account on this website. There are special circumstances where staff members have granted an account switch or a similar situation. These circumstances are determined by the staff members which have banning privileges. If you do have more than one account, messaging a staff member will allow you to stay at this site. Having multiple accounts but not mentioning them will result in a punishment, and possible a ban. Continuing to be active on multiple accounts may result in a permanent ban.</p>
<p>Never evade a punishment of any kind. Evasion will almost always result in a ban from the website.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Rule 7:</span><br>
Respect the staff and the decisions the staff have made. We aren’t asking you to like us, but we are asking you to respect us. As a staff body, we put forth our volunteered time to enforce these rules and foster the ideologies of this community.</p>
<p>If you do not like the decision a particular staff member made, then you should bring up the issue with them, or an equal or higher member of staff. We have our own guidelines we must follow and not doing so is being abusive. We want to know what we are doing wrong.</p>
<p>If you do not like the decision of the staff in general, please post a topic in ‘General site discussions’. We are here to ensure the rules and ideologies of the community are kept, not to pick on any particular people in general. We want to know what we are doing wrong.</p>
</blockquote>
<p>I think the above rules are acceptable. They cover nearly everything the current rules cover, and then some. I don’t think any are particularly vague and need extra explaining, but I may be wrong.</p>
<p>I started this topic talking about moderator discretion. Now I will list out the rule numbers of the rules I just created and show guidelines that we, the staff, need to follow in order to have parallel discretion.</p>
<blockquote>Members should only receive infractions when they repeatedly break any of these rules, or they danger the integrity or legal status of this site. If you are unsure about either of these, message another member of staff. Never let a rule-breaker go unnoticed by the staff in general. You may not know whether the person should receive an infraction, but another staff member may.
<p><span class="bbcode-i">Note: The below rules are intended specifically for <a href="http://Moparisthebest.com" rel="nofollow noopener">Moparisthebest.com</a>. A new set of rules and respective guidelines needs to be written for MoparScape.</span></p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Rule 1 Guidelines:</span><br>
Unless blatantly obvious (beyond the explanation covered here), you shouldn’t deal with a topic that is considered spam unless the community also thinks so. Whether the community wants the topic/post dealt with depends on private messages, reports, forum discussion, or other communication (internet relay chat, instant messaging, telephone, etc).</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Rule 2 Guidelines:</span><br>
There should be general techniques we follow to check whether work is stolen. However, most of the time other members of the community will post about it. If no members have direct proof (such as a link) that the work is stolen, then whether the topic or post stays depends on the amount of members that rise against it. If ten people say it’s stolen, then likely it’s stolen (even if it wasn’t proven).</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Rule 3 Guidelines:</span><br>
Maturity is initially vague in this rule, yet should be easy to measure. A particular member’s maturity should be compared to the overall maturity of the community. If the community is generally immature on a particular subject, then a member’s maturity should be equal, slightly lower, or greater than that general immaturity.</p>
<p>Immaturity is initially a low-level infraction. However, since there are multiple degrees to this rule, the severity of the punishment can start to rise (esp. in cases where a member is abusing another member).</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Rule 4 Guidelines:</span><br>
Topics should be moved to the correct section. Multiple topics should be removed, and the topic owner should be notified that multiple topics aren’t allowed.</p>
<p>Make sure you always post when making a moderator operation on someone else’s topic or post. We believe in accountability, to a certain extent.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Rule 5 Guidelines:</span><br>
This rule requires the most discretion of any of the rules. Members are punished for negative criticism based on the topic at hand, not on this rule. If the general topic is implying a certain level of negativity, then a lower infraction may be given out to particular members. We are looking for people who are downright nasty, not for people who are just slightly rude.</p>
<p>We want everyone to respect each other, but that isn’t always going to happen. Be very mature when enforcing this rule. This is the touchiest subject on the website and needs to be dealt with very cautiously. Make sure you realize that this community can be expected to be mature in any scenario, even in criticism.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Rule 6 Guidelines:</span><br>
<a href="http://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php/topic,373331.0.html" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">Please refer to the standard of banning</a>. I feel it’s time to start using this standard, assuming we can agree on that particular standard.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Rule 7 Guidelines:</span><br>
This rule may only be enforced by a member of staff with a higher rank than the person being disrespected. For the sake of preventing major fighting, don’t punish people if they don’t respect you (directed at non-administrators). This is considered abuse on both ends, and does not have a very pretty result.</p>
</blockquote>
<p>There it is-- a new direction for the staff, and a new direction for the community.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/moderator-discretion-and-the-rules/312301/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/moderator-discretion-and-the-rules/312301/1</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 03 Nov 2009 16:17:07 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-312301-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/moderator-discretion-and-the-rules/312301.rss">Moderator discretion and the rules</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
