<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>[New] Eros Online Project [New]</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-eros-online-project-new/528857</link>
    <description>Do any of your remember the Dodian server? Where Yanille was the home, you fought rats in the beginning, moved to the farmer, moved to I think priest, then guards. Then when you got to a high enough level, you were able to fight &#39;Dad&#39;. And after killing him, a server message would pop up saying who killed &#39;Dad&#39;. I am looking into re-making that, and I would like to get some sort of a team to help me with this. Cause what I want to do is make is clean. I want to make a stable working server like that. And I need to put together a team of someone with good coding, and the skill to be able to make an area not acessable by non-donaters. 

Now that being said.. I want Yanille to obviouslly be the home. Ahaha. Now, the little wizards tower, I want to be donaters only area, Where the monsters I put in there actually drop better than others. And make another monster, just like &#39;Dad&#39; but a much higher health than &#39;Dad&#39; and have it to the same thing when it&#39;s killed.

I would like to intergrade so much stuff into this, I would like to make it acessable by a webclient. [Since I seem to not be able to do that. Anymore... :/] I would like to just have a bunch of stuff.. Working pick pocketing on the farmer, working cages that you can pick the lock with a 50, 50 chance of getting either one a small amount of money, or a item, not so rare... Or a 50% money, 45% item, and a 5% rare item.. And have it so you can&#39;t spam click it, make it so it&#39;s like every 5-10 seconds.. This way it&#39;s not that bad... I would like all the skills to be working.. I haven&#39;t choosen a base yet, I know more coding in PI... But alot of people don&#39;t like PI, so I would like to get an opinion on this, for the base used.. As long as it can be used as a webclient... The website no worries about, I already have a website, I just have to re-set it up..

I need a website team, where you work on the website.... Make it look good. Update it frequently..

I need 1 developer, since I see as if there are more, there will be an all out war on what happens with what.. So 1 developer, including me.

I need at least 3 testers.. If anything, and I need more, then more will be on.

We will also have to work hard to make decent prices, and decent drops from all the bad people/monsters. 

If you are down for helping, leave a comment, or send me a message.. I do use Skype, so feel free to hit me up on some skype. (:

Demon6994

I don&#39;t use MSN, or Yahoo anymore.. Just skype... So hit me up, where ever is good enough for you..

Server Developer:
Client Developer:
Website Developer:
Beta Tester:
Beta Tester:
Beta Tester:</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2013 20:18:33 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-eros-online-project-new/528857.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>[New] Eros Online Project [New]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@furyking50 furyking50]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/furyking50">@furyking50</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Good Luck sounds really awsome i would totally play</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-eros-online-project-new/528857/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-eros-online-project-new/528857/5</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2013 20:18:33 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-528857-5</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-eros-online-project-new/528857.rss">[New] Eros Online Project [New]</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[New] Eros Online Project [New]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@ajax_i ajax i]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/ajax_i">@ajax_i</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I’d be completely down to be a beta tester.<br>
I know basic not-so-extensive knowledge of HTML also, for the website, but to be honest probably not enough.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-eros-online-project-new/528857/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-eros-online-project-new/528857/4</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2013 08:24:02 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-528857-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-eros-online-project-new/528857.rss">[New] Eros Online Project [New]</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[New] Eros Online Project [New]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Demon6994 Demon6994]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/demon6994">@Demon6994</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote" data-post="2" data-topic="528857">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 arham 4:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Haha. Funny thing is, I used to be working on a side and its name was Eris. xD</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Nice. This was one of the first RSPS’s I ever played, before I got into developing… And now, I feel I don’t see it anymore, and I would like to bring it back… I mean, it seems right to me… I’m not one to like to do things, but I just don’t see this part anymore, and i’d like to make it work. (:</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-eros-online-project-new/528857/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-eros-online-project-new/528857/3</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 25 Aug 2013 23:44:14 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-528857-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-eros-online-project-new/528857.rss">[New] Eros Online Project [New]</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[New] Eros Online Project [New]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@arham_4 arham 4]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/arham_4">@arham_4</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Haha. Funny thing is, I used to be working on a side and its name was Eris. xD</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-eros-online-project-new/528857/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-eros-online-project-new/528857/2</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 25 Aug 2013 23:36:07 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-528857-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-eros-online-project-new/528857.rss">[New] Eros Online Project [New]</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[New] Eros Online Project [New]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Demon6994 Demon6994]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/demon6994">@Demon6994</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Do any of your remember the Dodian server? Where Yanille was the home, you fought rats in the beginning, moved to the farmer, moved to I think priest, then guards. Then when you got to a high enough level, you were able to fight ‘Dad’. And after killing him, a server message would pop up saying who killed ‘Dad’. I am looking into re-making that, and I would like to get some sort of a team to help me with this. Cause what I want to do is make is clean. I want to make a stable working server like that. And I need to put together a team of someone with good coding, and the skill to be able to make an area not acessable by non-donaters.</p>
<p>Now that being said… I want Yanille to obviouslly be the home. Ahaha. Now, the little wizards tower, I want to be donaters only area, Where the monsters I put in there actually drop better than others. And make another monster, just like ‘Dad’ but a much higher health than ‘Dad’ and have it to the same thing when it’s killed.</p>
<p>I would like to intergrade so much stuff into this, I would like to make it acessable by a webclient. [Since I seem to not be able to do that. Anymore… :/] I would like to just have a bunch of stuff… Working pick pocketing on the farmer, working cages that you can pick the lock with a 50, 50 chance of getting either one a small amount of money, or a item, not so rare… Or a 50% money, 45% item, and a 5% rare item… And have it so you can’t spam click it, make it so it’s like every 5-10 seconds… This way it’s not that bad… I would like all the skills to be working… I haven’t choosen a base yet, I know more coding in PI… But alot of people don’t like PI, so I would like to get an opinion on this, for the base used… As long as it can be used as a webclient… The website no worries about, I already have a website, I just have to re-set it up…</p>
<p>I need a website team, where you work on the website… Make it look good. Update it frequently…</p>
<p>I need 1 developer, since I see as if there are more, there will be an all out war on what happens with what… So 1 developer, including me.</p>
<p>I need at least 3 testers… If anything, and I need more, then more will be on.</p>
<p>We will also have to work hard to make decent prices, and decent drops from all the bad people/monsters.</p>
<p>If you are down for helping, leave a comment, or send me a message… I do use Skype, so feel free to hit me up on some skype. (:</p>
<p>Demon6994</p>
<p>I don’t use MSN, or Yahoo anymore… Just skype… So hit me up, where ever is good enough for you…</p>
<p>Server Developer:<br>
Client Developer:<br>
Website Developer:<br>
Beta Tester:<br>
Beta Tester:<br>
Beta Tester:</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-eros-online-project-new/528857/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-eros-online-project-new/528857/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 25 Aug 2013 22:55:37 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-528857-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-eros-online-project-new/528857.rss">[New] Eros Online Project [New]</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
