<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>I will pay for it</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/i-will-pay-for-it/311018</link>
    <description>Firts of all i dont know why cookie edited and closed my last post... i didnt say i deob that client, i was asking for help to deob a decompile it... Since i tryed with all decompiler and couldnt do it, im looking for someone with more experience than me, that can do it... i can pay a rasonable amount if its necesary, or i can make co-owner, i have my own vps, and i just wanna host this server.. I also tryed to contact the guy that already decompiled it, but he seems to never be online...

So i need help on this if anyone can do it please let me know, here is the link of the client, i just need someone to change the ip to mine xsystex.no-ip.info, thats all, there is only a class file to modify, the one named UZ.Class, thats all...

Thanks in advance</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 27 Oct 2009 13:36:36 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Game Development</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/i-will-pay-for-it/311018.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>I will pay for it</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Fat_Cookies Fat Cookies]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/fat_cookies">@Fat_Cookies</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>You have missed my point. The whole point that you have to decompile the client to edit it because the creator does not want people like yourself using it. I should email/pm the creator for the source and pay him, not us. If you cannot contact him: Tough.</p>
<p>I apologise that I did not explain the original lock properly.<br>
If you wish to continue this discussion please PM me- just dont make silly posts like this.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/i-will-pay-for-it/311018/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/i-will-pay-for-it/311018/2</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 27 Oct 2009 13:36:36 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-311018-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/i-will-pay-for-it/311018.rss">I will pay for it</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>I will pay for it</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@xsystex xsystex]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/xsystex">@xsystex</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Firts of all i dont know why cookie edited and closed my last post… i didnt say i deob that client, i was asking for help to deob a decompile it… Since i tryed with all decompiler and couldnt do it, im looking for someone with more experience than me, that can do it… i can pay a rasonable amount if its necesary, or i can make co-owner, i have my own vps, and i just wanna host this server… I also tryed to contact the guy that already decompiled it, but he seems to never be online…</p>
<p>So i need help on this if anyone can do it please let me know, here is the link of the client, i just need someone to change the ip to mine xsystex.no-ip.info, thats all, there is only a class file to modify, the one named UZ.Class, thats all…</p>
<p>Thanks in advance</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/i-will-pay-for-it/311018/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/i-will-pay-for-it/311018/1</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 27 Oct 2009 13:23:31 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-311018-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/i-will-pay-for-it/311018.rss">I will pay for it</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
