<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Rune - One of the most ambitious projects ever</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rune-one-of-the-most-ambitious-projects-ever/533991</link>
    <description>[center][img]http://i.imgur.com/MvPo4EU.gif[/img]

[/center][font=verdana][url=http://rune.rs]Rune[/url] is a brand new game currently in the beta stages of development seeking to capture the hearts of RS enthusiasts. With months of private development, the team are now seeking player feedback so we can shape the game to correspond with the desires of our valued players. With the project now publicly revealed, we aim to release daily content updates to further what is already an exclusive and feature intensive project. 

Rune is managed by an ambitious and professional team who have a large amount of experience working on top games and work closely behind the scenes on server management, game development, web development and marketing. We aim to become one of the most popular and feature intensive games around whilst incorporating a large community who will be highly involved in how the game is created. However we are realistic and understand our aims will not happen overnight. We have a large amount of capital to invest in top quality dedicated servers and are focused on success over profits.

Part of our ambition to provide a feature intensive game includes quests. We have a rapidly growing list of quests which include both replicates of well known quests as well as our own styled quests. [i] (Animal Magnetism, Christmas Mystery, Cook&#39;s Assistant, Demon Slayer, Dragon Slayer, Gertrudes Cat, Goblin Diplomacy, Greedy Monkey, Horror from the Deep, Knight Fall, Lost City, Monkey Madness, Murder Mystery, One Small Favour, Romeo &amp; Juliet, Saving Souls, Sewage Cleanup, Sweet Tooth, Vampire Slayer, What&#39;s Mine is Yours, Witch&#39;s Potion) [/i]

[center][img]http://i.imgur.com/KGgXlKs.png[/img][/center]

In addition to an expanding lineup of quests, we also have a broad range of mini games and activities. These include: [i]Barrows, Castle Wars, Fight Caves, Fight Pits, Pest Control, Godwars, Duel Arena, Postie Pete Gambling, Champions Challenge, Mage Arena, Warriors Guild, Party Room, Curse of the Undead.[/i]

[center][img]http://i.imgur.com/KRG696U.png[/img][/center]

We also believe the map should be utilized to its full potential - which is exactly what we&#39;ve done. Rune offers 20+ accessible, content filled cities which are still undergoing constant development. This includes quests, tasks, activities, mini games and much more. With a range of engrossing cities, we recognized the great importance to facilitate easy movement throughout the whole map. Accordingly we have developed a large scope of different transportation methods which include: [i]Sailing Ships, Gnome Gliders, Spirit Trees, Correct Teleports, Karajama carts. [/i]

[center][img]http://i.imgur.com/deQInJn.png[/img][/center]

Further features include, 21 fully functional skills to train (including all prayers), a full music system with a variety of different songs for different areas, full slayer with all 5 slayer masters, agility with 5 different courses, fully functional clan chat, fully explorable dungeons and so much more.

*</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 11 Oct 2013 20:00:43 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rune-one-of-the-most-ambitious-projects-ever/533991.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Rune - One of the most ambitious projects ever</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Loveandpower Loveandpower]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/loveandpower">@Loveandpower</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“runetown, post:3, topic:533991”]wats the website name[/quote]Rune  <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/expressionless.png?v=5" title=":expressionless:" class="emoji" alt=":expressionless:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rune-one-of-the-most-ambitious-projects-ever/533991/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rune-one-of-the-most-ambitious-projects-ever/533991/4</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 11 Oct 2013 20:00:43 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-533991-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rune-one-of-the-most-ambitious-projects-ever/533991.rss">Rune - One of the most ambitious projects ever</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Rune - One of the most ambitious projects ever</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@runetown runetown]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/runetown">@runetown</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>wats the website name</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rune-one-of-the-most-ambitious-projects-ever/533991/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rune-one-of-the-most-ambitious-projects-ever/533991/3</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 11 Oct 2013 19:56:32 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-533991-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rune-one-of-the-most-ambitious-projects-ever/533991.rss">Rune - One of the most ambitious projects ever</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Rune - One of the most ambitious projects ever</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@si_force Si Force]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/si_force">@si_force</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>This section is for showing off your server developments, you may not advertise your website here without permission. I have removed the links to your website until you seek approval and then if they are subsequently approved.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rune-one-of-the-most-ambitious-projects-ever/533991/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rune-one-of-the-most-ambitious-projects-ever/533991/2</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 11 Oct 2013 18:50:37 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-533991-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rune-one-of-the-most-ambitious-projects-ever/533991.rss">Rune - One of the most ambitious projects ever</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Rune - One of the most ambitious projects ever</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Rune.rs Rune.rs]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/rune.rs">@Rune.rs</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[center]<img src="http://i.imgur.com/MvPo4EU.gif" alt width="" height=""></p>
<p>[/center][font=verdana]<a href="http://rune.rs" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">Rune</a> is a brand new game currently in the beta stages of development seeking to capture the hearts of RS enthusiasts. With months of private development, the team are now seeking player feedback so we can shape the game to correspond with the desires of our valued players. With the project now publicly revealed, we aim to release daily content updates to further what is already an exclusive and feature intensive project.</p>
<p>Rune is managed by an ambitious and professional team who have a large amount of experience working on top games and work closely behind the scenes on server management, game development, web development and marketing. We aim to become one of the most popular and feature intensive games around whilst incorporating a large community who will be highly involved in how the game is created. However we are realistic and understand our aims will not happen overnight. We have a large amount of capital to invest in top quality dedicated servers and are focused on success over profits.</p>
<p>Part of our ambition to provide a feature intensive game includes quests. We have a rapidly growing list of quests which include both replicates of well known quests as well as our own styled quests. <span class="bbcode-i"> (Animal Magnetism, Christmas Mystery, Cook’s Assistant, Demon Slayer, Dragon Slayer, Gertrudes Cat, Goblin Diplomacy, Greedy Monkey, Horror from the Deep, Knight Fall, Lost City, Monkey Madness, Murder Mystery, One Small Favour, Romeo &amp; Juliet, Saving Souls, Sewage Cleanup, Sweet Tooth, Vampire Slayer, What’s Mine is Yours, Witch’s Potion) </span></p>
<p>[center]<img src="http://i.imgur.com/KGgXlKs.png" alt width="" height="">[/center]</p>
<p>In addition to an expanding lineup of quests, we also have a broad range of mini games and activities. These include: <span class="bbcode-i">Barrows, Castle Wars, Fight Caves, Fight Pits, Pest Control, Godwars, Duel Arena, Postie Pete Gambling, Champions Challenge, Mage Arena, Warriors Guild, Party Room, Curse of the Undead.</span></p>
<p>[center]<img src="http://i.imgur.com/KRG696U.png" alt width="" height="">[/center]</p>
<p>We also believe the map should be utilized to its full potential - which is exactly what we’ve done. Rune offers 20+ accessible, content filled cities which are still undergoing constant development. This includes quests, tasks, activities, mini games and much more. With a range of engrossing cities, we recognized the great importance to facilitate easy movement throughout the whole map. Accordingly we have developed a large scope of different transportation methods which include: <span class="bbcode-i">Sailing Ships, Gnome Gliders, Spirit Trees, Correct Teleports, Karajama carts. </span></p>
<p>[center]<img src="http://i.imgur.com/deQInJn.png" alt width="" height="">[/center]</p>
<p>Further features include, 21 fully functional skills to train (including all prayers), a full music system with a variety of different songs for different areas, full slayer with all 5 slayer masters, agility with 5 different courses, fully functional clan chat, fully explorable dungeons and so much more.</p>
<ul>
<li>
</li>
</ul>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rune-one-of-the-most-ambitious-projects-ever/533991/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rune-one-of-the-most-ambitious-projects-ever/533991/1</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 11 Oct 2013 18:43:57 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-533991-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rune-one-of-the-most-ambitious-projects-ever/533991.rss">Rune - One of the most ambitious projects ever</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
