<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Mixcraft 4</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/mixcraft-4/289593</link>
    <description>[b][size=18pt]things you need[/size][/b]

[ul][li]Microphone[/li]
[li]and a brain :p[/li][/ul]



Please leave a comment.

[b]fyi- these are both demos[/b]

With Mixcraft 4&#39;s Virtual Instrument support and unbelievable professional instrument collection, you can turn your computer into an entire music production facility with the addition of a simple, inexpensive USB music keyboard or MIDI keyboard.

Mixcraft is deceptively simple. It will appeal to the novice who requires easy-to-use software and at the same time meets the criteria for the seasoned professional that wants an elegant but powerful interface.

So download a free trial or purchase Mixcraft today!
Product Features

    * Clear, colorful, and intelligently designed interface to streamline your work.
    * Custom loop library includes hundreds of royalty-free sounds in dozens of musical styles.
    * Works with Acid™ and Apple Garage Band™ loops.
    * Record multiple MIDI and audio tracks simultaneously.
    * Piano roll to view and edit MIDI.
    * Includes a General MIDI library, two sampled grand pianos, Hammond B-3™ emulator, MiniMoog™ emulator and a polyphonic synthesizer.
    * Includes 18 high quality effects.
    * Create mega presets that layer and split multiple virtual synthesizers and effects.
    * Add unlimited VSTi™ instruments, VST™ and DirectX™effects.
    * Mix down to MP3, WAV and other audio file types.
    * Burn CDs of your mix with just one click.

[url=http://www.acoustica.com/mixcraft/download.htm]http://www.acoustica.com/mixcraft/download.htm[/url]

[b][size=12pt]you can get the 30 day trial, or get it free (torrent)[/size][/b]





[b][size=18pt]Bonus![/size][/b]

Autotune (t-pain) software

Hailed as a &quot;holy grail of recording,&quot; by Recording magazine (and adopted worldwide as the largest-selling audio plug-in of all time), Auto-Tune corrects intonation problems in vocals or solo instruments, in real time, without distortion or artifacts, while preserving all of the expressive nuance of the original performance - with audio quality so pristine that the only difference between what goes in and what comes out is the intonation. All with a user-interface that is a model of clarity, speed and ease-of-use.

For most common pitch problems, Auto-Tune Evo&#39;s Automatic Mode instantaneously detects the pitch of the input, identifies the closest pitch in a user-specified scale (including minor, major, chromatic and 26 historical and microtonal scales), and corrects the input pitch to match the scale pitch. A Retune Speed control lets you match the retune rate to virtually any performance style.

For meticulous tweaking, the Graphical Mode displays the performance&#39;s detected pitch envelope and allows you to specify the desired pitch using a variety of graphics tools. This mode gives complete control over the correction or modification of the most elaborate expressive gestures.

Auto-Tune is used daily by thousands of audio professionals around the world. Whether to save studio and editing time, ease the frustration of endless retakes, to save that otherwise once-in-a-lifetime performance, or to create striking special effects, Auto-Tune Evo is the tool of choice.

Prepare to be amazed.

[url=http://www.antarestech.com/download/demoform.php]http://www.antarestech.com/download/demoform.php[/url]


[b]any questions, just ask.[/b]</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 19 Jul 2009 01:12:32 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Technology</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/mixcraft-4/289593.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Mixcraft 4</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@YoungMula YoungMula]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/youngmula">@YoungMula</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p><span class="bbcode-b">[size=18pt]things you need[/size]</span></p>
<p>[ul][li]Microphone[/li]<br>
[li]and a brain :p[/li][/ul]</p>
<p>Please leave a comment.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">fyi- these are both demos</span></p>
<p>With Mixcraft 4’s Virtual Instrument support and unbelievable professional instrument collection, you can turn your computer into an entire music production facility with the addition of a simple, inexpensive USB music keyboard or MIDI keyboard.</p>
<p>Mixcraft is deceptively simple. It will appeal to the novice who requires easy-to-use software and at the same time meets the criteria for the seasoned professional that wants an elegant but powerful interface.</p>
<p>So download a free trial or purchase Mixcraft today!<br>
Product Features</p>
<pre><code>* Clear, colorful, and intelligently designed interface to streamline your work.
* Custom loop library includes hundreds of royalty-free sounds in dozens of musical styles.
* Works with Acid™ and Apple Garage Band™ loops.
* Record multiple MIDI and audio tracks simultaneously.
* Piano roll to view and edit MIDI.
* Includes a General MIDI library, two sampled grand pianos, Hammond B-3™ emulator, MiniMoog™ emulator and a polyphonic synthesizer.
* Includes 18 high quality effects.
* Create mega presets that layer and split multiple virtual synthesizers and effects.
* Add unlimited VSTi™ instruments, VST™ and DirectX™effects.
* Mix down to MP3, WAV and other audio file types.
* Burn CDs of your mix with just one click.
</code></pre>
<p><a href="http://www.acoustica.com/mixcraft/download.htm" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">http://www.acoustica.com/mixcraft/download.htm</a></p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">[size=12pt]you can get the 30 day trial, or get it free (torrent)[/size]</span></p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">[size=18pt]Bonus![/size]</span></p>
<p>Autotune (t-pain) software</p>
<p>Hailed as a “holy grail of recording,” by Recording magazine (and adopted worldwide as the largest-selling audio plug-in of all time), Auto-Tune corrects intonation problems in vocals or solo instruments, in real time, without distortion or artifacts, while preserving all of the expressive nuance of the original performance - with audio quality so pristine that the only difference between what goes in and what comes out is the intonation. All with a user-interface that is a model of clarity, speed and ease-of-use.</p>
<p>For most common pitch problems, Auto-Tune Evo’s Automatic Mode instantaneously detects the pitch of the input, identifies the closest pitch in a user-specified scale (including minor, major, chromatic and 26 historical and microtonal scales), and corrects the input pitch to match the scale pitch. A Retune Speed control lets you match the retune rate to virtually any performance style.</p>
<p>For meticulous tweaking, the Graphical Mode displays the performance’s detected pitch envelope and allows you to specify the desired pitch using a variety of graphics tools. This mode gives complete control over the correction or modification of the most elaborate expressive gestures.</p>
<p>Auto-Tune is used daily by thousands of audio professionals around the world. Whether to save studio and editing time, ease the frustration of endless retakes, to save that otherwise once-in-a-lifetime performance, or to create striking special effects, Auto-Tune Evo is the tool of choice.</p>
<p>Prepare to be amazed.</p>
<p><a href="http://www.antarestech.com/download/demoform.php" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">http://www.antarestech.com/download/demoform.php</a></p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">any questions, just ask.</span></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/mixcraft-4/289593/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/mixcraft-4/289593/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 19 Jul 2009 01:12:32 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-289593-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/mixcraft-4/289593.rss">Mixcraft 4</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
