<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Need a favor please!</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/need-a-favor-please/50758</link>
    <description>This isnt a big favor or anything, but I need this to be done so I can updat my rune crafter of its biggest bug. I just need a picture of the rune essence uptext from you guys. Try to make the uptext against light colors or colors where you dont think SRL&#39;s uptext procedure will work. I tried with my computer, and had SOME luck with making dtm&#39;s, but I thought if I got pictures of the uptext from other peoples computer, I can make a dtm that will work all the time. If you want to help out please do so. 
~jr</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2007 03:52:30 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/need-a-favor-please/50758.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Need a favor please!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@junior junior]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/junior">@junior</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>This isnt a big favor or anything, but I need this to be done so I can updat my rune crafter of its biggest bug. I just need a picture of the rune essence uptext from you guys. Try to make the uptext against light colors or colors where you dont think SRL’s uptext procedure will work. I tried with my computer, and had SOME luck with making dtm’s, but I thought if I got pictures of the uptext from other peoples computer, I can make a dtm that will work all the time. If you want to help out please do so.<br>
~jr</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/need-a-favor-please/50758/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/need-a-favor-please/50758/1</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2007 03:52:30 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-50758-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/need-a-favor-please/50758.rss">Need a favor please!</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
