<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>My intro I guess?</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-intro-i-guess/453801</link>
    <description>Hey guys! I don&#39;t know if this is allowed in this section or not, but I just want to introduce myself because I&#39;m not an avid poster on these forums. This post is actually more about this section of the forums and my server but whatever. Anyway, I have been a member of Moparscape since I first put my advertisement page on the status list. I didn&#39;t even know about this section up until recently. The only real reason I&#39;m a part of it is because my server has been hosted on the status list for a few years now. I wanted to let other server owners know a tiny bit about me, and MITB, I have mad respect for you hosting a large community like this for years.

If I wasted your time, sorry. Also if this is not allowed, you mods can do whatever to this post.

Have a nice day!</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 11 Aug 2012 04:36:39 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-intro-i-guess/453801.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>My intro I guess?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@lilwermscape_ftw lilwermscape_ftw]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/lilwermscape_ftw">@lilwermscape_ftw</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Hey guys! I don’t know if this is allowed in this section or not, but I just want to introduce myself because I’m not an avid poster on these forums. This post is actually more about this section of the forums and my server but whatever. Anyway, I have been a member of Moparscape since I first put my advertisement page on the status list. I didn’t even know about this section up until recently. The only real reason I’m a part of it is because my server has been hosted on the status list for a few years now. I wanted to let other server owners know a tiny bit about me, and MITB, I have mad respect for you hosting a large community like this for years.</p>
<p>If I wasted your time, sorry. Also if this is not allowed, you mods can do whatever to this post.</p>
<p>Have a nice day!</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-intro-i-guess/453801/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-intro-i-guess/453801/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 11 Aug 2012 04:36:39 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-453801-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-intro-i-guess/453801.rss">My intro I guess?</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
