<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>[317] Classic RSPS [Amazing Website Features]</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/317-classic-rsps-amazing-website-features/541949</link>
    <description>Hello, after being in development and working on this server for a while now, my brother and I have decided that it&#39;s time to post a development thread as we&#39;re nearing BETA. This project started about five months ago, it&#39;s a two brother team. My brother is managing anything and everything server-sided. Myself, on the other hand, am doing everything pertaining to the website. This is going to be a clean and simple 317 economy server. With it being so basic, a lot of people start to wonder what&#39;s going to be the attraction, what&#39;ll make us stand out from everyone else? Well, the website. With the server and website being heavily integrated, our possibilities are endless. We have several website features already added, and many more to come. Currently all of the skills are being re-done, with only a few to go. The skills are being optimized for the cleanest performance, and realistic to Runescape &#39;07. The economy has been well thought out, and it&#39;ll be average, but not easy to obtain wealth. Here are some of our packed website features that have been already developed.

- Homepage, About page, etc. (this is all just basic HTML and CSS aside from the home page that taps into SMF for live announcements and game updates.)
- Forums (a given, just basic SMF with a majority of the code re-written for performance.)
- Highscores (what&#39;s a good server if it doesn&#39;t have highscores? However, these highscores were written from scratch, optimizing performance.)
- Token System (this is a pretty cool feature, throughout playing time, players will receive tokens for various different actions. Some of these actions include, but aren&#39;t limited to: random events, finding bugs and glitches, reporting a rule breaker, trading in PK points, etc. Tokens can also be automatically obtained through the following: Donating [number one way to get tokens], useful tutorials or forums posts, allowance [donors will get X amount of tokens per week/day]. These tokens can be used on an endless amount of items, perks, and bonuses. Some of these include: armor, weapons, potions, runes; 2 hours of double XP, forum ranks, etc. More information on the token system coming soon.)
- Automatic donations (when you donate, you get tokens, the tokens can be used in the shop to instantly get items.)
- Automatic voting (nothing special, a rough mockup of GTLVote)
- Player, Donor, Moderator, and Administrator panels. (This is rank-based, players will be able to view stats, messages, etc. through their panel. Donors will be able to claim donor presents, moderators can view reports on bugs and glitches, administrators can ban, unban, kick, etc from the website-based panel)
- Gambling (This system is complete also, it&#39;s called fifty/fifty, you enter the amount you want to gamble, and you hit gamble, pretty simple. If you&#39;re a regular player you will get what you gambled+50%, donors get gambled+70%. In other words, when a normal player gambles 100 tokens, they&#39;ll get 150 back. A donor will get 170.
- Lottery (participate in the daily, weekly, and monthly lotteries. Lottery tickets are X amount of tokens to win big!)

Some more features will be added soon, that&#39;s just what has been already coded. A lot of the player interaction is website based.

[size=14pt]We are in need of BETA testers, if you&#39;re interested in becoming a BETA tester (receive tokens for new bugs and glitches, and daily tokens during BETA mode) just send me a message on Skype: aj.cordio (or private message me on Moparscape)[/size]

Thanks for reading, I&#39;ll take some pictures tomorrow and throw them up here for those interested.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 07 Apr 2014 05:01:39 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/317-classic-rsps-amazing-website-features/541949.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>[317] Classic RSPS [Amazing Website Features]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@The_Web_Guy The Web Guy]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/the_web_guy">@The_Web_Guy</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“Vain_, post:5, topic:541949”][quote author=The Web Guy link=topic=660820.msg4417859#msg4417859 date=1396836175]Here are some of our packed website features that have been already developed.[/quote]hm…</p>
<p>[quote author=The Web Guy link=topic=660820.msg4417859#msg4417859 date=1396836175]</p>
<ul>
<li>Homepage, About page, etc. (this is all just basic HTML and CSS aside from the home page that taps into SMF for live announcements and game updates.)<br>
[/quote]i don’t really see how this is a ‘packed’ feature as smf has a handy ssi.</li>
</ul>
<p>[quote author=The Web Guy link=topic=660820.msg4417859#msg4417859 date=1396836175]</p>
<ul>
<li>Forums (a given, just basic SMF with a majority of the code re-written for performance.)<br>
[/quote]curious to know what was rewritten and how performance was altered.</li>
</ul>
<p>[quote author=The Web Guy link=topic=660820.msg4417859#msg4417859 date=1396836175]</p>
<ul>
<li>Highscores (what’s a good server if it doesn’t have highscores? However, these highscores were written from scratch, optimizing performance.)<br>
[/quote]i don’t see how writing it from scratch optimized anything, but who cares.</li>
</ul>
<p><a class="mention" href="/u/token">@token</a> system - i believe you should rethink it. you’re not going to get far by purposely saying you’re pay-to-win, not early stages anyway.</p>
<p><span class="mention">@topic</span> - please add pictures of media.[/quote]</p>
<p>Not necessarily a “packed feature” just one of the features. A lot of the pointless scripts and resources in SMF were removed. And the highscores were written in more efficient code (to what I believe) than the default one that everyone uses.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/317-classic-rsps-amazing-website-features/541949/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/317-classic-rsps-amazing-website-features/541949/6</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 07 Apr 2014 05:01:39 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-541949-6</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/317-classic-rsps-amazing-website-features/541949.rss">[317] Classic RSPS [Amazing Website Features]</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[317] Classic RSPS [Amazing Website Features]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Vain1 Vain_]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/vain1">@Vain1</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“The Web Guy, post:1, topic:541949”]Here are some of our packed website features that have been already developed.[/quote]hm…</p>
<p>[quote=“The Web Guy, post:1, topic:541949”]- Homepage, About page, etc. (this is all just basic HTML and CSS aside from the home page that taps into SMF for live announcements and game updates.)[/quote]i don’t really see how this is a ‘packed’ feature as smf has a handy ssi.</p>
<p>[quote=“The Web Guy, post:1, topic:541949”]- Forums (a given, just basic SMF with a majority of the code re-written for performance.)[/quote]curious to know what was rewritten and how performance was altered.</p>
<p>[quote=“The Web Guy, post:1, topic:541949”]- Highscores (what’s a good server if it doesn’t have highscores? However, these highscores were written from scratch, optimizing performance.)[/quote]i don’t see how writing it from scratch optimized anything, but who cares.</p>
<p><a class="mention" href="/u/token">@token</a> system - i believe you should rethink it. you’re not going to get far by purposely saying you’re pay-to-win, not early stages anyway.</p>
<p><span class="mention">@topic</span> - please add pictures of media.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/317-classic-rsps-amazing-website-features/541949/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/317-classic-rsps-amazing-website-features/541949/5</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 07 Apr 2014 04:08:45 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-541949-5</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/317-classic-rsps-amazing-website-features/541949.rss">[317] Classic RSPS [Amazing Website Features]</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[317] Classic RSPS [Amazing Website Features]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@arham_4 arham 4]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/arham_4">@arham_4</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Picz pls.</p>
<p>Gl</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/317-classic-rsps-amazing-website-features/541949/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/317-classic-rsps-amazing-website-features/541949/4</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 07 Apr 2014 04:01:56 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-541949-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/317-classic-rsps-amazing-website-features/541949.rss">[317] Classic RSPS [Amazing Website Features]</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[317] Classic RSPS [Amazing Website Features]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@artem543 artem543]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/artem543">@artem543</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I wanna get the link or a screenshot of your website <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=5" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"> good luck. but what about the server itself?  <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/expressionless.png?v=5" title=":expressionless:" class="emoji" alt=":expressionless:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/317-classic-rsps-amazing-website-features/541949/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/317-classic-rsps-amazing-website-features/541949/3</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 07 Apr 2014 02:30:37 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-541949-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/317-classic-rsps-amazing-website-features/541949.rss">[317] Classic RSPS [Amazing Website Features]</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[317] Classic RSPS [Amazing Website Features]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Encryption Encryption]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/encryption">@Encryption</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Less talky more pixies.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/317-classic-rsps-amazing-website-features/541949/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/317-classic-rsps-amazing-website-features/541949/2</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 07 Apr 2014 02:16:15 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-541949-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/317-classic-rsps-amazing-website-features/541949.rss">[317] Classic RSPS [Amazing Website Features]</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[317] Classic RSPS [Amazing Website Features]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@The_Web_Guy The Web Guy]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/the_web_guy">@The_Web_Guy</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Hello, after being in development and working on this server for a while now, my brother and I have decided that it’s time to post a development thread as we’re nearing BETA. This project started about five months ago, it’s a two brother team. My brother is managing anything and everything server-sided. Myself, on the other hand, am doing everything pertaining to the website. This is going to be a clean and simple 317 economy server. With it being so basic, a lot of people start to wonder what’s going to be the attraction, what’ll make us stand out from everyone else? Well, the website. With the server and website being heavily integrated, our possibilities are endless. We have several website features already added, and many more to come. Currently all of the skills are being re-done, with only a few to go. The skills are being optimized for the cleanest performance, and realistic to Runescape '07. The economy has been well thought out, and it’ll be average, but not easy to obtain wealth. Here are some of our packed website features that have been already developed.</p>
<ul>
<li>Homepage, About page, etc. (this is all just basic HTML and CSS aside from the home page that taps into SMF for live announcements and game updates.)</li>
<li>Forums (a given, just basic SMF with a majority of the code re-written for performance.)</li>
<li>Highscores (what’s a good server if it doesn’t have highscores? However, these highscores were written from scratch, optimizing performance.)</li>
<li>Token System (this is a pretty cool feature, throughout playing time, players will receive tokens for various different actions. Some of these actions include, but aren’t limited to: random events, finding bugs and glitches, reporting a rule breaker, trading in PK points, etc. Tokens can also be automatically obtained through the following: Donating [number one way to get tokens], useful tutorials or forums posts, allowance [donors will get X amount of tokens per week/day]. These tokens can be used on an endless amount of items, perks, and bonuses. Some of these include: armor, weapons, potions, runes; 2 hours of double XP, forum ranks, etc. More information on the token system coming soon.)</li>
<li>Automatic donations (when you donate, you get tokens, the tokens can be used in the shop to instantly get items.)</li>
<li>Automatic voting (nothing special, a rough mockup of GTLVote)</li>
<li>Player, Donor, Moderator, and Administrator panels. (This is rank-based, players will be able to view stats, messages, etc. through their panel. Donors will be able to claim donor presents, moderators can view reports on bugs and glitches, administrators can ban, unban, kick, etc from the website-based panel)</li>
<li>Gambling (This system is complete also, it’s called fifty/fifty, you enter the amount you want to gamble, and you hit gamble, pretty simple. If you’re a regular player you will get what you gambled+50%, donors get gambled+70%. In other words, when a normal player gambles 100 tokens, they’ll get 150 back. A donor will get 170.</li>
<li>Lottery (participate in the daily, weekly, and monthly lotteries. Lottery tickets are X amount of tokens to win big!)</li>
</ul>
<p>Some more features will be added soon, that’s just what has been already coded. A lot of the player interaction is website based.</p>
<p>[size=14pt]We are in need of BETA testers, if you’re interested in becoming a BETA tester (receive tokens for new bugs and glitches, and daily tokens during BETA mode) just send me a message on Skype: aj.cordio (or private message me on Moparscape)[/size]</p>
<p>Thanks for reading, I’ll take some pictures tomorrow and throw them up here for those interested.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/317-classic-rsps-amazing-website-features/541949/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/317-classic-rsps-amazing-website-features/541949/1</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 07 Apr 2014 02:02:55 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-541949-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/317-classic-rsps-amazing-website-features/541949.rss">[317] Classic RSPS [Amazing Website Features]</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
