<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Euthanasia?</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/euthanasia/10241</link>
    <description>i have a report on euthanasia are there any ppl who can help? its like another word for assisted suicide. :confused:</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 26 Aug 2006 06:04:44 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>General Discussion</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/euthanasia/10241.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Euthanasia?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@protocol protocol]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/protocol">@protocol</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p><a class="mention" href="/u/freegee">@freegee</a>  lmao doesnt add ne think to the thread its just spam</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/euthanasia/10241/10">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/euthanasia/10241/10</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 26 Aug 2006 06:04:44 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-10241-10</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/euthanasia/10241.rss">Euthanasia?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Euthanasia?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@freegee freegee]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/freegee">@freegee</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote no-group quote-modified" data-post="2" data-topic="10241">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/ryefox2/40/5_6259e4fa9dfe0dec282fb0955bb1974c.png" class="avatar"> ryefox2:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Emos… Research emos…</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>LMAO</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/euthanasia/10241/9">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/euthanasia/10241/9</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2006 01:40:15 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-10241-9</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/euthanasia/10241.rss">Euthanasia?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Euthanasia?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@protocol protocol]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/protocol">@protocol</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <blockquote>euthanasia -The act or practice of ending the life of an individual suffering from a terminal illness or an incurable condition, as by lethal injection or the suspension of extraordinary medical treatment.</blockquote>
nice summary of euthanasia, general talk should get you a C for your grades but if you want to hit the higher marks read my post before since this is a very contversal issue, my people have there own views on it and their entitled to there opinions but to look at euthanasia properly your need to discuss most elements that can decide what people thing for example religion. my view is that people should not be playing god, 
<blockquote>[center]//Please not this was taken from the bbc site : http://www.bbc.co.uk/religion/ethics/euthanasia/euth_slipslope.shtml
all credit goes to them for writting this argument.[/center]
<p>Ethics &gt; Euthanasia<br>
Printable version of this page</p>
<p>Arguments against Euthanasia</p>
<pre><code>Once you accept killing as a solution for a single problem, you will find tomorrow hundreds of problems for which killing can be seen as a solution.
Dr. K. F. Gunning 
</code></pre>
<p>The Slippery Slope<br>
Many people worry that if voluntary euthanasia were to become legal, it would not be long before involuntary euthanasia would start to happen.</p>
<pre><code>We concluded that it was virtually impossible to ensure that all acts of euthanasia were truly voluntary and that any liberalisation of the law in the United Kingdom could not be abused.

We were also concerned that vulnerable people - the elderly, lonely, sick or distressed - would feel pressure, whether real or imagined, to request early death.
Lord Walton, Chairman, House of Lords Select Committee on Medical Ethics looking into euthanasia, 1993.
</code></pre>
<p>This is called the Slippery Slope argument. In general form it says that if we allow something relatively harmless today, we may start a trend that results in something currently unthinkable becoming accepted.</p>
<p>Those who oppose this argument say that properly drafted legislation can draw a firm barrier across the slippery slope.</p>
<p>The slippery slope argument</p>
<p>If we change the law and accept voluntary euthanasia, we will not be able to keep it under control</p>
<pre><code>* Euthanasia would never be legalised without proper regulation and control mechanisms in place
</code></pre>
<p>Doctors may soon start killing people without bothering with their permission</p>
<pre><code>* There is a huge difference between killing people who ask for death under appropriate circumstances, and killing people without their permission
* Very few people are so lacking in moral understanding that they would ignore this distinction
* Very few people are so lacking in intellect that they can't make the distinction above
* Any doctor who would ignore this distinction probably wouldn't worry about the law anyway
</code></pre>
<p>Health care costs will lead to doctors killing patients to save money or free up beds</p>
<pre><code>* The main reason some doctors support voluntary euthanasia is because they believe that they should respect their patients' right to be treated as autonomous human beings
* i.e. when doctors are in favour of euthanasia it's because they want to respect the wishes of their patients
* So doctors are unlikely to kill people without their permission because that contradicts the whole motivation for allowing voluntary euthanasia
* But cost-conscious doctors are more likely to honour their patients' requests for death
* A 1998 study found that doctors who are cost-conscious and 'practice resource-conserving medicine' are significantly more likely to write a lethal prescription for terminally-ill patients [Arch. Intern. Med., 5/11/98, p. 974]
* This suggests that medical costs do influence doctors' opinions in this area of medical ethics
</code></pre>
<p>The Nazis engaged in massive programmes of involuntary euthanasia, so we shouldn’t place our trust in the good moral sense of doctors</p>
<pre><code>* The Nazis are not a useful moral example, because their actions are almost universally regarded as both criminal and morally wrong
* The Nazis embarked on invountary euthanasia as a deliberate political act - they didn't slip into it from voluntary euthanasia (although at first they did pretend it was for the benefit of the patient)
* What the Nazis did wasn't euthanasia by even the widest definition, it was the use of murder to get rid of people they disapproved of
* The universal horror at Nazi euthanasia demonstrates that almost everyone can make the distinction between voluntary and involuntary euthanasia
* The example of the Nazis has made people more sensitive to the dangers of involuntary euthanasia
</code></pre>
<p>Allowing voluntary euthanasia makes it easier to commit murder, since the perpetrators can disguise it as active voluntary euthanasia</p>
<pre><code>* The law is able to deal with the possibility of self-defence or suicide being used as disguises for murder. It will thus be able to deal with this case equally well
* To use active voluntary euthanasia as a criminal action will involve medical co-operation. The need for a conspiracy will make it an unattractive option

Many are needlessly condemned to suffering by the chief anti-euthanasia argument: that murder might lurk under the cloak of kindness.
A C Grayling, Guardian 2001&lt;/blockquote&gt;</code></pre>
</blockquote>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/euthanasia/10241/8">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/euthanasia/10241/8</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 22 Aug 2006 18:42:26 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-10241-8</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/euthanasia/10241.rss">Euthanasia?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Euthanasia?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@leader leader]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/leader">@leader</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>euthanasia -The act or practice of ending the life of an individual suffering from a terminal illness or an incurable condition, as by lethal injection or the suspension of extraordinary medical treatment.</p>
<p><a href="http://Euthanasia.com" class="onebox" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Euthanasia.com</a></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/euthanasia/10241/7">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/euthanasia/10241/7</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 22 Aug 2006 13:21:04 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-10241-7</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/euthanasia/10241.rss">Euthanasia?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Euthanasia?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Kryptizzler Kryptizzler]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/kryptizzler">@Kryptizzler</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Ryefox2, you are fucking stupid.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/euthanasia/10241/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/euthanasia/10241/6</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 22 Aug 2006 06:40:24 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-10241-6</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/euthanasia/10241.rss">Euthanasia?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Euthanasia?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@protocol protocol]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/protocol">@protocol</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>o m g, wtf thats not what hes asking for read the thread before posting please</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/euthanasia/10241/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/euthanasia/10241/5</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 22 Aug 2006 00:37:22 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-10241-5</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/euthanasia/10241.rss">Euthanasia?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Euthanasia?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@o_m_g o  m  g]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/o_m_g">@o_m_g</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>euthania is full of very poor black familys</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/euthanasia/10241/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/euthanasia/10241/4</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 21 Aug 2006 15:21:09 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-10241-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/euthanasia/10241.rss">Euthanasia?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Euthanasia?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@protocol protocol]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/protocol">@protocol</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p><span class="bbcode-u">my guild to A*</span></p>
<p>this is a very philosophical subject, i studied it for a while at school and there are many elements that have impact on it, religion is a key aspect you should look at, since catholics beielve that it is wrong to end your life becuase you are in pain. you should continue to live your life to the best you can whilst in pain and you will be rewarded in heaven this is the classical catholic approach to euthanasia. to get really good grades / marks on your report i would go in to discussion about Utilitarianism which in basic terms means the greatest good for the greatest number, take the anology of a two people in a burning house you must save one but only one. one if you mother/father depending on who you live with etc and one is a doctor who has just discovered the cure for cancer but has not yet writen it down who would you save? a Utilitarian would suggest saving the doctor because he would cure many millons of people with cancer saving more lives then just your fathers/mothers,</p>
<p>then you should go on to explain well you have a duty towards your mother/father then explian about kantian ethics, basicly that you need to decide were your duty lyes when carrying out everyday life, take this simple anlogy, do you go to hospital to see a sick freind becuase you want to? or becuase they have helped you out when you were short on money etc making it your duty to go see them? applying yhis to euthanasia you can ask the question is it your duty to carry on living to help out others or be there for them, or your duty for relief of pain for your self the down for of kantian ethics is that you can get comflicting interests/dutys, if you were hiding a friend at your house from a muder and the muder knocks your door asking for your friend do you a) tell the muder a lie in order to save your friends life or b) give your freind up, there is a conflict in duties/interests becuase you should be truthful but you have a duty of loyaty toward your friend.</p>
<p>i know this might be really deep but i can assure you read up and word it well your get A* easy <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/smiley.png?v=9" title=":smiley:" class="emoji" alt=":smiley:"><br>
then to conclude your report sum up the pros and cons of kantian and Utilitarian  ethics and give a personal opinion on euthanasia. do not forget to mention the slipry slope effect if we allow Euthanasia how long will it before we allow muder?</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-u">resource and helpful links</span><br>
<a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Immanuel_Kant" rel="nofollow noopener">http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Immanuel_Kant</a> [kantian ethics the founder immanuel kant]<br>
<a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Euthanasia" rel="nofollow noopener">http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Euthanasia</a> [ talks about Euthanasia ]<br>
<a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Utilitarianism" rel="nofollow noopener">http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Utilitarianism</a> [<a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Utilitarianism" rel="nofollow noopener">http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Utilitarianism</a>]</p>
<p>rep if helpful <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/smiley.png?v=9" title=":smiley:" class="emoji" alt=":smiley:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/euthanasia/10241/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/euthanasia/10241/3</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 20 Aug 2006 19:11:28 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-10241-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/euthanasia/10241.rss">Euthanasia?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Euthanasia?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@ryefox2 ryefox2]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/ryefox2">@ryefox2</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Emos… Research emos…</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/euthanasia/10241/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/euthanasia/10241/2</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 20 Aug 2006 07:54:08 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-10241-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/euthanasia/10241.rss">Euthanasia?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Euthanasia?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Choti Choti]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/choti">@Choti</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>i have a report on euthanasia are there any ppl who can help? its like another word for assisted suicide. <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/confused.png?v=9" title=":confused:" class="emoji" alt=":confused:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/euthanasia/10241/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/euthanasia/10241/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 20 Aug 2006 07:47:36 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-10241-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/euthanasia/10241.rss">Euthanasia?</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
