<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Map Editor</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/map-editor/436521</link>
    <description>This is a project I&#39;ve been working on for a couple days. It loads maps from the cache and displays their terrain with my own form of rendering, almost perfectly. There is no texture mapping as of now; instead the program just gets the average color of the texture and displays that. This is just a sneak-peak, assuming I&#39;ll add more. I want to add texture mapping, object loading, good blending (I added blending but removed it since it looks like garbage with the lighting), and smoother lighting... And maybe editing. Not sure yet.

[b]EDIT: Got basic terraforming. Not sure if I&#39;ll continue this. If I do it probably won&#39;t pack map files to the cache - instead just generate and possibly compress them.[/b]
http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=RGl039UaTD8

Anyway, I made this with C# and XNA. I ported it over to OpenGL because of z-fighting and depth issues, only to find out AFTER porting everything how to fix them. The performance is significantly better too. Here&#39;s a couple screenshots.

[img]http://puu.sh/kZbj[/img]
[img]http://puu.sh/kZbg[/img]
[img]http://puu.sh/kZb1[/img]

[b]Features[/b]
-Able to display any map at level 0 height (it was programmed to support any level but I&#39;m lazy)
-Basic lighting
-A basic blending (disabled)
-Loads everything from the cache (not really anything significant but I thought I&#39;d point it out)
-Unpacks and saves the title screen music for your enjoyment (/cache/0.midi)

[b]Known Issues[/b]
-Lava appears magenta (transparent - not supported in the viewer. All transparent tiles will appear magenta). The overlay ID tiles have a texture of -1, meaning there is no texture. I have absolutely no idea what&#39;s causing this.
-The bottom and right edges of the maps have the wrong height - this is just to display the overlay tiles since only one map region is loaded, the edge tiles don&#39;t connect to the next height map. It&#39;s not a big deal.
-When tilting the camera, some higher overlays might slightly appear over the underlay when they shouldn&#39;t. This is because of the depth bias to get rid of z-fighting between the overlay and underlay tiles. It&#39;s as good as it&#39;s gonna get.

Any insight on the above issues would be helpful. And before I forget, I owe a huge thanks to the people who worked on project rename317. Without their hard work, I probably wouldn&#39;t have been able to figure anything out. Also big thanks to Endian for his cache dumper - I was able to learn how the cache actually works and to unpack files that rely on other index files.

A lot of the loading code is copied from the rename317 client due to it being... sorta pointless to recode it from scratch, so again, big thank you to the owners of that. I also would like to thank Peterbjornx for his map editor, for it helped me when comparing my map results to his editor&#39;s.

Finally, I would like to leave this here for your pleasure. Not my image.

[img]http://images.wikia.com/mugen/images/e/e4/Twilight_Sparkle.jpeg[/img]

And post-finally, here&#39;s the download to the viewer. Arrow keys to move regions, mouse wheel to zoom, P to pause/unpause the program. You need the XNA 3.1 runtime and .NET 2.0+. Also be sure you have your cache data in a called &quot;cache&quot; in the same directory as the program (program/cache/main_file_cache.dat, etc).

[url=http://www.mediafire.com/?kzm9k6nff7kt992]Download[/url]

Funny story. While typing this up, I realized underlay tiles also had to be greater than 0 and had 1 subtracted from their floor IDs. After taking the screenshots and looking into it further, I fixed it and ended up having to take more. :P Also this isn&#39;t really an official release. Just a little something so I can get some feedback. If it crashes or something, oh well. Also I could make this program much faster by using VertexBuffers, but for the sake of making my life easier if I ever decide to add editing, I&#39;ll be glad I stuck with sending the vertices over and over again. 60 FPS isn&#39;t anything to be afraid of either.

Oh and one last thing - CEBL.DLL is a horrible, horrible library I made a while ago and I don&#39;t recommend using it. However, it was able to unpack files from the cache a certain way the code I wrote (well copied from the client) wasn&#39;t able to. It would have just taken more time to rewrite the code, and since I am kinda lazy...

Source coming when I abandon or finish it.

~Lin</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 10 Oct 2012 06:37:45 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/map-editor/436521.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Map Editor</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@zeh_fiend zeh fiend]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/zeh_fiend">@zeh_fiend</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Someone should release a map editor… lol, well a good one.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/map-editor/436521/41">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/map-editor/436521/41</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 10 Oct 2012 06:37:45 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-436521-41</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/map-editor/436521.rss">Map Editor</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Map Editor</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Lin Lin]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/lin">@Lin</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“zeh fiend, post:39, topic:436521”]link is down, will this ever be updated?[/quote]Nope, sorry. I don’t even think I have the source code to this anymore.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/map-editor/436521/40">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/map-editor/436521/40</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 09 Oct 2012 22:13:33 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-436521-40</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/map-editor/436521.rss">Map Editor</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Map Editor</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@zeh_fiend zeh fiend]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/zeh_fiend">@zeh_fiend</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>link is down, will this ever be updated?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/map-editor/436521/39">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/map-editor/436521/39</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 09 Oct 2012 07:44:46 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-436521-39</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/map-editor/436521.rss">Map Editor</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Map Editor</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Lin Lin]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/lin">@Lin</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“Fridder, post:37, topic:436521”]When I run this, I get the error ‘RuneScape Map Viewer has stopped working. A problem caused the program to stop working correctly. Windows will close the program and notify you if a solution is available.’ I’ve tried running it in different compatibility options, none worked.[/quote]Have .NET Framework 3.5 and XNA Redistributable 3.1 installed.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/map-editor/436521/38">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/map-editor/436521/38</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 28 Apr 2012 01:46:34 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-436521-38</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/map-editor/436521.rss">Map Editor</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Map Editor</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Fridder Fridder]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/fridder">@Fridder</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>When I run this, I get the error ‘RuneScape Map Viewer has stopped working. A problem caused the program to stop working correctly. Windows will close the program and notify you if a solution is available.’ I’ve tried running it in different compatibility options, none worked.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/map-editor/436521/37">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/map-editor/436521/37</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Apr 2012 20:27:16 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-436521-37</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/map-editor/436521.rss">Map Editor</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Map Editor</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Lin Lin]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/lin">@Lin</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“CoonHunter, post:35, topic:436521”]They are saying that to edit properly if is easier to see the terrain how it would appear in game with no difference at all, or at least as little as possible. Otherwise the map that looked awesome in the editor may now look like shit once its in game.[/quote]I know. However, I’m saying it won’t really make a difference when viewed. If you all remember Peterbjornx’s first editor, it didn’t render maps exactly like RuneScape did. Instead, the terrain was a lot higher than it should’ve been and floor colors were kind of misleading with their shading (if I remember correctly anyway). However, I still made maps look the way I wanted them to in-game, despite having to change the height multiple times. But, in my program, the height is pretty accurate, just sharper. I purposely made the lighting strong and not smooth, so the normals of the quads were very visible. The only difference in my blending (at least from code memory) is the client calculates the average HSL in a ±5 square, and mine does the same but with RGB (Although I think RuneScape’s results make single tile differences a lot more noticeable). The results look very similar, or at least I think they do. Just look at the blending of the terrain above Draynor. There is some different and smaller shading that goes on in RuneScape’s way, but I’m pretty sure that’s because of the lighting.</p>
<p>Anyway, I’m done defending myself. If you’re talk about about how it’s so much better to use RuneScape’s engine, then by all means write an editor that does. This was a personal project for fun and learning, but clearly I made the mistake of posting it here for support on continuing it.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/map-editor/436521/36">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/map-editor/436521/36</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 25 Mar 2012 06:13:27 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-436521-36</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/map-editor/436521.rss">Map Editor</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Map Editor</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@CoonHunter CoonHunter]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/coonhunter">@CoonHunter</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>They are saying that to edit properly if is easier to see the terrain how it would appear in game with no difference at all, or at least as little as possible. Otherwise the map that looked awesome in the editor may now look like shit once its in game.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/map-editor/436521/35">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/map-editor/436521/35</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 25 Mar 2012 04:48:59 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-436521-35</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/map-editor/436521.rss">Map Editor</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Map Editor</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Lin Lin]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/lin">@Lin</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Well, the color blending is pretty similar (although not exactly the same), the lighting in the game is more of an ambient style but I chose what I did to give map designers a more accurate idea of what angle terrain triangles are going at. The culling is just for performance. Any regular graphics card can render the terrain without any issues. Honestly, when I started the project, my only goal was to display terrain, but I decided to keep going. Now that I’ve changed “viewer” into “editor”, everyone is pointing out flaws and issues for not using RuneScape’s engine and some differences in the rendering.</p>
<p>I’ve built tons of editors for games and worked a lot with editing 2D and 3D maps, so it’s not like I have no idea what I’m doing past getting maps to render. From experience, I know how I’m doing things now is enough to create terrain and knowing it should look like it was designed in-game.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/map-editor/436521/34">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/map-editor/436521/34</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 24 Mar 2012 20:22:28 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-436521-34</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/map-editor/436521.rss">Map Editor</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Map Editor</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@sinisoul sini]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/sinisoul">@sinisoul</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Those sound like large differences. I don’t think the engine is difficult to work with at all. I’ve had other people I have spoken with trying and do what you’re doing and I think the easiest route until you understand all the mechanics is just to use their engine and then maybe take it to the next level and rewrite it in C#</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/map-editor/436521/33">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/map-editor/436521/33</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 24 Mar 2012 20:05:18 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-436521-33</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/map-editor/436521.rss">Map Editor</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Map Editor</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Lin Lin]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/lin">@Lin</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>That still really doesn’t make any sense. If by clipping you’re talking about whether or not a player can walk on a tile, that’s related to the clipping data built within the map. I still fail to see how that relates to how program renders maps. As of performance, it will never drop because of the terrain you’re making it render as far as I know, and I believe objects are culled properly to allow as many as wanted, which aren’t even shown in my editor.</p>
<p>I really think you two are confused about something because what you’re saying makes no sense at all. I want you to remember that the only difference between my terrain rendering and RuneScape’s terrain rendering is the color blending, lighting, and culling.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/map-editor/436521/32">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/map-editor/436521/32</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 24 Mar 2012 19:59:32 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-436521-32</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/map-editor/436521.rss">Map Editor</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Map Editor</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Lord_Harry Lord Harry]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/lord_harry">@Lord_Harry</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote quote-modified" data-post="28" data-topic="436521">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/lin/40/5_e05bb34c421432ee4d40de30c10af3e5.png" class="avatar"> Lin:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>And the only reason I mention the performance is because of seeing Peterbjornx’s most recent editor. It uses the RuneScape engine and performs pretty poorly and is impossible to work with.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Just because peters map editor wasn’t very good to work with, doesn’t mean the entire engine is bad.  Here is a fully functional map editor that I built myself using the Runescape engine, I assure you it performs extremely well and has no issues.</p>
<p>You can find the link to my thread here: <a href="http://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php/topic,497895" rel="nofollow noopener">http://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php/topic,497895</a></p>
<p><img src="http://dl.dropbox.com/u/2428061/apocalyptism/buildingg.gif" alt width="" height=""></p>
<aside class="quote quote-modified" data-post="28" data-topic="436521">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/lin/40/5_e05bb34c421432ee4d40de30c10af3e5.png" class="avatar"> Lin:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>That makes no sense. The way the map looks in the editor and performs in the client aren’t at all related.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>You clearly have no idea what you are talking about, that is a very important factor.</p>
<p>When you are designing a map it is very important that you can see how it looks and performs in-game, it allows you to spot any potential issues strait away (i.e clipping).  You don’t want to spend hours building a map to later find that it doesn’t look or perform correctly with the actual engine that its needed for.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/map-editor/436521/31">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/map-editor/436521/31</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 24 Mar 2012 15:29:02 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-436521-31</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/map-editor/436521.rss">Map Editor</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Map Editor</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Daginith Daginith]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/daginith">@Daginith</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“Davidi2, post:29, topic:436521”]help i tried to run this on any os besides windows and it doesnt work?</p>
<p>plz help rep++[/quote]<br>
<img src="http://www.swtorguild.co.uk/wp-content/uploads/2012/02/cant-tell-if-trolling-or-serious.jpg.png" alt width="" height=""></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/map-editor/436521/30">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/map-editor/436521/30</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 24 Mar 2012 06:13:51 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-436521-30</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/map-editor/436521.rss">Map Editor</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Map Editor</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@davidi2 Davidi2]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/davidi2">@davidi2</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>help i tried to run this on any os besides windows and it doesnt work?</p>
<p>plz help rep++</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/map-editor/436521/29">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/map-editor/436521/29</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 24 Mar 2012 05:54:43 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-436521-29</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/map-editor/436521.rss">Map Editor</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Map Editor</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Lin Lin]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/lin">@Lin</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Nope. Besides, I did this primarily for fun, which is why I probably will just drop the project since it’s boring to work on now. And the only reason I mention the performance is because of seeing Peterbjornx’s most recent editor. It uses the RuneScape engine and performs pretty poorly and is impossible to work with.</p>
<p>[quote=“Miss Silabsoft, post:27, topic:436521”]really does not do good if your map looks better in an editor when it performs like shit in the client.[/quote]That makes no sense. The way the map looks in the editor and performs in the client aren’t at all related. Though, since I do know what you mean, The way my program renders maps is generally the same as the client’s. You get an idea of how the landscape height will be, the colors will look together, and how paths &amp; other overlay will look.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/map-editor/436521/28">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/map-editor/436521/28</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 24 Mar 2012 05:40:39 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-436521-28</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/map-editor/436521.rss">Map Editor</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Map Editor</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@silabsoft RuneAgent]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/silabsoft">@silabsoft</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“Lin, post:25, topic:436521”][quote author=Lord Harry link=topic=539228.msg3953512#msg3953512 date=1332521532]<br>
Makes more sense to just build it out of the runescape engine<br>
[/quote]That is a horrible idea. The old RuneScape engine was made to render basic 3D objects using the CPU for all the work. It wasn’t made for editing or anything past displaying. The ONLY benefit using the original engine is to get an exact preview of what would be seen in-game, but the bad performance and lack of understanding is not worth it.[/quote]<br>
hope your joking?</p>
<blockquote>exact preview of what would be seen in-game, but the bad performance</blockquote>
<p>really does not do good if your map looks better in an editor when it performs like shit in the client.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/map-editor/436521/27">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/map-editor/436521/27</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 24 Mar 2012 04:53:21 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-436521-27</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/map-editor/436521.rss">Map Editor</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Map Editor</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@sinisoul sini]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/sinisoul">@sinisoul</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote" data-post="24" data-topic="436521">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 Lord Harry:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Makes more sense to just build it out of the runescape engine</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I was thinking this as well.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/map-editor/436521/26">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/map-editor/436521/26</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 24 Mar 2012 03:48:29 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-436521-26</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/map-editor/436521.rss">Map Editor</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Map Editor</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Lin Lin]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/lin">@Lin</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“Lord Harry, post:24, topic:436521”]Makes more sense to just build it out of the runescape engine[/quote]That is a horrible idea. The old RuneScape engine was made to render basic 3D objects using the CPU for all the work. It wasn’t made for editing or anything past displaying. The ONLY benefit using the original engine is to get an exact preview of what would be seen in-game, but the bad performance and lack of understanding is not worth it.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/map-editor/436521/25">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/map-editor/436521/25</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 23 Mar 2012 23:12:38 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-436521-25</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/map-editor/436521.rss">Map Editor</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Map Editor</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Lord_Harry Lord Harry]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/lord_harry">@Lord_Harry</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Makes more sense to just build it out of the runescape engine</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/map-editor/436521/24">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/map-editor/436521/24</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 23 Mar 2012 16:52:12 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-436521-24</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/map-editor/436521.rss">Map Editor</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Map Editor</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Native1 Native^]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/native1">@Native1</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“Lin, post:20, topic:436521”][quote author=The Wanderer link=topic=539228.msg3951759#msg3951759 date=1332350928]<br>
If you ever add support for editing you should look into how sculpting programs edit their mesh as that would be the best way to edit the map IMO.</p>
<p>Wonderful job. good luck if you decide to add texture support still.<br>
[/quote]You mean like…</p>
<p><div class="lazyYT" data-youtube-id="RGl039UaTD8" data-youtube-title="RuneScape Map Viewer - Terraforming" data-width="480" data-height="270" data-parameters="feature=oembed&amp;wmode=opaque"></div><br>
omg, that’s fucking amazing</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/map-editor/436521/23">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/map-editor/436521/23</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 22 Mar 2012 15:20:48 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-436521-23</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/map-editor/436521.rss">Map Editor</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Map Editor</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@the_wanderer The Wanderer]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/the_wanderer">@the_wanderer</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Um yes. Precisely. Besides there’s usually more options like pinch, smooth, pull, crease and such for more precise uses, but that is awesome! &lt;3 loving this.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/map-editor/436521/22">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/map-editor/436521/22</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 22 Mar 2012 03:15:53 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-436521-22</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/map-editor/436521.rss">Map Editor</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Map Editor</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Kidpaparoach Kidpaparoach]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/kidpaparoach">@Kidpaparoach</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Lin, sell the map to Rs. Make huge irl geepee’s(:. It’d be sexy in Rs, shame they’d probably not buy it though just to be annoying:(.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/map-editor/436521/21">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/map-editor/436521/21</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 21 Mar 2012 23:40:53 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-436521-21</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/map-editor/436521.rss">Map Editor</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Map Editor</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Lin Lin]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/lin">@Lin</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“The Wanderer, post:19, topic:436521”]If you ever add support for editing you should look into how sculpting programs edit their mesh as that would be the best way to edit the map IMO.</p>
<p>Wonderful job. good luck if you decide to add texture support still.[/quote]You mean like…</p>
<div class="lazyYT" data-youtube-id="RGl039UaTD8" data-youtube-title="RuneScape Map Viewer - Terraforming" data-width="480" data-height="270" data-parameters="feature=oembed&amp;wmode=opaque"></div>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/map-editor/436521/20">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/map-editor/436521/20</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 21 Mar 2012 22:16:25 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-436521-20</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/map-editor/436521.rss">Map Editor</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Map Editor</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@the_wanderer The Wanderer]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/the_wanderer">@the_wanderer</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>If you ever add support for editing you should look into how sculpting programs edit their mesh as that would be the best way to edit the map IMO.</p>
<p>Wonderful job. good luck if you decide to add texture support still.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/map-editor/436521/19">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/map-editor/436521/19</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 21 Mar 2012 17:28:48 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-436521-19</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/map-editor/436521.rss">Map Editor</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Map Editor</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Kidpaparoach Kidpaparoach]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/kidpaparoach">@Kidpaparoach</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Windows vista is crap, been trying to sell it for ages for $30 cause I have 4 copies and nobody will buy it… even the 4 copies for $40… &gt;.&gt; Thats how bad vista is</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/map-editor/436521/18">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/map-editor/436521/18</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 20 Mar 2012 15:41:31 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-436521-18</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/map-editor/436521.rss">Map Editor</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Map Editor</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@imsuperman05 imsuperman05]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/imsuperman05">@imsuperman05</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“dain bramage, post:13, topic:436521”][quote author=imsuperman05 link=topic=539228.msg3949606#msg3949606 date=1332188763]<br>
You are amazing.  ye mine crashes… im on Windows 7 Vista if that means anything<br>
[/quote]<br>
Windows 7 Vista sounds nice.[/quote]<br>
Lolololo Windows 7*</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/map-editor/436521/17">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/map-editor/436521/17</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 20 Mar 2012 15:11:30 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-436521-17</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/map-editor/436521.rss">Map Editor</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
