<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>War on Logic</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/war-on-logic/32291</link>
    <description>The War on Terrorism does not make sense. War is the most disastrous thing monkeys have yet invented, though the personal automobile gives it a run for its money. It should never be undertaken lightly, and certainly never without a clear objective that can be won. Terrorism is defined by the US government:

&lt;blockquote&gt;&quot;the unlawful use of -- or threatened use of -- force or violence against individuals or property to coerce or intimidate governments or societies, often to achieve political, religious, or ideological objectives.&quot;&lt;/blockquote&gt;

Was the war in Iraq illegal? 
[url=http://www.worldpress.org/specials/iraq/]Judge[/url] for yourself. 

Certainly the war in Iraq has caused massive amounts of violence. 50,000 [b]civilians[/b] are dead [url=http://www.iraqbodycount.org/]today[/url].

And there is no doubt the war in Iraq was launched to achieve political, if not ideological objectives.



The war on logic began a long time ago, with Reagan spreading terrorism across the world.

&lt;blockquote&gt;Following this policy, the U.S. funded groups the administration called &quot;freedom fighters&quot;, such as the mujahideen in Afghanistan, the Contras in Nicaragua, and, with the white government of South Africa, Jonas Savimbi&#39;s rebel forces in Angola&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;Reagan offered controversial support to the rightist El Salvador government throughout his term; he feared a takeover by the FMLN during the El Salvador Civil War which had begun in the late 1970s. The war left 75,000 people dead, 8,000 missing and one million homeless; some one million El Salvadoreans, fleeing the war and government backed right-wing death squads, immigrated to the United States. He backed attempts at introducing democratic elections with mixed success.&lt;/blockquote&gt;


As did the [url=http://www.bushflash.com/thanks.html]CIA[/url] (Must see link).

And, of course, the US provided Saddam with weapons of mass destruction:
&lt;blockquote&gt;The U.S. also allowed the shipment of &quot;dual use&quot; materials, that could be used for chemical and biological weapons, ostensibly for agriculture, medical research, and other civilian purposes, but they were diverted for use in Saddam&#39;s weapons of mass destruction programs.&lt;/blockquote&gt;



If you do some searching on &quot;Saddam CIA&quot; on google, you find loads of interesting things:

&lt;blockquote&gt;But Google also turns up stories infrequently if ever reported in the mainstream press about Saddam Hussein and the CIA -- as it turns out the Iraqi dictator and the now reviled Ba&#39;ath Party were once favored CIA assets serving US interests. This is the sort of information you will not find splashed across the front page of the New York Times, let alone buried in section F16. In fact, most of this information appears primarily in papers such as the Hindustan Times or in books written by Arab authors. Since the story is at odds with the Bush version of reality, it&#39;s not front-page material in America.&lt;/blockquote&gt;





[b]Now that you know that the US installed Saddam in power, and provided him with WMD, is there anyone here who actually supports the &quot;War on Terror?&quot;[/b]</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2006 03:17:09 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>General Discussion</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/war-on-logic/32291.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>War on Logic</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@yakman yakman]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/yakman">@yakman</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>i dont think the war was approved by the UN, so therefore its illigal</p>
<p>i think the west invaded iraq because of its oil, there are other dictators who also did terrible things, i cant name any now because they are not very publicised, but i think theres one in africa, not too sure though.</p>
<p>i think saddam hussains punishment should be drowning in oil, then the punishment would fit the crime</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/war-on-logic/32291/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/war-on-logic/32291/3</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2006 03:17:09 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-32291-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/war-on-logic/32291.rss">War on Logic</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>War on Logic</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Ron Ron]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/ron">@Ron</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <blockquote>Certainly the war in Iraq has caused massive amounts of violence. 50,000 civilians are dead today.</blockquote>
I read in an article on yahoo that 5000 US citizens and over 100,000 Iraqis are dead in the war total.
<p>Yeah we were buddies with Saddam for so long. We were his friend and we shafted him just like now in Brazil. If china didn’t have any nuclear weapons, we would attack them too. :rolleyes:</p>
<blockquote>Now that you know that the US installed Saddam in power, and provided him with WMD, is there anyone here who actually supports the "War on Terror?"</blockquote>
Sadly, there are so many stupid americans, that a good percentage does support the war. Did you hear about the woman who hung a wreath with a peace sign on her door a week ago? A group of people (about 50 or 60) went and complained saying she was Anti War and tried to take her to court. They obviously through it out and the lady who put the peace sign up basically said fuck you, I'm not taking that off until Christmas is over. lol. 
<p>Some people are just so retarded. <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/frowning.png?v=6" title=":frowning:" class="emoji" alt=":frowning:"></p>
<p>Nice post by the way.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/war-on-logic/32291/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/war-on-logic/32291/2</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2006 01:23:36 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-32291-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/war-on-logic/32291.rss">War on Logic</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>War on Logic</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@PaulT PaulT]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/pault">@PaulT</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>The War on Terrorism does not make sense. War is the most disastrous thing monkeys have yet invented, though the personal automobile gives it a run for its money. It should never be undertaken lightly, and certainly never without a clear objective that can be won. Terrorism is defined by the US government:</p>
<blockquote>"the unlawful use of -- or threatened use of -- force or violence against individuals or property to coerce or intimidate governments or societies, often to achieve political, religious, or ideological objectives."</blockquote>
<p>Was the war in Iraq illegal?<br>
<a href="http://www.worldpress.org/specials/iraq/" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">Judge</a> for yourself.</p>
<p>Certainly the war in Iraq has caused massive amounts of violence. 50,000 <span class="bbcode-b">civilians</span> are dead <a href="http://www.iraqbodycount.org/" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">today</a>.</p>
<p>And there is no doubt the war in Iraq was launched to achieve political, if not ideological objectives.</p>
<p>The war on logic began a long time ago, with Reagan spreading terrorism across the world.</p>
<blockquote>Following this policy, the U.S. funded groups the administration called "freedom fighters", such as the mujahideen in Afghanistan, the Contras in Nicaragua, and, with the white government of South Africa, Jonas Savimbi's rebel forces in Angola</blockquote>
<blockquote>Reagan offered controversial support to the rightist El Salvador government throughout his term; he feared a takeover by the FMLN during the El Salvador Civil War which had begun in the late 1970s. The war left 75,000 people dead, 8,000 missing and one million homeless; some one million El Salvadoreans, fleeing the war and government backed right-wing death squads, immigrated to the United States. He backed attempts at introducing democratic elections with mixed success.</blockquote>
<p>As did the <a href="http://www.bushflash.com/thanks.html" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">CIA</a> (Must see link).</p>
<p>And, of course, the US provided Saddam with weapons of mass destruction:</p>
<blockquote>The U.S. also allowed the shipment of "dual use" materials, that could be used for chemical and biological weapons, ostensibly for agriculture, medical research, and other civilian purposes, but they were diverted for use in Saddam's weapons of mass destruction programs.</blockquote>
<p>If you do some searching on “Saddam CIA” on google, you find loads of interesting things:</p>
<blockquote>But Google also turns up stories infrequently if ever reported in the mainstream press about Saddam Hussein and the CIA -- as it turns out the Iraqi dictator and the now reviled Ba'ath Party were once favored CIA assets serving US interests. This is the sort of information you will not find splashed across the front page of the New York Times, let alone buried in section F16. In fact, most of this information appears primarily in papers such as the Hindustan Times or in books written by Arab authors. Since the story is at odds with the Bush version of reality, it's not front-page material in America.</blockquote>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Now that you know that the US installed Saddam in power, and provided him with WMD, is there anyone here who actually supports the “War on Terror?”</span></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/war-on-logic/32291/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/war-on-logic/32291/1</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2006 22:59:32 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-32291-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/war-on-logic/32291.rss">War on Logic</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
