<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Letter wrote for my friend&#39;s drug program</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/letter-wrote-for-my-friends-drug-program/172169</link>
    <description>Well, my friend has a drug program, called SWFAS (South West Florida Addiction Center) because he skipped school, and he got caught by his mom when she came home on her lunch (she usually didn&#39;t), and brought him back to school. At the time, he hadjust smoked two bowls of very potent crippy weed, so he was buzzing pretty well. The school resource officer wanted to talk to him when he got there, and knew right away we has high. He told his mom that he should take him home because he is so high my friend probably saw them all with three heads. My friend turned around and told the officer that he was dumb, and that he only smoked to bowls, and that he could see him just fine. The resource officer than suggested SWFAS for him.

Now he&#39;s accepted into SWFAS, which is a once a week hour meeting which the only way he can get in any kind of legal trouble is if he goes there with weed on him. Me and him are getting a kick out of what the program and he told me that he needs to write a letter to Marijuana as if it were a girlfriend that he has to break up with because he is moving away. He can&#39;t write for shit, and I knew right away I had to take it, so he&#39;s letting me.

Here&#39;s the letter, I based it off of a Kotton Mouth Kings song:
&lt;blockquote&gt;Dear Mary Jane,

     Mary Jane is who I&#39;m dreaming of, the one I adore and the one I love. my beautiful lady, your so so sweet, your forever lasting love that I always want to meet. My friends say that you gots a good vibe, and everytime they see you, you get them high. Your so so sly, your my flyest baby, the one and only Mary that drives me crazy. Now we feel so good, you can&#39;t deny, our spirit will never die, I never wanted to see the day that you go. Now when the night is done and most the people gone home, and we&#39;re by our friends, with them were never alone. Gather up in a circle and light up a fat cone, and if you hit it right, you&#39;ll be gettin&#39; stoned all night long. Favorite song, on the radio playin, and your family&#39;s all around if you know what I&#39;m saying, the feelings tight, with lots of smoke in the air, and your just being yourself because good times is true wealth. Now I&#39;ve been through it all, from the thick to the thin, I&#39;ve fought many battles, some I did not win. You take the good with the bad, play the cards that your dealt, and Mary&#39;s love helps ease all the pain I&#39;ve felt. So I dedicate this to her, may she one day be free, free to grow upon this earth, free to reproduce seeds, free so all my fellow brethren can breathe easily, and free so we can live in peace with unity. But until that day, I got to say goodbye, so may you live in peace and keep all my friends high.&lt;/blockquote&gt;</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 29 Jan 2008 19:19:49 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>General Discussion</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/letter-wrote-for-my-friends-drug-program/172169.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Letter wrote for my friend&#39;s drug program</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@ThatOneServer Mike_]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/thatoneserver">@ThatOneServer</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>OMFG BUZZY YOUR T3H 1337 S3x0rz0rz!!!</p>
<p>edit: WTF when the hell did i post this? I was probably… nvm.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/letter-wrote-for-my-friends-drug-program/172169/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/letter-wrote-for-my-friends-drug-program/172169/3</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jan 2008 19:19:49 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-172169-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/letter-wrote-for-my-friends-drug-program/172169.rss">Letter wrote for my friend&#39;s drug program</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Letter wrote for my friend&#39;s drug program</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Silver_Lining Silver Lining]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/silver_lining">@Silver_Lining</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Beautiful, but fix the usage of yohr in the possesive into the “you’re” form when appropriate. Also, from experience, I suggest you be very careful in the timing of humor when it comes to juvenile delinquent programs.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/letter-wrote-for-my-friends-drug-program/172169/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/letter-wrote-for-my-friends-drug-program/172169/2</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 10 Jan 2008 06:57:49 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-172169-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/letter-wrote-for-my-friends-drug-program/172169.rss">Letter wrote for my friend&#39;s drug program</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Letter wrote for my friend&#39;s drug program</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Buzzy Buzzy]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/buzzy">@Buzzy</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Well, my friend has a drug program, called SWFAS (South West Florida Addiction Center) because he skipped school, and he got caught by his mom when she came home on her lunch (she usually didn’t), and brought him back to school. At the time, he hadjust smoked two bowls of very potent crippy weed, so he was buzzing pretty well. The school resource officer wanted to talk to him when he got there, and knew right away we has high. He told his mom that he should take him home because he is so high my friend probably saw them all with three heads. My friend turned around and told the officer that he was dumb, and that he only smoked to bowls, and that he could see him just fine. The resource officer than suggested SWFAS for him.</p>
<p>Now he’s accepted into SWFAS, which is a once a week hour meeting which the only way he can get in any kind of legal trouble is if he goes there with weed on him. Me and him are getting a kick out of what the program and he told me that he needs to write a letter to Marijuana as if it were a girlfriend that he has to break up with because he is moving away. He can’t write for shit, and I knew right away I had to take it, so he’s letting me.</p>
<p>Here’s the letter, I based it off of a Kotton Mouth Kings song:</p>
<blockquote>Dear Mary Jane,
<pre><code> Mary Jane is who I'm dreaming of, the one I adore and the one I love. my beautiful lady, your so so sweet, your forever lasting love that I always want to meet. My friends say that you gots a good vibe, and everytime they see you, you get them high. Your so so sly, your my flyest baby, the one and only Mary that drives me crazy. Now we feel so good, you can't deny, our spirit will never die, I never wanted to see the day that you go. Now when the night is done and most the people gone home, and we're by our friends, with them were never alone. Gather up in a circle and light up a fat cone, and if you hit it right, you'll be gettin' stoned all night long. Favorite song, on the radio playin, and your family's all around if you know what I'm saying, the feelings tight, with lots of smoke in the air, and your just being yourself because good times is true wealth. Now I've been through it all, from the thick to the thin, I've fought many battles, some I did not win. You take the good with the bad, play the cards that your dealt, and Mary's love helps ease all the pain I've felt. So I dedicate this to her, may she one day be free, free to grow upon this earth, free to reproduce seeds, free so all my fellow brethren can breathe easily, and free so we can live in peace with unity. But until that day, I got to say goodbye, so may you live in peace and keep all my friends high.&lt;/blockquote&gt;</code></pre>
</blockquote>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/letter-wrote-for-my-friends-drug-program/172169/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/letter-wrote-for-my-friends-drug-program/172169/1</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 10 Jan 2008 00:32:38 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-172169-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/letter-wrote-for-my-friends-drug-program/172169.rss">Letter wrote for my friend&#39;s drug program</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
