<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>[Delta - 317] Attack NPC crashes client when in a special area? [317 - Delta]</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/delta-317-attack-npc-crashes-client-when-in-a-special-area-317-delta/350064</link>
    <description>[b][u]Hello, thank you for viewing my thread.[/u][/b]

As the title would sudjest I&#39;m using Delta source. I havn&#39;t had any combat problems before this. Anyways, I thought of a minigame where you would face a random &quot;boss&quot; monster and if you managed to defeat it you would be given a reward. I found that Fight Arena (the Khazard place) was the perfect location for this minigame. So I went there, removed the khazard that already were there, fixed the doors in the main building so they could be opened and closed. Next I added some basic Arena Guard NPC and placed a few inside the main building, just for looks.

I added an admin command that would start the minigame for me to test my minigame.
[code]if(command.equalsIgnoreCase(&quot;arena&quot;) &amp;&amp; (playerRights &gt;= 2)) {
killMyNPCs();
resetfollowers();
heightLevel = 0;
talk(&quot;Good look out there. Try not to die too fast.&quot;,1200);
toX = 2603;
toY = 3155;
FightOpp = misc.random(2) +1 ;
resetfollowers();
if(FightOpp == 0){
FightOppID = 1885;
sM(&quot;You will face Dad.&quot;);
}
if(FightOpp == 1){
FightOppID = 100;
sM(&quot;You will face Goblin Invader.&quot;);
}else if(FightOpp == 2){
FightOppID = 1540;
sM(&quot;You will face Teraz Lahyl.&quot;);
}
SpawnFightOpp(FightOppID);
sM(&quot;Enemy ID:&quot;+FightOppID);
}[/code]

NPC&#39;s spawned just fine (random NPC) but when I attacked a monster I was disconnected and my client displayed a T2 Error.
[b]Error message:[/b]
[URL=http://img840.imageshack.us/i/clienterrorlog.png/][IMG]http://img840.imageshack.us/img840/7179/clienterrorlog.png[/img][/URL]

Since T2 is a rather common error message I tried removing what I had added to the area. I removed all the Arena Guards I had placed, didn&#39;t help. I tried spawning loads of different NPC&#39;s to attack (not by ::npc ID, but by adding them to autospawn.cfg) but every time I attack any NPC at that area I get the error and I get disconnected.

Oh almost forgot, I know it&#39;s the area casuing this because when I try to attack the same NPC&#39;s at an other location (falador mine) it works perfectly fine.

I uploaded a video of me first fighting &quot;Goblin Invader&quot; and  &quot;Teraz Lahyl&quot; without any bugs in Falador Mine and then teleporting to Fight Arena and trying to attack the exact same NPC&#39;s but over there I get the error and disconnect.

[b]VIDEO LINK:[/b] http://tiny.cc/a9xwe

It should be mentioned that there already was some sort of an &quot;Assult&quot; minigame located at the Fight Arena where you would kill Khazard warriors to get points and then buy rune claws. But I removed these NPC&#39;s.

If you have any idea what is causing this or how to fix it, please help me... I wouldn&#39;t want to move my minigame because I feel that the Fight Arena is the perfect place for it.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 19 Jul 2010 18:41:59 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/delta-317-attack-npc-crashes-client-when-in-a-special-area-317-delta/350064.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>[Delta - 317] Attack NPC crashes client when in a special area? [317 - Delta]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Praktikanten Praktikanten]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/praktikanten">@Praktikanten</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p><span class="bbcode-b"><span class="bbcode-u">Hello, thank you for viewing my thread.</span></span></p>
<p>As the title would sudjest I’m using Delta source. I havn’t had any combat problems before this. Anyways, I thought of a minigame where you would face a random “boss” monster and if you managed to defeat it you would be given a reward. I found that Fight Arena (the Khazard place) was the perfect location for this minigame. So I went there, removed the khazard that already were there, fixed the doors in the main building so they could be opened and closed. Next I added some basic Arena Guard NPC and placed a few inside the main building, just for looks.</p>
<p>I added an admin command that would start the minigame for me to test my minigame.</p>
<p><code>if(command.equalsIgnoreCase("arena") &amp;&amp; (playerRights &gt;= 2)) {
killMyNPCs();
resetfollowers();
heightLevel = 0;
talk("Good look out there. Try not to die too fast.",1200);
toX = 2603;
toY = 3155;
FightOpp = misc.random(2) +1 ;
resetfollowers();
if(FightOpp == 0){
FightOppID = 1885;
sM("You will face Dad.");
}
if(FightOpp == 1){
FightOppID = 100;
sM("You will face Goblin Invader.");
}else if(FightOpp == 2){
FightOppID = 1540;
sM("You will face Teraz Lahyl.");
}
SpawnFightOpp(FightOppID);
sM("Enemy ID:"+FightOppID);
}</code></p>
<p>NPC’s spawned just fine (random NPC) but when I attacked a monster I was disconnected and my client displayed a T2 Error.<br>
<span class="bbcode-b">Error message:</span><br>
<a href="http://img840.imageshack.us/i/clienterrorlog.png/" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener"><img src="http://img840.imageshack.us/img840/7179/clienterrorlog.png" alt width="" height=""></a></p>
<p>Since T2 is a rather common error message I tried removing what I had added to the area. I removed all the Arena Guards I had placed, didn’t help. I tried spawning loads of different NPC’s to attack (not by ::npc ID, but by adding them to autospawn.cfg) but every time I attack any NPC at that area I get the error and I get disconnected.</p>
<p>Oh almost forgot, I know it’s the area casuing this because when I try to attack the same NPC’s at an other location (falador mine) it works perfectly fine.</p>
<p>I uploaded a video of me first fighting “Goblin Invader” and  “Teraz Lahyl” without any bugs in Falador Mine and then teleporting to Fight Arena and trying to attack the exact same NPC’s but over there I get the error and disconnect.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">VIDEO LINK:</span> <a href="http://tiny.cc/a9xwe" rel="nofollow noopener">http://tiny.cc/a9xwe</a></p>
<p>It should be mentioned that there already was some sort of an “Assult” minigame located at the Fight Arena where you would kill Khazard warriors to get points and then buy rune claws. But I removed these NPC’s.</p>
<p>If you have any idea what is causing this or how to fix it, please help me… I wouldn’t want to move my minigame because I feel that the Fight Arena is the perfect place for it.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/delta-317-attack-npc-crashes-client-when-in-a-special-area-317-delta/350064/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/delta-317-attack-npc-crashes-client-when-in-a-special-area-317-delta/350064/1</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jul 2010 18:41:59 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-350064-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/delta-317-attack-npc-crashes-client-when-in-a-special-area-317-delta/350064.rss">[Delta - 317] Attack NPC crashes client when in a special area? [317 - Delta]</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
