<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Wtf! javac?</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/wtf-javac/155839</link>
    <description>i was making my private server on a different computer,
but i am moving it to this one...
so.
when i was trying to compile i ran across the &quot;path&quot; error.

so i followed the Tut in the other section...
i looked in my java folders and there is no Javac file in ANY of them..

wtf do i do???  :eek:</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 01 Nov 2007 02:44:01 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/wtf-javac/155839.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Wtf! javac?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@owned654321241 owned654321241]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/owned654321241">@owned654321241</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>i know how to do all of that.</p>
<p>i have the new java downloaded and everything but…</p>
<p>the file “javac” is not in the “bin” folder…</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/wtf-javac/155839/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/wtf-javac/155839/4</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 01 Nov 2007 02:44:01 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-155839-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/wtf-javac/155839.rss">Wtf! javac?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Wtf! javac?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@arquillius arquillius]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/arquillius">@arquillius</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>this problem has been solved before…<br>
luckily back then i made a back up of the answer to use when i was alone, so i could work on my server in piece.</p>
<p>TUTORIAL BY BLIZZIND OF FAGEX, I TAKE NO CREDIT!</p>
<p>Getting these errors and not knowing how to fix them can drive you nuts, so follow this tutorial!</p>
<p>If you ever get this error, it means your java environment variables aren’t set. Environment variables are a set location of a folder, in this case it is the bin folder. Setting them will allow your computer to read and run programs in java.</p>
<p>Lets get started!</p>
<p>You will need the latest JDK and JRE (Java Develupment Kit and Java Run Time Environment). To get this, go to the link bellow:<br>
<a href="http://java.sun.com/javase/downloads/index.jsp" class="onebox" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">http://java.sun.com/javase/downloads/index.jsp</a></p>
<p>Once the page loads, it should bring you to a bunch of download links. You need to download the JDK 5.0 Update 7. If you cant find it, look at the photo:</p>
<p>After you find it and click download, it will bring you to an agreement pag. You need to accept the terms to download JDK.</p>
<p>Once you accept the terms, it will bring you to the download options page. If you are using Linux, this tutorial is meaningless to you. You need to look for this:</p>
<p>Now, after you click the selected link, a download link should appear. Give it a few minutes to download if you have slower internet and continue afterwords.</p>
<p>Good, now that you have JDK downloaded, lets install it. I’m not going to help you with the installation part because it should be self explainitory. Continue once you’ve successfully installed it and have restarted your computer.</p>
<p>Now we need to setup your environment variables. To do this you have two options:</p>
<p>Option 1:<br>
Go to Start and right click on My computer then select Proproties. A window with a bunch of tabs should have loaded. Choose the Advanced tab and click on the Environmant Variables button.</p>
<p>Option 2:<br>
Go to Start -&gt; Control Panel and click on the System icon (). A window with a bunch of tabs should have came up. Click on the Advanced tab then click on the Environment Variables button.</p>
<p>Now that we have the Environment Variable window open, lets set them. Look for a variable named Path in your list:</p>
<p>Then we put the Path to the Java’s Bin folder. If you didn’t change the folder and saved it into Program Files the folder would be: C:\Program Files\Java\JDK1.5.0_07\bin</p>
<p>Now, to set your Classpath. Click on New and for the name, enter:</p>
<p>Code:<br>
CLASSPATH<br>
For the Value enter in:<br>
YOU WILL NEED TO CHANGE THE VERSION; E.G jdk1.5.0_07.</p>
<p>Code:<br>
CLASSPATH=C:\Program Files\Java\jdk1.5.0_06\bin;%CLASSPATH%;<br>
Click Ok then get out of everything and you should be set! PM me if you have any problems.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/wtf-javac/155839/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/wtf-javac/155839/3</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 31 Oct 2007 22:16:06 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-155839-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/wtf-javac/155839.rss">Wtf! javac?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Wtf! javac?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@tobias222 tobias222]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/tobias222">@tobias222</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>inside your java folder, there is a bin folder  , inside the bin folder is javac</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/wtf-javac/155839/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/wtf-javac/155839/2</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 31 Oct 2007 19:41:46 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-155839-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/wtf-javac/155839.rss">Wtf! javac?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Wtf! javac?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@owned654321241 owned654321241]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/owned654321241">@owned654321241</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>i was making my private server on a different computer,<br>
but i am moving it to this one…<br>
so.<br>
when i was trying to compile i ran across the “path” error.</p>
<p>so i followed the Tut in the other section…<br>
i looked in my java folders and there is no Javac file in ANY of them…</p>
<p>wtf do i do???  :eek:</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/wtf-javac/155839/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/wtf-javac/155839/1</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 31 Oct 2007 17:40:08 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-155839-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/wtf-javac/155839.rss">Wtf! javac?</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
