<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Images</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/images/381134</link>
    <description>I&#39;m currently running a 508 Pali, i forget the exact source.

Excuse me if I am not very experienced with this, I&#39;ve never been good at editing images and sprites. And I&#39;m thinking this is server sided, but I&#39;m not 100% sure, so if this needs to be moved please say so.

In the source, some of the repeating messages use &lt;img=1&gt;, which shows the gold crown for Jagex Mods. I want to use my own custom crowns, but I don&#39;t know where to do that. I&#39;ve tried using a Sprite compiler and make image &quot;1&quot; my custom crown, but that doesn&#39;t work, so I&#39;m thinking it&#39;s server sided. I&#39;ve also tried uploading the custom crown image to a site and then using the url in place of &quot;1&quot;, that didn&#39;t work either. I can&#39;t even find where to declare what image 1 would be so I&#39;m in need of some help, thanks.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 04 Feb 2011 03:29:04 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/images/381134.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Images</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Mod_Hershey Mod Hershey]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/mod_hershey">@Mod_Hershey</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I’m currently running a 508 Pali, i forget the exact source.</p>
<p>Excuse me if I am not very experienced with this, I’ve never been good at editing images and sprites. And I’m thinking this is server sided, but I’m not 100% sure, so if this needs to be moved please say so.</p>
<p>In the source, some of the repeating messages use &lt;img=1&gt;, which shows the gold crown for Jagex Mods. I want to use my own custom crowns, but I don’t know where to do that. I’ve tried using a Sprite compiler and make image “1” my custom crown, but that doesn’t work, so I’m thinking it’s server sided. I’ve also tried uploading the custom crown image to a site and then using the url in place of “1”, that didn’t work either. I can’t even find where to declare what image 1 would be so I’m in need of some help, thanks.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/images/381134/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/images/381134/1</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 04 Feb 2011 03:29:04 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-381134-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/images/381134.rss">Images</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
