<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Delphi RS Client help</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/delphi-rs-client-help/159014</link>
    <description>ok so i&#39;m working on my own RS Client in Delphi, and i&#39;m using TWebBrowser, and it works fine, and i load it up, go into rs, and that works fine but as soon as i try to leave (quit program or change page) from the game page, my whole comp crashes (like someone pulled a plug, except quickly put it back in so it starts to boot again), I&#39;m guessing it has to do with the java, it&#39;ll load fine and i can play, its just as soon as i leave it the comp. goes... I&#39;ve tried using unsigned java to see if it helped any but it still crashes. It might just be my computer, i haven&#39;t had a chance to try it on another computer, and probably won&#39;t for a while

any help would be greatly appreciated</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 19 Nov 2007 02:33:58 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>General Programming</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/delphi-rs-client-help/159014.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Delphi RS Client help</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@deathbyvirus deathbyvirus]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/deathbyvirus">@deathbyvirus</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>ok so i’m working on my own RS Client in Delphi, and i’m using TWebBrowser, and it works fine, and i load it up, go into rs, and that works fine but as soon as i try to leave (quit program or change page) from the game page, my whole comp crashes (like someone pulled a plug, except quickly put it back in so it starts to boot again), I’m guessing it has to do with the java, it’ll load fine and i can play, its just as soon as i leave it the comp. goes… I’ve tried using unsigned java to see if it helped any but it still crashes. It might just be my computer, i haven’t had a chance to try it on another computer, and probably won’t for a while</p>
<p>any help would be greatly appreciated</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/delphi-rs-client-help/159014/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/delphi-rs-client-help/159014/1</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 19 Nov 2007 02:33:58 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-159014-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/delphi-rs-client-help/159014.rss">Delphi RS Client help</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
