<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>[JPN] Dangan Ronpa [PSP]</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/jpn-dangan-ronpa-psp/524078</link>
    <description>[center][img]http://images1.wikia.nocookie.net/__cb62214/danganronpa/images/thumb/b/b8/TZ7EgWK.jpg/670px-0%2C1920%2C0%2C1198-TZ7EgWK.jpg[/img][/center]

[b]Description:[/b] 
[hr]
Dangan Ronpa, or its full name Dangan Ronpa: Academy of Hope and High School Students of Despair (ダンガンロンパ 希望の学園と絶望の高校生) is a Japanese murder mystery visual novel developed by Spike exclusively for Japan. The game is available on PSP, iOS and Android OS devices. The game has a sequel called Super Dangan Ronpa 2: Farewell Despair Academy (スーパーダンガンロンパ2 さよなら絶望学園) and a light novel called Dangan Ronpa Zero. An anime has been announced which is to begin airing in Summer 2013. (The game-play is similar to the Ace Attorney series but with an emphasis on faster game-play. Each chapter of game-play takes place in three distinct stages: exposition, investigation, and school trial. In the exposition stage, the main plot progresses and the player can build relationships by spending time with the other characters, in a system similar to Social Links in the Shin Megami Tensei: Persona series. This section typically ends with the discovery of a crime scene, which leads to the investigation stage. Investigation parallels that found in the Ace Attorney series, as its basic purpose is to gather points of evidence to use in the school trial. The school trial stage includes several different minigames, all of which require high speed action and critical thinking to complete.) 

[b]Synopsis:[/b]
[hr]
The story takes place at Hope&#39;s Peak Academy, an illustrious private school that only accepts &quot;super&quot; students: the best of the best of the best. The criteria extends to any niche, so in addition to super-geniuses and super-athletes, they take super-idols, gang leaders, and geeks. Makoto Naegi, the protagonist, is still baffled as to how he got in, as his only outstanding trait seems to be his super &quot;good&quot; luck - and that&#39;s only because he was randomly chosen to be accepted by the school. In fact, he hasn&#39;t even started his first day of school when he suddenly loses consciousness and wakes up in a creepy alternate version of the academy.

It&#39;s soon revealed that Naegi and fourteen other new students have all been abducted by a sadistic teddy bear named Monobear, who refuses to let them leave. The only way out of the locked-down dark school is to graduate...by killing another student. Once a murder is committed, Monobear holds a trial so that the class can try to figure out which one of them is the culprit, culminating in a vote. If they make the right choice, the murderer will be messily executed. Make the wrong choice, and not only does the murderer escape, but the rest of them will take the punishment in their place... 

[b]Requirements:[/b] 
[hr]
Custom PSP Firmware, a copy of the game (legally or otherwise), and [url=http://danganronpa.wordpress.com/2013/06/23/release-danganronpa-english-translation-v1-0/]this English patch[/url]
[hr]





Possibly my favorite PSP game I&#39;ve played in a while, aside from other Japanese games. I recommend anyone with a PSP (or if they can get a PSP emulator to work with it) to play this. Be sure to save often.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 07 Jul 2013 06:41:50 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Games</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/jpn-dangan-ronpa-psp/524078.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>[JPN] Dangan Ronpa [PSP]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@LilXCj LilXCj]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/lilxcj">@LilXCj</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[center]<img src="http://images1.wikia.nocookie.net/__cb62214/danganronpa/images/thumb/b/b8/TZ7EgWK.jpg/670px-0%2C1920%2C0%2C1198-TZ7EgWK.jpg" alt width="" height="">[/center]</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Description:</span><br>
[hr]<br>
Dangan Ronpa, or its full name Dangan Ronpa: Academy of Hope and High School Students of Despair (ダンガンロンパ 希望の学園と絶望の高校生) is a Japanese murder mystery visual novel developed by Spike exclusively for Japan. The game is available on PSP, iOS and Android OS devices. The game has a sequel called Super Dangan Ronpa 2: Farewell Despair Academy (スーパーダンガンロンパ2 さよなら絶望学園) and a light novel called Dangan Ronpa Zero. An anime has been announced which is to begin airing in Summer 2013. (The game-play is similar to the Ace Attorney series but with an emphasis on faster game-play. Each chapter of game-play takes place in three distinct stages: exposition, investigation, and school trial. In the exposition stage, the main plot progresses and the player can build relationships by spending time with the other characters, in a system similar to Social Links in the Shin Megami Tensei: Persona series. This section typically ends with the discovery of a crime scene, which leads to the investigation stage. Investigation parallels that found in the Ace Attorney series, as its basic purpose is to gather points of evidence to use in the school trial. The school trial stage includes several different minigames, all of which require high speed action and critical thinking to complete.)</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Synopsis:</span><br>
[hr]<br>
The story takes place at Hope’s Peak Academy, an illustrious private school that only accepts “super” students: the best of the best of the best. The criteria extends to any niche, so in addition to super-geniuses and super-athletes, they take super-idols, gang leaders, and geeks. Makoto Naegi, the protagonist, is still baffled as to how he got in, as his only outstanding trait seems to be his super “good” luck - and that’s only because he was randomly chosen to be accepted by the school. In fact, he hasn’t even started his first day of school when he suddenly loses consciousness and wakes up in a creepy alternate version of the academy.</p>
<p>It’s soon revealed that Naegi and fourteen other new students have all been abducted by a sadistic teddy bear named Monobear, who refuses to let them leave. The only way out of the locked-down dark school is to graduate…by killing another student. Once a murder is committed, Monobear holds a trial so that the class can try to figure out which one of them is the culprit, culminating in a vote. If they make the right choice, the murderer will be messily executed. Make the wrong choice, and not only does the murderer escape, but the rest of them will take the punishment in their place…</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Requirements:</span><br>
[hr]<br>
Custom PSP Firmware, a copy of the game (legally or otherwise), and <a href="http://danganronpa.wordpress.com/2013/06/23/release-danganronpa-english-translation-v1-0/" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">this English patch</a><br>
[hr]</p>
<p>Possibly my favorite PSP game I’ve played in a while, aside from other Japanese games. I recommend anyone with a PSP (or if they can get a PSP emulator to work with it) to play this. Be sure to save often.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/jpn-dangan-ronpa-psp/524078/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/jpn-dangan-ronpa-psp/524078/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jul 2013 06:41:50 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-524078-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/jpn-dangan-ronpa-psp/524078.rss">[JPN] Dangan Ronpa [PSP]</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
