<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>[TUT] Overwritten Models? 317 [TUT]</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/tut-overwritten-models-317-tut/338982</link>
    <description>[center][url=http://www.deedscape.com][img]http://i891.photobucket.com/albums/ac118/Simpleee/DeedShad.png[/img][/url][/center]

[font=times new roman][center][size=20pt]Welcome to the Overwritten Model Guide.[/size][/center]

Now, Doing this Isn&#39;t difficult, but it might be different for other servers.

Overwritten models Wreck your whole client, And if you haven&#39;t made a backup, then this can be a real problem, so i made this tutorial to help people. When I had this problem, I really struggled, but thanks to some people i know.. i was able to fix the client after a few days. I am posting this for people who don&#39;t have anyone to help and for people who are amateur coders.  

So here is an example of an overwritten model.. In this case, its the Vengeance emote overwriting trees.

[img]http://i861.photobucket.com/albums/ab179/xxdemibabexx/Untitled.jpg[/img]

Now, First we need to get a new cache. &quot;Ohh noes!! I will loose all my models, and all my perfect Godsword specials!&quot;

You will mess up allot of your models, But they will be fixed later.

[Note: If your client is different to mine, I cant be sure what will happen, You are doing this at your own risk.. if it messes up your client more then don&#39;t blame me.. I&#39;m just showing you what i did to fix mine, i strongly suggest you backup your client before doing this anyway, because its easy to make a mistake.]

You can download the new cache Here (This is just a Blank 317 Cache): {LINK GOES HERE}

Now go In [b]Your client[/b] and Into the folder named &quot;Cache&quot; It should look a Little bit like this, but may be different  depending on what base you are using.

[img]http://i43.tinypic.com/jafcrb.png[/img]

Now, In [b]Your Client&#39;s[/b] cache there will be some folders and some files.

There should be 7 Files Named;

Main_File_Cache.dat
Main_File_Cach.icx4
Main_File_Cach.idx1
Main_File_Cach.idx2
Main_File_Cach.idx3
Main_File_Cach.idx4

Highlight them and delete them,

Now Extract the file you downloaded, and there should be a folder with 7 Files with the same names that you have just deleted out of your client;

Main_File_Cache.dat
Main_File_Cach.icx4
Main_File_Cach.idx1
Main_File_Cach.idx2
Main_File_Cach.idx3
Main_File_Cach.idx4

Don&#39;t worry, they should be the same.. There will be some small differences, like the size of the files. Now highlight all of the files in the folder that you have downloaded, and drag them into your cache. 

Once you have done that, find the code of the object that is overwriting, in my case.. it would be the Vengance model, because it is overwriting my trees.

The vengeance model ID in my client is 700. So I would look through my client, and find the file named &quot;700.dat&quot; or &quot;700.gz&quot;.

Now. Right click the file and click Rename. Now chose a number that isn&#39;t being used by any other models, For example, 1124.. This Number might be used in your client, but this is an example.

Now, Go back into your main files, and look for Class23.Java, Then you want to search (CRTL+F) for the model ID that you changed your name from.. (In my case.. 700), once you have found it, Delete it and change it to the number you replaced the overwritten object with (In my case.. 1124) Now Compile and Run Your client. 

[b][Note, If your Screen goes black whilst loading your client, with an error message, or Gets stuck loading the Models. Then You should discontinue with this tutorial and restore your files to their original state, but if your client has loaded, working well.. then you can carry on.][/b]

Now. Login on an Owner permission Account, and Try typing one of the following commands/Say this.

&quot;::addmodels&quot;
&quot;add models&quot; [I had problems understanding this, but you just normally type (without ::) &quot;add models&quot; (With a space in between &quot;add&quot; and &quot;models&quot;]

They are the only ones I know, but there should be a command for adding models, If you can&#39;t find one.. then You will have to make one, but I&#39;m not going through that in this Tutorial.

If one of those sayings/commands worked, then It should Spam &quot;Model added successfully&quot;, and then you should lose connection. Now the objects may still looked messed up, but all you need to do is.. log out, and then close your client, and reload it. Login, and You will keep your models, and your Overwritten model should be fixed!

[img]http://i39.tinypic.com/2w5q6px.png[/img]

If it hasn&#39;t fixed, then post saying what happened, and what your circumstance is, and i might be able to help you more.. But, as i said above, I strongly recommend backing up your client before trying to do this.

I hope this helped.. If you used this tutorial, and it helped you fix the problem, Please Rep me?

If you need anymore help Post below or Contact me on: Staff@deedscape.com [Email only]

Note: I can&#39;t do it for everyone, I may be able to correct a few small errors, but if this doesn&#39;t work for you, its probably because you have the wrong type of client for the cache you download.. maybe look for a new clean cache.

I hope this helped you solve this annoying problem.

Regards, Ed.

[b]DeedScape Owner[/b]</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 03 May 2010 20:57:47 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/tut-overwritten-models-317-tut/338982.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>[TUT] Overwritten Models? 317 [TUT]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@dragion dragion]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/dragion">@dragion</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>nice!!!<br>
First post w00t <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=5" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/tut-overwritten-models-317-tut/338982/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/tut-overwritten-models-317-tut/338982/2</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 03 May 2010 20:57:47 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-338982-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/tut-overwritten-models-317-tut/338982.rss">[TUT] Overwritten Models? 317 [TUT]</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[TUT] Overwritten Models? 317 [TUT]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@DeedScape DeedScape]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/deedscape">@DeedScape</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[center]<a href="http://www.deedscape.com" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener"><img src="http://i891.photobucket.com/albums/ac118/Simpleee/DeedShad.png" alt width="400" height="70"></a>[/center]</p>
<p>[font=times new roman][center][size=20pt]Welcome to the Overwritten Model Guide.[/size][/center]</p>
<p>Now, Doing this Isn’t difficult, but it might be different for other servers.</p>
<p>Overwritten models Wreck your whole client, And if you haven’t made a backup, then this can be a real problem, so i made this tutorial to help people. When I had this problem, I really struggled, but thanks to some people i know… i was able to fix the client after a few days. I am posting this for people who don’t have anyone to help and for people who are amateur coders.</p>
<p>So here is an example of an overwritten model… In this case, its the Vengeance emote overwriting trees.</p>
<p><img src="http://i861.photobucket.com/albums/ab179/xxdemibabexx/Untitled.jpg" alt width="138" height="228"></p>
<p>Now, First we need to get a new cache. “Ohh noes!! I will loose all my models, and all my perfect Godsword specials!”</p>
<p>You will mess up allot of your models, But they will be fixed later.</p>
<p>[Note: If your client is different to mine, I cant be sure what will happen, You are doing this at your own risk… if it messes up your client more then don’t blame me… I’m just showing you what i did to fix mine, i strongly suggest you backup your client before doing this anyway, because its easy to make a mistake.]</p>
<p>You can download the new cache Here (This is just a Blank 317 Cache): {LINK GOES HERE}</p>
<p>Now go In <span class="bbcode-b">Your client</span> and Into the folder named “Cache” It should look a Little bit like this, but may be different  depending on what base you are using.</p>
<p><img src="http://i43.tinypic.com/jafcrb.png" alt width="611" height="422"></p>
<p>Now, In <span class="bbcode-b">Your Client’s</span> cache there will be some folders and some files.</p>
<p>There should be 7 Files Named;</p>
<p>Main_File_Cache.dat<br>
Main_File_Cach.icx4<br>
Main_File_Cach.idx1<br>
Main_File_Cach.idx2<br>
Main_File_Cach.idx3<br>
Main_File_Cach.idx4</p>
<p>Highlight them and delete them,</p>
<p>Now Extract the file you downloaded, and there should be a folder with 7 Files with the same names that you have just deleted out of your client;</p>
<p>Main_File_Cache.dat<br>
Main_File_Cach.icx4<br>
Main_File_Cach.idx1<br>
Main_File_Cach.idx2<br>
Main_File_Cach.idx3<br>
Main_File_Cach.idx4</p>
<p>Don’t worry, they should be the same… There will be some small differences, like the size of the files. Now highlight all of the files in the folder that you have downloaded, and drag them into your cache.</p>
<p>Once you have done that, find the code of the object that is overwriting, in my case… it would be the Vengance model, because it is overwriting my trees.</p>
<p>The vengeance model ID in my client is 700. So I would look through my client, and find the file named “700.dat” or “700.gz”.</p>
<p>Now. Right click the file and click Rename. Now chose a number that isn’t being used by any other models, For example, 1124… This Number might be used in your client, but this is an example.</p>
<p>Now, Go back into your main files, and look for Class23.Java, Then you want to search (CRTL+F) for the model ID that you changed your name from… (In my case… 700), once you have found it, Delete it and change it to the number you replaced the overwritten object with (In my case… 1124) Now Compile and Run Your client.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">[Note, If your Screen goes black whilst loading your client, with an error message, or Gets stuck loading the Models. Then You should discontinue with this tutorial and restore your files to their original state, but if your client has loaded, working well… then you can carry on.]</span></p>
<p>Now. Login on an Owner permission Account, and Try typing one of the following commands/Say this.</p>
<p>“::addmodels”<br>
“add models” [I had problems understanding this, but you just normally type (without :<img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=5" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"> “add models” (With a space in between “add” and “models”]</p>
<p>They are the only ones I know, but there should be a command for adding models, If you can’t find one… then You will have to make one, but I’m not going through that in this Tutorial.</p>
<p>If one of those sayings/commands worked, then It should Spam “Model added successfully”, and then you should lose connection. Now the objects may still looked messed up, but all you need to do is… log out, and then close your client, and reload it. Login, and You will keep your models, and your Overwritten model should be fixed!</p>
<p><img src="http://i39.tinypic.com/2w5q6px.png" alt width="493" height="323"></p>
<p>If it hasn’t fixed, then post saying what happened, and what your circumstance is, and i might be able to help you more… But, as i said above, I strongly recommend backing up your client before trying to do this.</p>
<p>I hope this helped… If you used this tutorial, and it helped you fix the problem, Please Rep me?</p>
<p>If you need anymore help Post below or Contact me on: <a href="mailto:Staff@deedscape.com">Staff@deedscape.com</a> [Email only]</p>
<p>Note: I can’t do it for everyone, I may be able to correct a few small errors, but if this doesn’t work for you, its probably because you have the wrong type of client for the cache you download… maybe look for a new clean cache.</p>
<p>I hope this helped you solve this annoying problem.</p>
<p>Regards, Ed.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">DeedScape Owner</span></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/tut-overwritten-models-317-tut/338982/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/tut-overwritten-models-317-tut/338982/1</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 03 May 2010 16:45:17 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-338982-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/tut-overwritten-models-317-tut/338982.rss">[TUT] Overwritten Models? 317 [TUT]</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
