<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Problem with Source</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/problem-with-source/407565</link>
    <description>I get this when i try and start up my server and i also downloaded apache ant.
[code]&#39;ant&#39; is not recognized as an internal or external command,
operable program or batch file.
Press any key to continue . . .[/code]
Also can someone make me a run client.bat file for my client cause it does not seem to have one.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 01 Aug 2011 00:56:36 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/problem-with-source/407565.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Problem with Source</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Not_a_bot Not_a_bot]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/not_a_bot">@Not_a_bot</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Where to start…</p>
<p>Well based on the error code presented, the main ‘ant’ has escaped your computer. What does this mean? It could be a number of things:</p>
<ol>
<li>Your anti-virus program has detected it as an insect/bacteria-like entity (like virus), and has quarantined it.</li>
<li>Windows by default, has sprayed your system with RAID to protect against mass infection, thus killing this ‘ant’ from mass invasion of your file system.</li>
<li>You fucked up paths and disregarded simple instructions given in the installion manual.</li>
</ol>
<p>You may try contacting your software provider for assistance, or your local repair shop for help. The good news is, there are alternatives to executing the source code, typically by compiling it and executing it through Java’s VM. Now you might ask, well why would I do try such a thing? If you already didn’t know, the high-level language used to write the code is written in Java. Luckily, the developers have allowed us a way to compile this code into what’s called “bytecode” which can be interpreted to machine code (low-level) at runtime.</p>
<p>Now, you depending on what operating system you’re using, you can utilize native tool(s) to create files locally. By doing this, you may want to consult your system administrator or your common sense to accomplish this. From there, you can write a small “shell” script (also known as batch in Windows) to do what otherwise is considered tedious to write out time and time again, which in your case would be sent to Java’s VM for execution. From there, you can feel content you’ve done what most find near impossible to do. <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=5" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/problem-with-source/407565/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/problem-with-source/407565/2</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 01 Aug 2011 00:56:36 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-407565-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/problem-with-source/407565.rss">Problem with Source</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Problem with Source</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@FoCuSeD_KiNeTiKz FoCuSeD_KiNeTiKz]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/focused_kinetikz">@FoCuSeD_KiNeTiKz</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I get this when i try and start up my server and i also downloaded apache ant.</p>
<p><code>'ant' is not recognized as an internal or external command,
operable program or batch file.
Press any key to continue . . .</code><br>
Also can someone make me a run client.bat file for my client cause it does not seem to have one.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/problem-with-source/407565/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/problem-with-source/407565/1</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 01 Aug 2011 00:39:33 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-407565-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/problem-with-source/407565.rss">Problem with Source</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
