<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>!Error Connection to Server</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/error-connection-to-server/515820</link>
    <description>Hey guys, new here...

Alright, so I&#39;ve worked on private servers WITH other people a few times in the past, and I&#39;ve gotten pretty decent at the coding part.. (ik what i&#39;m about to say is coding..) Well anyway it seems that each time the person I was helping would just kick me off as soon as I finished the project and claim it as their own  :confused: :confused: .

So I made my own, and it&#39;s actually really really nice, JUST the way I want it to be.  But, I&#39;ve NEVER portforwarded (They always did that).. I tried that last night and well, ended up changing a few things I probably shouldn&#39;t have :p .   Now I&#39;m getting an &quot;Error Connecting to Server&quot; from my own client even though my server is online.


I also would like to use a different client, the one I have isn&#39;t exactly the greatest... So basically my question is: [b]How do I connect a new client to my own server?[/b]</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2013 09:14:13 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Game Development</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/error-connection-to-server/515820.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>!Error Connection to Server</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Anaujiram Anaujiram]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/anaujiram">@Anaujiram</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Hey guys, new here…</p>
<p>Alright, so I’ve worked on private servers WITH other people a few times in the past, and I’ve gotten pretty decent at the coding part… (ik what i’m about to say is coding…) Well anyway it seems that each time the person I was helping would just kick me off as soon as I finished the project and claim it as their own  <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/confused.png?v=5" title=":confused:" class="emoji" alt=":confused:"> <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/confused.png?v=5" title=":confused:" class="emoji" alt=":confused:"> .</p>
<p>So I made my own, and it’s actually really really nice, JUST the way I want it to be.  But, I’ve NEVER portforwarded (They always did that)… I tried that last night and well, ended up changing a few things I probably shouldn’t have <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=5" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"> .   Now I’m getting an “Error Connecting to Server” from my own client even though my server is online.</p>
<p>I also would like to use a different client, the one I have isn’t exactly the greatest… So basically my question is: <span class="bbcode-b">How do I connect a new client to my own server?</span></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/error-connection-to-server/515820/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/error-connection-to-server/515820/1</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2013 09:14:13 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-515820-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/error-connection-to-server/515820.rss">!Error Connection to Server</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
