<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Need a Very good Server Side Coder to code this one code!</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/need-a-very-good-server-side-coder-to-code-this-one-code/228848</link>
    <description>Hello Coders.  I need your help.  I&#39;m new to coding and I&#39;m actually doing pretty good.

Anyways, lets get to my problem.  I need to make it so:

[b]Players can only log in every 20 seconds, so let&#39;s say 10 players are trying to log in..this would mean each player would have to wait 20 seconds between each login.  This makes it that; players can&#39;t just all login at once, they must wait 20 seconds between each log in.[/b]

Get what I mean?

So could anyone help?  :|  I would appreciate the help a lot.

Thank you for taking the time to read my thread.

[i]PS: I will be checking this thread out every minute or so.[/i]  ;D

[font=Verdana]Edit:  TonyPker&#39;s Question + Answered[/font][quote=&quot;tonypker13, post:2, topic:228555&quot;]Well, Ive actually never heard of login Timers.. Ive been working on this same thing for my server.May I ask why you need this?[/quote]

Sure you may ask why; I&#39;ve noticed a huge glitch.  I&#39;ve seen players &quot;Multilogin&quot; on the SAME character.  This means this person hooks up with a friend, over the phone for example, and says; &quot;Login at the same time as me (Same Character name/Pass) And they both hit &quot;Login&quot; At the same time.  Then they both succesfully login on one character on both computers.  Then they can just trade the items with the same characters creating duped items.

Basically, to narrow it down, if the same player logs in on two computers at the excact same time (Also the same username/Pass), they both actually log in.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 30 Aug 2008 19:27:29 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/need-a-very-good-server-side-coder-to-code-this-one-code/228848.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Need a Very good Server Side Coder to code this one code!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@parkview parkview]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/parkview">@parkview</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Hello Coders.  I need your help.  I’m new to coding and I’m actually doing pretty good.</p>
<p>Anyways, lets get to my problem.  I need to make it so:</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Players can only log in every 20 seconds, so let’s say 10 players are trying to log in…this would mean each player would have to wait 20 seconds between each login.  This makes it that; players can’t just all login at once, they must wait 20 seconds between each log in.</span></p>
<p>Get what I mean?</p>
<p>So could anyone help?  <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/expressionless.png?v=6" title=":expressionless:" class="emoji" alt=":expressionless:">  I would appreciate the help a lot.</p>
<p>Thank you for taking the time to read my thread.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-i">PS: I will be checking this thread out every minute or so.</span>  ;D</p>
<p>[font=Verdana]Edit:  TonyPker’s Question + Answered[/font][quote=“tonypker13, post:2, topic:228555”]Well, Ive actually never heard of login Timers… Ive been working on this same thing for my server.May I ask why you need this?[/quote]</p>
<p>Sure you may ask why; I’ve noticed a huge glitch.  I’ve seen players “Multilogin” on the SAME character.  This means this person hooks up with a friend, over the phone for example, and says; "Login at the same time as me (Same Character name/Pass) And they both hit “Login” At the same time.  Then they both succesfully login on one character on both computers.  Then they can just trade the items with the same characters creating duped items.</p>
<p>Basically, to narrow it down, if the same player logs in on two computers at the excact same time (Also the same username/Pass), they both actually log in.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/need-a-very-good-server-side-coder-to-code-this-one-code/228848/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/need-a-very-good-server-side-coder-to-code-this-one-code/228848/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 30 Aug 2008 19:27:29 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-228848-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/need-a-very-good-server-side-coder-to-code-this-one-code/228848.rss">Need a Very good Server Side Coder to code this one code!</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
