<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Changing combat to 138 and clanchat</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/changing-combat-to-138-and-clanchat/318454</link>
    <description>OK first off, I&#39;m new and I&#39;ve searched google forever until i&#39;ve come upon this site. I&#39;ve read many post using the all mighty &quot;search&quot; feature for my answer, sadly it didn&#39;t give me any relevant results. That search is completely irrelevant no matter how you use it. I do remember at one point it brought me to a post that had my same problem but had no replies to it.

[b]My problem: [/b]
I&#39;m completely new to coding with java and I have a 508 base with all working skills on it. When you get 99 on all combat skills your combat level stops at 126 when supposedly it should be 138. How do I fix this? I do not want anyone to spoon feed me but to explain this to me somehow, as it is my first time to this.

I also want to know how to add a clan chat with working ranks, I have an already coded clanchat.java and room.java that includes working ranks and cc interfaces. But I don&#39;t know how to add this in and how each function relatively works. I already clarified that I searched tutorials on this and I received irrelevant results. 

All help appreciated![br][br][size=1]Posted on: December 08, 2009, 08:59:53 pm[/size][hr]wow...anyone wanna even bother helping :)</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 09 Dec 2009 00:38:32 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/changing-combat-to-138-and-clanchat/318454.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Changing combat to 138 and clanchat</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Originally_posted_by Originally posted byWaldo]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/originally_posted_by">@Originally_posted_by</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>OK first off, I’m new and I’ve searched google forever until i’ve come upon this site. I’ve read many post using the all mighty “search” feature for my answer, sadly it didn’t give me any relevant results. That search is completely irrelevant no matter how you use it. I do remember at one point it brought me to a post that had my same problem but had no replies to it.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">My problem: </span><br>
I’m completely new to coding with java and I have a 508 base with all working skills on it. When you get 99 on all combat skills your combat level stops at 126 when supposedly it should be 138. How do I fix this? I do not want anyone to spoon feed me but to explain this to me somehow, as it is my first time to this.</p>
<p>I also want to know how to add a clan chat with working ranks, I have an already coded clanchat.java and room.java that includes working ranks and cc interfaces. But I don’t know how to add this in and how each function relatively works. I already clarified that I searched tutorials on this and I received irrelevant results.</p>
<p>All help appreciated![br][br][size=1]Posted on: December 08, 2009, 08:59:53 pm[/size][hr]wow…anyone wanna even bother helping <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=5" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/changing-combat-to-138-and-clanchat/318454/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/changing-combat-to-138-and-clanchat/318454/1</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 09 Dec 2009 00:38:32 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-318454-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/changing-combat-to-138-and-clanchat/318454.rss">Changing combat to 138 and clanchat</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
