<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>List Of Pranks :D!</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/list-of-pranks-d/15500</link>
    <description>[center][u][b]List Of Pranks and Prank Ideas :D !!![/b][/u][/center]
[center][glow=red,2,300]I take no responsibility for what you use this for[/glow][/center]
[center][u][b]Computer Pranks[/b][/u][/center]

[ul][li] When someone leaves their computer, go into Microsoft Word and make an Auto-Correct option to Change the word &quot;the&quot; into the word &quot;SEX&quot;
[/li]
[li]Wait for someone to walk away from their PC. Click Start -&gt; Settings -&gt; Control Panel -&gt; Mouse. Select the &quot;Pointers&quot; tab and change the first cursor (Normal Select) from an arrow to the same thing they use for the &quot;Busy&quot; cursor. See how long they will stare at their screen waiting for the computer to finish what it&#39;s doing.
[/li]
[li]A more elaborate Word prank is to use the &quot;AutoCorrect&quot; feature to turn everyday words into wacky variations. In Word 2002, go to Tools &gt; AutoCorrect Options. Make sure &quot;Replace text as you type&quot; is checked. In the box below, you can add new words. You want to use common words, but not too common. Here are some suggestions:

    dear:rear
    thanks:yanks
    sincerely:sinqueerly
    test:testicle
    hello:yo yo yo (or &quot;what up&quot;)
    person&#39;s name:Batman (or Wonder Woman)

This prank also works with Microsoft Excel.
[/li]
[li]Pry open the keyboard of a someone you know who can take a joke, and remove the rubber punching pad. The computer will still see the keyboard, but nothing will happen when your prankee punches the keys.
[/li]
[li]Go to the Windows Control Panel and double-click &quot;Mouse.&quot; Switch the right mouse button so that it&#39;s activated by the left mouse button, and vice-versa. For even more fun, make the mouse go as slowly as you can, then laugh as it takes them forever to switch it back.
[/li]
[li]Take a screenshot of someones desktop, make that their wallpaper, then hide all of their icons and the taskbar. When they start up their computer the next day, they will click and click on everything, to no avail. :D
[/li]
[li]First, do a web search for &quot;Windows shutdown utility.&quot; Download it to someones PC when they are away. It puts an icon on the desktop that you just double-click to shut down the PC. Then change the icon to something like Internet Explorer, or some other commonly-used program. It&#39;s funny to watch them constantly shutting down their PC and not knowing why.
[/li]
[li]Go to the Windows Control Panel and double-click &quot;Mouse.&quot; Switch the right mouse button so that it&#39;s activated by the left mouse button, and vice-versa. For even more fun, make the mouse go as slowly as you can, then laugh as it takes them forever to switch it back.
[/li][/ul]

[center][u][b]Office Pranks[/b][/u][/center]

[ul][li]Take a paperclip and make a a few dozen photocopies of it. Mix them up with normal, unused paper. Watch people go crazy trying to find the paperclip that&#39;s stuck in the photocopier.
[/li]
[li]This prank will require a few accomplices. Pick the most gullible and hopefully vocal person in your office. Bring in some home automation electronics (you can get these off the Web, or at your local Radio Shack), and wire up the victim&#39;s office. We wired up my co-worker&#39;s office so that I could turn her oscillating fan and her giant desk calculator on or off from anywhere in the building using a remote control. Accomplice #1 is a disbeliever. Every time accomplice #1 leaves the victim&#39;s office, things start turning on and off, but never when the accomplice is in the office. Accomplice #2 is a believer. When the victim admits stranges things have been happening, #2 will tell the victim that he/she has noticed strange things in his/her office too. Accomplice #3 is hopefully the victim&#39;s boss. Anytime accomplice #3 hears the victim talking about strange things happening, or sees accomplices 1 or 2 in the victim&#39;s office, he/she tells them to quit talking about this nonsense and get back to work, getting angrier each time. See how long this will work for you. ;)
[/li]
[li]Icy Hot on the toilet seats. ;D
[/li]
[li]This is a classic prank that works best in an office setting. All you need to do is go to your local grocery store, and buy a LARGE amount of gelatin (not Jell-O, just clear disgusting-tasting gelatin). Go to your bathroom at work -- this works best with the men&#39;s urinal/stall combo bathroom -- and put it in the toilets. You&#39;ll need to use 3-4 &quot;servings&quot; per toilet, but this is still quite inexpensive. Within minutes, the water in the toilets will have congealed into a CLEAR, yet hard substance. Now, when someone goes into a stall (which means, of course, that they have to expel solid waste), their feces will fall out, bounce up, then remain SITTING on top of the toilet &quot;water,&quot; stinking like hell! This does no permanent damage -- all you have to do is scoop about 1/2 of the congealed water out, then flush, and it&#39;s gone.
[/li]
[li]Take a picture of a beloved personal item on your coworker&#39;s desk (stuffed animal, small plant, trinket, etc.) Then kidnap the item and leave the picture in its place with a fake ransom letter.
[/li]
[li]First, take the little pieces of paper out of all the hole punchers in the office. Sneak into one of your workmates&#39; cars and tip all the little pieces of paper into the air vents. Point them upwards, and set the fan to full power. When they get into the car and start the engine, the paper should come at them like a blizzard! Classic.
[/li]
[li]
Put confetti in a co-worker&#39;s umbrella. Simple, harmless, annoying.
[/li]
[li]Bake cookies for everyone. Divide the dough. For one batch, bake normally. For the second, add cayenne pepper, Tabasco sauce, peppercorns, etc.
[/li]
[li]Find a box about the size of a cake. Then cover it with frosting, making it look like a cake. Then put it out in the office kitchen, or wherever people leave free food. Sit back as one of your co-workers tries to cut a slice.
[/li]
[li]Find a &quot;zip tie&quot; (also known as a &quot;cable tie&quot;) that&#39;s similar in color to your co-worker&#39;s phone cord. Place around both ends of the cord, as close to the handset as possible. This will shorten the cord to about an inch. Clip the end of the zip tie so it&#39;s not sticking out suspiciously. Wait until your co-worker tries to answer the phone.
[/li][/ul]

[center][u][b]College Pranks[/b][/u][/center]

[ul][li]You know those Christmas cards that play jingles when you open them? You can remove the music chip from cards and affix it to the insides of door hinges. Every time someone opens the door, the jingle plays -- over and over. Also works well on the bottom hinge of a dark closet. Can take months to discover -- or run out of power.
[/li]
[li]Fill a very large manilla envelope with shaving cream, slide the mouth of the envelope under the door, and stomp on it. The shock of it is splendid!
[/li]
[li]Get a tube of glue, and a bag full of those googly craft eyes from Wal-Mart. Glue pairs of them to anything: toilet seats, computer monitors, doorknobs, peoples&#39; dishes ... then hide somewhere and watch for their reactions.
[/li]
[li]This prank requires a group of people to help you out, along with a LOT of aluminum cans and some ribbon.
Step 1: Collect an assload of empty aluminum cans. (Just don&#39;t recycle for a few months.)
Step 2: Take all the empty cans and ribbon to a different residence building on campus, a rival college, the President&#39;s house, etc., when everyone will be asleep.
Step 3: Put a very long strip of ribbon on the floor, and put a row of cans on top of the ribbon. Then put another ribbon on top of the cans, and put another row of cans on top of that. Continue this until you have a huge stack of cans. Make sure to leave enough extra ribbon hanging out as a &quot;starter.&quot; You might also want to stack the cans along a wall so that they don&#39;t fall over while you&#39;re stacking them.
Step 4: When stacking is complete, grab the extra ribbon that&#39;s between all the cans, give it a huge pull and run. If all is successful, you will wake up everyone in the building, as well as neighboring counties.
[/li]
[li]Gather up a small stack of paper, some tape, and a couple hundred aluminum cans. Start layering the cans against your victim&#39;s door. Tape the paper to the doorframe as you go up, to keep the cans in place. When the cans are all the way up, remove the paper gently. As soon as the victim opens his door the next morning, the suction will send 400+ cans crashing down on him.
[/li]
[li]Obtain nine of the same type of animal (pigs, chickens, any animal that you can get your hands on). Then paint on their backs the numbers 1-10, but skip a number like 5 or something. Turn the animals loose in your dorm or student union building. Once they find all the other animals, they&#39;ll be looking for the &quot;missing&quot; animal forever
[/li]
[li]Get a packet of instant milk and put it in someone&#39;s bed on a particulary hot night. In their sleep, they will sweat, and in the morning the milk will have mutated into SOUR STINKY MILK! They will stink for a week.
[/li]
[li]Hot sauce on the toothbrush. Only works if you use something strong like Dave&#39;s Insanity
[/li]
[li]For revenge on a vehicle: first, use shoe polish to write creative sayings on the windows, then re-write the sayings on the inside of the windows and watch them try to wash it off. Next: put confetti in the A/C vents and turn the blowers on high. Finally, fill the entire vehicle with packing peanuts. Make sure you have a camera, and an escape route!
[/li]
[li]When someone&#39;s sick, cut up several large clear plastic bags and then tape them together in order to create a large sheet of plastic. Then at 4 in the morning, tape the sheet of plastic to the person&#39;s doorframe with duct tape and then tape a big sign that says QUARANTINED.
[/li]
[li]If your doors open inward, tie one doorknobs to another one with rope. Bang on both doors and watch the hilarity.
[/li]
[li]You can easily remove peepholes from doors (not just reverse them), and then use a super-soaker water gun to awaken your friend.
[/li]
[li]When one of your guy friends is in the room with a girl, find a cheap, disgusting porno off of e-Bay and throw it at him. Proceed to tell him that you were returning &quot;Ass-Blasters 2000&quot; or whatever the title may be.
[/li]
[li]Go to the dollar store and get a bunch of those cheap travel alarm clocks, set them to go off every half hour in the night, and then hide them throughout the room. Drives them nuts!
[/li]
[li]Draw a chalk outline of someone&#39;s body on a driveway or sidewalk, and surround it with caution tape. This is legal, as long as you do not use official police caution tape
[/li]
[li]Find the toilet of your victim, then empty the water basin, and replace the water with vinegar. Add baking powder into the toilet&#39;s water reservoir (the part that contains the water that is flushed in after you do your thing). When the victim flushes, the baking soda and vinegar will mix and expand, overflowing the place with their feces.
[/li][/ul]


[center][u][b]Sources[/b][/u][/center]

[ul][li]http://www.zug.com/pranks/ideas/college.html [/li]
[li]http://www.zug.com/pranks/ideas/office.html [/li]
[li]http://www.zug.com/pranks/ideas/computer.html [/li][/ul]</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 27 Aug 2007 12:52:22 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>General Discussion</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/list-of-pranks-d/15500.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>List Of Pranks :D!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@MastrChief MastrChief]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/mastrchief">@MastrChief</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>All of these seem like “pranks” little kids put together <span class="bbcode-i">and</span> aren’t funny at all.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/list-of-pranks-d/15500/13">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/list-of-pranks-d/15500/13</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 27 Aug 2007 12:52:22 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-15500-13</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/list-of-pranks-d/15500.rss">List Of Pranks :D!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>List Of Pranks :D!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Yz85Racer Yz85Racer]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/yz85racer">@Yz85Racer</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“goatee, post:9, topic:15500”][quote author=blablaman link=topic=23113.msg1704018#msg1704018 date=1188152736]<br>
what about this<br>
at ur office when nobody is using it sit on photocopier  make sure nobody is there and then  make picture of ur ass but make sure the photo copier is facin at the door then it will shoot out at people then wtf!!!<br>
[/quote]</p>
<p>That’s original isn’t it![/quote]<br>
And just grave dug.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/list-of-pranks-d/15500/12">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/list-of-pranks-d/15500/12</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 27 Aug 2007 12:37:36 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-15500-12</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/list-of-pranks-d/15500.rss">List Of Pranks :D!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>List Of Pranks :D!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@wazup2 wazup2]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/wazup2">@wazup2</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>this looks like it has been copyd and pasted…</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/list-of-pranks-d/15500/11">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/list-of-pranks-d/15500/11</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 27 Aug 2007 11:24:07 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-15500-11</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/list-of-pranks-d/15500.rss">List Of Pranks :D!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>List Of Pranks :D!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@nicatron nicatron]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/nicatron">@nicatron</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>rofl, lol, and many more are what i experienced as i read these dang!!!</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/list-of-pranks-d/15500/10">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/list-of-pranks-d/15500/10</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 26 Aug 2007 19:01:41 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-15500-10</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/list-of-pranks-d/15500.rss">List Of Pranks :D!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>List Of Pranks :D!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@goatee goatee]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/goatee">@goatee</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“blablaman, post:8, topic:15500”]what about this<br>
at ur office when nobody is using it sit on photocopier  make sure nobody is there and then  make picture of ur ass but make sure the photo copier is facin at the door then it will shoot out at people then wtf!!![/quote]</p>
<p>That’s original isn’t it!</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/list-of-pranks-d/15500/9">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/list-of-pranks-d/15500/9</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 26 Aug 2007 18:57:51 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-15500-9</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/list-of-pranks-d/15500.rss">List Of Pranks :D!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>List Of Pranks :D!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@blablaman blablaman]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/blablaman">@blablaman</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>what about this<br>
at ur office when nobody is using it sit on photocopier  make sure nobody is there and then  make picture of ur ass but make sure the photo copier is facin at the door then it will shoot out at people then wtf!!!</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/list-of-pranks-d/15500/8">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/list-of-pranks-d/15500/8</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 26 Aug 2007 18:25:36 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-15500-8</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/list-of-pranks-d/15500.rss">List Of Pranks :D!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>List Of Pranks :D!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@blacker blacker]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/blacker">@blacker</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>HILARIOUS!!! lol i did the thing where you change the to sex. Now my buds teacher is wondering why he keeps sayin sex in his oral report WOOTZERS. This is the best tut ever dude!</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/list-of-pranks-d/15500/7">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/list-of-pranks-d/15500/7</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 08 Oct 2006 08:38:45 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-15500-7</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/list-of-pranks-d/15500.rss">List Of Pranks :D!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>List Of Pranks :D!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@weed_boy weed_boy]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/weed_boy">@weed_boy</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>ROFL!</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/list-of-pranks-d/15500/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/list-of-pranks-d/15500/6</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 08 Oct 2006 08:30:44 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-15500-6</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/list-of-pranks-d/15500.rss">List Of Pranks :D!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>List Of Pranks :D!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Buzzy Buzzy]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/buzzy">@Buzzy</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>omfg this is gonna be hilarious… im only in junior high… but i REALLY REALLY wanna try the chalk outline, confetti umbrella, alarm clock, and vinegar in the toilet, or the gelatin one… this is definetly priceless</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/list-of-pranks-d/15500/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/list-of-pranks-d/15500/5</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 22 Sep 2006 04:21:35 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-15500-5</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/list-of-pranks-d/15500.rss">List Of Pranks :D!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>List Of Pranks :D!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@ghostboy195 ghostboy195]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/ghostboy195">@ghostboy195</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote no-group" data-post="2" data-topic="15500">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 wall of fir the 2nd:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Can you edit it so we know where the DIFFERENT pranks are?</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>fine, i’ll put some space between each just for you</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/list-of-pranks-d/15500/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/list-of-pranks-d/15500/4</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 22 Sep 2006 03:04:29 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-15500-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/list-of-pranks-d/15500.rss">List Of Pranks :D!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>List Of Pranks :D!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@wyn10 wyn10]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/wyn10">@wyn10</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>holy crap</p>
<p>thanks</p>
<p>P.S:  I have a april fools joke prank and that is wake up early and the mourning and get duck tape and put it over your brother’s eyes and when he gets up he will think he is blind!!! I found this out from the simpsons and i always wanted to try this and going to this year!!!</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/list-of-pranks-d/15500/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/list-of-pranks-d/15500/3</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 22 Sep 2006 02:42:22 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-15500-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/list-of-pranks-d/15500.rss">List Of Pranks :D!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>List Of Pranks :D!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@wall_of_fir_the_2nd wall of fir the 2nd]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/wall_of_fir_the_2nd">@wall_of_fir_the_2nd</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Can you edit it so we know where the DIFFERENT pranks are?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/list-of-pranks-d/15500/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/list-of-pranks-d/15500/2</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 22 Sep 2006 02:40:26 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-15500-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/list-of-pranks-d/15500.rss">List Of Pranks :D!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>List Of Pranks :D!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@ghostboy195 ghostboy195]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/ghostboy195">@ghostboy195</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[center]<span class="bbcode-u"><span class="bbcode-b">List Of Pranks and Prank Ideas <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/smiley.png?v=9" title=":smiley:" class="emoji" alt=":smiley:"> !!!</span></span>[/center]<br>
[center][glow=red,2,300]I take no responsibility for what you use this for[/glow][/center]<br>
[center]<span class="bbcode-u"><span class="bbcode-b">Computer Pranks</span></span>[/center]</p>
<p>[ul][li] When someone leaves their computer, go into Microsoft Word and make an Auto-Correct option to Change the word “the” into the word “SEX”<br>
[/li]<br>
[li]Wait for someone to walk away from their PC. Click Start -&gt; Settings -&gt; Control Panel -&gt; Mouse. Select the “Pointers” tab and change the first cursor (Normal Select) from an arrow to the same thing they use for the “Busy” cursor. See how long they will stare at their screen waiting for the computer to finish what it’s doing.<br>
[/li]<br>
[li]A more elaborate Word prank is to use the “AutoCorrect” feature to turn everyday words into wacky variations. In Word 2002, go to Tools &gt; AutoCorrect Options. Make sure “Replace text as you type” is checked. In the box below, you can add new words. You want to use common words, but not too common. Here are some suggestions:</p>
<pre><code>dear:rear
thanks:yanks
sincerely:sinqueerly
test:testicle
hello:yo yo yo (or "what up")
person's name:Batman (or Wonder Woman)
</code></pre>
<p>This prank also works with Microsoft Excel.<br>
[/li]<br>
[li]Pry open the keyboard of a someone you know who can take a joke, and remove the rubber punching pad. The computer will still see the keyboard, but nothing will happen when your prankee punches the keys.<br>
[/li]<br>
[li]Go to the Windows Control Panel and double-click “Mouse.” Switch the right mouse button so that it’s activated by the left mouse button, and vice-versa. For even more fun, make the mouse go as slowly as you can, then laugh as it takes them forever to switch it back.<br>
[/li]<br>
[li]Take a screenshot of someones desktop, make that their wallpaper, then hide all of their icons and the taskbar. When they start up their computer the next day, they will click and click on everything, to no avail. <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/smiley.png?v=9" title=":smiley:" class="emoji" alt=":smiley:"><br>
[/li]<br>
[li]First, do a web search for “Windows shutdown utility.” Download it to someones PC when they are away. It puts an icon on the desktop that you just double-click to shut down the PC. Then change the icon to something like Internet Explorer, or some other commonly-used program. It’s funny to watch them constantly shutting down their PC and not knowing why.<br>
[/li]<br>
[li]Go to the Windows Control Panel and double-click “Mouse.” Switch the right mouse button so that it’s activated by the left mouse button, and vice-versa. For even more fun, make the mouse go as slowly as you can, then laugh as it takes them forever to switch it back.<br>
[/li][/ul]</p>
<p>[center]<span class="bbcode-u"><span class="bbcode-b">Office Pranks</span></span>[/center]</p>
<p>[ul][li]Take a paperclip and make a a few dozen photocopies of it. Mix them up with normal, unused paper. Watch people go crazy trying to find the paperclip that’s stuck in the photocopier.<br>
[/li]<br>
[li]This prank will require a few accomplices. Pick the most gullible and hopefully vocal person in your office. Bring in some home automation electronics (you can get these off the Web, or at your local Radio Shack), and wire up the victim’s office. We wired up my co-worker’s office so that I could turn her oscillating fan and her giant desk calculator on or off from anywhere in the building using a remote control. Accomplice <span class="hashtag">#1</span> is a disbeliever. Every time accomplice <span class="hashtag">#1</span> leaves the victim’s office, things start turning on and off, but never when the accomplice is in the office. Accomplice <span class="hashtag">#2</span> is a believer. When the victim admits stranges things have been happening, <span class="hashtag">#2</span> will tell the victim that he/she has noticed strange things in his/her office too. Accomplice <span class="hashtag">#3</span> is hopefully the victim’s boss. Anytime accomplice <span class="hashtag">#3</span> hears the victim talking about strange things happening, or sees accomplices 1 or 2 in the victim’s office, he/she tells them to quit talking about this nonsense and get back to work, getting angrier each time. See how long this will work for you. <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/wink.png?v=9" title=":wink:" class="emoji" alt=":wink:"><br>
[/li]<br>
[li]Icy Hot on the toilet seats. ;D<br>
[/li]<br>
[li]This is a classic prank that works best in an office setting. All you need to do is go to your local grocery store, and buy a LARGE amount of gelatin (not Jell-O, just clear disgusting-tasting gelatin). Go to your bathroom at work – this works best with the men’s urinal/stall combo bathroom – and put it in the toilets. You’ll need to use 3-4 “servings” per toilet, but this is still quite inexpensive. Within minutes, the water in the toilets will have congealed into a CLEAR, yet hard substance. Now, when someone goes into a stall (which means, of course, that they have to expel solid waste), their feces will fall out, bounce up, then remain SITTING on top of the toilet “water,” stinking like hell! This does no permanent damage – all you have to do is scoop about 1/2 of the congealed water out, then flush, and it’s gone.<br>
[/li]<br>
[li]Take a picture of a beloved personal item on your coworker’s desk (stuffed animal, small plant, trinket, etc.) Then kidnap the item and leave the picture in its place with a fake ransom letter.<br>
[/li]<br>
[li]First, take the little pieces of paper out of all the hole punchers in the office. Sneak into one of your workmates’ cars and tip all the little pieces of paper into the air vents. Point them upwards, and set the fan to full power. When they get into the car and start the engine, the paper should come at them like a blizzard! Classic.<br>
[/li]<br>
[li]<br>
Put confetti in a co-worker’s umbrella. Simple, harmless, annoying.<br>
[/li]<br>
[li]Bake cookies for everyone. Divide the dough. For one batch, bake normally. For the second, add cayenne pepper, Tabasco sauce, peppercorns, etc.<br>
[/li]<br>
[li]Find a box about the size of a cake. Then cover it with frosting, making it look like a cake. Then put it out in the office kitchen, or wherever people leave free food. Sit back as one of your co-workers tries to cut a slice.<br>
[/li]<br>
[li]Find a “zip tie” (also known as a “cable tie”) that’s similar in color to your co-worker’s phone cord. Place around both ends of the cord, as close to the handset as possible. This will shorten the cord to about an inch. Clip the end of the zip tie so it’s not sticking out suspiciously. Wait until your co-worker tries to answer the phone.<br>
[/li][/ul]</p>
<p>[center]<span class="bbcode-u"><span class="bbcode-b">College Pranks</span></span>[/center]</p>
<p>[ul][li]You know those Christmas cards that play jingles when you open them? You can remove the music chip from cards and affix it to the insides of door hinges. Every time someone opens the door, the jingle plays – over and over. Also works well on the bottom hinge of a dark closet. Can take months to discover – or run out of power.<br>
[/li]<br>
[li]Fill a very large manilla envelope with shaving cream, slide the mouth of the envelope under the door, and stomp on it. The shock of it is splendid!<br>
[/li]<br>
[li]Get a tube of glue, and a bag full of those googly craft eyes from Wal-Mart. Glue pairs of them to anything: toilet seats, computer monitors, doorknobs, peoples’ dishes … then hide somewhere and watch for their reactions.<br>
[/li]<br>
[li]This prank requires a group of people to help you out, along with a LOT of aluminum cans and some ribbon.<br>
Step 1: Collect an assload of empty aluminum cans. (Just don’t recycle for a few months.)<br>
Step 2: Take all the empty cans and ribbon to a different residence building on campus, a rival college, the President’s house, etc., when everyone will be asleep.<br>
Step 3: Put a very long strip of ribbon on the floor, and put a row of cans on top of the ribbon. Then put another ribbon on top of the cans, and put another row of cans on top of that. Continue this until you have a huge stack of cans. Make sure to leave enough extra ribbon hanging out as a “starter.” You might also want to stack the cans along a wall so that they don’t fall over while you’re stacking them.<br>
Step 4: When stacking is complete, grab the extra ribbon that’s between all the cans, give it a huge pull and run. If all is successful, you will wake up everyone in the building, as well as neighboring counties.<br>
[/li]<br>
[li]Gather up a small stack of paper, some tape, and a couple hundred aluminum cans. Start layering the cans against your victim’s door. Tape the paper to the doorframe as you go up, to keep the cans in place. When the cans are all the way up, remove the paper gently. As soon as the victim opens his door the next morning, the suction will send 400+ cans crashing down on him.<br>
[/li]<br>
[li]Obtain nine of the same type of animal (pigs, chickens, any animal that you can get your hands on). Then paint on their backs the numbers 1-10, but skip a number like 5 or something. Turn the animals loose in your dorm or student union building. Once they find all the other animals, they’ll be looking for the “missing” animal forever<br>
[/li]<br>
[li]Get a packet of instant milk and put it in someone’s bed on a particulary hot night. In their sleep, they will sweat, and in the morning the milk will have mutated into SOUR STINKY MILK! They will stink for a week.<br>
[/li]<br>
[li]Hot sauce on the toothbrush. Only works if you use something strong like Dave’s Insanity<br>
[/li]<br>
[li]For revenge on a vehicle: first, use shoe polish to write creative sayings on the windows, then re-write the sayings on the inside of the windows and watch them try to wash it off. Next: put confetti in the A/C vents and turn the blowers on high. Finally, fill the entire vehicle with packing peanuts. Make sure you have a camera, and an escape route!<br>
[/li]<br>
[li]When someone’s sick, cut up several large clear plastic bags and then tape them together in order to create a large sheet of plastic. Then at 4 in the morning, tape the sheet of plastic to the person’s doorframe with duct tape and then tape a big sign that says QUARANTINED.<br>
[/li]<br>
[li]If your doors open inward, tie one doorknobs to another one with rope. Bang on both doors and watch the hilarity.<br>
[/li]<br>
[li]You can easily remove peepholes from doors (not just reverse them), and then use a super-soaker water gun to awaken your friend.<br>
[/li]<br>
[li]When one of your guy friends is in the room with a girl, find a cheap, disgusting porno off of e-Bay and throw it at him. Proceed to tell him that you were returning “Ass-Blasters 2000” or whatever the title may be.<br>
[/li]<br>
[li]Go to the dollar store and get a bunch of those cheap travel alarm clocks, set them to go off every half hour in the night, and then hide them throughout the room. Drives them nuts!<br>
[/li]<br>
[li]Draw a chalk outline of someone’s body on a driveway or sidewalk, and surround it with caution tape. This is legal, as long as you do not use official police caution tape<br>
[/li]<br>
[li]Find the toilet of your victim, then empty the water basin, and replace the water with vinegar. Add baking powder into the toilet’s water reservoir (the part that contains the water that is flushed in after you do your thing). When the victim flushes, the baking soda and vinegar will mix and expand, overflowing the place with their feces.<br>
[/li][/ul]</p>
<p>[center]<span class="bbcode-u"><span class="bbcode-b">Sources</span></span>[/center]</p>
<p>[ul][li]<a href="http://www.zug.com/pranks/ideas/college.html" rel="nofollow noopener">http://www.zug.com/pranks/ideas/college.html</a> [/li]<br>
[li]<a href="http://www.zug.com/pranks/ideas/office.html" rel="nofollow noopener">http://www.zug.com/pranks/ideas/office.html</a> [/li]<br>
[li]<a href="http://www.zug.com/pranks/ideas/computer.html" rel="nofollow noopener">http://www.zug.com/pranks/ideas/computer.html</a> [/li][/ul]</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/list-of-pranks-d/15500/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/list-of-pranks-d/15500/1</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Sep 2006 01:55:39 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-15500-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/list-of-pranks-d/15500.rss">List Of Pranks :D!</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
