<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Why wouldn&#39;t it work anymore?!</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/why-wouldnt-it-work-anymore/554087</link>
    <description>Hey guys, today i&#39;ve downloaded 667 server and i ran it for first time and well it worked well with hamachi it connects perfectly to the client as i putted the hamachi&#39;s ip in the client and complie then hell yesh it worked, so yeah but when i gave the client to my friend and server is running! he actually went in like for 10 seconds and he kept disconnecting then after he closed the client  he tried again but his client won&#39;t load while the server is working perfectly with my pc and my client too and i can enter the server normally and oh yeah i tried this on 718 and other servers but now it won&#39;t all of sudden ? Like wtf? something blocking maybe? please help me and sorry for bad english :(</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 13 Dec 2015 17:35:58 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/why-wouldnt-it-work-anymore/554087.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Why wouldn&#39;t it work anymore?!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@malimt malimt]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/malimt">@malimt</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>You need to explain the matter in a more detailed way, your friend can’t what? He can’t get on? If so, what error does he get? What is he using to access your server? Maybe Firewall, Maybe port? Maybe Anti-virus/Internet Security… It could be many things, but if you could explain a lil more, I <span class="bbcode-b"><span class="bbcode-i">might</span></span> be able to help you.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/why-wouldnt-it-work-anymore/554087/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/why-wouldnt-it-work-anymore/554087/2</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 13 Dec 2015 17:35:58 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-554087-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/why-wouldnt-it-work-anymore/554087.rss">Why wouldn&#39;t it work anymore?!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Why wouldn&#39;t it work anymore?!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Project1337 Project1337]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/project1337">@Project1337</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Hey guys, today i’ve downloaded 667 server and i ran it for first time and well it worked well with hamachi it connects perfectly to the client as i putted the hamachi’s ip in the client and complie then hell yesh it worked, so yeah but when i gave the client to my friend and server is running! he actually went in like for 10 seconds and he kept disconnecting then after he closed the client  he tried again but his client won’t load while the server is working perfectly with my pc and my client too and i can enter the server normally and oh yeah i tried this on 718 and other servers but now it won’t all of sudden ? Like wtf? something blocking maybe? please help me and sorry for bad english <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/frowning.png?v=5" title=":frowning:" class="emoji" alt=":frowning:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/why-wouldnt-it-work-anymore/554087/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/why-wouldnt-it-work-anymore/554087/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 12 Dec 2015 17:05:59 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-554087-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/why-wouldnt-it-work-anymore/554087.rss">Why wouldn&#39;t it work anymore?!</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
