<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>All At Stake - Punching Above Your Wieght EP</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/all-at-stake-punching-above-your-wieght-ep/352708</link>
    <description>Samples of the EP can be previewed here: http://www.myspace.com/allatstakeuk (Including &quot;You&#39;ll thank me (When you&#39;re older)&quot;)
Old songs like &quot;The Pledge&quot;, &quot;In Good Taste&quot; and &quot;Anchors&quot; are still available to listen to.


About all at stake:

&#39;They say themselves they play powerful pop music and indeed they do.&#39; - Ourzone Magazine  

All At Stake are a hard hitting emotionally driven power pop band based in the Midlands of the United Kingdom. The band came together in all its six piece glory in early 2007 later that year being crowned Derbyshire band of the Year. From this point on All At Stake became as ambitious as fun loving and to this very day strive to play energetic, fun filled shows at the same time as writing music exactly how they&#39;d want to hear it. Powerful and epic sounding pop rock music taking influence from various different pop punk, hardcore and rock acts with a tinge of trance/electro.With a new E.P. &#39;Punching Above Your Weight&#39; set to drop and more touring ahead of them the future only looks bright for the mighty six piece. 

The band are currently at their strongest, still bettering themselves and playing shows all over the United Kingdom so be sure to check them out at a venue near you.  This page is ran by the band so feel free to chat and leave some love accordingly.   

&quot;We&#39;re not trying to be anything we&#39;re not. We just write music taking into account all of our influences, exactly how we want to hear it. We aim to push ourselves as far as we can and have a lot of fun doing so- the day it stops being fun is the day we&#39;ll stop. We love the people who come to our shows so never hesitate to come and mingle.Hopefully see you soon&quot; -All At Stake 

They are unsigned and last week my band played with them so if your looking for unsigned bands around the uk, these are you guys :)</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 03 Aug 2010 16:35:26 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>General Discussion</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/all-at-stake-punching-above-your-wieght-ep/352708.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>All At Stake - Punching Above Your Wieght EP</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@XharveyX XharveyX]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/xharveyx">@XharveyX</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Samples of the EP can be previewed here: <a href="http://www.myspace.com/allatstakeuk" rel="nofollow noopener">http://www.myspace.com/allatstakeuk</a> (Including “You’ll thank me (When you’re older)”)<br>
Old songs like “The Pledge”, “In Good Taste” and “Anchors” are still available to listen to.</p>
<p>About all at stake:</p>
<p>‘They say themselves they play powerful pop music and indeed they do.’ - Ourzone Magazine</p>
<p>All At Stake are a hard hitting emotionally driven power pop band based in the Midlands of the United Kingdom. The band came together in all its six piece glory in early 2007 later that year being crowned Derbyshire band of the Year. From this point on All At Stake became as ambitious as fun loving and to this very day strive to play energetic, fun filled shows at the same time as writing music exactly how they’d want to hear it. Powerful and epic sounding pop rock music taking influence from various different pop punk, hardcore and rock acts with a tinge of trance/electro.With a new E.P. ‘Punching Above Your Weight’ set to drop and more touring ahead of them the future only looks bright for the mighty six piece.</p>
<p>The band are currently at their strongest, still bettering themselves and playing shows all over the United Kingdom so be sure to check them out at a venue near you.  This page is ran by the band so feel free to chat and leave some love accordingly.</p>
<p>“We’re not trying to be anything we’re not. We just write music taking into account all of our influences, exactly how we want to hear it. We aim to push ourselves as far as we can and have a lot of fun doing so- the day it stops being fun is the day we’ll stop. We love the people who come to our shows so never hesitate to come and mingle.Hopefully see you soon” -All At Stake</p>
<p>They are unsigned and last week my band played with them so if your looking for unsigned bands around the uk, these are you guys <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=5" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/all-at-stake-punching-above-your-wieght-ep/352708/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/all-at-stake-punching-above-your-wieght-ep/352708/1</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 03 Aug 2010 16:35:26 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-352708-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/all-at-stake-punching-above-your-wieght-ep/352708.rss">All At Stake - Punching Above Your Wieght EP</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
