<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Need some help related to Dedicated servers</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/need-some-help-related-to-dedicated-servers/329586</link>
    <description>Hello there, first of all. I&#39;m sorry of this is the wrong section. Couldn&#39;t find any Off Topic forums so I thought I did it here, feel free to move this to the right section if needed.

So, I&#39;ve currently got 1 server online and I&#39;m working on my second server, I&#39;d like to have both online 24/7 on a VPS or Dedicated server, my budget for one of these is around $25 monthly.

Now, I need some one or something that could explain me exactly how a Dedicated server works. I need something that&#39;s easy accessable since I have to re-compile my server every time I added code to it - which is usually.

Thanks for reading this. Hope I could get some RIGHT information this time cause I tried many times on google.

Bakpao/Ripper.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 15 Feb 2010 20:33:54 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/need-some-help-related-to-dedicated-servers/329586.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Need some help related to Dedicated servers</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Bakpao Bakpao]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/bakpao">@Bakpao</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Hello there, first of all. I’m sorry of this is the wrong section. Couldn’t find any Off Topic forums so I thought I did it here, feel free to move this to the right section if needed.</p>
<p>So, I’ve currently got 1 server online and I’m working on my second server, I’d like to have both online 24/7 on a VPS or Dedicated server, my budget for one of these is around $25 monthly.</p>
<p>Now, I need some one or something that could explain me exactly how a Dedicated server works. I need something that’s easy accessable since I have to re-compile my server every time I added code to it - which is usually.</p>
<p>Thanks for reading this. Hope I could get some RIGHT information this time cause I tried many times on google.</p>
<p>Bakpao/Ripper.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/need-some-help-related-to-dedicated-servers/329586/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/need-some-help-related-to-dedicated-servers/329586/1</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 15 Feb 2010 20:33:54 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-329586-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/need-some-help-related-to-dedicated-servers/329586.rss">Need some help related to Dedicated servers</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
