<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>I wrote a story</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/i-wrote-a-story/283009</link>
    <description>I guess it&#39;s along the lines of dark humor, gothic literature, etc.

This morning on the bus I got this idea and started writing it. I proofread it and then added some, subtracted some. Then I typed it up on my site. It&#39;s really the only story I&#39;ve ever written because I felt like it, other than my screenplays. It was 8 pages on paper. It&#39;s pretty lengthy.

Here it is. Tell me what you think.

[center][b]Flies[/b][/center]

     A brand new house was finished in Cliffhaven last month. It&#39;s been the talk of the neighborhood since then. Most of that talk has come from Mrs. Jeffries, the nosy gossip across the street. Why anyone would want to live like that in such a place was unthinkable. The house rose a story above the rest. Its paint wasn&#39;t peeling and was more saturated than the other houses around it. The sidewalk glimmered as if the concrete pourer added in a few gallons of star dust as it was drying. The front door&#39;s handle also shone, it was made of platinum and was untouched by fingerprints because no one had yet visited, or been let in. The garage was open and inside was two cars. A &#39;72 Mustang, yellow with a black stripe, and the brand new Ford Focus model in blue. Both cars were equally clean and reflective.

     The word was that someone around town made a fortune on some online program, but didn&#39;t have the heart to leave the area, so they built a newer house in the neighborhood. That&#39;s what Mrs. Jeffries started saying. The original word was that a celebrity moved into town. Mrs. Jeffries was always in someone else&#39;s business, anyone’s but her own. Her son David had taken after her. He was snoopier and when he noticed cars in the garage, he began to spy on the owners. The owners never came outside or seemed to leave the house at all, so he watched them in their natural habitat. Every day after school he would go straight to the house, sneak around the side, and hide in the bushes by the kitchen window. The kitchen window offered the best view inside their lives. It didn&#39;t have blinds and the shade from the bushes hid him from their view. David wasn&#39;t sure what he wanted to do with his life, but he knew there had to be some job where he could spy on people for a living. That way he could use his skills that his mom&#39;s DNA supplied and he perfected.

     From the kitchen window he had a full view of the kitchen, of course, and half of the living room. There wasn&#39;t much living in there, he never saw anyone enter the room. The standard furniture occupied the room, although it was a few steps above in quality. The furniture was white leather, the walls were an off white sort of grey, and the TV and surrounding electronics all black. The kitchen seemed to follow the same theme. The cabinets, a white wood, the countertops, white marble, and all the appliances were brushed aluminum. The sink was above the dishwasher and there was a microwave/oven/stove combo across the room. In between them was a huge refrigerator, industrial size. It opened in such a way that from the window view, David couldn&#39;t see inside of it. Besides that, the countertops were empty and it&#39;d be hard to tell if anyone even lived there at all except that David saw a man walk into it and get a glass of water.

     For the first two days David was people peeping, he only saw this man twice. Both times, he followed the same schedule. He walked into the kitchen, got a glass of water, drank it, and put it in the fridge. David wondered how many days it would take for the mystery man to fill it with glasses of water. Other than this, David hadn&#39;t seen much of this man of the house. He was the only living thing he saw inside of the house, but he didn&#39;t know anything about the rest of his life because he wasn&#39;t tall enough to get a good look into the upstairs windows, where the man spent most of his time. By three days David got a little tired of waiting for the man to get thirsty and stopped sneaking over there as much. Summer came and David noticed the man was mowing his grass. This was the first time he&#39;d seen him outside of his house. A step up from drinking water, but this guy still seemed pretty normal. David was going to call it a day and then he heard glass shattering. The neighbors hit a baseball into one of his windows and ran away. Mystery man, pissed, quit mowing the grass halfway through and went inside. David went to his usual sneaking spot and looked inside the kitchen window. Something was up because the guy was also sneaking. But he couldn&#39;t find out why he was sneaking. If he wasn&#39;t moving, he was crouched down always looking at something like he was ready to pounce. If he was moving it was very slow as if the floor might crumple beneath him if he pressed any harder. David almost forgot he was watching a human being. The kitchen was this man&#39;s jungle and he was hunting his prey.

     David had to leave to eat dinner and get ready for bed, but he couldn&#39;t get this guy out of his head. What the hell was he doing? David had a hard time sleeping that night and he decided that he would skip school tomorrow to get a few extra hours of spooking and figure this man out. He packed a small lunch and proceeded to the residential castle. A little had changed since his last visit. The Focus had obviously been driven last night and was parked a little crooked and the man was now holding a fly swatter as he creeped in between the kitchen furniture. David couldn&#39;t help but laugh. A curious fly had made its way into the broken window before he had a chance to cover it with a towel. It shouldn&#39;t be that hard to kill a fly right? Otherwise, there&#39;d be a technological advancement for it. David was only guessing there wasn&#39;t, because the man was using the same fly swatter he&#39;s always used, and he wasn&#39;t blessed with money.

     The guy mostly crept around and the swatter occasionally snapped at some inanimate object the fly might be perched on. Either there were many flies around the house, or one fly was playing some serious cat and mouse with him. From the window, David couldn&#39;t spot something as small as a fly buzzing around the room, so he just assumed there was more than one because the guy kept at it for the rest of the day. Sneaking around. Waiting.

     The next day David went again, but this time the man wasn&#39;t home. The Focus was gone and the towel against the window had a hole eaten in it by worms of some sort. David went home wondering what this man had in store next. This fly sure was giving this man a hell of a fight. When the man came home David gave him a few minutes and then left to see his progress. A few different places in the kitchen were catapult looking contraptions. They all had fly swatters and pointed down. Every minute or so one of them cracked down on a surface. They didn&#39;t seem to work, because David could see the man almost hidden behind the table, watching a fly make his way through each trap like a joke. He damn sure didn&#39;t look happy. David didn&#39;t share the same initiative to wait on a fly to take a half a second too long on a single surface and meet his untimely doom, so he went home that night. And yet again, he was thinking about the man on the way home. Then he began to ask questions. Why didn&#39;t the man just open the back door and let the damn thing out?

     Another day went by and David didn&#39;t bother going out because the Focus was gone again, and not to mention that he had fallen behind on his schoolwork.  He used the day to catch up and when he was done he wondered if he should help the man out. After all, he didn&#39;t seem to have any family or friends and the neighborhood wasn&#39;t very receptive towards him. In all his young life David never had any trouble killing a fly and didn&#39;t know a person who did until this guy moved in.

     David resumed his usual spying the next day after school. He noticed more traps, slightly more advanced, mainly around the fridge. David came to the conclusion that there&#39;s more than one fly because at some moments more than one trap went off at a time. The guy didn&#39;t catch David&#39;s attention at first, but his attention shifted when he saw him holding a sledgehammer above his head. He wasn&#39;t swinging it, yet, but boy was he ready. The island countertop seemed to be his target, and he was poised just like one of his little contraptions, waiting for a fly to land on his polished white countertop. David again asked himself questions. Why the sledgehammer? Isn&#39;t that a bit overkill? But his thoughts were broken as the guy tore the counter in two, the top half crumbling over and shattering the marble as it hit the ground. He kept at it, smashing the pieces into more, smaller, pieces. It started to tear into the hardwood floor and white and tan shards of wood were flying into the air, little missiles to the flies. Two or three of the traps were in his path of destruction and much like the island, were reduced to the pieces that created them. David had no idea what to think, and when the guy seemed too tired to swing the hammer anymore he decided to call it a night. Maybe the guy was pteronarcophobic. What other reason could there be to cause a man to destroy his grandeur new kitchen to get at a few flies? Maybe this all was too big for David&#39;s head to wrap around. He just didn&#39;t understand.

    The next morning was David&#39;s day off of school, so he left early to the mystery house. All of the counters were stripped from their original place, smashed to bits, and the remaining rubble pushed against the fridge, creating a miniature mountain. David didn&#39;t see the man anywhere, so he spent his time looking closer at the kitchen. He could actually see the flies. They were much too small to see flying around, but when a few of them landed on the fridge he could see the small black clusters. There were also a few on a half eaten sandwich that was pretty close to the window, maybe an attempt to draw them all to one place. The traps had mostly stopped working. Some of their swings were weak and some of them were just stuck. David didn&#39;t think they worked at all in the first place, considering most of them looked pretty clean.

     Something loud jarred his attention. It sounded like someone fell down the stairs, or maybe Sledgehammer vs. Counters Round 2. A few seconds later the man busted into the room. In the short flash that David got a look at him, he sure noticed a lot. He had been wearing the same clothes for the past few days. His hair was affray and his eyes as wide as the fridge. He was panting loudly, not that David could hear that, but because he looked like it.  In his right hand at his side he was carrying a gun. It was too small to be a rifle, but a little long to be a shotgun. But David didn&#39;t know much about guns. The man held it into the air and fired it off, sending a piece of the ceiling down to the ground with a trail of sawdust. David shrunk a little behind the bushes leaving just enough room for his eyes to peer into the window. Now was not the time to get caught. He saw his shadow flashing against the window and turned around to see the police. They turned off their lights and started to step out of their car. David turned back around to see the man kiss the refrigerator, turn around and lean his back to it, then bite the barrel of his gun. One of the officers pulled David back and away from the window but David still saw him slump to the ground as a flash splattered his head onto the fridge and surrounding walls while the other officer kicked in the door.

     David waited, sitting on the curb. Within an hour, another squad car arrived with an ambulance, and three bodies were carried out of the house in bags and stuffed into the ambulance. He didn&#39;t really want to think about what was in the other two bags, his mind was still blown in a somewhat less extravagant way than the old mystery man&#39;s.

     In a week’s time he had heard the same story dozens of times from his mother. Mrs. Jeffries had talked to a &quot;friend&quot; on the investigation team and found out all they knew, though he must not have been a very good friend because she never found out that David was there to see the fireworks show in action. The man, Alex Pensworth, had kept his wife and son in his industrial freezer. Their causes of death: unknown. They only know they died before they were frozen, but not too long before so probably while they were in this house. Alex of course sprayed his own grey matter across a few square feet of surfaces. The rest of the house was messed with, but not nearly as bad as the kitchen. Most rooms had cryptic messages sprayed on the walls in a black paint, a nice contrast to the otherwise bland furniture. Maybe he was in to feng shui? The flies were trying to get into the freezer, where the real good stuff was at.

     David was left a little screwed in the head. His mom was too busy to know that he was watching the rising action at the Pensworth house, and was thereafter too busy spreading the word of spread remains in Alex&#39;s kitchen to care for him at all. David&#39;s spooking around taught him something though. The satisfaction of the splattering after the sound of the gun was enough to shape his destiny. He was sure of what he wanted to do with his life now. It wasn&#39;t very professional, but oh, blood and hair would spray the walls.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 27 Jun 2009 13:45:13 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>General Discussion</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/i-wrote-a-story/283009.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>I wrote a story</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Lil_Goon Lil Goon]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/lil_goon">@Lil_Goon</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Good story, little flawed. Rifles and shotguns are pretty much the same length. At least my 30.30 and 12 gauge are (if I remember right).</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/i-wrote-a-story/283009/14">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/i-wrote-a-story/283009/14</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 27 Jun 2009 13:45:13 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-283009-14</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/i-wrote-a-story/283009.rss">I wrote a story</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>I wrote a story</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Man_UTD_Freak Man UTD Freak]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/man_utd_freak">@Man_UTD_Freak</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote no-group quote-modified" data-post="3" data-topic="283009">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/sanga282/40/5_513041d5f7104045db30895d3b90af16.png" class="avatar"> sanga282:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>its nice, i like the opening paragraph the descriptions are very nice. Although i feel its in the wrong board <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/confused.png?v=5" title=":confused:" class="emoji" alt=":confused:"> i’ve been writing stories for ages i just never finish them <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=5" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"> ive probably got a 1GB of them spread across my house of half started novels</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Yes, exactly the same. I have never ever finished a story that I’ve started, and tell you what, I have attempted many stories but I just can’t be bothered to write them when I get to the median stage.</p>
<p>Now back to this story. I liked it as it was very imaginative but it seemed a bit slow starting, but overall I’ll give you a thumbs up.  <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/smiley.png?v=5" title=":smiley:" class="emoji" alt=":smiley:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/i-wrote-a-story/283009/13">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/i-wrote-a-story/283009/13</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 12 Jun 2009 22:52:52 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-283009-13</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/i-wrote-a-story/283009.rss">I wrote a story</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>I wrote a story</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@jc22493 Jc22493]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/jc22493">@jc22493</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>This is pretty good, but I’d like to see a bit more imagery. <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/wink.png?v=5" title=":wink:" class="emoji" alt=":wink:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/i-wrote-a-story/283009/12">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/i-wrote-a-story/283009/12</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 12 Jun 2009 01:17:13 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-283009-12</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/i-wrote-a-story/283009.rss">I wrote a story</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>I wrote a story</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@SomethingToHide STH]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/somethingtohide">@SomethingToHide</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Action dialogue? Dialogue plays almost no role in this story.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/i-wrote-a-story/283009/11">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/i-wrote-a-story/283009/11</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jun 2009 16:43:11 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-283009-11</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/i-wrote-a-story/283009.rss">I wrote a story</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>I wrote a story</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Andrew Andrew]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/andrew">@Andrew</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I think it’s very good - but what you need to work on is your action dialogue to make it more exciting/</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/i-wrote-a-story/283009/10">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/i-wrote-a-story/283009/10</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jun 2009 10:57:15 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-283009-10</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/i-wrote-a-story/283009.rss">I wrote a story</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>I wrote a story</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@sanga282 sanga282]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/sanga282">@sanga282</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“SomethingToHide, post:4, topic:283009”]What’s the other board for this O_o</p>
<p>1GB of stories. That’s a lot<br>
considering most of my documents aren’t more than 2mb.[/quote]<br>
my documents are quite a bit longer and this is spread across about 9 years</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/i-wrote-a-story/283009/9">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/i-wrote-a-story/283009/9</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jun 2009 08:34:04 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-283009-9</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/i-wrote-a-story/283009.rss">I wrote a story</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>I wrote a story</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@SomethingToHide STH]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/somethingtohide">@SomethingToHide</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Longer? Oh man this was like one of the longest I’ve written. I don’t write stories. Actually this is the second story I’ve written on my own, the first was never finished.</p>
<p>I felt like ENG102 has helped me a lot this quarter. Otherwise I wouldn’t have written this. I’ve learned a lot about plot structure, what happens after the climax, and just good things in general. Flannery O’Connor definitely had an influence on me.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/i-wrote-a-story/283009/8">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/i-wrote-a-story/283009/8</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jun 2009 02:43:31 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-283009-8</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/i-wrote-a-story/283009.rss">I wrote a story</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>I wrote a story</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@maniown maniown]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/maniown">@maniown</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I enjoyed this =]. Write another but a little longer. Lots of rising action!</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/i-wrote-a-story/283009/7">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/i-wrote-a-story/283009/7</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jun 2009 21:13:35 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-283009-7</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/i-wrote-a-story/283009.rss">I wrote a story</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>I wrote a story</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Fat_Cookies Fat Cookies]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/fat_cookies">@Fat_Cookies</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <blockquote>The sidewalk glimmered as if the concrete pourer added in a few gallons of star dust as it was drying. The front door's handle also shone, it was made of platinum and was untouched by fingerprints because no one had yet visited,</blockquote>
<blockquote>The next morning was David's day off of school, so he left early to the mystery house. All of the counters were stripped from their original place, smashed to bits, and the remaining rubble pushed against the fridge, creating a miniature mountain</blockquote>
<p>I Love these two sentences, very imaginative.</p>
<p>Heres the board: <a href="http://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php/board,30.0.html">http://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php/board,30.0.html</a></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/i-wrote-a-story/283009/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/i-wrote-a-story/283009/6</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jun 2009 19:56:46 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-283009-6</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/i-wrote-a-story/283009.rss">I wrote a story</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>I wrote a story</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@archerer98 Archer]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/archerer98">@archerer98</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Yea, I liked it.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/i-wrote-a-story/283009/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/i-wrote-a-story/283009/5</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jun 2009 19:40:38 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-283009-5</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/i-wrote-a-story/283009.rss">I wrote a story</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>I wrote a story</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@SomethingToHide STH]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/somethingtohide">@SomethingToHide</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>What’s the other board for this O_o</p>
<p>1GB of stories. That’s a lot considering most of my documents aren’t more than 2mb.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/i-wrote-a-story/283009/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/i-wrote-a-story/283009/4</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jun 2009 19:35:10 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-283009-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/i-wrote-a-story/283009.rss">I wrote a story</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>I wrote a story</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@sanga282 sanga282]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/sanga282">@sanga282</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>its nice, i like the opening paragraph the descriptions are very nice. Although i feel its in the wrong board <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/confused.png?v=5" title=":confused:" class="emoji" alt=":confused:"> i’ve been writing stories for ages i just never finish them <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=5" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"> ive probably got a 1GB of them spread across my house of half started novels</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/i-wrote-a-story/283009/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/i-wrote-a-story/283009/3</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jun 2009 19:33:08 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-283009-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/i-wrote-a-story/283009.rss">I wrote a story</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>I wrote a story</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@silabsoft RuneAgent]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/silabsoft">@silabsoft</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Cool story bro!</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/i-wrote-a-story/283009/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/i-wrote-a-story/283009/2</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jun 2009 19:31:15 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-283009-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/i-wrote-a-story/283009.rss">I wrote a story</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>I wrote a story</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@SomethingToHide STH]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/somethingtohide">@SomethingToHide</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I guess it’s along the lines of dark humor, gothic literature, etc.</p>
<p>This morning on the bus I got this idea and started writing it. I proofread it and then added some, subtracted some. Then I typed it up on my site. It’s really the only story I’ve ever written because I felt like it, other than my screenplays. It was 8 pages on paper. It’s pretty lengthy.</p>
<p>Here it is. Tell me what you think.</p>
<p>[center]<span class="bbcode-b">Flies</span>[/center]</p>
<pre><code> A brand new house was finished in Cliffhaven last month. It's been the talk of the neighborhood since then. Most of that talk has come from Mrs. Jeffries, the nosy gossip across the street. Why anyone would want to live like that in such a place was unthinkable. The house rose a story above the rest. Its paint wasn't peeling and was more saturated than the other houses around it. The sidewalk glimmered as if the concrete pourer added in a few gallons of star dust as it was drying. The front door's handle also shone, it was made of platinum and was untouched by fingerprints because no one had yet visited, or been let in. The garage was open and inside was two cars. A '72 Mustang, yellow with a black stripe, and the brand new Ford Focus model in blue. Both cars were equally clean and reflective.

 The word was that someone around town made a fortune on some online program, but didn't have the heart to leave the area, so they built a newer house in the neighborhood. That's what Mrs. Jeffries started saying. The original word was that a celebrity moved into town. Mrs. Jeffries was always in someone else's business, anyone’s but her own. Her son David had taken after her. He was snoopier and when he noticed cars in the garage, he began to spy on the owners. The owners never came outside or seemed to leave the house at all, so he watched them in their natural habitat. Every day after school he would go straight to the house, sneak around the side, and hide in the bushes by the kitchen window. The kitchen window offered the best view inside their lives. It didn't have blinds and the shade from the bushes hid him from their view. David wasn't sure what he wanted to do with his life, but he knew there had to be some job where he could spy on people for a living. That way he could use his skills that his mom's DNA supplied and he perfected.

 From the kitchen window he had a full view of the kitchen, of course, and half of the living room. There wasn't much living in there, he never saw anyone enter the room. The standard furniture occupied the room, although it was a few steps above in quality. The furniture was white leather, the walls were an off white sort of grey, and the TV and surrounding electronics all black. The kitchen seemed to follow the same theme. The cabinets, a white wood, the countertops, white marble, and all the appliances were brushed aluminum. The sink was above the dishwasher and there was a microwave/oven/stove combo across the room. In between them was a huge refrigerator, industrial size. It opened in such a way that from the window view, David couldn't see inside of it. Besides that, the countertops were empty and it'd be hard to tell if anyone even lived there at all except that David saw a man walk into it and get a glass of water.

 For the first two days David was people peeping, he only saw this man twice. Both times, he followed the same schedule. He walked into the kitchen, got a glass of water, drank it, and put it in the fridge. David wondered how many days it would take for the mystery man to fill it with glasses of water. Other than this, David hadn't seen much of this man of the house. He was the only living thing he saw inside of the house, but he didn't know anything about the rest of his life because he wasn't tall enough to get a good look into the upstairs windows, where the man spent most of his time. By three days David got a little tired of waiting for the man to get thirsty and stopped sneaking over there as much. Summer came and David noticed the man was mowing his grass. This was the first time he'd seen him outside of his house. A step up from drinking water, but this guy still seemed pretty normal. David was going to call it a day and then he heard glass shattering. The neighbors hit a baseball into one of his windows and ran away. Mystery man, pissed, quit mowing the grass halfway through and went inside. David went to his usual sneaking spot and looked inside the kitchen window. Something was up because the guy was also sneaking. But he couldn't find out why he was sneaking. If he wasn't moving, he was crouched down always looking at something like he was ready to pounce. If he was moving it was very slow as if the floor might crumple beneath him if he pressed any harder. David almost forgot he was watching a human being. The kitchen was this man's jungle and he was hunting his prey.

 David had to leave to eat dinner and get ready for bed, but he couldn't get this guy out of his head. What the hell was he doing? David had a hard time sleeping that night and he decided that he would skip school tomorrow to get a few extra hours of spooking and figure this man out. He packed a small lunch and proceeded to the residential castle. A little had changed since his last visit. The Focus had obviously been driven last night and was parked a little crooked and the man was now holding a fly swatter as he creeped in between the kitchen furniture. David couldn't help but laugh. A curious fly had made its way into the broken window before he had a chance to cover it with a towel. It shouldn't be that hard to kill a fly right? Otherwise, there'd be a technological advancement for it. David was only guessing there wasn't, because the man was using the same fly swatter he's always used, and he wasn't blessed with money.

 The guy mostly crept around and the swatter occasionally snapped at some inanimate object the fly might be perched on. Either there were many flies around the house, or one fly was playing some serious cat and mouse with him. From the window, David couldn't spot something as small as a fly buzzing around the room, so he just assumed there was more than one because the guy kept at it for the rest of the day. Sneaking around. Waiting.

 The next day David went again, but this time the man wasn't home. The Focus was gone and the towel against the window had a hole eaten in it by worms of some sort. David went home wondering what this man had in store next. This fly sure was giving this man a hell of a fight. When the man came home David gave him a few minutes and then left to see his progress. A few different places in the kitchen were catapult looking contraptions. They all had fly swatters and pointed down. Every minute or so one of them cracked down on a surface. They didn't seem to work, because David could see the man almost hidden behind the table, watching a fly make his way through each trap like a joke. He damn sure didn't look happy. David didn't share the same initiative to wait on a fly to take a half a second too long on a single surface and meet his untimely doom, so he went home that night. And yet again, he was thinking about the man on the way home. Then he began to ask questions. Why didn't the man just open the back door and let the damn thing out?

 Another day went by and David didn't bother going out because the Focus was gone again, and not to mention that he had fallen behind on his schoolwork.  He used the day to catch up and when he was done he wondered if he should help the man out. After all, he didn't seem to have any family or friends and the neighborhood wasn't very receptive towards him. In all his young life David never had any trouble killing a fly and didn't know a person who did until this guy moved in.

 David resumed his usual spying the next day after school. He noticed more traps, slightly more advanced, mainly around the fridge. David came to the conclusion that there's more than one fly because at some moments more than one trap went off at a time. The guy didn't catch David's attention at first, but his attention shifted when he saw him holding a sledgehammer above his head. He wasn't swinging it, yet, but boy was he ready. The island countertop seemed to be his target, and he was poised just like one of his little contraptions, waiting for a fly to land on his polished white countertop. David again asked himself questions. Why the sledgehammer? Isn't that a bit overkill? But his thoughts were broken as the guy tore the counter in two, the top half crumbling over and shattering the marble as it hit the ground. He kept at it, smashing the pieces into more, smaller, pieces. It started to tear into the hardwood floor and white and tan shards of wood were flying into the air, little missiles to the flies. Two or three of the traps were in his path of destruction and much like the island, were reduced to the pieces that created them. David had no idea what to think, and when the guy seemed too tired to swing the hammer anymore he decided to call it a night. Maybe the guy was pteronarcophobic. What other reason could there be to cause a man to destroy his grandeur new kitchen to get at a few flies? Maybe this all was too big for David's head to wrap around. He just didn't understand.

The next morning was David's day off of school, so he left early to the mystery house. All of the counters were stripped from their original place, smashed to bits, and the remaining rubble pushed against the fridge, creating a miniature mountain. David didn't see the man anywhere, so he spent his time looking closer at the kitchen. He could actually see the flies. They were much too small to see flying around, but when a few of them landed on the fridge he could see the small black clusters. There were also a few on a half eaten sandwich that was pretty close to the window, maybe an attempt to draw them all to one place. The traps had mostly stopped working. Some of their swings were weak and some of them were just stuck. David didn't think they worked at all in the first place, considering most of them looked pretty clean.

 Something loud jarred his attention. It sounded like someone fell down the stairs, or maybe Sledgehammer vs. Counters Round 2. A few seconds later the man busted into the room. In the short flash that David got a look at him, he sure noticed a lot. He had been wearing the same clothes for the past few days. His hair was affray and his eyes as wide as the fridge. He was panting loudly, not that David could hear that, but because he looked like it.  In his right hand at his side he was carrying a gun. It was too small to be a rifle, but a little long to be a shotgun. But David didn't know much about guns. The man held it into the air and fired it off, sending a piece of the ceiling down to the ground with a trail of sawdust. David shrunk a little behind the bushes leaving just enough room for his eyes to peer into the window. Now was not the time to get caught. He saw his shadow flashing against the window and turned around to see the police. They turned off their lights and started to step out of their car. David turned back around to see the man kiss the refrigerator, turn around and lean his back to it, then bite the barrel of his gun. One of the officers pulled David back and away from the window but David still saw him slump to the ground as a flash splattered his head onto the fridge and surrounding walls while the other officer kicked in the door.

 David waited, sitting on the curb. Within an hour, another squad car arrived with an ambulance, and three bodies were carried out of the house in bags and stuffed into the ambulance. He didn't really want to think about what was in the other two bags, his mind was still blown in a somewhat less extravagant way than the old mystery man's.

 In a week’s time he had heard the same story dozens of times from his mother. Mrs. Jeffries had talked to a "friend" on the investigation team and found out all they knew, though he must not have been a very good friend because she never found out that David was there to see the fireworks show in action. The man, Alex Pensworth, had kept his wife and son in his industrial freezer. Their causes of death: unknown. They only know they died before they were frozen, but not too long before so probably while they were in this house. Alex of course sprayed his own grey matter across a few square feet of surfaces. The rest of the house was messed with, but not nearly as bad as the kitchen. Most rooms had cryptic messages sprayed on the walls in a black paint, a nice contrast to the otherwise bland furniture. Maybe he was in to feng shui? The flies were trying to get into the freezer, where the real good stuff was at.

 David was left a little screwed in the head. His mom was too busy to know that he was watching the rising action at the Pensworth house, and was thereafter too busy spreading the word of spread remains in Alex's kitchen to care for him at all. David's spooking around taught him something though. The satisfaction of the splattering after the sound of the gun was enough to shape his destiny. He was sure of what he wanted to do with his life now. It wasn't very professional, but oh, blood and hair would spray the walls.</code></pre>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/i-wrote-a-story/283009/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/i-wrote-a-story/283009/1</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jun 2009 19:22:30 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-283009-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/i-wrote-a-story/283009.rss">I wrote a story</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
