<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>HTML/CSS website template!</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/html-css-website-template/515932</link>
    <description>I made this myself using HTML/CSS. There are no PHP stuff added so you would need to add it in yourself if you want the vote/donation page to work! 

Credits menucool for the image slider! 

[b]Features: [/b]
-Donation page
-Vote page
-Downloads page
-Index
-Really cool pop out webclient

[img]http://victoriaconnelly.co.uk/wp-content/uploads/2013/04/web.png[/img]


[img]http://victoriaconnelly.co.uk/wp-content/uploads/2013/04/web1.png[/img]

Download link: http://up.ht/16UVV2C

Some code previews:

[index.html]
[code=html]&lt;!DOCTYPE html&gt;
&lt;html&gt;
	&lt;head&gt;
		&lt;title&gt;Index&lt;/title&gt;
		&lt;link rel=&quot;stylesheet&quot; href=&quot;style.css&quot; /&gt;
		&lt;link href=&quot;themes/4/js-image-slider.css&quot; rel=&quot;stylesheet&quot; type=&quot;text/css&quot; /&gt;
		&lt;script src=&quot;themes/4/js-image-slider.js&quot; type=&quot;text/javascript&quot;&gt;&lt;/script&gt;	
		&lt;script&gt;
			function newPopup(url) {
				popupWindow = window.open(
					url,&#39;popUpWindow&#39;,&#39;height=700,width=800,left=10,top=10,resizable=yes,scrollbars=yes,toolbar=yes,menubar=no,location=no,directories=no,status=yes&#39;)}
		&lt;/script&gt;
	&lt;/head&gt;
	&lt;body&gt;
		&lt;div id=&#39;nav-bar&#39;&gt;
			&lt;ul&gt;
			   &lt;li class=&#39;active&#39;&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;index.html&#39;&gt;&lt;span&gt;Home&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
			   &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;#&#39;&gt;&lt;span&gt;Forums&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
			   &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;vote.html&#39;&gt;&lt;span&gt;Vote&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
			   &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;donate.html&#39;&gt;&lt;span&gt;Donate&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
			   &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;download.html&#39;&gt;&lt;span&gt;Download Client&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
			   &lt;li class=&#39;last&#39;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;JavaScript:newPopup(&#39;play.html&#39;);&quot;&gt;&lt;span&gt;Webclient&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
			&lt;/ul&gt;
		&lt;/div&gt;
		&lt;div id=&quot;sliderFrame&quot;&gt;
			&lt;div id=&quot;slider&quot;&gt;
				&lt;img src=&quot;images/1000x400.gif&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;
				&lt;img src=&quot;images/black-bg.gif&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;
				&lt;img src=&quot;images/1000x400.gif&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;
				&lt;img src=&quot;images/black-bg.gif&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;
			&lt;/div&gt;
			&lt;!-- Navigation buttons on both sides--&gt;
			&lt;div class=&quot;group1-Wrapper&quot;&gt;
				&lt;a onclick=&quot;imageSlider.previous()&quot; class=&quot;group1-Prev&quot;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;
				&lt;a onclick=&quot;imageSlider.next()&quot; class=&quot;group1-Next&quot;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;
			&lt;/div&gt;
			&lt;!-- Secondary naviagion buttons --&gt;
			&lt;div id=&quot;thumbs&quot;&gt;
				&lt;a onclick=&quot;imageSlider.previous()&quot; class=&quot;group2-Prev&quot;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;
				&lt;a onclick=&quot;imageSlider.next()&quot; class=&quot;group2-Next&quot; style=&quot;margin-right:30px;&quot;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;
			&lt;/div&gt;
		&lt;/div&gt;
		&lt;br&gt;
		&lt;div class=&quot;imagec&quot;&gt;
			&lt;a href=&quot;#&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;images/400x300.gif&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;
			&lt;a href=&quot;#&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;images/400x300.gif&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;
			&lt;a href=&quot;#&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;images/400x300.gif&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;
		&lt;/div&gt;
		&lt;div class=&quot;imagec&quot;&gt;
			&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;330&quot; src=&quot;http://www.youtube.com/embed/EBmROluwLkc&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;
			&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;330&quot; src=&quot;http://www.youtube.com/embed/CYLBSnxQMc4&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;
		&lt;/div&gt;
		&lt;footer&gt;
			&lt;div class=&quot;center&quot;&gt;
				@Copyright SpiderPigs 2012-2013. All Rights Reserved. SpiderPigs is in no way affiliated with Jagex or Runescape. SpiderPigs exists purely for educational purposes only.
				&lt;br&gt;
				This website is objected to our &lt;a href=&quot;tos.html&quot;&gt;Terms and conditions&lt;/a&gt;. Any violations may lead to prosicution.
			&lt;/div&gt;
		&lt;/footer&gt;
	&lt;/body&gt;
&lt;/html&gt;[/code]

[donations.html]
[code=html]&lt;!DOCTYPE html&gt;
&lt;html&gt;
	&lt;head&gt;
		&lt;title&gt;Donation&lt;/title&gt;
		&lt;link rel=&quot;stylesheet&quot; href=&quot;style.css&quot; /&gt;
		&lt;script&gt;
			function newPopup(url) {
				popupWindow = window.open(
					url,&#39;popUpWindow&#39;,&#39;height=700,width=800,left=10,top=10,resizable=yes,scrollbars=yes,toolbar=yes,menubar=no,location=no,directories=no,status=yes&#39;)}
		&lt;/script&gt;
	&lt;/head&gt;
	&lt;body&gt;
		&lt;div id=&#39;nav-bar&#39;&gt;
			&lt;ul&gt;
			   &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;index.html&#39;&gt;&lt;span&gt;Home&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
			   &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;#&#39;&gt;&lt;span&gt;Forums&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
			   &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;vote.html&#39;&gt;&lt;span&gt;Vote&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
			   &lt;li class=&#39;active&#39;&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;donate.html&#39;&gt;&lt;span&gt;Donate&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
			   &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;download.html&#39;&gt;&lt;span&gt;Download Client&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
			   &lt;li class=&#39;last&#39;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;JavaScript:newPopup(&#39;play.html&#39;);&quot;&gt;&lt;span&gt;Webclient&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
			&lt;/ul&gt;
		&lt;/div&gt;
			&lt;div class=&quot;center&quot;&gt;
				&lt;br&gt;
				&lt;img src=&quot;images/1000x100.gif&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;/&gt;
			&lt;/div&gt;
			&lt;br&gt;
		&lt;form method=&quot;POST&quot;&gt;
			&lt;table class=&quot;vicky&quot;&gt;
					&lt;tr&gt;
						&lt;td&gt;
						&lt;hr&gt;
							Please enter your username:&lt;input type=&quot;text&quot; id=&quot;username&quot; name=&quot;username&quot; placeholder=&quot;type your username&quot; /&gt;
							&lt;br&gt;
							Please select an item:					
							&lt;select name=&quot;prod&quot; style=&#39;width: 300px;&#39; id=&#39;prod&#39;&gt;
								&lt;option value=&quot;1&quot;&gt; Torva&#39;s Platebody - $15.59 &lt;/option&gt;
								&lt;option value=&quot;2&quot;&gt; Party Hat - $17.50 &lt;/option&gt;
								&lt;option value=&quot;3&quot;&gt; Korasi&#39;s Sword - $5.99 &lt;/option&gt;
								&lt;option value=&quot;4&quot;&gt; Armadyl Godsword - $8.45 &lt;/option&gt;
							&lt;/select&gt;
						
						&lt;/td&gt;
					&lt;/tr&gt;
				
					&lt;tr&gt;
						&lt;td&gt;
							&lt;input type=&quot;submit&quot; name=&quot;submit&quot; value=&quot;Donate Now!&quot;/&gt;
							&lt;hr&gt;
						&lt;/td&gt;
					&lt;/tr&gt;
			&lt;/table&gt;
		&lt;/form&gt;
		&lt;div class=&quot;donator-table&quot; &gt;
                &lt;table &gt;
                    &lt;tr&gt;
                        &lt;td class=&quot;10&quot;&gt;
                            Image
                        &lt;/td&gt;
                        &lt;td &gt;
                            Description
                        &lt;/td&gt;
                        &lt;td&gt;
                            Price
                        &lt;/td&gt;
                    &lt;/tr&gt; 
                    &lt;tr&gt;
                        &lt;td &gt;
                            &lt;img width=&quot;100&quot; height=&quot;100&quot; src=&quot;images/torva.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;
                        &lt;/td&gt;
                        &lt;td&gt;
                            &lt;h3&gt; Torva Platebody &lt;/h3&gt;
							Torva armour is a set of degradable high level melee equipment that requires 80 Defence and 80 Constitution to wear. It was first mentioned on 3 January 2011[1] and released into the game on 10 January 2011[2]. Torva armour pieces may only be obtained as rare drops from Nex, the boss of the Zarosian stronghold of the God Wars Dungeon, the Ancient Prison. It is the melee companion armour set to Virtus equipment and Pernix armour, which are Magic and Ranged sets, respectively.
							As level 80 equipment, Torva armour is currently the second highest-level melee armour in the game, behind Tetsu armour.
							Wearing any piece of Torva, Pernix, or Virtus armours, or wielding a zaryte bow, will cause all factions of monsters in the God Wars Dungeon (aside from bosses and zarosian monsters in the Ancient Prison) to be unaggressive.
							Torva armour is named and modelled after Torva, an elite warrior who served in Zaros&#39; army during the Second Age.
                        &lt;/td&gt;
                        &lt;td&gt;
                            $12.59
                        &lt;/td&gt;
                    &lt;/tr&gt;
                    &lt;tr&gt;
                        &lt;td &gt;
                           &lt;img width=&quot;100&quot; height=&quot;100&quot; src=&quot;images/partyhat.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;/&gt;
                        &lt;/td&gt;
                        &lt;td&gt;
                           &lt;h3&gt; Party Hat &lt;/h3&gt;
								Partyhats, abbreviated phats, are obtained by opening Christmas crackers, dropped during the 2001 Christmas event. There are six different coloured partyhats, all with the same shape and size. When worn by a player they resemble a crown. Because they are discontinued, they are very rare, much sought after and worth billions of coins, although they don&#39;t offer any stat bonuses. These are currently some of the most valuable objects in RuneScape. Partyhats are used to hold large sums of cash, because the gold coin limit is 2.147B and these hats are gaining wealth over time. Due to their rarity, these items hold a much higher Street value than their value on the Grand Exchange. In Runescape Classic, the price of partyhats was drastically changed after players abused this glitch by creating many partyhats. (See Partyhat duplication glitch for more info.) Due to their high price, they have become recognised as a symbol of wealth in the game by players and non-player characters alike.
								Over time, the volume of partyhats has been diminishing. The much smaller number of players when partyhats were released meant that not as many were acquired when available. Also, at the time of the release, partyhats were virtually worthless, meaning many players discarded them immediately. The majority of the few players who held onto them eventually quit RuneScape or were banned, leaving the number of active players with party hats at a very, very low number. The volume of partyhats diminished even further when players quit Runescape due to the EoC update and even alching the partyhat.
								Surprisingly, partyhats do play a pivotal role in the RuneScape economy. Players will use these items as investments, cash placements, staked items, and collectables. They are used as cash holders for players because of the stability of the item. Majority of partyhats are traded in world 2 around the grand exchange, but collectibles players wishing to buy or sell a partyhat may either have to advertise on the RuneScape forums, leave it in the Grand Exchange, or trade at much lower/higher prices to accommodate the few players that are willing to trade party hats.
                        &lt;/td&gt;
                        &lt;td&gt;
                            $17.50
                        &lt;/td&gt;
                    &lt;/tr&gt;
                    &lt;tr&gt;
                        &lt;td &gt;
                          &lt;img width=&quot;100&quot; height=&quot;100&quot; src=&quot;images/korasi.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;/&gt;
                        &lt;/td&gt;
                        &lt;td&gt;
                          &lt;h3&gt; Korasi&#39;s sword &lt;/h3&gt;
							Korasi&#39;s sword is a weapon obtained from the quest The Void Stares Back. Although it was officially released with the quest on 6 October 2010, it is also used in the earlier quest Quiet Before the Swarm, but only while in Korasi&#39;s mind. As the name suggests, the sword is the personal weapon of Commander Korasi, and is used to defeat the Pest Queen at the conclusion of The Void Stares Back. The sword itself requires 78 Attack and Strength to wield, and The Void Stares Back requires other skill requirements, which effectively act as additional minimum requirements to wield the sword.
							To use the Disrupt special move during The Void Stares Back whilst fighting the Pest Queen, a player would have to use the Backhand ability to activate it.
							If lost during The Void Stares Back, it can be re-obtained by speaking to either Korasi or Jessika, depending on the NPC saved during the quest. After the quest it can be re-purchased from Commodore Tyr for 500,000 coins. When lost upon death, the sword turns into 245,000 coins(Wilderness).
							Prior to the Evolution of Combat, Korasi&#39;s Sword had a magic special called Disrupt. This special made the sword very popular in PvP use for rushing or anti-rushing, as it could hit up to 800&#39;s and could not be blocked unless the target had Disruption Shield activated. This special, along with most other weapon specific special attacks, has been removed in the Evolution of Combat.
                        &lt;/td&gt;
                        &lt;td&gt;
                            $5.99
                        &lt;/td&gt;
                    &lt;/tr&gt;
                    &lt;tr&gt;
                        &lt;td &gt;
                         &lt;img width=&quot;100&quot; height=&quot;100&quot; src=&quot;images/ags.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;/&gt;
                        &lt;/td&gt;
                        &lt;td&gt;
                           &lt;h3&gt; Armadyl godsword &lt;/h3&gt;
								The Armadyl godsword is one of the four legendary godswords that was fought over during the God Wars. Requiring 75 Attack to wield, it is created by attaching an Armadyl hilt to a completed godsword blade, which has no requirements and can be done by any player. Along with the Bandos godsword, the Saradomin godsword, and the Zamorak godsword, the Armadyl godsword carries one of the highest damage bonuses in the surface world, surpassed only by vesta&#39;s spear and the chaotic maul.
								The armadyl godsword has a passive effect that hits 25% of the time; when it does, it raises the wielder&#39;s Attack and Strength levels by 1 each time, for up to 10% of the wielder&#39;s attack and strength levels. This boost does not stack with potions.
								After the Evolution of Combat, the Armadyl godsword is considered the least desirable godsword in general because its effect of raising the wielder&#39;s attack and strength level by 1, up to 10% of the wielder&#39;s level, is considerably inferior to the boost given by super potions and does not stack with them. Any uses this effect may have bogs down to saving a few inventory spaces a player would normally use for attack or strength potions, in the hope of lasting longer in PvM situations. However the Saradomin godsword is far superior at lasting longer in almost any conceivable situation. While the Armadyl godsword is considerably cheaper than the Saradomin godsword, the considerable difference in cost between the Armadyl godsword and the Bandos godsword (along with some super potions) doesn&#39;t realistically justify the former&#39;s use in any likely PvM or PvP situation a player chooses to engage in.
                        &lt;/td&gt;
                        &lt;td&gt;
                            $8.45
                        &lt;/td&gt;
                    &lt;/tr&gt;
                &lt;/table&gt;
            &lt;/div&gt;
		&lt;footer&gt;
			&lt;div class=&quot;center&quot;&gt;
				@Copyright SpiderPigs 2012-2013. All Rights Reserved. SpiderPigs is in no way affiliated with Jagex or Runescape. SpiderPigs exists purely for educational purposes only.
				&lt;br&gt;
				This website is objected to our &lt;a href=&quot;tos.html&quot;&gt;Terms and conditions&lt;/a&gt;. Any violations may lead to prosicution.
			&lt;/div&gt;
		&lt;/footer&gt;
	&lt;/body&gt;
&lt;/html&gt;[/code]

Enjoy :)</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 14 Apr 2013 17:39:56 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>General Programming</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/html-css-website-template/515932.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>HTML/CSS website template!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@sk8rdude461 sk8rdude461]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/sk8rdude461">@sk8rdude461</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I love it<br>
1 question <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/wink.png?v=5" title=":wink:" class="emoji" alt=":wink:"><br>
Is it w3 verified? heh</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/html-css-website-template/515932/8">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/html-css-website-template/515932/8</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 14 Apr 2013 17:39:56 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-515932-8</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/html-css-website-template/515932.rss">HTML/CSS website template!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>HTML/CSS website template!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Kidpaparoach Kidpaparoach]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/kidpaparoach">@Kidpaparoach</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Looks pretty nice. Rep++ for veela</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/html-css-website-template/515932/7">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/html-css-website-template/515932/7</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 14 Apr 2013 15:48:31 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-515932-7</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/html-css-website-template/515932.rss">HTML/CSS website template!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>HTML/CSS website template!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Ashi Ashi]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/ashi">@Ashi</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“Ruby, post:5, topic:515932”]Is there any particular reason why you change between single quotes (’) and double quotes (")?</p>
<p>Looks aesthetically pleasing but the code is a little weird, it’s like you’ve taken snippets of code from here there and everywhere to construct it. The single quotes then double quotes, you also only use  as a structural tag, what about   ? You also mix internal styling with external styling.</p>
<p>Overall it’s a good job, but just some of the code is a little quirky.[/quote]</p>
<p>There is not no specific reason for the quotes it just a habit more like e.g. i use quotes randomly and for the rest of the code its most likely me badly reflecting off from where i learnt most my crap. When I was learning html all the sources gave different information on what you should/shouldn’t do each of them going against each other) so I kinda do just throw code in lol.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/html-css-website-template/515932/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/html-css-website-template/515932/6</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 14 Apr 2013 14:44:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-515932-6</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/html-css-website-template/515932.rss">HTML/CSS website template!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>HTML/CSS website template!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Ruby_Forums_Coder Ruby]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/ruby_forums_coder">@Ruby_Forums_Coder</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Is there any particular reason why you change between single quotes (’) and double quotes (")?</p>
<p>Looks aesthetically pleasing but the code is a little weird, it’s like you’ve taken snippets of code from here there and everywhere to construct it. The single quotes then double quotes, you also only use  as a structural tag, what about   ? You also mix internal styling with external styling.</p>
<p>Overall it’s a good job, but just some of the code is a little quirky.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/html-css-website-template/515932/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/html-css-website-template/515932/5</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 14 Apr 2013 13:58:54 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-515932-5</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/html-css-website-template/515932.rss">HTML/CSS website template!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>HTML/CSS website template!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Ashi Ashi]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/ashi">@Ashi</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“nickb, post:3, topic:515932”]Looks cool, the only thing I’m wondering is:<br>
Are you realy making a class too center the footer text?[/quote]</p>
<p>I don’t know why I miss stuff out or do it differently to everything else. Thanks for pointing it out. I left footer blank which i was meant to get back too!</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/html-css-website-template/515932/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/html-css-website-template/515932/4</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 14 Apr 2013 12:23:07 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-515932-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/html-css-website-template/515932.rss">HTML/CSS website template!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>HTML/CSS website template!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@nickb nickb]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/nickb">@nickb</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Looks cool, the only thing I’m wondering is:<br>
Are you realy making a class too center the footer text?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/html-css-website-template/515932/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/html-css-website-template/515932/3</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 14 Apr 2013 09:02:06 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-515932-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/html-css-website-template/515932.rss">HTML/CSS website template!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>HTML/CSS website template!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Clawz_fury lare69]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/clawz_fury">@Clawz_fury</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>looks really good why r u releasing?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/html-css-website-template/515932/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/html-css-website-template/515932/2</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 13 Apr 2013 23:50:50 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-515932-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/html-css-website-template/515932.rss">HTML/CSS website template!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>HTML/CSS website template!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Ashi Ashi]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/ashi">@Ashi</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I made this myself using HTML/CSS. There are no PHP stuff added so you would need to add it in yourself if you want the vote/donation page to work!</p>
<p>Credits menucool for the image slider!</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Features: </span><br>
-Donation page<br>
-Vote page<br>
-Downloads page<br>
-Index<br>
-Really cool pop out webclient</p>
<p><img src="http://victoriaconnelly.co.uk/wp-content/uploads/2013/04/web.png" alt width="" height=""></p>
<p><img src="http://victoriaconnelly.co.uk/wp-content/uploads/2013/04/web1.png" alt width="" height=""></p>
<p>Download link: <a href="http://up.ht/16UVV2C" rel="nofollow noopener">http://up.ht/16UVV2C</a></p>
<p>Some code previews:</p>
<p>[index.html]</p>
<p>[code=html]</p>

	
		Index
		
		
			
		
	
	
		<div>
			<ul>
			   <li><a><span>Home</span></a></li>
			   <li><a><span>Forums</span></a></li>
			   <li><a><span>Vote</span></a></li>
			   <li><a><span>Donate</span></a></li>
			   <li><a><span>Download Client</span></a></li>
			   <li><a><span>Webclient</span></a></li>
			</ul>
		</div>
		<div>
			<div>
				<img alt>
				<img alt>
				<img alt>
				<img alt>
			</div>
			
			<div>
				<a></a>
				<a></a>
			</div>
			
			<div>
				<a></a>
				<a></a>
			</div>
		</div>
		<br>
		<div>
			<a><img alt></a>
			<a><img alt></a>
			<a><img alt></a>
		</div>
		<div>
			
			
		</div>
		
			<div>
				@Copyright SpiderPigs 2012-2013. All Rights Reserved. SpiderPigs is in no way affiliated with Jagex or Runescape. SpiderPigs exists purely for educational purposes only.
				<br>
				This website is objected to our <a>Terms and conditions</a>. Any violations may lead to prosicution.
			</div>
		
	
[/code]
<p>[donations.html]</p>
<p>[code=html]</p>

	
		Donation
		
		
	
	
		<div>
			<ul>
			   <li><a><span>Home</span></a></li>
			   <li><a><span>Forums</span></a></li>
			   <li><a><span>Vote</span></a></li>
			   <li><a><span>Donate</span></a></li>
			   <li><a><span>Download Client</span></a></li>
			   <li><a><span>Webclient</span></a></li>
			</ul>
		</div>
			<div>
				<br>
				<img alt>
			</div>
			<br>
		
			<table>
					<tr>
						<td>
						<hr>
							Please enter your username:
							<br>
							Please select an item:					
							
								 Torva's Platebody - $15.59 
								 Party Hat - $17.50 
								 Korasi's Sword - $5.99 
								 Armadyl Godsword - $8.45 
							
<pre><code>					&lt;/td&gt;
				&lt;/tr&gt;
			
				&lt;tr&gt;
					&lt;td&gt;
						&lt;input type="submit" name="submit" value="Donate Now!"/&gt;
						&lt;hr&gt;
					&lt;/td&gt;
				&lt;/tr&gt;
		&lt;/table&gt;
	&lt;/form&gt;
	&lt;div class="donator-table" &gt;
            &lt;table &gt;
                &lt;tr&gt;
                    &lt;td class="10"&gt;
                        Image
                    &lt;/td&gt;
                    &lt;td &gt;
                        Description
                    &lt;/td&gt;
                    &lt;td&gt;
                        Price
                    &lt;/td&gt;
                &lt;/tr&gt; 
                &lt;tr&gt;
                    &lt;td &gt;
                        &lt;img width="100" height="100" src="images/torva.png" alt="" /&gt;
                    &lt;/td&gt;
                    &lt;td&gt;
                        &lt;h3&gt; Torva Platebody &lt;/h3&gt;
						Torva armour is a set of degradable high level melee equipment that requires 80 Defence and 80 Constitution to wear. It was first mentioned on 3 January 2011[1] and released into the game on 10 January 2011[2]. Torva armour pieces may only be obtained as rare drops from Nex, the boss of the Zarosian stronghold of the God Wars Dungeon, the Ancient Prison. It is the melee companion armour set to Virtus equipment and Pernix armour, which are Magic and Ranged sets, respectively.
						As level 80 equipment, Torva armour is currently the second highest-level melee armour in the game, behind Tetsu armour.
						Wearing any piece of Torva, Pernix, or Virtus armours, or wielding a zaryte bow, will cause all factions of monsters in the God Wars Dungeon (aside from bosses and zarosian monsters in the Ancient Prison) to be unaggressive.
						Torva armour is named and modelled after Torva, an elite warrior who served in Zaros' army during the Second Age.
                    &lt;/td&gt;
                    &lt;td&gt;
                        $12.59
                    &lt;/td&gt;
                &lt;/tr&gt;
                &lt;tr&gt;
                    &lt;td &gt;
                       &lt;img width="100" height="100" src="images/partyhat.png" alt=""/&gt;
                    &lt;/td&gt;
                    &lt;td&gt;
                       &lt;h3&gt; Party Hat &lt;/h3&gt;
							Partyhats, abbreviated phats, are obtained by opening Christmas crackers, dropped during the 2001 Christmas event. There are six different coloured partyhats, all with the same shape and size. When worn by a player they resemble a crown. Because they are discontinued, they are very rare, much sought after and worth billions of coins, although they don't offer any stat bonuses. These are currently some of the most valuable objects in RuneScape. Partyhats are used to hold large sums of cash, because the gold coin limit is 2.147B and these hats are gaining wealth over time. Due to their rarity, these items hold a much higher Street value than their value on the Grand Exchange. In Runescape Classic, the price of partyhats was drastically changed after players abused this glitch by creating many partyhats. (See Partyhat duplication glitch for more info.) Due to their high price, they have become recognised as a symbol of wealth in the game by players and non-player characters alike.
							Over time, the volume of partyhats has been diminishing. The much smaller number of players when partyhats were released meant that not as many were acquired when available. Also, at the time of the release, partyhats were virtually worthless, meaning many players discarded them immediately. The majority of the few players who held onto them eventually quit RuneScape or were banned, leaving the number of active players with party hats at a very, very low number. The volume of partyhats diminished even further when players quit Runescape due to the EoC update and even alching the partyhat.
							Surprisingly, partyhats do play a pivotal role in the RuneScape economy. Players will use these items as investments, cash placements, staked items, and collectables. They are used as cash holders for players because of the stability of the item. Majority of partyhats are traded in world 2 around the grand exchange, but collectibles players wishing to buy or sell a partyhat may either have to advertise on the RuneScape forums, leave it in the Grand Exchange, or trade at much lower/higher prices to accommodate the few players that are willing to trade party hats.
                    &lt;/td&gt;
                    &lt;td&gt;
                        $17.50
                    &lt;/td&gt;
                &lt;/tr&gt;
                &lt;tr&gt;
                    &lt;td &gt;
                      &lt;img width="100" height="100" src="images/korasi.png" alt=""/&gt;
                    &lt;/td&gt;
                    &lt;td&gt;
                      &lt;h3&gt; Korasi's sword &lt;/h3&gt;
						Korasi's sword is a weapon obtained from the quest The Void Stares Back. Although it was officially released with the quest on 6 October 2010, it is also used in the earlier quest Quiet Before the Swarm, but only while in Korasi's mind. As the name suggests, the sword is the personal weapon of Commander Korasi, and is used to defeat the Pest Queen at the conclusion of The Void Stares Back. The sword itself requires 78 Attack and Strength to wield, and The Void Stares Back requires other skill requirements, which effectively act as additional minimum requirements to wield the sword.
						To use the Disrupt special move during The Void Stares Back whilst fighting the Pest Queen, a player would have to use the Backhand ability to activate it.
						If lost during The Void Stares Back, it can be re-obtained by speaking to either Korasi or Jessika, depending on the NPC saved during the quest. After the quest it can be re-purchased from Commodore Tyr for 500,000 coins. When lost upon death, the sword turns into 245,000 coins(Wilderness).
						Prior to the Evolution of Combat, Korasi's Sword had a magic special called Disrupt. This special made the sword very popular in PvP use for rushing or anti-rushing, as it could hit up to 800's and could not be blocked unless the target had Disruption Shield activated. This special, along with most other weapon specific special attacks, has been removed in the Evolution of Combat.
                    &lt;/td&gt;
                    &lt;td&gt;
                        $5.99
                    &lt;/td&gt;
                &lt;/tr&gt;
                &lt;tr&gt;
                    &lt;td &gt;
                     &lt;img width="100" height="100" src="images/ags.png" alt=""/&gt;
                    &lt;/td&gt;
                    &lt;td&gt;
                       &lt;h3&gt; Armadyl godsword &lt;/h3&gt;
							The Armadyl godsword is one of the four legendary godswords that was fought over during the God Wars. Requiring 75 Attack to wield, it is created by attaching an Armadyl hilt to a completed godsword blade, which has no requirements and can be done by any player. Along with the Bandos godsword, the Saradomin godsword, and the Zamorak godsword, the Armadyl godsword carries one of the highest damage bonuses in the surface world, surpassed only by vesta's spear and the chaotic maul.
							The armadyl godsword has a passive effect that hits 25% of the time; when it does, it raises the wielder's Attack and Strength levels by 1 each time, for up to 10% of the wielder's attack and strength levels. This boost does not stack with potions.
							After the Evolution of Combat, the Armadyl godsword is considered the least desirable godsword in general because its effect of raising the wielder's attack and strength level by 1, up to 10% of the wielder's level, is considerably inferior to the boost given by super potions and does not stack with them. Any uses this effect may have bogs down to saving a few inventory spaces a player would normally use for attack or strength potions, in the hope of lasting longer in PvM situations. However the Saradomin godsword is far superior at lasting longer in almost any conceivable situation. While the Armadyl godsword is considerably cheaper than the Saradomin godsword, the considerable difference in cost between the Armadyl godsword and the Bandos godsword (along with some super potions) doesn't realistically justify the former's use in any likely PvM or PvP situation a player chooses to engage in.
                    &lt;/td&gt;
                    &lt;td&gt;
                        $8.45
                    &lt;/td&gt;
                &lt;/tr&gt;
            &lt;/table&gt;
        &lt;/div&gt;
	&lt;footer&gt;
		&lt;div class="center"&gt;
			@Copyright SpiderPigs 2012-2013. All Rights Reserved. SpiderPigs is in no way affiliated with Jagex or Runescape. SpiderPigs exists purely for educational purposes only.
			&lt;br&gt;
			This website is objected to our &lt;a href="tos.html"&gt;Terms and conditions&lt;/a&gt;. Any violations may lead to prosicution.
		&lt;/div&gt;
	&lt;/footer&gt;
&lt;/body&gt;
</code></pre>
[/code]
<p>Enjoy <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=5" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
</td>
</tr>
</table>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/html-css-website-template/515932/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/html-css-website-template/515932/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 13 Apr 2013 21:53:18 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-515932-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/html-css-website-template/515932.rss">HTML/CSS website template!</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
