<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Need help adding a few things please</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/need-help-adding-a-few-things-please/421897</link>
    <description>HiI need some help on how to add something

Basically what I am trying to do is add a counter which adds up every kill and death in a specified area so for example if the area was in falador I would want the counter to appear at the top right of the screen and go up everytime someone killed say.. a guard and the death counter to go up everytime a player dies I need this badly for my plans with my server but im not sure how to do it if you guys can help I thank you very much</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 17 Nov 2011 05:47:08 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/need-help-adding-a-few-things-please/421897.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Need help adding a few things please</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@fasthop10 fasthop10]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/fasthop10">@fasthop10</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>you could make a new interface and add it to the client , but if you just want text displaed you can use one thats already there and change the text lines to what you need, i personaly tend to use the pc interface when i need text displayed on my screen if offers many lines of text. and you will need to define the area for whitch you want this to display on the screen and set your lines and as he said above add the playerkill and player deaths to the player save, the inefficiant way to load that a player killed something would be to add a playerKills += 1; in the npc manager i believ it is for each npc id that is spawned in the area, a better more efficient way is to check for npcneedspawn inside the listed coords you want. the better way would take more effort but offers alot less glitches in the end. most of this info to do just about everything you need to do can be found in the pc minigame files as it is basicly has all the same things in it that you need to do. if you need any further help in finding what to do.</p>
<p>ps. if you want something other then just text to display on the screen  you will need a new interface, but if its just text there are numerous interfaces already there that offer text display.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/need-help-adding-a-few-things-please/421897/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/need-help-adding-a-few-things-please/421897/3</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 17 Nov 2011 05:47:08 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-421897-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/need-help-adding-a-few-things-please/421897.rss">Need help adding a few things please</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Need help adding a few things please</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@3lv3n_snip3r 3lv3n snip3r]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/3lv3n_snip3r">@3lv3n_snip3r</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Make a little interface for it in RSInterface.java.<br>
Go into PlayerAssistant.java and find where you added pkPoints and make a thing in PlayerSave.java like PlayerKills or just use KC.</p>
<p>Add this with your pkPoints in PlayerAssistant.java if you used this.</p>
<pre><code class="lang-auto"></code></pre>
<p>For something like a death counter, do the opposite with the PlayerKills.</p>
<p>Add:</p>
<pre><code class="lang-auto"></code></pre>
<p>Under or above <code>o.PlayerKills += 1;</code></p>
<p>This is just something quick and could be made better, but it’s just to get you started.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/need-help-adding-a-few-things-please/421897/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/need-help-adding-a-few-things-please/421897/2</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 17 Nov 2011 03:59:38 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-421897-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/need-help-adding-a-few-things-please/421897.rss">Need help adding a few things please</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Need help adding a few things please</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@elatechris elatechris]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/elatechris">@elatechris</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>HiI need some help on how to add something</p>
<p>Basically what I am trying to do is add a counter which adds up every kill and death in a specified area so for example if the area was in falador I would want the counter to appear at the top right of the screen and go up everytime someone killed say… a guard and the death counter to go up everytime a player dies I need this badly for my plans with my server but im not sure how to do it if you guys can help I thank you very much</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/need-help-adding-a-few-things-please/421897/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/need-help-adding-a-few-things-please/421897/1</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 17 Nov 2011 00:35:27 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-421897-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/need-help-adding-a-few-things-please/421897.rss">Need help adding a few things please</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
