<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Custom Client? Custom item need help moving it into client! READ!</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/custom-client-custom-item-need-help-moving-it-into-client-read/325514</link>
    <description>I made a few custom items and move it into the client and compiled, everything works good but how do you make it say a different name for the item. For instance, I change Dragon Battleaxe a different look and name, but the name I don&#39;t know how to change. In the source I change it but it only shows the new name when your choosing attack styes. But when it&#39;s in your bag it still has dragon battleaxe as name, how do I change it to what I want. Someone told me in client, but what file, like Applet_Sub1 or what! there so many and I don&#39;t know where, Please help! I asked for help months ago and no one answered me =(

Pleaseee help, Thanks.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 14 Jan 2010 03:16:52 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/custom-client-custom-item-need-help-moving-it-into-client-read/325514.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Custom Client? Custom item need help moving it into client! READ!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@wanbliscape wanbliscape]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/wanbliscape">@wanbliscape</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I made a few custom items and move it into the client and compiled, everything works good but how do you make it say a different name for the item. For instance, I change Dragon Battleaxe a different look and name, but the name I don’t know how to change. In the source I change it but it only shows the new name when your choosing attack styes. But when it’s in your bag it still has dragon battleaxe as name, how do I change it to what I want. Someone told me in client, but what file, like Applet_Sub1 or what! there so many and I don’t know where, Please help! I asked for help months ago and no one answered me =(</p>
<p>Pleaseee help, Thanks.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/custom-client-custom-item-need-help-moving-it-into-client-read/325514/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/custom-client-custom-item-need-help-moving-it-into-client-read/325514/1</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 14 Jan 2010 03:16:52 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-325514-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/custom-client-custom-item-need-help-moving-it-into-client-read/325514.rss">Custom Client? Custom item need help moving it into client! READ!</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
