<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>My Dream~</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-dream/549213</link>
    <description>Im part of The RSPS community and have been playing rsps&#39;s since &#39;09. I quit RS after eoc came out ever since then server&#39;s are just fun temperarily but not in the long run. To cut the story short I&#39;m  looking for Dev&#39;s, previous owners, and anyone that has good intentions, time, and dedication. I have a dev helping me out as of right now but the time limitations with him are really slowing down the process. If anyone wants to join pm me or leave ur skype down below. I am interested in advice and anything that can help me in the long run as well~

if u want you can pm me on skype as well - Kingharmizzle</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2015 17:49:25 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-dream/549213.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>My Dream~</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@BluEcstacy BluEcstacy]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/bluecstacy">@BluEcstacy</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Im part of The RSPS community and have been playing rsps’s since '09. I quit RS after eoc came out ever since then server’s are just fun temperarily but not in the long run. To cut the story short I’m  looking for Dev’s, previous owners, and anyone that has good intentions, time, and dedication. I have a dev helping me out as of right now but the time limitations with him are really slowing down the process. If anyone wants to join pm me or leave ur skype down below. I am interested in advice and anything that can help me in the long run as well~</p>
<p>if u want you can pm me on skype as well - Kingharmizzle</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-dream/549213/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-dream/549213/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2015 17:49:25 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-549213-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-dream/549213.rss">My Dream~</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
