<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>My homework story</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-homework-story/182552</link>
    <description>Well, we had to write a 3 page story that was on something that has happened to us recently for homework. I just competed mine and thought I&#39;d post it. I decided to do mine on when I competed at Regional Championships this day last month. Also, don&#39;t worry about grammar, as this is only the &quot;prototype&quot; of it. My real copy is in my English workbook. Enjoy:


&lt;blockquote&gt;5:30 am, Sunday morning.. Here I am. Laying awake staring at the marks in the ceiling imagining the day ahead. What was to come? 
Dad walked into my room and grinned at me “Up you get matey`, it&#39;s time”. Ahh music to my ears, I sprung up, got out of bed, changed, walked straight to the car...

Dad hooked up the trailer and within the next 10 minutes, we were on the road. We had a quick stop at Macca&#39;s to grab something to chew. My heart was beating and my hands were shaking so vigorously, most of my burger found its way on to my lap. The next hour seemed to go so quickly, it was as if something was taking over my entire body. Could this be it, have I finally reached my goal? 

Thirty minutes later, we had arrived. I saw the sign, “LMMC” (Lake Macquarie Motocross Club) I couldn&#39;t help noticing how full the spectators area was with heaps of great looking chicks selling food and drinks. Was I in heaven?   

Dad popped the top on the trailer, and we started setting up. My legs seemed to forget that they belonged to me, I couldn&#39;t move. I dropped my helmet on my toe and fell over the trailer door. A five year old girl helped me to my feet. The applause from the older boys fueled my nerves.
I jumped a meter when the  announcer bellowed, “Sign on will begin in a few moments.”.
“Go sign in” Dad said. “I&#39;ll finish setting up”.
“Yeah, okay.” I answered as I began searching through my gear bag.. “Errr... Dad, I think I&#39;ve forgotten my license.”. I seriously hope to never be on the end of the look dad gave me again .
&quot;You&#39;re joking aren&#39;t you?&quot;
I wished I was. Just as i was about to drift into depression, that precious piece of plastic fell out of my jacket pocket. I was back.

Filled with hope and joy, I began preparing my bike, setting tire pressure, etc. The usual race-day procedure.
“All competitors are to bring their equipment to the pit entrance for scrutineering, immediately.”
I managed to be first there, so they started examining my bike, checking the spokes on the tires, etc. My mine was in a spin.
“Yep, you&#39;re right. Take your position. Ride hard, fast and safely”. The man said as he put the red dot on my number plate.
“Come on Kyle settle down, this is a walk in the grass, focus, focus.” Directed dad.

I was more nervous than I ever have been in my entire life my teeth were chattering. This is it, now or never,
“All 85cc Big Wheel 13-16 year olds to the grid please.&quot; The announcer said over the loud speaker. Well, here we go. I quickly put my helmet on and rested my goggles on my handlebars. Slowly I began to ride my bike to the grid area. As I turned towards the gate, I was hit with a titlewave of thoughts, I wasn&#39;t sure if was still breathing.

I was focused on was the 30 second board, held by the official. It dropped sideways and I clicked my bike into gear. I lent forward and watched the gate ever so closely..... It dropped, game on.

Heads in the crowd turned as we all charged into the first corner. Down the straight I began to attack, riders were falling down everywhere. Next the rutted second corner. I went on the outside line and came out next to the rider next to me. Over the massive drop off we went. The sweat was fogging my goggles. By the 20th lap my arms and legs were in crippling pain. The checked flag was a sight of bliss.

I had finished I was fore filled I had found my destiny.
It&#39;s fast, it&#39;s dangerous and it&#39;s extremely physically demanding. That&#39;s motocross.&lt;/blockquote&gt;</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 19 Feb 2008 22:11:58 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>General Discussion</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-homework-story/182552.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>My homework story</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Baros_Rocks Baros Rocks]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/baros_rocks">@Baros_Rocks</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I can read. It says nothing about spelling there.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-homework-story/182552/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-homework-story/182552/4</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 19 Feb 2008 22:11:58 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-182552-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-homework-story/182552.rss">My homework story</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>My homework story</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Yz85Racer Yz85Racer]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/yz85racer">@Yz85Racer</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote no-group quote-modified" data-post="2" data-topic="182552">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 Baros Rocks:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>[quote]Could this be it, have <span class="bbcode-b">a</span> finally reached my goal? </p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p>I wasn’t <span class="bbcode-b">shore</span> if was still breathing</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Not sure if they was implanted there purposely but they don’t make sense to me.[/quote]<br>
Yeah. I know, can you not read?</p>
<aside class="quote no-group quote-modified" data-post="1" data-topic="182552">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/yz85racer/40/5_6bca9977b612b7aeef77ba1ec1cd67b3.png" class="avatar"> Yz85Racer:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Also, don’t worry about grammar, as this is only the “prototype” of it. My real copy is in my English workbook.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-homework-story/182552/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-homework-story/182552/3</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 19 Feb 2008 09:41:35 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-182552-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-homework-story/182552.rss">My homework story</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>My homework story</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Baros_Rocks Baros Rocks]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/baros_rocks">@Baros_Rocks</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <blockquote>Could this be it, have [b]a[/b] finally reached my goal?</blockquote>
<blockquote>I wasn't [b]shore[/b] if was still breathing</blockquote>
<p>Not sure if they was implanted there purposely but they don’t make sense to me.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-homework-story/182552/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-homework-story/182552/2</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 18 Feb 2008 18:07:39 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-182552-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-homework-story/182552.rss">My homework story</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>My homework story</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Yz85Racer Yz85Racer]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/yz85racer">@Yz85Racer</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Well, we had to write a 3 page story that was on something that has happened to us recently for homework. I just competed mine and thought I’d post it. I decided to do mine on when I competed at Regional Championships this day last month. Also, don’t worry about grammar, as this is only the “prototype” of it. My real copy is in my English workbook. Enjoy:</p>
<blockquote>5:30 am, Sunday morning.. Here I am. Laying awake staring at the marks in the ceiling imagining the day ahead. What was to come? 
Dad walked into my room and grinned at me “Up you get matey`, it's time”. Ahh music to my ears, I sprung up, got out of bed, changed, walked straight to the car...
<p>Dad hooked up the trailer and within the next 10 minutes, we were on the road. We had a quick stop at Macca’s to grab something to chew. My heart was beating and my hands were shaking so vigorously, most of my burger found its way on to my lap. The next hour seemed to go so quickly, it was as if something was taking over my entire body. Could this be it, have I finally reached my goal?</p>
<p>Thirty minutes later, we had arrived. I saw the sign, “LMMC” (Lake Macquarie Motocross Club) I couldn’t help noticing how full the spectators area was with heaps of great looking chicks selling food and drinks. Was I in heaven?</p>
<p>Dad popped the top on the trailer, and we started setting up. My legs seemed to forget that they belonged to me, I couldn’t move. I dropped my helmet on my toe and fell over the trailer door. A five year old girl helped me to my feet. The applause from the older boys fueled my nerves.<br>
I jumped a meter when the  announcer bellowed, “Sign on will begin in a few moments.”.<br>
“Go sign in” Dad said. “I’ll finish setting up”.<br>
“Yeah, okay.” I answered as I began searching through my gear bag… “Errr… Dad, I think I’ve forgotten my license.”. I seriously hope to never be on the end of the look dad gave me again .<br>
“You’re joking aren’t you?”<br>
I wished I was. Just as i was about to drift into depression, that precious piece of plastic fell out of my jacket pocket. I was back.</p>
<p>Filled with hope and joy, I began preparing my bike, setting tire pressure, etc. The usual race-day procedure.<br>
“All competitors are to bring their equipment to the pit entrance for scrutineering, immediately.”<br>
I managed to be first there, so they started examining my bike, checking the spokes on the tires, etc. My mine was in a spin.<br>
“Yep, you’re right. Take your position. Ride hard, fast and safely”. The man said as he put the red dot on my number plate.<br>
“Come on Kyle settle down, this is a walk in the grass, focus, focus.” Directed dad.</p>
<p>I was more nervous than I ever have been in my entire life my teeth were chattering. This is it, now or never,<br>
“All 85cc Big Wheel 13-16 year olds to the grid please." The announcer said over the loud speaker. Well, here we go. I quickly put my helmet on and rested my goggles on my handlebars. Slowly I began to ride my bike to the grid area. As I turned towards the gate, I was hit with a titlewave of thoughts, I wasn’t sure if was still breathing.</p>
<p>I was focused on was the 30 second board, held by the official. It dropped sideways and I clicked my bike into gear. I lent forward and watched the gate ever so closely… It dropped, game on.</p>
<p>Heads in the crowd turned as we all charged into the first corner. Down the straight I began to attack, riders were falling down everywhere. Next the rutted second corner. I went on the outside line and came out next to the rider next to me. Over the massive drop off we went. The sweat was fogging my goggles. By the 20th lap my arms and legs were in crippling pain. The checked flag was a sight of bliss.</p>
<p>I had finished I was fore filled I had found my destiny.<br>
It’s fast, it’s dangerous and it’s extremely physically demanding. That’s motocross.</p>
</blockquote>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-homework-story/182552/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-homework-story/182552/1</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 18 Feb 2008 11:26:01 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-182552-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-homework-story/182552.rss">My homework story</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
