<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Deadlock [PI]</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/deadlock-pi/380022</link>
    <description>My server has recently been going offline a lot, and the biggest issue is that it isn&#39;t easily resolved, since the command line for the server shows no signs of anything happening. There are no errors being thrown, it just stops updating.

I looked into this and found out this is called a Deadlock, which is caused when two synchronized threads are waiting for the other to finish. Since they are waiting on eachother, they lock up and the server stops responding.

You can use jconsole to detect deadlocks in a java application and figure out what threads are causing it, but I can&#39;t get it to connect to the server.
Does anyone know how to get it to connect to an RSPS, or know any other ways to detect a deadlock?</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 26 Jan 2011 05:02:41 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/deadlock-pi/380022.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Deadlock [PI]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@revengr revengr]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/revengr">@revengr</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>My server has recently been going offline a lot, and the biggest issue is that it isn’t easily resolved, since the command line for the server shows no signs of anything happening. There are no errors being thrown, it just stops updating.</p>
<p>I looked into this and found out this is called a Deadlock, which is caused when two synchronized threads are waiting for the other to finish. Since they are waiting on eachother, they lock up and the server stops responding.</p>
<p>You can use jconsole to detect deadlocks in a java application and figure out what threads are causing it, but I can’t get it to connect to the server.<br>
Does anyone know how to get it to connect to an RSPS, or know any other ways to detect a deadlock?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/deadlock-pi/380022/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/deadlock-pi/380022/1</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 26 Jan 2011 05:02:41 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-380022-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/deadlock-pi/380022.rss">Deadlock [PI]</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
