<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Runescape Map</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/runescape-map/176416</link>
    <description>Deciding the correct forum to ask this in was difficult but in the end it seemed to be more on the Server Development side more than Client Hacking side.

Now my friend owns a private server (not saying the name) and I am part of his coding team.
Recently we were scouting new spots we could have as training spots, ban spots, testing spots, etc.
While scouting we came across many many sections of runescape in random parts of the world of runescape in small sections.
I.E. We found the main part of Draynor but surrounded in black, like someone cut a peice of Draynor out and placed it somewhere, we came to believe this was for early testing or something to that effect.
Well the whole point of this is to find out if there is a program out there with the entire map of runescape available to scroll through or veiw some other way.
I&#39;m not interested in the map that Fagex has released, we are interested in seeing EVERYTHING runescape has to offer. If this hasn&#39;t been done (probably because nobody has ever been interested enough to make one) then I was wondering if there was a way to do this. My friend is working on it but he has his hands full with a decently popular server and a cache editor that he is working on, so I thought i&#39;d look into this for him. It doesn&#39;t seem like it would be very difficult.
I am fairly good at Java and learning as much as I can every day.
So at this point I ask for YOUR help. If you have ANY information on this then please do share.
Please post any HELPFUL information that you have, please don&#39;t post things like &quot;No, this is impossible.&quot; if in reality you have no idea what you are talking about. I am looking for information from people who know what they are doing, which is why I came here.
If you wish you can add my msn. (aceofspades7078@msn.com)

Thanks everyone. =]
-Justin</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 27 Jan 2008 09:55:20 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/runescape-map/176416.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Runescape Map</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@6aceofspades 6aceofspades]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/6aceofspades">@6aceofspades</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Well considering I cannot be helped here, do you have any ideas where I can be helped?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/runescape-map/176416/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/runescape-map/176416/2</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 27 Jan 2008 09:55:20 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-176416-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/runescape-map/176416.rss">Runescape Map</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Runescape Map</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@6aceofspades 6aceofspades]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/6aceofspades">@6aceofspades</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Deciding the correct forum to ask this in was difficult but in the end it seemed to be more on the Server Development side more than Client Hacking side.</p>
<p>Now my friend owns a private server (not saying the name) and I am part of his coding team.<br>
Recently we were scouting new spots we could have as training spots, ban spots, testing spots, etc.<br>
While scouting we came across many many sections of runescape in random parts of the world of runescape in small sections.<br>
I.E. We found the main part of Draynor but surrounded in black, like someone cut a peice of Draynor out and placed it somewhere, we came to believe this was for early testing or something to that effect.<br>
Well the whole point of this is to find out if there is a program out there with the entire map of runescape available to scroll through or veiw some other way.<br>
I’m not interested in the map that Fagex has released, we are interested in seeing EVERYTHING runescape has to offer. If this hasn’t been done (probably because nobody has ever been interested enough to make one) then I was wondering if there was a way to do this. My friend is working on it but he has his hands full with a decently popular server and a cache editor that he is working on, so I thought i’d look into this for him. It doesn’t seem like it would be very difficult.<br>
I am fairly good at Java and learning as much as I can every day.<br>
So at this point I ask for YOUR help. If you have ANY information on this then please do share.<br>
Please post any HELPFUL information that you have, please don’t post things like “No, this is impossible.” if in reality you have no idea what you are talking about. I am looking for information from people who know what they are doing, which is why I came here.<br>
If you wish you can add my msn. (<a href="mailto:aceofspades7078@msn.com">aceofspades7078@msn.com</a>)</p>
<p>Thanks everyone. =]<br>
-Justin</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/runescape-map/176416/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/runescape-map/176416/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 27 Jan 2008 09:15:01 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-176416-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/runescape-map/176416.rss">Runescape Map</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
