<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Guidance</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/guidance/550123</link>
    <description>I&#39;ve learned the basics of a few different things. Whether it be simple python, java, c, html/css/js, I know the basic syntax of each of them. 

I&#39;m a junior in high school and plan on doing something related into CS in college and I could really use some opinions. I&#39;m interested in pretty much every division of computers that you can think of. 

I&#39;m not very good at math, but I do realize that math is pretty important in college for this type of thing and I will grind it out if I must.

Basically in my situation.. Which direction would you go, which language would you try and extend your knowledge, what major would you pick, Why?</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2015 17:55:09 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>General Programming</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/guidance/550123.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Guidance</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@chassy13 Chassy13]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/chassy13">@chassy13</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I’m currently on my 4th semester with my school’s software engineering program, which is pretty much a combined CS and SE degree at my university, with application classes using hardware as well. So, in my case, I get a mixture of all three majors.</p>
<p>I am currently in Calculus II, and have yet to take Calc III, Discrete Mathematics, Stats, and Differential Equations or Linear Algebra. I am also required to take two years of physics. I am sure it varies depending on schools, but if you’re looking into any form of engineering…buckle down on math, and literally everything else. It (and any form of engineering OR computer-related field) is a challenging program. And yes, Computer Science still has plenty of math. Take any AP math courses your high school offers, because even if you don’t test out of them then you have the experience.</p>
<p>Currently I’ve taken classes utilizing the languages Java, C++, and right now, x86 Assembly. I will learn more languages in future courses.</p>
<p>Look into internships even as a freshman. You likely won’t get one that soon, but I managed to snag one as a sophomore where I will likely be doing some software analysis and working on a small project for a loan-service company. Looks good on a resume, teaches you what the real world is like, and might even help pay for school.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/guidance/550123/11">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/guidance/550123/11</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2015 17:55:09 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-550123-11</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/guidance/550123.rss">Guidance</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Guidance</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@justaguy justaguy]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/justaguy">@justaguy</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote" data-post="5" data-topic="550123">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 Bowser jr:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Fat Cookies: What are the benefits of a pure functional programming language compared to a more mixed one like Scala?</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Scheme and OCaml are impure.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/guidance/550123/10">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/guidance/550123/10</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2015 16:56:09 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-550123-10</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/guidance/550123.rss">Guidance</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Guidance</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@x_rush_x x rush x]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/x_rush_x">@x_rush_x</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>If you go into computer science, you will deal with multiple languages, in canada, montreal, our university and colleges focus you around, C, C#, C++, JAVA, SQL, PHP, they run you through abit of all of em, my personal suggestion is read some books or ebooks or sites around the C’s, most object oriented languages have similar syntax so you will find yourself learning others easier after learning one, but its best to learn 1 at a time or you can risk confusing yourself lol… thank being said, ultimately what are your goals? game programming, software development, hacking, different languages are used for different things and once you know your end goal then its easier to say which one you should focus on most.</p>
<p>anyways, good luck and all the best with your schooling <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=5" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/guidance/550123/9">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/guidance/550123/9</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2015 14:52:35 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-550123-9</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/guidance/550123.rss">Guidance</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Guidance</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Fat_Cookies Fat Cookies]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/fat_cookies">@Fat_Cookies</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote" data-post="5" data-topic="550123">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 Bowser jr:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Fat Cookies: What are the benefits of a pure functional programming language compared to a more mixed one like Scala?</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I’m not one of those “hurr durr pure functional or gtfo” kind of fellows but for learning functional concepts it’s nice to have a language that essentially forces you to program functionally. I’m not too bothered if I write a lengthy Scheme/Haskell program and it doesn’t actually do anything useful provided I learnt something along the way <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=5" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"> Some people prefer learning by creating practical applications.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/guidance/550123/8">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/guidance/550123/8</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2015 10:15:23 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-550123-8</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/guidance/550123.rss">Guidance</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Guidance</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Yz85Racer Yz85Racer]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/yz85racer">@Yz85Racer</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Lin’s advice seems sound, excluding the part which says “most jobs don’t require a bachelor’s degree from what I’ve looked into”. Not sure what jobs you’ve looked into, but most usually require a degree in a related field or lots of work experience.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/guidance/550123/7">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/guidance/550123/7</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2015 05:24:39 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-550123-7</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/guidance/550123.rss">Guidance</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Guidance</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Lin Lin]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/lin">@Lin</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“Bowser jr, post:2, topic:550123”]I would learn a database language and how to properly model a database. Other than that you should improve your programming skills, it doesn’t matter if you know everything about Java syntax and the standard libs if you don’t know how to program a complex program. Learning any new language shouldn’t be too hard if you know Java, C++ and Python. You should also learn how to properly work in a team, but that might not be as easy for you to practise at this moment.[/quote]This this and so much this. Note that most jobs don’t require a bachelor’s degree from what I’ve looked into, but almost all of them require you know SQL and how to manage databases. Experience and familiarity with existing and widely-used libraries helps too.</p>
<p>If there’s one piece of unique advice I can offer, it’s to do what you want. I went to college immediately after graduating from high school and dropped out as a junior a few weeks ago. Don’t learn what will just make you the most money, but what will help you get where you want. College isn’t as required as people say it is, and any smart employer knows that someone with years and years of programming experience and a gigantic portfolio with (at least some) experience working in groups is better than someone fresh out of college with a piece of paper.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/guidance/550123/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/guidance/550123/6</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2015 03:05:56 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-550123-6</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/guidance/550123.rss">Guidance</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Guidance</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@bowserjr2 Bowser jr]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/bowserjr2">@bowserjr2</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Fat Cookies: What are the benefits of a pure functional programming language compared to a more mixed one like Scala?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/guidance/550123/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/guidance/550123/5</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2015 01:10:54 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-550123-5</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/guidance/550123.rss">Guidance</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Guidance</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Fat_Cookies Fat Cookies]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/fat_cookies">@Fat_Cookies</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Knowing the basic syntax of a programming language is useful but if you want to go into further education <span class="bbcode-b">understanding</span> a programming language is what counts.</p>
<p>Extending on what justaguy said: if you want to go into software development it’s great to expose yourself to as many languages and different technologies! If you like javascript node.js is a great thing to get familiar with. If you like hardware, robotics go learn the in and outs of C and even some assembly - you could pick up a raspberry pi and program ARM assembly!</p>
<p>As a computer scientist I’d recommend dipping your toes into functional programming - python has a few functional features pushed into it on the side however if you really want to learn programming in a functional style you should have a go at <a href="http://mitpress.mit.edu/sicp/full-text/book/book.html" data-bbcode="true">learning Scheme</a>. Once you’ve familiarised yourself with Scheme you might want to check out more pure function languages like Haskell or OCaml.</p>
<p>On a side note if you’re still unsure on what you want to study, a bog standard Computer Science degree is a good compromise and will mean you get to study things from all sorts of fields.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/guidance/550123/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/guidance/550123/4</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2015 00:05:10 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-550123-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/guidance/550123.rss">Guidance</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Guidance</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@justaguy justaguy]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/justaguy">@justaguy</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Being in high school and thinking about your career path is very important and it’s good you’re doing it early. With that said you have several things to consider…</p>
<p>Figure out what field of computers you want to study for your degree. Since you mention CS-related subjects, here are a few off the top of my head:</p>
<p>[ul][li]Computer Engineering - Deals mainly with the hardware aspects of computers such as digital circuits, electronics, computer architecture, programming, etc. You will be taking physics and lots of applied and discrete mathematics (especially math courses that will complement your physics courses) and also programming courses.[/li]<br>
[li]Software Engineering - Deals with the software development life-cycle and programming from an engineering perspective (design, testing, and modelling software). Lots of programming and applied mathematics[/li]<br>
[li]Computer Science - Deals with the mathematical basis of computers and programming; to sum it up generally you’re basically studying algorithms (these include programs). <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/cool.png?v=5" title=":cool:" class="emoji" alt=":cool:"> You’ll end up taking a lot of discrete mathematics, and if you want to study theoretical computer science,  you will also be studying a lot of logic graph theory. This is what I’m currently taking as a second-year university student so feel free to ask me questions about this either here or via PM.[/li][/ul]</p>
<p>This is generally how my school approaches these. Any creditable program will require you to take atleast a few math courses so prepare yourself early.</p>
<p>My advice for for extending your programming knowledge would be to stay competent with the web (the internet of things is becoming even more relevant these days) and to learn more C and Python. C is great because it’s a statically-typed language that can help you understand computers and lower-level programming while being a high-level language. Python is great because it is a dynamically-typed language and also has object-oriented capabilities which are also relevant. Usually introductory college courses on programming use Python or Java (from what I’ve noticed).</p>
<p>It never hurts trying out different languages, even if you don’t master them, because you learn many techniques and paradigms which are mostly transferable to other languages.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/guidance/550123/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/guidance/550123/3</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2015 22:49:08 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-550123-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/guidance/550123.rss">Guidance</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Guidance</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@bowserjr2 Bowser jr]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/bowserjr2">@bowserjr2</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I would learn a database language and how to properly model a database. Other than that you should improve your programming skills, it doesn’t matter if you know everything about Java syntax and the standard libs if you don’t know how to program a complex program. Learning any new language shouldn’t be too hard if you know Java, C++ and Python. You should also learn how to properly work in a team, but that might not be as easy for you to practise at this moment.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/guidance/550123/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/guidance/550123/2</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2015 21:50:34 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-550123-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/guidance/550123.rss">Guidance</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Guidance</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@ISUB ISUB]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/isub">@ISUB</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I’ve learned the basics of a few different things. Whether it be simple python, java, c, html/css/js, I know the basic syntax of each of them.</p>
<p>I’m a junior in high school and plan on doing something related into CS in college and I could really use some opinions. I’m interested in pretty much every division of computers that you can think of.</p>
<p>I’m not very good at math, but I do realize that math is pretty important in college for this type of thing and I will grind it out if I must.</p>
<p>Basically in my situation… Which direction would you go, which language would you try and extend your knowledge, what major would you pick, Why?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/guidance/550123/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/guidance/550123/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2015 21:38:18 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-550123-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/guidance/550123.rss">Guidance</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
