<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Cloning an item</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/cloning-an-item/424541</link>
    <description>I would imagine this would be mostly client sided. But my question is how would I go about cloning an item so that they look exactly the same but have different stats and names. I know where to change the stats and names, but I don&#39;t know how to make the actual item with that particular model. The item I&#39;m trying to clone is anybody wants to know is a DDS, one of the co-owners on my server wishes to have his own personal DDS with enhanced stats, so I thought it would be a nice little thank you for making our forums that I give him what he wants. So any help would be appreciated.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 08 Dec 2011 06:29:58 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/cloning-an-item/424541.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Cloning an item</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@campop2 campop2]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/campop2">@campop2</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I would imagine this would be mostly client sided. But my question is how would I go about cloning an item so that they look exactly the same but have different stats and names. I know where to change the stats and names, but I don’t know how to make the actual item with that particular model. The item I’m trying to clone is anybody wants to know is a DDS, one of the co-owners on my server wishes to have his own personal DDS with enhanced stats, so I thought it would be a nice little thank you for making our forums that I give him what he wants. So any help would be appreciated.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/cloning-an-item/424541/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/cloning-an-item/424541/1</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 08 Dec 2011 06:29:58 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-424541-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/cloning-an-item/424541.rss">Cloning an item</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
