<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>LeoSleeper Source Code? VB6</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/leosleeper-source-code-vb6/334306</link>
    <description>I was wondering if anyone still have LeoSleeper or short for LeoSleep source code i&#39;m not talking about the ocrdll I&#39;m talking about the interface that was made in visual basic 6.

There was one peice of code there that I liked and I want to see it again..

Anyone still have it? 

It&#39;s because I remember LeoSleep had a very nice letter splitting feature which calculated nicely where splits should happen thats what I&#39;m after that algorithm 
I know I&#39;m trying to make one of those SVM myself with a use of models and dictionary with no luck so far.
I&#39;ve also tried neural network searches which work great but seem to fail on jointed letters.

Yeah if your wondering I am trying to make a Captcha solver for one type of captcha in particular has nothing to do with runescape though.

please let me know 
thanks  :D</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 27 Mar 2010 11:12:59 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/leosleeper-source-code-vb6/334306.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>LeoSleeper Source Code? VB6</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@repacsenur repacsenur]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/repacsenur">@repacsenur</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I was wondering if anyone still have LeoSleeper or short for LeoSleep source code i’m not talking about the ocrdll I’m talking about the interface that was made in visual basic 6.</p>
<p>There was one peice of code there that I liked and I want to see it again…</p>
<p>Anyone still have it?</p>
<p>It’s because I remember LeoSleep had a very nice letter splitting feature which calculated nicely where splits should happen thats what I’m after that algorithm<br>
I know I’m trying to make one of those SVM myself with a use of models and dictionary with no luck so far.<br>
I’ve also tried neural network searches which work great but seem to fail on jointed letters.</p>
<p>Yeah if your wondering I am trying to make a Captcha solver for one type of captcha in particular has nothing to do with runescape though.</p>
<p>please let me know<br>
thanks  <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/smiley.png?v=5" title=":smiley:" class="emoji" alt=":smiley:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/leosleeper-source-code-vb6/334306/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/leosleeper-source-code-vb6/334306/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 27 Mar 2010 11:12:59 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-334306-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/leosleeper-source-code-vb6/334306.rss">LeoSleeper Source Code? VB6</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
