<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>United Worlds Of Minecraft</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/united-worlds-of-minecraft/448968</link>
    <description>[center]The United Worlds Of Minecraft
IP: 46.105.237.96

Website: TheUnitedWorls.Enjin.com


[img]http://i48.tinypic.com/a0e0pt.png[/img]
 

If you are looking for a fun, legitimate minecraft server with people

who help out and work together, look no further.


In the UWM, all of our worlds, cities, and businesses are completely legitimate. We put our blood, sweat, and tears into making each and every structure without using item spawning or world edit. We know that it is unfair to players if we use spawned items, so we don&#39;t allow it, whether your a citizen or a Council Member. We also allow the citizens to speak and decide who they want to represent them.


 

Our Rules

I. Respect all people, including the government. Even if you hate them, you still have to respect them.

II. No griefing inside cities or marked areas. Outside a city or marked zone is free territory.

III. No swearing. No spamming. No caps. No begging. As a rule of thumb, try to keep it PG.

IV. No hacks or mods. We are a legitimate server, and everyone inside it is too.

V. Have fun! We care 





Citizen

Citizens make up the bulk of the server. They can live normal lives, open a business, play spleef with friends, or simply build a home. When you start out, you are given a basic set of tools and $30. How you use these items is completely up to you! Citizens also have basic commands, such is home, spawn, tpa, who.


 

VIP

The VIP rank is similar to a Donor Rank. To get VIP status, you must donate at least $8 to the server. This helps the Council to offset the cost of running the server. VIPs get the ability to fly, although it is important to note that they cannot ignore the rules and they do not have an extra resistance to them.


 

Officials

Officials are essentially &#39;police officers&#39; of a city. They are expected to be active in their community and live normal lives like the rest of us. If an issue arrises when a higher ranking official is not online, the city officials have the rights to kick someone off of the server.

Mayor

Dukes are like &#39;mayors&#39; of each city. Each city elects it&#39;s own Duke to oversee all things happening in that city. They have the ability to fly and teleport to quickly get somewhere. The Duke works with the City Officials to pass legislation for the city they serve.


 

Council

Council Members represent the entire server. They vote on issues that will affect all people. If legislation is passed in a lower tier and items are needed, the Council may be presented with a spawned items request. And because we normally do not allow spawned items or world edit, the Council Members can open a shop and build a home. They are expected to help others and moderate the server. They are here to help!

President

When elected, the President acts as a final vote when the Council is voting on legislation. Essentially, the President does not have much more power than the Council, but they may propose legislation and vote on issues.


 




We are looking for dedicated daily Minecraft players who are mature and follow the rules. We are not like other servers where donating is required to use basic features however we do have some nice features you can donate for, and we do accept donations because without donations this server simply wouldn&#39;t be possible. More info on donating and the perks you will receive can be found on our server

Join us for a fun, friendly, and exciting survival PVP experience![/center]</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 09 Jul 2012 17:04:50 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Minecraft</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/united-worlds-of-minecraft/448968.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>United Worlds Of Minecraft</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@callmedragon callmedragon]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/callmedragon">@callmedragon</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[center]The United Worlds Of Minecraft<br>
IP: 46.105.237.96</p>
<p>Website: <a href="http://TheUnitedWorls.Enjin.com" rel="nofollow noopener">TheUnitedWorls.Enjin.com</a></p>
<p><img src="http://i48.tinypic.com/a0e0pt.png" alt width="689" height="418"></p>
<p>If you are looking for a fun, legitimate minecraft server with people</p>
<p>who help out and work together, look no further.</p>
<p>In the UWM, all of our worlds, cities, and businesses are completely legitimate. We put our blood, sweat, and tears into making each and every structure without using item spawning or world edit. We know that it is unfair to players if we use spawned items, so we don’t allow it, whether your a citizen or a Council Member. We also allow the citizens to speak and decide who they want to represent them.</p>
<p>Our Rules</p>
<p>I. Respect all people, including the government. Even if you hate them, you still have to respect them.</p>
<p>II. No griefing inside cities or marked areas. Outside a city or marked zone is free territory.</p>
<p>III. No swearing. No spamming. No caps. No begging. As a rule of thumb, try to keep it PG.</p>
<p>IV. No hacks or mods. We are a legitimate server, and everyone inside it is too.</p>
<p>V. Have fun! We care</p>
<p>Citizen</p>
<p>Citizens make up the bulk of the server. They can live normal lives, open a business, play spleef with friends, or simply build a home. When you start out, you are given a basic set of tools and $30. How you use these items is completely up to you! Citizens also have basic commands, such is home, spawn, tpa, who.</p>
<p>VIP</p>
<p>The VIP rank is similar to a Donor Rank. To get VIP status, you must donate at least $8 to the server. This helps the Council to offset the cost of running the server. VIPs get the ability to fly, although it is important to note that they cannot ignore the rules and they do not have an extra resistance to them.</p>
<p>Officials</p>
<p>Officials are essentially ‘police officers’ of a city. They are expected to be active in their community and live normal lives like the rest of us. If an issue arrises when a higher ranking official is not online, the city officials have the rights to kick someone off of the server.</p>
<p>Mayor</p>
<p>Dukes are like ‘mayors’ of each city. Each city elects it’s own Duke to oversee all things happening in that city. They have the ability to fly and teleport to quickly get somewhere. The Duke works with the City Officials to pass legislation for the city they serve.</p>
<p>Council</p>
<p>Council Members represent the entire server. They vote on issues that will affect all people. If legislation is passed in a lower tier and items are needed, the Council may be presented with a spawned items request. And because we normally do not allow spawned items or world edit, the Council Members can open a shop and build a home. They are expected to help others and moderate the server. They are here to help!</p>
<p>President</p>
<p>When elected, the President acts as a final vote when the Council is voting on legislation. Essentially, the President does not have much more power than the Council, but they may propose legislation and vote on issues.</p>
<p>We are looking for dedicated daily Minecraft players who are mature and follow the rules. We are not like other servers where donating is required to use basic features however we do have some nice features you can donate for, and we do accept donations because without donations this server simply wouldn’t be possible. More info on donating and the perks you will receive can be found on our server</p>
<p>Join us for a fun, friendly, and exciting survival PVP experience![/center]</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/united-worlds-of-minecraft/448968/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/united-worlds-of-minecraft/448968/1</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 09 Jul 2012 17:04:50 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-448968-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/united-worlds-of-minecraft/448968.rss">United Worlds Of Minecraft</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
