<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Help with server please!</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/help-with-server-please/221189</link>
    <description>Ive asked many people about this problem, most of them didnt know a thing and gave me random information. I&#39;ve had my server up like this for about 3 weeks now. My problem is though, most of the time, even though the server is up, people can get into the serv with one click in the first few minutes, but after a while, its so hard to get in, and you have to mass click the log in button. Its so frustrating, ive set my auto restarters to restart every TEN minutes yet it still does that, and annoys my players while its at it. I dont get whats wrong. Ive had some info that it was my source, but some of my friends use the same source and their players can still get in by clicking once.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 18 Jul 2008 22:23:24 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/help-with-server-please/221189.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Help with server please!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@RingedPure RingedPure]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/ringedpure">@RingedPure</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>errrrr</p>
<blockquote>Ive had some info that it was my source, but some of my friends use the same source and their players can still get in by clicking once.</blockquote>
<p>But then again ive also tried Mod Allstar’s source and it seemed to fix it… Im not sure… how come my source will work for most of my friends, yet it wont for me? hmm…</p>
<p>Im pretty sure its not my source, and ill try hosting it on a new computer and see if it does anything.[br][br][size=1]Posted on: July 18, 2008, 01:45:44 PM[/size][hr]Hmm… i tried allstar and it did get better… but now, i wonder why my source works for my friends but not me.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/help-with-server-please/221189/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/help-with-server-please/221189/3</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 18 Jul 2008 22:23:24 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-221189-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/help-with-server-please/221189.rss">Help with server please!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Help with server please!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Austin2 -Austin-]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/austin2">@Austin2</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>it might be the source, test a new source for a little. if not then something might be wrong with ur hard drive</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/help-with-server-please/221189/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/help-with-server-please/221189/2</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 18 Jul 2008 22:13:47 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-221189-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/help-with-server-please/221189.rss">Help with server please!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Help with server please!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@RingedPure RingedPure]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/ringedpure">@RingedPure</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Ive asked many people about this problem, most of them didnt know a thing and gave me random information. I’ve had my server up like this for about 3 weeks now. My problem is though, most of the time, even though the server is up, people can get into the serv with one click in the first few minutes, but after a while, its so hard to get in, and you have to mass click the log in button. Its so frustrating, ive set my auto restarters to restart every TEN minutes yet it still does that, and annoys my players while its at it. I dont get whats wrong. Ive had some info that it was my source, but some of my friends use the same source and their players can still get in by clicking once.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/help-with-server-please/221189/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/help-with-server-please/221189/1</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 18 Jul 2008 22:10:15 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-221189-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/help-with-server-please/221189.rss">Help with server please!</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
