<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Useful ideas</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/useful-ideas/642</link>
    <description>This isn&#39;t a request, more of a suggestion. It&#39;s probably been done before, I don&#39;t look on many other forums. Anyway, I was wondering if you could set up a script so that if it found an unsolvable random, such as the new box, it could start playing a sound like an alarm to let you know. Just an idea.

Oh yeah, and one other thing, this might not work but anyway. You can&#39;t have more than one random at a time right? Well when a new boxbreaker is made, maybe someone could make one so that it would solve one if there was 2, and so on, so there is always one in your inventory, so no other randoms would come? Or doesn&#39;t it work like that?</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 19 Mar 2006 11:30:55 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/useful-ideas/642.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Useful ideas</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@bumfluff120 bumfluff120]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/bumfluff120">@bumfluff120</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>This isn’t a request, more of a suggestion. It’s probably been done before, I don’t look on many other forums. Anyway, I was wondering if you could set up a script so that if it found an unsolvable random, such as the new box, it could start playing a sound like an alarm to let you know. Just an idea.</p>
<p>Oh yeah, and one other thing, this might not work but anyway. You can’t have more than one random at a time right? Well when a new boxbreaker is made, maybe someone could make one so that it would solve one if there was 2, and so on, so there is always one in your inventory, so no other randoms would come? Or doesn’t it work like that?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/useful-ideas/642/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/useful-ideas/642/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 19 Mar 2006 11:30:55 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-642-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/useful-ideas/642.rss">Useful ideas</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
