<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Irritating</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/irritating/78288</link>
    <description>I was just reading someone&#39;s post on the bulletin board, and here is what I saw:

&lt;blockquote&gt;TS FUNNY HOW PEOPLE BE FUCKEN TALKING SHIT ON THE MEXICANS THAT WE&#39;RE FUCKIN &quot;WABZ&quot;...&quot;WETBACKS&quot;...&quot;IMIGRANTS&quot;...&quot;ALIENS&quot;...&quot;BEANERS&quot;...BLAH BLAH BLAH...BUT LET ME TELL YOU...CALL US WHAT YOU WANNA CALL US...SOMEDAY WE&#39;RE GONNA RUN THIS AGAIN CUZ WE OWNED THIS BEFORE... THE MAJORITY OF THE POPULATION IS MEXICAN...WE&quot;RE HARD WORKERS WE WORK FOR OUR SHIT... NO MATTER WHAT IT TAKES...YEAH YOU MIGHT SEE US FUKIN SELLING &#39;CORNS&#39;..&#39;PALETAS&#39;..&#39;CHICHARRONES&#39;...&#39;TAMALES&#39;.....
&#39;ORANGES&#39;...&#39;FLOWERS&#39;...&#39;CANDYS&#39;...AND MORE....BUT U DONT FUKIN SEE US MEXICANS ASKING FOR FOODSTAMPS (EVEN THOUGH THATS WHAT PPL LIKE TO SAY THAT WE COME HERE FOR THE FOODSTAMPS AND WELFARE CHECKS/) FUNNY &#39;CAUSE ALL THE PPL I KNOW THAT ARE ON THEM ARE HAVE AT ONE POINT HAVE BEEN OTHER RACES !!!!!! WE&#39;RE TOO PROUD FOR THAT!.... U DONT SEE US MEXICANS PICKING UP MONEY IN THE EXITS OF THE FREEWAYS...OUTSIDE OF 7-11&#39;S...OR FUKIN PICKING UP MONEY OUTSIDE THE DRIVE-THRU RESTAURANTS WHEN PPL DROP MONEY...ALL U FUKIN PPL TALKSHIT ON US...aLSO YOU SAY THAT WE GET ALL THE GOOD JOBS AND THERE AINT NONE FOR OTHER PPL WELL THATS BECAUSE WE WORK HARD NO MATTER WHAT IT IS ,SOME PPL ARE TOO LAZY TO DO THE THE HARD WORK.IT&#39;S GOTTA BE DONE SO WHO CARES WHO DOES IT?YOU SHOULD BE GRATEFUL THAT THERE IS HARD WORKING MEXICAN PPL THAT DON&#39;T CARE WHAT KIND/ HOW HARD IT IS(WORK) IF WE DON&#39;T DO IT WHO IS?THE STREETS WOULD NEVER GET FIXED,YOUR NEW HOUSES WOULDN&#39;T GET BUILT AMONG MANY OTHER THINGS!wE ARE PROD PPL THAT JUST WANT TO HAVE A BETTER LIFE FOR OURSELVES AND OUR FAMILIES WHATS THE HARM IN THAT?WHO DOESN&#39;T WANT A BETTER LIFE? KEEP UR FUKIN WORDS &quot;SWEET&amp;SOFT&quot; CUZ SOMEDAY UR GONNA HAVE TO EAT EM!!!!!...IM JUST KEEPING IT REAL...THINK BOUT IT ...NEXT TIME U GO TO A FAST FOOD PLACE LOOK WHOS MAKING YOUR FOOD...NEXT TIME SOME 1 DOES UR YARD LOOK WHOS MAKING UR HOUSE PRETTY...NEXT TIME YOU WANT A TACO...OR BURRITO LOOK ON WHAT FOOD CATEGORY THAT FALLS IN OR NEXT TIME U WANT TO DRINK A &quot;CORONA&quot; LOOK WHERE THAT SHIT WAS MADE......
IF YOU DONT REPOST THIS UR ASHAMED TO BE A MEXICAN&lt;/blockquote&gt;

WTF?????? I&#39;m mexican, born on the border (U.S. side) and even I think she&#39;s a god damn retard.

Yes I do see mexicans getting food stamps, yes some do come for welfare checks

I have seen mexicans picking up money plenty of times

Mexicans take jobs with construction, farm work etc because its easy to learn

Other races don&#39;t get the jobs because mexicans demand alot less pay, they live in  groups to support themselves and send the rest of the money back to their families in mexico

Houses would get built, gardens would get proper attention etc, without mexicans

Who&#39;s making my food? Stupid white people ( [b]not meant to be racist[/b], they just never get the order right. not even sure why I keep going back )

I think this chick needs to rethink her story.

What are your thoughts?

Mods, if you feel this would be better in Discussion and debate, I&#39;m all for it.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 13 Apr 2007 07:56:59 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>General Discussion</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/irritating/78288.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Irritating</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Vahuka Vahuka]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/vahuka">@Vahuka</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>picking a fight with who?<br>
i conclude what i said<br>
and RANTING is not posting IN ALL CAPS LIEK ZOMG!!!ONEONETWO LETZ HAV PUPEEZZZ!!!ELEVEN</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/irritating/78288/11">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/irritating/78288/11</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 13 Apr 2007 07:56:59 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-78288-11</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/irritating/78288.rss">Irritating</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Irritating</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@MastrChief MastrChief]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/mastrchief">@MastrChief</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“Vahuka, post:9, topic:78288”]I can’t read anything in all caps. it just hurts my eyes (seriously, ii can’t)<br>
but from what i read i have one thing to say:</p>
<p>Stop Complaining.</p>
<p>if people want to be racist idiots, let them! just DON’T CARE what they say!</p>
<p>so in conclusion:</p>
<p>quit whining.[/quote]</p>
<p>Why must you pick a fight?</p>
<p>If you don’t like ranting, don’t post.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/irritating/78288/10">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/irritating/78288/10</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 12 Apr 2007 20:29:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-78288-10</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/irritating/78288.rss">Irritating</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Irritating</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Vahuka Vahuka]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/vahuka">@Vahuka</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I can’t read anything in all caps. it just hurts my eyes (seriously, ii can’t)<br>
but from what i read i have one thing to say:</p>
<p>Stop Complaining.</p>
<p>if people want to be racist idiots, let them! just DON’T CARE what they say!</p>
<p>so in conclusion:</p>
<p>quit whining.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/irritating/78288/9">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/irritating/78288/9</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 12 Apr 2007 11:37:30 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-78288-9</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/irritating/78288.rss">Irritating</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Irritating</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@PaulT PaulT]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/pault">@PaulT</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I think this person is making a good case for higher fences.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/irritating/78288/8">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/irritating/78288/8</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 12 Apr 2007 11:10:55 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-78288-8</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/irritating/78288.rss">Irritating</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Irritating</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Nerice Nerice]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/nerice">@Nerice</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>“TS FUNNY HOW PEOPLE BE FUCKEN TALKING SHIT ON THE MEXICANS THAT WE’RE FUCKIN “WABZ”…“WETBACKS”…“IMIGRANTS”…“ALIENS”…“BEANERS”…”</p>
<p>If they are illegal tell them to go home to complain.</p>
<p>SOMEDAY WE’RE GONNA RUN THIS AGAIN CUZ WE OWNED THIS BEFORE…" Over my dead body. Bring it, because like the last time, you will lose.</p>
<p>“THE MAJORITY OF THE POPULATION IS MEXICAN…” Yeah, and 90% of them are illegal… So who gives a fuck?</p>
<p>WE"RE HARD WORKERS WE WORK FOR OUR SHIT… NO MATTER WHAT IT TAKES…" Like all races, some work hard, others dont. Most will work cheaper is all.</p>
<p>“YEAH YOU MIGHT SEE US FUKIN SELLING ‘CORNS’…‘PALETAS’…‘CHICHARRONES’…‘TAMALES’…<br>
‘ORANGES’…‘FLOWERS’…‘CANDYS’…AND MORE…” Yup, but my door is not a place to be selling them. Be like most legal residents and do it at your own house or place of business. If I wanted to buy something, I would be out getting it, not at home.</p>
<p>“BUT U DONT FUKIN SEE US MEXICANS ASKING FOR FOODSTAMPS (EVEN THOUGH THATS WHAT PPL LIKE TO SAY THAT WE COME HERE FOR THE FOODSTAMPS AND WELFARE CHECKS/) FUNNY 'CAUSE ALL THE PPL I KNOW THAT ARE ON THEM ARE HAVE AT ONE POINT HAVE BEEN OTHER RACES !!! WE’RE TOO PROUD FOR THAT!..”  I live close to one of their offices in Dallas, and it is full of nothing BUT Mexicans. Any person regardless of race that is here legally should be able to get them, any person that is not, if they really need help and are hungry should go back to where they came from to get help, or starve, either one is fine with me.</p>
<p>“U DONT SEE US MEXICANS PICKING UP MONEY IN THE EXITS OF THE FREEWAYS…OUTSIDE OF 7-11’S…OR FUKIN PICKING UP MONEY OUTSIDE THE DRIVE-THRU RESTAURANTS WHEN PPL DROP MONEY…” The area around I-75 and park ln here in Dallas, Go visit so you can see. Yes there are all races that do that in that area, but Mexicans do as well, which you say they dont.</p>
<p>“ALL U FUKIN PPL TALKSHIT ON US…aLSO YOU SAY THAT WE GET ALL THE GOOD JOBS AND THERE AINT NONE FOR OTHER PPL WELL THATS BECAUSE WE WORK HARD NO MATTER WHAT IT IS ,SOME PPL ARE TOO LAZY TO DO THE THE HARD WORK.IT’S GOTTA BE DONE SO WHO CARES WHO DOES IT?” Not the good jobs, why? Because you have to be legal, and because you have to speak english, which 90%+ here in Dallas are not, and cant.</p>
<p>“YOU SHOULD BE GRATEFUL THAT THERE IS HARD WORKING MEXICAN PPL THAT DON’T CARE WHAT KIND/ HOW HARD IT IS(WORK) IF WE DON’T DO IT WHO IS?” Same people that did it before.</p>
<p>“THE STREETS WOULD NEVER GET FIXED,YOUR NEW HOUSES WOULDN’T GET BUILT AMONG MANY OTHER THINGS!wE ARE PROD PPL THAT JUST WANT TO HAVE A BETTER LIFE FOR OURSELVES AND OUR FAMILIES WHATS THE HARM IN THAT?” Wow, didn’t realize Mexicans was the only people that could fix streets and build homes. Weird, because when I go to Mexico most of the streets are alot worse than the ones here, and the homes here are alot better built.  Guess I should be grateful Mexicans will build my streets and home better then they do for their own selves . Most people are proud, and who wouldn’t want a better life? Thats why so many come here illegally. The harm IS that for everyone illegal that comes here and gains a better life, a legal person is liable to have a worse life. (Just because the world is over populated, doesn’t mean its fine for me to go killing people…)</p>
<p>“KEEP UR FUKIN WORDS “SWEET&amp;SOFT” CUZ SOMEDAY UR GONNA HAVE TO EAT EM!!!..IM JUST KEEPING IT REAL…THINK BOUT IT …” I wont have to eat my words, I talk shit all day long about illegal immigrants. See, I am a US Citizen, I have the right to free speech, Illegal residents have the right to GO HOME.</p>
<p>“NEXT TIME U GO TO A FAST FOOD PLACE LOOK WHOS MAKING YOUR FOOD…” Yup, I don’t go to ANY burger king because the one close to where I live is KNOWN for only hiring Mexicans, irregardless of legal status. I talked to the corporate office of the franchise, they took no action. So I called INS and ICE, then proceeded to go to the resteraunt and inform the workers INS had been notified, the manager said everyone was legal, and wanted me to leave or he would call the police. Funny thing is, a few days later, the store was closed due to people not showing up for work… hmm, did their legal workers worry that ICE might deport them? Management at the store was finally fired and corporate changed their policy about hiring practices after they realized I had sunk my teeth into them once the labor department started their own investigation into discrimination. Screw’em, They was notified, they did nothing, so they was forced to do something.</p>
<p>“NEXT TIME SOME 1 DOES UR YARD LOOK WHOS MAKING UR HOUSE PRETTY…” Maybe my black gardener is really a Mexican with really bad sunburn?</p>
<p>“NEXT TIME YOU WANT A TACO…OR BURRITO LOOK ON WHAT FOOD CATEGORY THAT FALLS IN OR NEXT TIME U WANT TO DRINK A “CORONA” LOOK WHERE THAT SHIT WAS MADE…” There are many types of food, one thing you should think about doing, is LOOK AT WHAT COUNTRY YOUR IN.</p>
<p>“IF YOU DONT REPOST THIS UR ASHAMED TO BE A MEXICAN” Or they dont want to appear to be a stupid illegal.</p>
<p>I am not racist, but when it comes to illegal immigrants of any race, fuck them all.</p>
<p>Anyone here legally fighting for rights I will stand beside and give my full support, anyone here illegally can go home or die, either way they wont be here anymore!</p>
<p>Pretty funny how when I am in America, when a Spanish person speaking Spanish gets ignored, makes a comment about ME not being able to speak Spanish in a derogatory manner not knowing I actually understand Spanish but refuse to talk in anything in English gets the response… “En México digo el español. En América digo el inglés”.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/irritating/78288/7">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/irritating/78288/7</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 12 Apr 2007 11:00:48 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-78288-7</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/irritating/78288.rss">Irritating</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Irritating</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Dboi Dboi]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/dboi">@Dboi</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote no-group" data-post="3" data-topic="78288">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/user_avatar/forum.moparisthebest.com/moparisthebest/40/30_2.png" class="avatar"> Moparisthebest:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>I automatically conclude that anyone who types full sentences with the caps lock on is a moron.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I agree, People put Caps Locks on thinking that people will hear or Notice you more…Using Caps Lock for a Whole Paragraph is just Stupid.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/irritating/78288/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/irritating/78288/6</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 12 Apr 2007 09:59:53 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-78288-6</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/irritating/78288.rss">Irritating</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Irritating</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@MidGuardian MidGuardian]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/midguardian">@MidGuardian</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>i dont like racism, even if its not to me.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/irritating/78288/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/irritating/78288/5</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 12 Apr 2007 09:44:35 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-78288-5</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/irritating/78288.rss">Irritating</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Irritating</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Winter_Ice Winter Ice]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/winter_ice">@Winter_Ice</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>WHAT DID YOU SAY MOPAR? lol that is offencive to mexicans who wrote that anyways?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/irritating/78288/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/irritating/78288/4</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 12 Apr 2007 07:08:16 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-78288-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/irritating/78288.rss">Irritating</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Irritating</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@moparisthebest Moparisthebest]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/moparisthebest">@moparisthebest</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I automatically conclude that anyone who types full sentences with the caps lock on is a moron.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/irritating/78288/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/irritating/78288/3</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 12 Apr 2007 04:48:32 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-78288-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/irritating/78288.rss">Irritating</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Irritating</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@zoltanman zoltanman]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/zoltanman">@zoltanman</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Ye that person is a fag. Plus got her facts down totally wrong. They don’t all build houses, and fix alot of things. What a bitch</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/irritating/78288/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/irritating/78288/2</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 12 Apr 2007 04:45:49 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-78288-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/irritating/78288.rss">Irritating</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Irritating</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@MastrChief MastrChief]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/mastrchief">@MastrChief</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I was just reading someone’s post on the bulletin board, and here is what I saw:</p>
<blockquote>TS FUNNY HOW PEOPLE BE FUCKEN TALKING SHIT ON THE MEXICANS THAT WE'RE FUCKIN "WABZ"..."WETBACKS"..."IMIGRANTS"..."ALIENS"..."BEANERS"...BLAH BLAH BLAH...BUT LET ME TELL YOU...CALL US WHAT YOU WANNA CALL US...SOMEDAY WE'RE GONNA RUN THIS AGAIN CUZ WE OWNED THIS BEFORE... THE MAJORITY OF THE POPULATION IS MEXICAN...WE"RE HARD WORKERS WE WORK FOR OUR SHIT... NO MATTER WHAT IT TAKES...YEAH YOU MIGHT SEE US FUKIN SELLING 'CORNS'..'PALETAS'..'CHICHARRONES'...'TAMALES'.....
'ORANGES'...'FLOWERS'...'CANDYS'...AND MORE....BUT U DONT FUKIN SEE US MEXICANS ASKING FOR FOODSTAMPS (EVEN THOUGH THATS WHAT PPL LIKE TO SAY THAT WE COME HERE FOR THE FOODSTAMPS AND WELFARE CHECKS/) FUNNY 'CAUSE ALL THE PPL I KNOW THAT ARE ON THEM ARE HAVE AT ONE POINT HAVE BEEN OTHER RACES !!!!!! WE'RE TOO PROUD FOR THAT!.... U DONT SEE US MEXICANS PICKING UP MONEY IN THE EXITS OF THE FREEWAYS...OUTSIDE OF 7-11'S...OR FUKIN PICKING UP MONEY OUTSIDE THE DRIVE-THRU RESTAURANTS WHEN PPL DROP MONEY...ALL U FUKIN PPL TALKSHIT ON US...aLSO YOU SAY THAT WE GET ALL THE GOOD JOBS AND THERE AINT NONE FOR OTHER PPL WELL THATS BECAUSE WE WORK HARD NO MATTER WHAT IT IS ,SOME PPL ARE TOO LAZY TO DO THE THE HARD WORK.IT'S GOTTA BE DONE SO WHO CARES WHO DOES IT?YOU SHOULD BE GRATEFUL THAT THERE IS HARD WORKING MEXICAN PPL THAT DON'T CARE WHAT KIND/ HOW HARD IT IS(WORK) IF WE DON'T DO IT WHO IS?THE STREETS WOULD NEVER GET FIXED,YOUR NEW HOUSES WOULDN'T GET BUILT AMONG MANY OTHER THINGS!wE ARE PROD PPL THAT JUST WANT TO HAVE A BETTER LIFE FOR OURSELVES AND OUR FAMILIES WHATS THE HARM IN THAT?WHO DOESN'T WANT A BETTER LIFE? KEEP UR FUKIN WORDS "SWEET&amp;SOFT" CUZ SOMEDAY UR GONNA HAVE TO EAT EM!!!!!...IM JUST KEEPING IT REAL...THINK BOUT IT ...NEXT TIME U GO TO A FAST FOOD PLACE LOOK WHOS MAKING YOUR FOOD...NEXT TIME SOME 1 DOES UR YARD LOOK WHOS MAKING UR HOUSE PRETTY...NEXT TIME YOU WANT A TACO...OR BURRITO LOOK ON WHAT FOOD CATEGORY THAT FALLS IN OR NEXT TIME U WANT TO DRINK A "CORONA" LOOK WHERE THAT SHIT WAS MADE......
IF YOU DONT REPOST THIS UR ASHAMED TO BE A MEXICAN</blockquote>
<p>WTF??? I’m mexican, born on the border (U.S. side) and even I think she’s a god damn retard.</p>
<p>Yes I do see mexicans getting food stamps, yes some do come for welfare checks</p>
<p>I have seen mexicans picking up money plenty of times</p>
<p>Mexicans take jobs with construction, farm work etc because its easy to learn</p>
<p>Other races don’t get the jobs because mexicans demand alot less pay, they live in  groups to support themselves and send the rest of the money back to their families in mexico</p>
<p>Houses would get built, gardens would get proper attention etc, without mexicans</p>
<p>Who’s making my food? Stupid white people ( <span class="bbcode-b">not meant to be racist</span>, they just never get the order right. not even sure why I keep going back )</p>
<p>I think this chick needs to rethink her story.</p>
<p>What are your thoughts?</p>
<p>Mods, if you feel this would be better in Discussion and debate, I’m all for it.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/irritating/78288/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/irritating/78288/1</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 11 Apr 2007 12:54:50 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-78288-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/irritating/78288.rss">Irritating</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
