<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Tip.It Times - Biased Banning Raises Brows</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/tip-it-times-biased-banning-raises-brows/84998</link>
    <description>This article was removed because Andrew threatened to sue Tip.it  :) this was from last year.



Recently Jagex has been cracking the whip on rule-breakers who ruin the game for legitimate players.

Apparently they are going by the policy: you can’t make an omelet without breaking a few eggs.

There have been several reported cases of black marks or permanent bans for some of the most ridiculous reasons.

Even when confronted with their misdeeds, Jagex has done little to recompense those players that they have made suffer.

Furthermore, they have been very inconsistent with their processing, perhaps even biased against certain players, while overlooking others.

Do not take this the wrong way; I fully support Jagex in enforcing the rules of this game, but not at the expense of innocent players who mean no harm to others.

Jagex needs to put themselves in the shoes of the players they wrongfully punish.

Perhaps then they can accept their mistakes and take appropriate actions.

I will begin with my most general of three cases, namely the banning of players who simply mention fan sites such as Tip.It.

Even vague references have resulted in players being muted, some even temporarily banned. This is just the smallest of the atrocities players have faced.

The rule states: You are not allowed to actively advertise in the RuneScape game or RuneScape forums.

This includes advertising any website or product and no web addresses are allowed.

Telling other players any web-address is not allowed.

This rule states clearly that we can not say website addresses within the game.

Obviously people saying stuff like, “go look at Tip.It” are not the people being treated unfairly.

The rule is firm about stating addresses, as well as advertising sites.

The people who are treated unfairly are the people who are being banned or muted just for talking about a site with a friend, even without saying the address.

There have been numerous mutes and bans for players saying they saw something on “tipit”.

Is it fair that these players receive bans for saying they saw something? Saying the word “tipit” does not tell a person how to get to our website.

alking about something you see with a friend is not a form of advertisement (unless purposely dialogued to be one). The point is that saying “tipit” will not lead players to our site without some work on their own to find it, such as doing a search. One can not just throw on a .com at the end of the name and find our site (I would highly recommend against visiting tipit.com). So why ban players for saying the name of something without giving them directions to find it? What I find most ironic about this that Jagex supports the use of legitimate fan websites such as our own, yet bans players for talking about them (see Jagex’s Fan Site FAQ). Perhaps it is time for Jagex to review some of the popular sites, decide which sites players are allowed to cite, and end the unjust banning of players who want to talk about a site with their friends – bans they are receiving even without saying the site’s address. Or perhaps they should extend the rule, saying that even the title of the site is not allowed. Do one or the other, but do not ban players who are not breaking the rule – those who talk about “tipit” but do not give its address. As I said previously, this is just the weakest display of unjustified bans lately.

Since Jagex started their banning spree, there have been countless innocent players banned for supposed violations of rule 8: You may create more than one RuneScape account, but if you do, you may not log in more than one account at any time, and they must not interact with each other in any way. This includes &quot;drop trading&quot; or any other method of item transfer. This rule is completely understandable. There are obviously unfair advantages to having more than one account logged in at a time, or having your characters trade with each other. The problem with this rule is that players on the same network (many homes now have multiple computers with internet access) are getting banned for interacting with their roommates or families. I am not a networking expert, but when I visit my parents and log in from their house, it shows the same IP in the “last logged in from” section regardless which computer I use. This (I’m assuming) is because they are all on the same router. This greatly hinders players who want to participate in the game with their family. Even high ranked players such as our own beloved DroolMAN have suffered from this. He was recently banned for supposed violation of this rule; for giving several items to his daughter. Some unsupportive players believe that he was using his daughter’s account as a “mule” and giving her items for the sake of freeing up bank space. He denies these allegations, but his motives are insignificant in terms of this ban being unjust. Even if he was using his daughter to free up bank space, the point is that she played from an entirely different computer than he did. She is a separate person. He did not trade with himself; he traded with his daughter. Even if he had to walk her through it, he was not trading with himself. There is no rule stating that you can not have a friend or family member hold your items for you, nor that you can not trade with players on the same router.

Jagex should look into ways to better distinguish one computer from another on the same network. At the very least, they should give a warning to players to avoid trading with friends or family who share the same internet connection, or extend the rule to say that if you share a connection with somebody, you can not interact with him or her. Now you can prepare yourself for the heart of the hypocrisy; the biggest display of prejudice in the game; the undeniable truth that Jagex is biased in banning players. What other topic could this be than inappropriate names? This topic has been a concern with me for as long as I have played this game. If there is one aspect of Jagex that I am completely repulsed by, it is their ineffective control over appropriate player names.

What brings this disgust into the Times, however, is that Jagex is banning players for their names, but they are waiting until a player has been around for months, maybe even years; banning players whose names are not offensive (while saying that is the reason); and leaving players with indisputably offensive names untouched. As those of you who read our forums may have already guessed, much of this frustration lies with the ban of Limparse. He was banned after playing for several months, given the reason that his name is inappropriate. Jagex deemed this name unacceptable because they read it as Limp Arse. You would think that somebody at Jagex would realize &quot;limpar&quot; is a Portuguese verb, and that adding &quot;se&quot; to the end of a verb in Portuguese makes it reflexive. Either Jagex is taking a stand against names in non-English languages, or a verb meaning &quot;to clean oneself&quot; is somehow inappropriate.

I suppose we should take extra care in not letting other players know that we take showers; a moderator might mute us for bathing… This mistake was due to an oversight by Jagex. This case does prove that Jagex will ban players for inappropriate names even months after the account’s creation. They will not allow you to change your name, thus you start from scratch, unless you have another account already. The fact that they will take these measures also signifies that Jagex is letting some players with inappropriate names continue to enjoy the game.

Limparse was noticed due to other reports against him, but ultimately banned for his name. Why should players who do not get reported for other issues be allowed to keep their inappropriate names? If Jagex is going to ban players for inappropriate names, they should upgrade their settings so that less inappropriate names get past the filters. They should also have certain strings of characters that will flag their attention for a manual check of a name, so that players with potentially inappropriate names will get taken care of before they have become a long-term player. Also, if Jagex plans to ban players with inappropriate names (as they should be), they need to ban everybody with an inappropriate name. I myself could name at least fifty players who are level 110 combat or higher with indisputably offensive names. Some of these players have been around since RSC, and since the Jagex administrators like these players, they do not get banned. This would make it seem that the offensive language rules only apply to some.

What kind of names am I talking about? Obviously I can not name specific players without permission, much less if their names are inappropriate. I can, however, give a few loose examples: names containing the term “fuh qu” or “fah q”; names containing censor-evading misspellings such as “suxcox”; names with messages saying, “You’re a hoe”; or names with an inappropriate alternative for the word cat. It is very amusing how the phrases in these names are censored within the game’s chat, yet these players are above the rules. Many of the players I allude to are well over 1500 skill total. Given the amount of time they have been playing, it is evident that Jagex is conveniently overlooking these players’ names. Obviously they do not want to ban a long-term player, but does this justify allowing them to keep inappropriate names? Should the rules not apply to everybody? I hope Jagex sees this. I am interested how this may shape the future of their customer support.

I know I am not alone in my opinions. We do want the rules enforced, but we want them enforced without innocent players getting banned. We want the rules to apply to everybody equally. Giving some rule-breakers special treatment, while banning other players who have done nothing wrong, reflects poorly on RuneScape. End the hypocrisy, Jagex.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 30 Apr 2007 17:53:15 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/tip-it-times-biased-banning-raises-brows/84998.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Tip.It Times - Biased Banning Raises Brows</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@davidrofldude davidrofldude]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/davidrofldude">@davidrofldude</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Help, help, I’m being repressed!</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/tip-it-times-biased-banning-raises-brows/84998/8">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/tip-it-times-biased-banning-raises-brows/84998/8</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 30 Apr 2007 17:53:15 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-84998-8</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/tip-it-times-biased-banning-raises-brows/84998.rss">Tip.It Times - Biased Banning Raises Brows</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Tip.It Times - Biased Banning Raises Brows</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Original Original]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/original">@Original</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Yeah…over 150k players on at a time…like 50k are members. 50k X $5 = 250K…and the price is probably more than $5 plus all those people who buy sms pins to sell to others…Jagex only cares about money</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/tip-it-times-biased-banning-raises-brows/84998/7">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/tip-it-times-biased-banning-raises-brows/84998/7</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 29 Apr 2007 10:54:09 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-84998-7</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/tip-it-times-biased-banning-raises-brows/84998.rss">Tip.It Times - Biased Banning Raises Brows</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Tip.It Times - Biased Banning Raises Brows</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Rosk Rosk]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/rosk">@Rosk</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Jagex is a selfish company.</p>
<p>The only reason they care about players is money.<br>
They don’t care about players themself, but for the cash we are providing them.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/tip-it-times-biased-banning-raises-brows/84998/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/tip-it-times-biased-banning-raises-brows/84998/6</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 28 Apr 2007 22:23:28 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-84998-6</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/tip-it-times-biased-banning-raises-brows/84998.rss">Tip.It Times - Biased Banning Raises Brows</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Tip.It Times - Biased Banning Raises Brows</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@bootnecklad bootnecklad]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/bootnecklad">@bootnecklad</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote no-group quote-modified" data-post="4" data-topic="84998">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 Click Here:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>jagex are scared that they get a bad comment said about them, and then they loos players and get done for their “crime” so they sue the websites… pretty sad if you tell me…</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>VERY sad… why why jagex?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/tip-it-times-biased-banning-raises-brows/84998/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/tip-it-times-biased-banning-raises-brows/84998/5</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 28 Apr 2007 20:44:26 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-84998-5</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/tip-it-times-biased-banning-raises-brows/84998.rss">Tip.It Times - Biased Banning Raises Brows</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Tip.It Times - Biased Banning Raises Brows</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Click_Here Click Here]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/click_here">@Click_Here</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>jagex are scared that they get a bad comment said about them, and then they loos players and get done for their “crime” so they sue the websites… pretty sad if you tell me…</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/tip-it-times-biased-banning-raises-brows/84998/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/tip-it-times-biased-banning-raises-brows/84998/4</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 28 Apr 2007 02:28:44 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-84998-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/tip-it-times-biased-banning-raises-brows/84998.rss">Tip.It Times - Biased Banning Raises Brows</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Tip.It Times - Biased Banning Raises Brows</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@system system]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/system">@system</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote no-group quote-modified" data-post="2" data-topic="84998">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 cant touch this93:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>how could he sue for that…? but all of that is true.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Yep Too True, Jagex Are Gay E.O.S</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/tip-it-times-biased-banning-raises-brows/84998/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/tip-it-times-biased-banning-raises-brows/84998/3</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 Apr 2007 21:48:27 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-84998-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/tip-it-times-biased-banning-raises-brows/84998.rss">Tip.It Times - Biased Banning Raises Brows</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Tip.It Times - Biased Banning Raises Brows</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@cant_touch_this93 cant touch this93]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/cant_touch_this93">@cant_touch_this93</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>how could he sue for that…? but all of that is true.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/tip-it-times-biased-banning-raises-brows/84998/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/tip-it-times-biased-banning-raises-brows/84998/2</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 Apr 2007 04:55:36 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-84998-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/tip-it-times-biased-banning-raises-brows/84998.rss">Tip.It Times - Biased Banning Raises Brows</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Tip.It Times - Biased Banning Raises Brows</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@hellou hellou]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/hellou">@hellou</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>This article was removed because Andrew threatened to sue Tip.it  <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=6" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"> this was from last year.</p>
<p>Recently Jagex has been cracking the whip on rule-breakers who ruin the game for legitimate players.</p>
<p>Apparently they are going by the policy: you can’t make an omelet without breaking a few eggs.</p>
<p>There have been several reported cases of black marks or permanent bans for some of the most ridiculous reasons.</p>
<p>Even when confronted with their misdeeds, Jagex has done little to recompense those players that they have made suffer.</p>
<p>Furthermore, they have been very inconsistent with their processing, perhaps even biased against certain players, while overlooking others.</p>
<p>Do not take this the wrong way; I fully support Jagex in enforcing the rules of this game, but not at the expense of innocent players who mean no harm to others.</p>
<p>Jagex needs to put themselves in the shoes of the players they wrongfully punish.</p>
<p>Perhaps then they can accept their mistakes and take appropriate actions.</p>
<p>I will begin with my most general of three cases, namely the banning of players who simply mention fan sites such as Tip.It.</p>
<p>Even vague references have resulted in players being muted, some even temporarily banned. This is just the smallest of the atrocities players have faced.</p>
<p>The rule states: You are not allowed to actively advertise in the RuneScape game or RuneScape forums.</p>
<p>This includes advertising any website or product and no web addresses are allowed.</p>
<p>Telling other players any web-address is not allowed.</p>
<p>This rule states clearly that we can not say website addresses within the game.</p>
<p>Obviously people saying stuff like, “go look at Tip.It” are not the people being treated unfairly.</p>
<p>The rule is firm about stating addresses, as well as advertising sites.</p>
<p>The people who are treated unfairly are the people who are being banned or muted just for talking about a site with a friend, even without saying the address.</p>
<p>There have been numerous mutes and bans for players saying they saw something on “tipit”.</p>
<p>Is it fair that these players receive bans for saying they saw something? Saying the word “tipit” does not tell a person how to get to our website.</p>
<p>alking about something you see with a friend is not a form of advertisement (unless purposely dialogued to be one). The point is that saying “tipit” will not lead players to our site without some work on their own to find it, such as doing a search. One can not just throw on a .com at the end of the name and find our site (I would highly recommend against visiting <a href="http://tipit.com" rel="nofollow noopener">tipit.com</a>). So why ban players for saying the name of something without giving them directions to find it? What I find most ironic about this that Jagex supports the use of legitimate fan websites such as our own, yet bans players for talking about them (see Jagex’s Fan Site FAQ). Perhaps it is time for Jagex to review some of the popular sites, decide which sites players are allowed to cite, and end the unjust banning of players who want to talk about a site with their friends – bans they are receiving even without saying the site’s address. Or perhaps they should extend the rule, saying that even the title of the site is not allowed. Do one or the other, but do not ban players who are not breaking the rule – those who talk about “tipit” but do not give its address. As I said previously, this is just the weakest display of unjustified bans lately.</p>
<p>Since Jagex started their banning spree, there have been countless innocent players banned for supposed violations of rule 8: You may create more than one RuneScape account, but if you do, you may not log in more than one account at any time, and they must not interact with each other in any way. This includes “drop trading” or any other method of item transfer. This rule is completely understandable. There are obviously unfair advantages to having more than one account logged in at a time, or having your characters trade with each other. The problem with this rule is that players on the same network (many homes now have multiple computers with internet access) are getting banned for interacting with their roommates or families. I am not a networking expert, but when I visit my parents and log in from their house, it shows the same IP in the “last logged in from” section regardless which computer I use. This (I’m assuming) is because they are all on the same router. This greatly hinders players who want to participate in the game with their family. Even high ranked players such as our own beloved DroolMAN have suffered from this. He was recently banned for supposed violation of this rule; for giving several items to his daughter. Some unsupportive players believe that he was using his daughter’s account as a “mule” and giving her items for the sake of freeing up bank space. He denies these allegations, but his motives are insignificant in terms of this ban being unjust. Even if he was using his daughter to free up bank space, the point is that she played from an entirely different computer than he did. She is a separate person. He did not trade with himself; he traded with his daughter. Even if he had to walk her through it, he was not trading with himself. There is no rule stating that you can not have a friend or family member hold your items for you, nor that you can not trade with players on the same router.</p>
<p>Jagex should look into ways to better distinguish one computer from another on the same network. At the very least, they should give a warning to players to avoid trading with friends or family who share the same internet connection, or extend the rule to say that if you share a connection with somebody, you can not interact with him or her. Now you can prepare yourself for the heart of the hypocrisy; the biggest display of prejudice in the game; the undeniable truth that Jagex is biased in banning players. What other topic could this be than inappropriate names? This topic has been a concern with me for as long as I have played this game. If there is one aspect of Jagex that I am completely repulsed by, it is their ineffective control over appropriate player names.</p>
<p>What brings this disgust into the Times, however, is that Jagex is banning players for their names, but they are waiting until a player has been around for months, maybe even years; banning players whose names are not offensive (while saying that is the reason); and leaving players with indisputably offensive names untouched. As those of you who read our forums may have already guessed, much of this frustration lies with the ban of Limparse. He was banned after playing for several months, given the reason that his name is inappropriate. Jagex deemed this name unacceptable because they read it as Limp Arse. You would think that somebody at Jagex would realize “limpar” is a Portuguese verb, and that adding “se” to the end of a verb in Portuguese makes it reflexive. Either Jagex is taking a stand against names in non-English languages, or a verb meaning “to clean oneself” is somehow inappropriate.</p>
<p>I suppose we should take extra care in not letting other players know that we take showers; a moderator might mute us for bathing… This mistake was due to an oversight by Jagex. This case does prove that Jagex will ban players for inappropriate names even months after the account’s creation. They will not allow you to change your name, thus you start from scratch, unless you have another account already. The fact that they will take these measures also signifies that Jagex is letting some players with inappropriate names continue to enjoy the game.</p>
<p>Limparse was noticed due to other reports against him, but ultimately banned for his name. Why should players who do not get reported for other issues be allowed to keep their inappropriate names? If Jagex is going to ban players for inappropriate names, they should upgrade their settings so that less inappropriate names get past the filters. They should also have certain strings of characters that will flag their attention for a manual check of a name, so that players with potentially inappropriate names will get taken care of before they have become a long-term player. Also, if Jagex plans to ban players with inappropriate names (as they should be), they need to ban everybody with an inappropriate name. I myself could name at least fifty players who are level 110 combat or higher with indisputably offensive names. Some of these players have been around since RSC, and since the Jagex administrators like these players, they do not get banned. This would make it seem that the offensive language rules only apply to some.</p>
<p>What kind of names am I talking about? Obviously I can not name specific players without permission, much less if their names are inappropriate. I can, however, give a few loose examples: names containing the term “fuh qu” or “fah q”; names containing censor-evading misspellings such as “suxcox”; names with messages saying, “You’re a hoe”; or names with an inappropriate alternative for the word cat. It is very amusing how the phrases in these names are censored within the game’s chat, yet these players are above the rules. Many of the players I allude to are well over 1500 skill total. Given the amount of time they have been playing, it is evident that Jagex is conveniently overlooking these players’ names. Obviously they do not want to ban a long-term player, but does this justify allowing them to keep inappropriate names? Should the rules not apply to everybody? I hope Jagex sees this. I am interested how this may shape the future of their customer support.</p>
<p>I know I am not alone in my opinions. We do want the rules enforced, but we want them enforced without innocent players getting banned. We want the rules to apply to everybody equally. Giving some rule-breakers special treatment, while banning other players who have done nothing wrong, reflects poorly on RuneScape. End the hypocrisy, Jagex.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/tip-it-times-biased-banning-raises-brows/84998/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/tip-it-times-biased-banning-raises-brows/84998/1</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 Apr 2007 04:29:58 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-84998-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/tip-it-times-biased-banning-raises-brows/84998.rss">Tip.It Times - Biased Banning Raises Brows</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
