<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>A bit of questions... How to port foward... + I can&#39;t edit anything</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/a-bit-of-questions-how-to-port-foward-i-cant-edit-anything/29454</link>
    <description>I don&#39;t understand how to port foward...  Plus whenever I edit anything on my server and save it and compile and go on my server to try it out no changes happen...  I&#39;ve tried testscape and cheezscape... BLAHHHH someone please ask me questions what I&#39;m doing wrong.

     --- Sir Matt Man ---</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 26 Nov 2006 08:27:44 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/a-bit-of-questions-how-to-port-foward-i-cant-edit-anything/29454.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>A bit of questions... How to port foward... + I can&#39;t edit anything</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@supergamerz supergamerz]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/supergamerz">@supergamerz</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“lothy”]<span class="bbcode-b">Purpose</span>: <span class="bbcode-i">To aid people in port-forwarding.</span></p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Difficulty</span>: <span class="bbcode-i">1. If you can’t do this, then chances are you won’t be able to write your server code either.</span></p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Assumed Knowledge</span>: <span class="bbcode-i">You should be able to find Control Panel, and open an internet browser. Otherwise, leave the forums.</span></p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Server Base</span>: <span class="bbcode-i">Any and every server there is and ever will be. You need to do this if you use a router and actually want to HOST a server. =)</span></p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Classes Modified</span>: <span class="bbcode-i">None. This tutorial is for those looking to host their server.</span></p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b"><span class="bbcode-u">Procedure</span></span></p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Step 1 - Obtaining your INTERNAL IP ADDRESS</span>: [i]Firstly, you need to find the INTERNAL IP address of YOUR COMPUTER. As you can see, I’ve capitalised those words… Why, you may ask? Because many people, including myself at one stage, often put their EXTERNAL IP address in. This is a common missconception, and more often then not people stuff up because of this. So I’m explaining it very clearly.<br>
This screenshot shows exactly how to find it in Windows XP.<br>
Your internal IP address is the one circled in red. To access this:</p>
<ol>
<li>Open Control Panel.</li>
<li>Go to ‘Network Connections’.</li>
<li>Once in here, double click your network.</li>
<li>Click the ‘Support’ tab at the top of the window that comes up, and you will be in the same area shown in the screenshot below. Write that number down, because you’ll need it in a few minutes.<br>
<img src="http://img293.imageshack.us/img293/237/internalipcj1.jpg" alt width="" height="">[/i]</li>
</ol>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Step 2 - Accessing your Router</span>: [i]Now that you have successfully obtained the IP address of your computer, it’s time to actually port forward.<br>
For this section you will need the manual for your particular router. All screenshots will give you a general idea, but won’t be identical to your router settings screen unless you’re using the same router as me (Mine is a Netcomm ADSL Modem NB1300 PLUS 4).<br>
Ok, so lets begin. Firstly, open up your browser. I always use Internet Explorer when modifying router settings, but Firefox may work too.<br>
Once you’ve opened your browser of choice, enter the IP address of your ROUTER. This is NOT your COMPUTER’s IP address, and it’s NOT your EXTERNAL IP address either. The address for your router can be found in your manual, and will be accompanied by a username and password.<br>
By default, most routers have an IP that is something similar to 192.168.1.1 or 192.168.0.1 - It’ll be something similar to that.<br>
The default username for most routers is ‘admin’ or ‘administrator’ - something along those lines, but without the ’ ’ marks.<br>
The default password for most routers is 1234 or password.<br>
All of these are written in your manual, so you can find out the exact details below for your modem.<br>
See a few screenshots below so you get the idea.</p>
<p>This prompt or a similar box will appear when you enter your router’s IP address into the address bar of your browser:<br>
<img src="http://img175.imageshack.us/img175/8546/passwordrequestrouterys5.jpg" alt width="" height=""></p>
<p>A screen similar to this will appear once you have entered the correct username and password:<br>
<img src="http://img157.imageshack.us/img157/1213/routersettingspageve6.jpg" alt width="" height=""></p>
<p>This is the screen that comes up after clicking the ‘Advanced Settings’ link. As you can see, a link to ‘Port Forwarding’ has now appeared:<br>
<img src="http://img90.imageshack.us/img90/1000/routersettingsadvancedpzl9.jpg" alt width="" height=""></p>
<p>And finally, the page that comes up when you click the link to ‘Port Forwarding’. Please note that your router might not look exactly like mine does… but I presume most have a very similar interface:<br>
<img src="http://img182.imageshack.us/img182/6984/portforwardsettingsbs2.jpg" alt width="" height=""><br>
[/i]</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Step 3 - Actually Port Forwarding</span>: <span class="bbcode-i">Ok, remember the IP address you wrote down before? It’s time to use it. Once you’re into the page to modify your router’s port forwarding settings, you will need to forward the port 43594 to your computer.<br>
As you can see in the picture above, mine are already set.<br>
To set yours, type 43594 in all public and private port text boxes. Do this for both TCP and UDP port types. In the box labelled ‘Host IP Address’ or whatever yours is, enter the IP address that you wrote down before.</span></p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Step 4 - Save and Reboot your Router</span>: <span class="bbcode-i">Now that you’ve entered those in properly, save and reboot your router. This will only take a few seconds. If you don’t do it, the settings will be lost and you’ll be back where you started.<br>
Saved and Rebooted? Congratulations, the port forwarding part of your computer has been set up. If you have done the firewall exceptions settings, and have the NO-IP DUC set up (or if you have a static external IP address, people can use that to access your server) then you’re ready to host!</span></p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Credits</span>: <span class="bbcode-i">All credits to me, including screenshots which were taken Thursday 16th November 2006 AEST time.</span>[/quote]</p>
<p>this is in the tut all credit goes to him</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/a-bit-of-questions-how-to-port-foward-i-cant-edit-anything/29454/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/a-bit-of-questions-how-to-port-foward-i-cant-edit-anything/29454/2</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 26 Nov 2006 08:27:44 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-29454-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/a-bit-of-questions-how-to-port-foward-i-cant-edit-anything/29454.rss">A bit of questions... How to port foward... + I can&#39;t edit anything</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>A bit of questions... How to port foward... + I can&#39;t edit anything</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Potent Potent]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/potent">@Potent</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I don’t understand how to port foward…  Plus whenever I edit anything on my server and save it and compile and go on my server to try it out no changes happen…  I’ve tried testscape and cheezscape… BLAHHHH someone please ask me questions what I’m doing wrong.</p>
<pre><code> --- Sir Matt Man ---</code></pre>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/a-bit-of-questions-how-to-port-foward-i-cant-edit-anything/29454/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/a-bit-of-questions-how-to-port-foward-i-cant-edit-anything/29454/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 26 Nov 2006 07:50:05 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-29454-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/a-bit-of-questions-how-to-port-foward-i-cant-edit-anything/29454.rss">A bit of questions... How to port foward... + I can&#39;t edit anything</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
