<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>An Upper Force?</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/an-upper-force/184658</link>
    <description>This story starts at my parents restaurant. After leaving, i took my mother&#39;s keys and cell phone. i put the cell phone on the dashboard for later. I put the keys in and waited for her to get done. We&#39;re done shopping for the restaurant and getting my new computer! 
So we get home and i&#39;m just about ready to go to work and when people call home when i&#39;m away my wireless sags out and stops working. i was like &quot;fuck this&quot; and i unplugged the phones battery, not knowing this was my biggest mistake. 
We get to work and we pick up the stuff me and my dad are going to deliver and he locks the keys in the car. He gets angry and was swearing and stuff because he couldn&#39;t get to my mother. I remember unplugging the phone and leaving the phone in the car. And the ONE time i need to call my mom at home, i couldn&#39;t get to her. So we ended up going to get a thin piece of metal and bending the end and pulling the handle to unlock the car. And i look in the snow and i see &quot;haha&quot; in the snow. I looked up and i felt like i was playing chess and just lost my Queen. 


Weird Day.


-Nick`</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 28 Feb 2008 01:16:44 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>General Discussion</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/an-upper-force/184658.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>An Upper Force?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@dragonfire455 dragonfire455]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/dragonfire455">@dragonfire455</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>thats funny ^^</p>
<p>that happened to me once, my ass got whopped lol</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/an-upper-force/184658/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/an-upper-force/184658/2</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 28 Feb 2008 01:16:44 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-184658-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/an-upper-force/184658.rss">An Upper Force?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>An Upper Force?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@swordskid61 Swordskid61]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/swordskid61">@swordskid61</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>This story starts at my parents restaurant. After leaving, i took my mother’s keys and cell phone. i put the cell phone on the dashboard for later. I put the keys in and waited for her to get done. We’re done shopping for the restaurant and getting my new computer!<br>
So we get home and i’m just about ready to go to work and when people call home when i’m away my wireless sags out and stops working. i was like “fuck this” and i unplugged the phones battery, not knowing this was my biggest mistake.<br>
We get to work and we pick up the stuff me and my dad are going to deliver and he locks the keys in the car. He gets angry and was swearing and stuff because he couldn’t get to my mother. I remember unplugging the phone and leaving the phone in the car. And the ONE time i need to call my mom at home, i couldn’t get to her. So we ended up going to get a thin piece of metal and bending the end and pulling the handle to unlock the car. And i look in the snow and i see “haha” in the snow. I looked up and i felt like i was playing chess and just lost my Queen.</p>
<p>Weird Day.</p>
<p>-Nick`</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/an-upper-force/184658/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/an-upper-force/184658/1</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 27 Feb 2008 08:23:42 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-184658-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/an-upper-force/184658.rss">An Upper Force?</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
