<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>HungerScape - May the odds be ever in your favour</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/hungerscape-may-the-odds-be-ever-in-your-favour/546528</link>
    <description>[CENTER][IMG]http://i104.photobucket.com/albums/m193/mrgiggles1993/bannerhungergames2_zps54ceea01.png[/img]
[URL=http://www.hungerscape.com/home/play.html][IMG]http://i104.photobucket.com/albums/m193/mrgiggles1993/PlayNow2_zpsd1e23297.gif[/img][/URL] [URL=http://www.hungerscape.com][IMG]http://i104.photobucket.com/albums/m193/mrgiggles1993/Website_zpse52b2c12.gif[/img][/URL] [/CENTER]

[ADMIN=About][SIZE=3]Have you grown tired of most private servers, are you bored of doing the EXACT same thing on each and every one? Well, that&#39;s where we promise to be different at. Our server is entirely a [U]mini-game[/U] based server, no leveling, and no grinding for hours on end to achieve goals that you might just end up [SIZE=4]losing anyways![/SIZE]

Sound good? Well continue on reading! Our gameplay concept is based off the [b]Hunger Games[/b], similar to the [b]Minecraft[/b] servers, but unique and fun in its own way! - [SIZE=2][I]If you don&#39;t know what the Hunger Games are, then you should definitely go watch the movie or read the book, you&#39;ll love them![/I][/SIZE]

SO, do you think you can fight off 15 or more players in a timed death match? Oh not to mention, the only items you can acquire are the ones that you find around the map, or from the players you&#39;ve killed. Think you have what it takes? Only the best can win!

You can unlock or buy [I]special kits[/I] to help your chances of winning, unlock [I]new perks[/I] that increase passive abilities, and fight your way to the top! If you think you have what it takes, then please join, and be prepared to fight for your life![/SIZE][/ADMIN]

[CENTER][IMG]http://i104.photobucket.com/albums/m193/mrgiggles1993/portfolio4_zps56a141bf.jpg[/img] [IMG]http://i104.photobucket.com/albums/m193/mrgiggles1993/portfolio2_zps4d0b5240.jpg[/img] [IMG]http://i104.photobucket.com/albums/m193/mrgiggles1993/portfolio1_zps2b172606.jpg[/img]

[youtube]https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=AB0MWrj1-N8][/youtube]
[youtube]https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=UljZcm8knyo[/youtube]
[/CENTER]

[size=24pt]Kits Description[/size]

&lt;blockquote&gt;[ul][*][B][COLOR=blue]Default:[/COLOR][/B] Has a slight chance for a little more food from chest drops


[*][B][COLOR=blue]Berserk:[/COLOR][/B] Has a slight chance to increase your max hit damage, start with a zerker necklace and a super strength pot. Berserks do 5% more passive damaged but have -10% defense.


[*][B][COLOR=blue]Archer:[/COLOR][/B] Have the ability at random to shoot quicker with an MSB, also have a higher chance to get arrows or any ammo from chests. Start with ranger boots and an MSB. Archers have 5% more passive range damage but -5% melee.


[*][B][COLOR=blue]Elementalist:[/COLOR][/B] You don&#39;t need any elemental runes (Airs, fires, etc) while casting spells. Also you have a higher chance of getting runes from chests. Start with Ancient staff and wizard boots. Elementalist can hit upto 5 more damage with any spell.


[*][B][COLOR=blue]Alchemist:[/COLOR][/B] Start with a mixture of herbs and vials to make potions.(Note there is no other way to get most pots unless you&#39;re alchemist). Also have a high chance to drop herbs and vials from chests.


[*][B][COLOR=blue]Forsaken:[/COLOR][/B] Spawn in a random spot outside of the circle during the beginning of the match.


[*][B][COLOR=blue]Sickness:[/COLOR][/B] Has a 10% chance to rot 1 or 2 of your opponents food with melee and slightly less then 10% with range or mage!


[*][B][COLOR=blue]Saint:[/COLOR][/B] Prayer drain is drastically reduced, you&#39;re also immune to the decreasing prayer that happens throughout the match. You&#39;re given a permanent &quot;smite&quot; ability without actually having to use smite. If you&#39;re less than 99 hp you have a chance to randomly be healed by Saradomin. You start with a holy symbol, you must wear this for the effects. 


[*][B][COLOR=blue]Tagged:[/COLOR][/B] Tagged is a interesting kit where you get a special device, and with it, you can use some powerful abilities. First you must attack a player, after doing so they become tagged. The last person you attack is the person who becomes saved as your tagged player. Now with your device you&#39;ll be able to either &quot;Hurt&quot;, &quot;Teleport&quot;, or &quot;Copy&quot; them. Hurting will deal a random amount of damage up to 30. Teleporting will bring them to you, and last, copying them will copy their gear, but becareful because it has a high chance of failure.


[*][B][COLOR=blue]Perished:[/COLOR][/B] When you die you&#39;ll respawn on the same spot with your items and 60 hp. You can only do this once per game.


[*][B][COLOR=blue]Venom:[/COLOR][/B] Has a chance to poison anyone you hit with any weapon. Your poison will do 10 damage. You can&#39;t poison other venoms.


[*][B][COLOR=blue]Blizzard:[/COLOR][/B] You have a chance to freeze the person you&#39;re fighting with a ice barrage that does upto 10 extra damage (10% chance with range, and 20% with melee). You start with ice gloves and must wear these to get the effect, you&#39;re also immune to desert heat.


[*][B][COLOR=blue]Flash:[/COLOR][/B] You have the ability to teleport anywhere you click, whether it&#39;s on the minimap or the main game screen. You start with boots of lightness and must be wearing these for the effect. You&#39;ll have a 8 sec cooldown.


[*][B][COLOR=blue]Looter:[/COLOR][/B] Increase your chances for rare items by 50%, and increase your chance for a Grand chest from 1/75 for normal players too 1/45 for Looters. You start with a rogues mask and must wear this for the effect.


[*][B][COLOR=blue]Jumper:[/COLOR][/B] Start with a portal item that lets you place a portal down anywhere you want. Later you can teleport back to the portal and anyone else around you. The cooldown is 20 seconds.


[*][B][COLOR=blue]Skiller:[/COLOR][/B] Start with two saradomin brews, some unfinished rune arrows, and a prayer potion. You can fix barrows within your inventory with a 100% success rate, and you can steal already cooked fish from stalls.(Normally raw) You&#39;re immune to desert heat and trapped chests don&#39;t work on you.


[*][B][COLOR=blue]Chaos:[/COLOR][/B] Has a chance to randomly unequip and drop enemy items, cause bleeding damage that does upto 8 damage over a couple seconds and disable players run.


[*][B][COLOR=blue]Tainted:[/COLOR][/B] Can hit through players defense and prayer and steal their health. Also given a powerful orb that will steal all players health that are around you, and recover some prayer of yours too.


[*][B][COLOR=blue]Necromorpher:[/COLOR][/B] The Necromorpher is our &quot;upgraded&quot; version of the Elementalist except with a tad bit of evil mixed in. When using this kit, you&#39;ll be given a Necromancy book. If you read the book it will turn you into a skeleton mage, increasing magic attack by 100%, increasing magic damage by 10 (That&#39;s 5 more than Elementalist!), and a 50% defense increase. Not just that, but you&#39;ll also get unlimited runes of all types! Beware though, your body can only maintain being in this morphed state for 45 seconds. Once those 45 seconds are up you&#39;ll need to wait 75 seconds to morph again.


[*][B][COLOR=blue]Knight:[/COLOR][/B] Ready to be sworn in as a Knight of the round table? With this kit you&#39;ll be the tank of all other kits. The Knight gets a few very unique abilities that&#39;ll make him untouchable, yea, seriously! He starts with Excalibur, but because hes a Knight the sword syncs better to him. Making the special attack 2X better just for him. On top of the defense boost from the sword, he has a 10% higher passive defense (As if he always has defense prayer on). But, what makes the Knight most unique is his second item. The Holy Force. When used will make him completely invincible for 20 seconds! With such a power comes a down side, both melee and range will be -10% weaker and it has an 80 second cooldown before it can be used again.


[*][B][COLOR=blue]Wretched:[/COLOR][/B] Get ready to absorb one of the greatest powers of all Runescape! With this kit you&#39;ll get a special Tomb Book, when attemping to read, you&#39;ll become possessed by one of the anicent barrows warriors! You&#39;ll randomly be transform into one, and gain their powers. Some of which include; Dharoks the Wretched&#39;s insane strength, Guthans the Infested&#39;s hitpoint leeching, and Veracs the Defiled&#39;s ablity to pierce armor and prayer! Your stats will be based on how long the game has been going and progressively get higher as the game goes on. In the death match your equipment stats will be 110% of their normal power! Also, similar to the Necromopher kit you&#39;ll also get a +50% passive defense buff while being possessed![/COLOR][/ul]&lt;/blockquote&gt;



[size=24pt]More Media[/size]
[SPOILER=Player submitted pictures]
[img]http://gyazo.com/8ffa0d166a97d3c5283d15daa638769b.png[/img]
[img]http://imageshack.us/a/img5/8484/1gzm.png[/img]
[img]http://imageshack.us/a/img593/8064/wzb9.png[/img]
[img]http://gyazo.com/a08e9d4e86d742ed3bef1477cbf93404.png[/img]
[img]http://gyazo.com/bb65c86dc5c2b81a4d47fde17de287b7.png[/img]
[img]http://screencloud.net/img/screenshots/bfcc5bb14df90e6993055aaecc4435ca.png[/img]
[img]http://i44.tinypic.com/b9isnq.png[/img]
[img]http://i41.tinypic.com/14b3hxd.jpg[/img]
[img]http://s1122.photobucket.com/user/Risk_it/media/lotsofppl_zps7f1994ec.png.html[/img]
[img]http://i42.tinypic.com/2a91usn.jpg[/img]
[img]http://i44.tinypic.com/24zkj9d.jpg[/img]
[img]http://i40.tinypic.com/fxvtzs.jpg[/img]
[img]http://i44.tinypic.com/2jryic.jpg[/img]
[img]http://i39.tinypic.com/2a0azbo.png[/img]
[img]http://i40.tinypic.com/2rfttg0.png[/img]
[img]http://i41.tinypic.com/qpl0r6.png[/img]
[img]http://i40.tinypic.com/2cenr0z.png[/img]
[img]http://i43.tinypic.com/23roi6h.png[/img]
[img]http://i44.tinypic.com/5xpgzq.png[/img]
[img]http://i40.tinypic.com/dwf4o6.png[/img]
[img]http://i41.tinypic.com/1zd4pwi.png[/img]
[img]http://i42.tinypic.com/2ezsh2q.png[/img]
[/SPOILER]

[SPOILER=Pictures]
[CENTER]
[IMG]http://i104.photobucket.com/albums/m193/mrgiggles1993/19people_zpsba2da7e8.png[/img]
[IMG]http://i104.photobucket.com/albums/m193/mrgiggles1993/dm_zps93bf3268.png[/img]
[IMG]http://i104.photobucket.com/albums/m193/mrgiggles1993/desert2_zpsb56942ea.png[/img]
[IMG]http://i104.photobucket.com/albums/m193/mrgiggles1993/desert1_zps550aaeea.png[/img]
[IMG]http://i104.photobucket.com/albums/m193/mrgiggles1993/miscmap_2_zps8d917858.png[/img]
[IMG]http://i104.photobucket.com/albums/m193/mrgiggles1993/chestroom_zpse8b2d057.png[/img]
[IMG]http://i104.photobucket.com/albums/m193/mrgiggles1993/ice_zps150063b5.png[/img]

Lobby
[IMG]http://i104.photobucket.com/albums/m193/mrgiggles1993/4_zpsc4fef3e7.png[/img]

Count down
[IMG]http://i104.photobucket.com/albums/m193/mrgiggles1993/12_zps6fd1ef2e.png[/img]

Random in-game pictures
[IMG]http://i104.photobucket.com/albums/m193/mrgiggles1993/16_zps008d26af.png[/img]
[IMG]http://i104.photobucket.com/albums/m193/mrgiggles1993/18_zps5f573ab7.png[/img]
[IMG]http://i104.photobucket.com/albums/m193/mrgiggles1993/11_zpsc2be0347.png[/img]

Other
[IMG]http://i104.photobucket.com/albums/m193/mrgiggles1993/trap_zps1cc26403.png[/img]
[IMG]http://i104.photobucket.com/albums/m193/mrgiggles1993/7_zps7d7fbf6d.png[/img]
[IMG]http://i104.photobucket.com/albums/m193/mrgiggles1993/2_zps6ea070ec.png[/img]
[/CENTER]
[/SPOILER]</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 06 Sep 2014 17:35:14 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/hungerscape-may-the-odds-be-ever-in-your-favour/546528.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>HungerScape - May the odds be ever in your favour</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@naseem142 naseem142]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/naseem142">@naseem142</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote" data-post="3" data-topic="546528">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/ricky-v/40/5_e05bb34c421432ee4d40de30c10af3e5.png" class="avatar"> ricky-v:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>We and mr giggles are re-hosting this. Look on r-s if you want proof.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Just did , Mr.giggles has nothing to do with the re-hosting.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/hungerscape-may-the-odds-be-ever-in-your-favour/546528/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/hungerscape-may-the-odds-be-ever-in-your-favour/546528/4</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 06 Sep 2014 17:35:14 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-546528-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/hungerscape-may-the-odds-be-ever-in-your-favour/546528.rss">HungerScape - May the odds be ever in your favour</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>HungerScape - May the odds be ever in your favour</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@ricky-v ricky-v]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/ricky-v">@ricky-v</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>We and mr giggles are re-hosting this. Look on r-s if you want proof.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/hungerscape-may-the-odds-be-ever-in-your-favour/546528/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/hungerscape-may-the-odds-be-ever-in-your-favour/546528/3</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 06 Sep 2014 17:10:18 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-546528-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/hungerscape-may-the-odds-be-ever-in-your-favour/546528.rss">HungerScape - May the odds be ever in your favour</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>HungerScape - May the odds be ever in your favour</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@naseem142 naseem142]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/naseem142">@naseem142</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>You just literally took the pictures from the download thread too…  :palm:</p>
<p><a href="https://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php/topic,662108.msg4425415.html#msg4425415" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">[317] Official HungerGames Runescape Source Download</a></p>
<p>If you want to leech it at-least give credits…</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/hungerscape-may-the-odds-be-ever-in-your-favour/546528/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/hungerscape-may-the-odds-be-ever-in-your-favour/546528/2</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 06 Sep 2014 15:43:15 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-546528-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/hungerscape-may-the-odds-be-ever-in-your-favour/546528.rss">HungerScape - May the odds be ever in your favour</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>HungerScape - May the odds be ever in your favour</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@ricky-v ricky-v]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/ricky-v">@ricky-v</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[CENTER]<img src="http://i104.photobucket.com/albums/m193/mrgiggles1993/bannerhungergames2_zps54ceea01.png" alt width="" height=""><br>
[URL=http://www.hungerscape.com/home/play.html]<img src="http://i104.photobucket.com/albums/m193/mrgiggles1993/PlayNow2_zpsd1e23297.gif" alt width="" height="">[/URL] [URL=http://www.hungerscape.com]<img src="http://i104.photobucket.com/albums/m193/mrgiggles1993/Website_zpse52b2c12.gif" alt width="" height="">[/URL] [/CENTER]</p>
<p>[ADMIN=About][SIZE=3]Have you grown tired of most private servers, are you bored of doing the EXACT same thing on each and every one? Well, that’s where we promise to be different at. Our server is entirely a [U]mini-game[/U] based server, no leveling, and no grinding for hours on end to achieve goals that you might just end up [SIZE=4]losing anyways![/SIZE]</p>
<p>Sound good? Well continue on reading! Our gameplay concept is based off the <span class="bbcode-b">Hunger Games</span>, similar to the <span class="bbcode-b">Minecraft</span> servers, but unique and fun in its own way! - [SIZE=2][I]If you don’t know what the Hunger Games are, then you should definitely go watch the movie or read the book, you’ll love them![/I][/SIZE]</p>
<p>SO, do you think you can fight off 15 or more players in a timed death match? Oh not to mention, the only items you can acquire are the ones that you find around the map, or from the players you’ve killed. Think you have what it takes? Only the best can win!</p>
<p>You can unlock or buy [I]special kits[/I] to help your chances of winning, unlock [I]new perks[/I] that increase passive abilities, and fight your way to the top! If you think you have what it takes, then please join, and be prepared to fight for your life![/SIZE][/ADMIN]</p>
<p>[CENTER]<img src="http://i104.photobucket.com/albums/m193/mrgiggles1993/portfolio4_zps56a141bf.jpg" alt width="" height=""> <img src="http://i104.photobucket.com/albums/m193/mrgiggles1993/portfolio2_zps4d0b5240.jpg" alt width="" height=""> <img src="http://i104.photobucket.com/albums/m193/mrgiggles1993/portfolio1_zps2b172606.jpg" alt width="" height=""></p>
<p>[youtube]<a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=AB0MWrj1-N8" rel="nofollow noopener">https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=AB0MWrj1-N8</a>][/youtube]<br>
[youtube]<a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=UljZcm8knyo%5B/youtube%5D" rel="nofollow noopener">https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=UljZcm8knyo[/youtube]</a><br>
[/CENTER]</p>
<p>[size=24pt]Kits Description[/size]</p>
<blockquote>[ul][*][B][COLOR=blue]Default:[/COLOR][/B] Has a slight chance for a little more food from chest drops
<p>[*][B][COLOR=blue]Berserk:[/COLOR][/B] Has a slight chance to increase your max hit damage, start with a zerker necklace and a super strength pot. Berserks do 5% more passive damaged but have -10% defense.</p>
<p>[*][B][COLOR=blue]Archer:[/COLOR][/B] Have the ability at random to shoot quicker with an MSB, also have a higher chance to get arrows or any ammo from chests. Start with ranger boots and an MSB. Archers have 5% more passive range damage but -5% melee.</p>
<p>[*][B][COLOR=blue]Elementalist:[/COLOR][/B] You don’t need any elemental runes (Airs, fires, etc) while casting spells. Also you have a higher chance of getting runes from chests. Start with Ancient staff and wizard boots. Elementalist can hit upto 5 more damage with any spell.</p>
<p>[*][B][COLOR=blue]Alchemist:[/COLOR][/B] Start with a mixture of herbs and vials to make potions.(Note there is no other way to get most pots unless you’re alchemist). Also have a high chance to drop herbs and vials from chests.</p>
<p>[*][B][COLOR=blue]Forsaken:[/COLOR][/B] Spawn in a random spot outside of the circle during the beginning of the match.</p>
<p>[*][B][COLOR=blue]Sickness:[/COLOR][/B] Has a 10% chance to rot 1 or 2 of your opponents food with melee and slightly less then 10% with range or mage!</p>
<p>[*][B][COLOR=blue]Saint:[/COLOR][/B] Prayer drain is drastically reduced, you’re also immune to the decreasing prayer that happens throughout the match. You’re given a permanent “smite” ability without actually having to use smite. If you’re less than 99 hp you have a chance to randomly be healed by Saradomin. You start with a holy symbol, you must wear this for the effects.</p>
<p>[*][B][COLOR=blue]Tagged:[/COLOR][/B] Tagged is a interesting kit where you get a special device, and with it, you can use some powerful abilities. First you must attack a player, after doing so they become tagged. The last person you attack is the person who becomes saved as your tagged player. Now with your device you’ll be able to either “Hurt”, “Teleport”, or “Copy” them. Hurting will deal a random amount of damage up to 30. Teleporting will bring them to you, and last, copying them will copy their gear, but becareful because it has a high chance of failure.</p>
<p>[*][B][COLOR=blue]Perished:[/COLOR][/B] When you die you’ll respawn on the same spot with your items and 60 hp. You can only do this once per game.</p>
<p>[*][B][COLOR=blue]Venom:[/COLOR][/B] Has a chance to poison anyone you hit with any weapon. Your poison will do 10 damage. You can’t poison other venoms.</p>
<p>[*][B][COLOR=blue]Blizzard:[/COLOR][/B] You have a chance to freeze the person you’re fighting with a ice barrage that does upto 10 extra damage (10% chance with range, and 20% with melee). You start with ice gloves and must wear these to get the effect, you’re also immune to desert heat.</p>
<p>[*][B][COLOR=blue]Flash:[/COLOR][/B] You have the ability to teleport anywhere you click, whether it’s on the minimap or the main game screen. You start with boots of lightness and must be wearing these for the effect. You’ll have a 8 sec cooldown.</p>
<p>[*][B][COLOR=blue]Looter:[/COLOR][/B] Increase your chances for rare items by 50%, and increase your chance for a Grand chest from 1/75 for normal players too 1/45 for Looters. You start with a rogues mask and must wear this for the effect.</p>
<p>[*][B][COLOR=blue]Jumper:[/COLOR][/B] Start with a portal item that lets you place a portal down anywhere you want. Later you can teleport back to the portal and anyone else around you. The cooldown is 20 seconds.</p>
<p>[*][B][COLOR=blue]Skiller:[/COLOR][/B] Start with two saradomin brews, some unfinished rune arrows, and a prayer potion. You can fix barrows within your inventory with a 100% success rate, and you can steal already cooked fish from stalls.(Normally raw) You’re immune to desert heat and trapped chests don’t work on you.</p>
<p>[*][B][COLOR=blue]Chaos:[/COLOR][/B] Has a chance to randomly unequip and drop enemy items, cause bleeding damage that does upto 8 damage over a couple seconds and disable players run.</p>
<p>[*][B][COLOR=blue]Tainted:[/COLOR][/B] Can hit through players defense and prayer and steal their health. Also given a powerful orb that will steal all players health that are around you, and recover some prayer of yours too.</p>
<p>[*][B][COLOR=blue]Necromorpher:[/COLOR][/B] The Necromorpher is our “upgraded” version of the Elementalist except with a tad bit of evil mixed in. When using this kit, you’ll be given a Necromancy book. If you read the book it will turn you into a skeleton mage, increasing magic attack by 100%, increasing magic damage by 10 (That’s 5 more than Elementalist!), and a 50% defense increase. Not just that, but you’ll also get unlimited runes of all types! Beware though, your body can only maintain being in this morphed state for 45 seconds. Once those 45 seconds are up you’ll need to wait 75 seconds to morph again.</p>
<p>[*][B][COLOR=blue]Knight:[/COLOR][/B] Ready to be sworn in as a Knight of the round table? With this kit you’ll be the tank of all other kits. The Knight gets a few very unique abilities that’ll make him untouchable, yea, seriously! He starts with Excalibur, but because hes a Knight the sword syncs better to him. Making the special attack 2X better just for him. On top of the defense boost from the sword, he has a 10% higher passive defense (As if he always has defense prayer on). But, what makes the Knight most unique is his second item. The Holy Force. When used will make him completely invincible for 20 seconds! With such a power comes a down side, both melee and range will be -10% weaker and it has an 80 second cooldown before it can be used again.</p>
<p>[*][B][COLOR=blue]Wretched:[/COLOR][/B] Get ready to absorb one of the greatest powers of all Runescape! With this kit you’ll get a special Tomb Book, when attemping to read, you’ll become possessed by one of the anicent barrows warriors! You’ll randomly be transform into one, and gain their powers. Some of which include; Dharoks the Wretched’s insane strength, Guthans the Infested’s hitpoint leeching, and Veracs the Defiled’s ablity to pierce armor and prayer! Your stats will be based on how long the game has been going and progressively get higher as the game goes on. In the death match your equipment stats will be 110% of their normal power! Also, similar to the Necromopher kit you’ll also get a +50% passive defense buff while being possessed![/COLOR][/ul]</p>
</blockquote>
<p>[size=24pt]More Media[/size]<br>
[SPOILER=Player submitted pictures]<br>
<img src="http://gyazo.com/8ffa0d166a97d3c5283d15daa638769b.png" alt width="" height=""><br>
<img src="http://imageshack.us/a/img5/8484/1gzm.png" alt width="" height=""><br>
<img src="http://imageshack.us/a/img593/8064/wzb9.png" alt width="" height=""><br>
<img src="http://gyazo.com/a08e9d4e86d742ed3bef1477cbf93404.png" alt width="" height=""><br>
<img src="http://gyazo.com/bb65c86dc5c2b81a4d47fde17de287b7.png" alt width="" height=""><br>
<img src="http://screencloud.net/img/screenshots/bfcc5bb14df90e6993055aaecc4435ca.png" alt width="" height=""><br>
<img src="http://i44.tinypic.com/b9isnq.png" alt width="" height=""><br>
<img src="http://i41.tinypic.com/14b3hxd.jpg" alt width="" height=""><br>
<img src="http://s1122.photobucket.com/user/Risk_it/media/lotsofppl_zps7f1994ec.png.html" alt width="" height=""><br>
<img src="http://i42.tinypic.com/2a91usn.jpg" alt width="" height=""><br>
<img src="http://i44.tinypic.com/24zkj9d.jpg" alt width="" height=""><br>
<img src="http://i40.tinypic.com/fxvtzs.jpg" alt width="" height=""><br>
<img src="http://i44.tinypic.com/2jryic.jpg" alt width="" height=""><br>
<img src="http://i39.tinypic.com/2a0azbo.png" alt width="" height=""><br>
<img src="http://i40.tinypic.com/2rfttg0.png" alt width="" height=""><br>
<img src="http://i41.tinypic.com/qpl0r6.png" alt width="" height=""><br>
<img src="http://i40.tinypic.com/2cenr0z.png" alt width="" height=""><br>
<img src="http://i43.tinypic.com/23roi6h.png" alt width="" height=""><br>
<img src="http://i44.tinypic.com/5xpgzq.png" alt width="" height=""><br>
<img src="http://i40.tinypic.com/dwf4o6.png" alt width="" height=""><br>
<img src="http://i41.tinypic.com/1zd4pwi.png" alt width="" height=""><br>
<img src="http://i42.tinypic.com/2ezsh2q.png" alt width="" height=""><br>
[/SPOILER]</p>
<p>[SPOILER=Pictures]<br>
[CENTER]<br>
<img src="http://i104.photobucket.com/albums/m193/mrgiggles1993/19people_zpsba2da7e8.png" alt width="" height=""><br>
<img src="http://i104.photobucket.com/albums/m193/mrgiggles1993/dm_zps93bf3268.png" alt width="" height=""><br>
<img src="http://i104.photobucket.com/albums/m193/mrgiggles1993/desert2_zpsb56942ea.png" alt width="" height=""><br>
<img src="http://i104.photobucket.com/albums/m193/mrgiggles1993/desert1_zps550aaeea.png" alt width="" height=""><br>
<img src="http://i104.photobucket.com/albums/m193/mrgiggles1993/miscmap_2_zps8d917858.png" alt width="" height=""><br>
<img src="http://i104.photobucket.com/albums/m193/mrgiggles1993/chestroom_zpse8b2d057.png" alt width="" height=""><br>
<img src="http://i104.photobucket.com/albums/m193/mrgiggles1993/ice_zps150063b5.png" alt width="" height=""></p>
<p>Lobby<br>
<img src="http://i104.photobucket.com/albums/m193/mrgiggles1993/4_zpsc4fef3e7.png" alt width="" height=""></p>
<p>Count down<br>
<img src="http://i104.photobucket.com/albums/m193/mrgiggles1993/12_zps6fd1ef2e.png" alt width="" height=""></p>
<p>Random in-game pictures<br>
<img src="http://i104.photobucket.com/albums/m193/mrgiggles1993/16_zps008d26af.png" alt width="" height=""><br>
<img src="http://i104.photobucket.com/albums/m193/mrgiggles1993/18_zps5f573ab7.png" alt width="" height=""><br>
<img src="http://i104.photobucket.com/albums/m193/mrgiggles1993/11_zpsc2be0347.png" alt width="" height=""></p>
<p>Other<br>
<img src="http://i104.photobucket.com/albums/m193/mrgiggles1993/trap_zps1cc26403.png" alt width="" height=""><br>
<img src="http://i104.photobucket.com/albums/m193/mrgiggles1993/7_zps7d7fbf6d.png" alt width="" height=""><br>
<img src="http://i104.photobucket.com/albums/m193/mrgiggles1993/2_zps6ea070ec.png" alt width="" height=""><br>
[/CENTER]<br>
[/SPOILER]</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/hungerscape-may-the-odds-be-ever-in-your-favour/546528/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/hungerscape-may-the-odds-be-ever-in-your-favour/546528/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 06 Sep 2014 15:33:44 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-546528-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/hungerscape-may-the-odds-be-ever-in-your-favour/546528.rss">HungerScape - May the odds be ever in your favour</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
