<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Sincerity | Cammy PvP | Random Mushrooms | Elo Rating | Slayer |</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/sincerity-cammy-pvp-random-mushrooms-elo-rating-slayer/549957</link>
    <description>[CENTER][IMG]http://sincerity317.org/Forum/public/style_images/5_Sincerity_Forum_BAnner.png[/img]

Sincerity - the quality of being free from pretense, deceit, or hypocrisy.

[FONT=arial black][URL=http://&quot;http://sincerity317.org/&quot;][COLOR=#ffffff]Website [/COLOR][/URL][COLOR=#ffffff] | [/COLOR][URL=http://&quot;http://sincerity317.org/Forum&quot;][COLOR=#ffffff]Forum [/COLOR][/URL][COLOR=#ffffff] | [/COLOR][URL=http://&quot;http://sincerity317.org/Sinceritypvp.jar&quot;][COLOR=#ffffff]Webclient [/COLOR][/URL][COLOR=#ffffff] | [/COLOR][URL=http://&quot;http://sincerity317.org/Sinceritypvp.jar&quot;][COLOR=#ffffff]DOWNLOAD Client [/COLOR][/URL][/FONT]

[ADMIN=About Sincerity - Cammy PvP Edition]Sincerity has came back to a different aspect on the PvP perspective to revamp the outlook on PvP Servers. We&#39;re attempting a go at Cammy PvP. We&#39;ve all played our fair share of private servers and many of us have played various Cammy PvP servers, as well as Frostiescape. We&#39;re currently pursuing our base as Frostiescape, with full credits and permissions from &quot;Atomic_Int&quot;, aka Ryley, grants us full use and permission to host this source as it is NOT RELEASED ANY WHERE! 

What aspect does Sincerity have?
-As a strict Cammy PvP server, it has to have many ways to keep activity in game. We currently possess the skill &#39;Slayer&#39;, as the alternative to money making as well as thieving. When attempting to level your slayer up, you&#39;ll work your way up the tower, from the lowest npc&#39;s, to the best. Granting the best and the worst experience, as we all must start from the bottom. Abyssal demons and Dark Beasts will be the main accumulative to the money making method within&#39; this skill. Not the slayin&#39; type? Pursue the skill in thieving, granting you fair and balanced amounts of cash to supply your Pk&#39;ing Hunger. 

-We&#39;ll be taking a turn to our Hybridders and Main Pkers. Why do we want to bring those of you in? I myself have been testing out servers and noticing nothing but Prodding and Pay to win servers. Where when you first start off, they all have Zuriels and maxed out armour, meanwhile you&#39;re wearing Mystic/ Ahrims and using DDS. We&#39;re edging away from that, everyone will play equally. And for those who tend to donate, will receive donator benefits, such as yell, overloads, and other minor things. These won&#39;t edge donators to pay for winning, as players will have extremes to level out the playing field. 

-Are you a Tri-Bridder? Are you a welfare bridder? What about just your average range/mage pure? Occasionally feel like NH&#39;ing? We&#39;ll provide exceptional combat for you to enjoy that aspect while Pk&#39;ing. With great delays and providing intermediate combat. We ensure you to have a good time around Sincerity. Building up your bank, your Elo Rating, and your bank, but while enjoying the Cammy PvP days.

-Is there any Multi areas?
With the home being Camelot Castle, the safe area is only in that one designated area, from there outside is PvP zones. Believe it or not, huge clan wars can take place very frequently a few clicks to the east. The Camelot Party Room and from there on east, is all Multi zoned Combat. With multiple entrances to Flank and surprise clans, you can start a nasty clan war out there. The combat is great to tri-brid on. You enjoy Nh&#39;ing and bridding? Pull off the tri-brid switching, instant switching, and great combat formula&#39;s and many other flawless aspects to our server.

What is an EloRating? Our Elo Rating system is a custom system, that classifies each player by ranking. The higher your rating, by EARNINGkills, the better your skull gets. If you&#39;re a good pker, and dominating the wildy, your Elo Rating goes up, causing your skull to change colors.
 
 
What&#39;s the aspect on our Elo Rating System? If you&#39;re a pker with a high Elo Rating, for example, if you&#39;re Elo Rating is 1500, and your opponents Elo Rating is 1000, and they kill you, they&#39;re Elo Rating will raise a lot more as they&#39;re killing someone of a higher ranking. And the user who died with the higher ranking, their Elo will drop a fair amount, and it&#39;s the same way around.[/ADMIN]

[img]http://i.imgur.com/qg9CZlM.png[/img]

-Elo Rating System
-Cammy PvP
-Party Room Multi Pking
-Three selected Bosses
-Slayer for money making
-Thieving Stalls for quick cash
-Random Mushrooms
-Intermediate Hybridding
-Great Combat
-Intense Pure Pking
-Boss Pets
-Kdr System
-And much more!

[img]http://i.imgur.com/LTMfkft.png[/img]

[SPOILER=Media]
[img]http://i.imgur.com/qQDUxla.png[/img]
[img]http://i.imgur.com/Ot5uLMR.png[/img]
[img]http://i.imgur.com/NSqSlV4.png[/img]
[img]http://i.imgur.com/T4iZu7t.png[/img]
[img]http://i.imgur.com/m7WaS3N.png[/img]
[img]http://i.imgur.com/zpjmRVi.png[/img]
[img]http://i.imgur.com/XNI1Yqd.png[/img]
[img]http://i.imgur.com/9vnv3BA.png[/img]
[img]http://i.imgur.com/qAfJ5sR.png[/img]
[img]http://i.imgur.com/2oilqlh.png[/img]
[img]http://i.imgur.com/GadF3Fc.png[/img]
[img]http://i.imgur.com/VKe5k18.png[/img]
[img]http://i.imgur.com/ODkStpm.png[/img]
[img]http://i.imgur.com/pTt4gvm.png[/img]
[img]http://i.imgur.com/O5ETno7.png[/img]
[img]http://i.imgur.com/Y2J3Mcq.png[/img]
[img]http://i.imgur.com/qHuYQEZ.png[/img]
[img]http://i.imgur.com/wJmbVtw.png[/img]
[img]http://i.imgur.com/tgtkcQl.png[/img]
[/SPOILER]

[SPOILER=Support us - Our Designs]
 
 
 
[IMG]http://i.imgur.com/9HSukor.gif[/img]
 
 
[IMG]http://i.imgur.com/JDtzanb.gif[/img][/SPOILER]

Developer(s)-
[IMG]http://toolkit.sfu.ca/webct/browser/java/images/java_icon.gif[/img][URL=http://&quot;http://www.rune-server.org/members/hiken/&quot;]Hiken[/URL]
[IMG]http://toolkit.sfu.ca/webct/browser/java/images/java_icon.gif[/img][URL=http://&quot;http://www.rune-server.org/members/twisty/&quot;]Twisty (Myself)[/URL]
[IMG]http://toolkit.sfu.ca/webct/browser/java/images/java_icon.gif[/img][URL=http://&quot;http://www.rune-server.org/members/morphine/&quot;]Morphine[/URL]

[img]http://i.imgur.com/fIMEy6X.gif[/img]

[/CENTER]</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2015 23:04:41 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/sincerity-cammy-pvp-random-mushrooms-elo-rating-slayer/549957.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Sincerity | Cammy PvP | Random Mushrooms | Elo Rating | Slayer |</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@hiken hiken]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/hiken">@hiken</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[CENTER]<img src="http://sincerity317.org/Forum/public/style_images/5_Sincerity_Forum_BAnner.png" alt width="" height=""></p>
<p>Sincerity - the quality of being free from pretense, deceit, or hypocrisy.</p>
<p>[FONT=arial black][URL=http://“<a href="http://sincerity317.org/" rel="nofollow noopener">http://sincerity317.org/</a>”][COLOR=#ffffff]Website [/COLOR][/URL][COLOR=#ffffff] | [/COLOR][URL=http://“<a href="http://sincerity317.org/Forum" rel="nofollow noopener">http://sincerity317.org/Forum</a>”][COLOR=#ffffff]Forum [/COLOR][/URL][COLOR=#ffffff] | [/COLOR][URL=http://“<a href="http://sincerity317.org/Sinceritypvp.jar" rel="nofollow noopener">http://sincerity317.org/Sinceritypvp.jar</a>”][COLOR=#ffffff]Webclient [/COLOR][/URL][COLOR=#ffffff] | [/COLOR][URL=http://“<a href="http://sincerity317.org/Sinceritypvp.jar" rel="nofollow noopener">http://sincerity317.org/Sinceritypvp.jar</a>”][COLOR=#ffffff]DOWNLOAD Client [/COLOR][/URL][/FONT]</p>
<p>[ADMIN=About Sincerity - Cammy PvP Edition]Sincerity has came back to a different aspect on the PvP perspective to revamp the outlook on PvP Servers. We’re attempting a go at Cammy PvP. We’ve all played our fair share of private servers and many of us have played various Cammy PvP servers, as well as Frostiescape. We’re currently pursuing our base as Frostiescape, with full credits and permissions from “Atomic_Int”, aka Ryley, grants us full use and permission to host this source as it is NOT RELEASED ANY WHERE!</p>
<p>What aspect does Sincerity have?<br>
-As a strict Cammy PvP server, it has to have many ways to keep activity in game. We currently possess the skill ‘Slayer’, as the alternative to money making as well as thieving. When attempting to level your slayer up, you’ll work your way up the tower, from the lowest npc’s, to the best. Granting the best and the worst experience, as we all must start from the bottom. Abyssal demons and Dark Beasts will be the main accumulative to the money making method within’ this skill. Not the slayin’ type? Pursue the skill in thieving, granting you fair and balanced amounts of cash to supply your Pk’ing Hunger.</p>
<p>-We’ll be taking a turn to our Hybridders and Main Pkers. Why do we want to bring those of you in? I myself have been testing out servers and noticing nothing but Prodding and Pay to win servers. Where when you first start off, they all have Zuriels and maxed out armour, meanwhile you’re wearing Mystic/ Ahrims and using DDS. We’re edging away from that, everyone will play equally. And for those who tend to donate, will receive donator benefits, such as yell, overloads, and other minor things. These won’t edge donators to pay for winning, as players will have extremes to level out the playing field.</p>
<p>-Are you a Tri-Bridder? Are you a welfare bridder? What about just your average range/mage pure? Occasionally feel like NH’ing? We’ll provide exceptional combat for you to enjoy that aspect while Pk’ing. With great delays and providing intermediate combat. We ensure you to have a good time around Sincerity. Building up your bank, your Elo Rating, and your bank, but while enjoying the Cammy PvP days.</p>
<p>-Is there any Multi areas?<br>
With the home being Camelot Castle, the safe area is only in that one designated area, from there outside is PvP zones. Believe it or not, huge clan wars can take place very frequently a few clicks to the east. The Camelot Party Room and from there on east, is all Multi zoned Combat. With multiple entrances to Flank and surprise clans, you can start a nasty clan war out there. The combat is great to tri-brid on. You enjoy Nh’ing and bridding? Pull off the tri-brid switching, instant switching, and great combat formula’s and many other flawless aspects to our server.</p>
<p>What is an EloRating? Our Elo Rating system is a custom system, that classifies each player by ranking. The higher your rating, by EARNINGkills, the better your skull gets. If you’re a good pker, and dominating the wildy, your Elo Rating goes up, causing your skull to change colors.</p>
<p>What’s the aspect on our Elo Rating System? If you’re a pker with a high Elo Rating, for example, if you’re Elo Rating is 1500, and your opponents Elo Rating is 1000, and they kill you, they’re Elo Rating will raise a lot more as they’re killing someone of a higher ranking. And the user who died with the higher ranking, their Elo will drop a fair amount, and it’s the same way around.[/ADMIN]</p>
<p><img src="http://i.imgur.com/qg9CZlM.png" alt width="" height=""></p>
<p>-Elo Rating System<br>
-Cammy PvP<br>
-Party Room Multi Pking<br>
-Three selected Bosses<br>
-Slayer for money making<br>
-Thieving Stalls for quick cash<br>
-Random Mushrooms<br>
-Intermediate Hybridding<br>
-Great Combat<br>
-Intense Pure Pking<br>
-Boss Pets<br>
-Kdr System<br>
-And much more!</p>
<p><img src="http://i.imgur.com/LTMfkft.png" alt width="" height=""></p>
<p>[SPOILER=Media]<br>
<img src="http://i.imgur.com/qQDUxla.png" alt width="" height=""><br>
<img src="http://i.imgur.com/Ot5uLMR.png" alt width="" height=""><br>
<img src="http://i.imgur.com/NSqSlV4.png" alt width="" height=""><br>
<img src="http://i.imgur.com/T4iZu7t.png" alt width="" height=""><br>
<img src="http://i.imgur.com/m7WaS3N.png" alt width="" height=""><br>
<img src="http://i.imgur.com/zpjmRVi.png" alt width="" height=""><br>
<img src="http://i.imgur.com/XNI1Yqd.png" alt width="" height=""><br>
<img src="http://i.imgur.com/9vnv3BA.png" alt width="" height=""><br>
<img src="http://i.imgur.com/qAfJ5sR.png" alt width="" height=""><br>
<img src="http://i.imgur.com/2oilqlh.png" alt width="" height=""><br>
<img src="http://i.imgur.com/GadF3Fc.png" alt width="" height=""><br>
<img src="http://i.imgur.com/VKe5k18.png" alt width="" height=""><br>
<img src="http://i.imgur.com/ODkStpm.png" alt width="" height=""><br>
<img src="http://i.imgur.com/pTt4gvm.png" alt width="" height=""><br>
<img src="http://i.imgur.com/O5ETno7.png" alt width="" height=""><br>
<img src="http://i.imgur.com/Y2J3Mcq.png" alt width="" height=""><br>
<img src="http://i.imgur.com/qHuYQEZ.png" alt width="" height=""><br>
<img src="http://i.imgur.com/wJmbVtw.png" alt width="" height=""><br>
<img src="http://i.imgur.com/tgtkcQl.png" alt width="" height=""><br>
[/SPOILER]</p>
<p>[SPOILER=Support us - Our Designs]</p>
<p><img src="http://i.imgur.com/9HSukor.gif" alt width="" height=""></p>
<p><img src="http://i.imgur.com/JDtzanb.gif" alt width="" height="">[/SPOILER]</p>
<p>Developer(s)-<br>
<img src="http://toolkit.sfu.ca/webct/browser/java/images/java_icon.gif" alt width="" height="">[URL=http://“<a href="http://www.rune-server.org/members/hiken/" rel="nofollow noopener">http://www.rune-server.org/members/hiken/</a>”]Hiken[/URL]<br>
<img src="http://toolkit.sfu.ca/webct/browser/java/images/java_icon.gif" alt width="" height="">[URL=http://“<a href="http://www.rune-server.org/members/twisty/" rel="nofollow noopener">http://www.rune-server.org/members/twisty/</a>”]Twisty (Myself)[/URL]<br>
<img src="http://toolkit.sfu.ca/webct/browser/java/images/java_icon.gif" alt width="" height="">[URL=http://“<a href="http://www.rune-server.org/members/morphine/" rel="nofollow noopener">http://www.rune-server.org/members/morphine/</a>”]Morphine[/URL]</p>
<p><img src="http://i.imgur.com/fIMEy6X.gif" alt width="" height=""></p>
<p>[/CENTER]</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/sincerity-cammy-pvp-random-mushrooms-elo-rating-slayer/549957/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/sincerity-cammy-pvp-random-mushrooms-elo-rating-slayer/549957/1</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2015 23:04:41 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-549957-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/sincerity-cammy-pvp-random-mushrooms-elo-rating-slayer/549957.rss">Sincerity | Cammy PvP | Random Mushrooms | Elo Rating | Slayer |</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
