<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Does anyone here bike? (bmx)</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/does-anyone-here-bike-bmx/449522</link>
    <description>Wasssupp&#39; guys.
To those who see me post in the RSPS section of these forums, you might know me. Anwayysss...
Since it&#39;s the Summer, I&#39;ve been wanting to bike lately because I hate sitting inside whilst on my PC during this time of the year. It&#39;s also annoying when I see my friends on Facebook talking about having an awesome day. So yeah, what I&#39;m asking for is if anyone is experienced in biking, and has some tips for me. I&#39;m decent I guess; I have bars, 360&#39;s, 180&#39;s, tuck no-handers, and chase hawks off of a fly out. I&#39;m trying to learn flat 360&#39;s, I get the rotation fine but as soon as I get to the 270 degree spin, the back of my bike drops. -.-
I&#39;ve been told to lean forward once I&#39;m at an 180 degree spin, then force the weight back once I spot my landing. And please don&#39;t tell me to whip the back of the bike, because that&#39;s what makes a biker sloppy, and lastly, don&#39;t tell me to look over my shoulder. I already do that lol.

Any advice?</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 13 Jul 2012 17:35:58 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>General Discussion</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/does-anyone-here-bike-bmx/449522.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Does anyone here bike? (bmx)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@DannyIsSoPro DannyIsSoPro]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/dannyissopro">@DannyIsSoPro</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Wasssupp’ guys.<br>
To those who see me post in the RSPS section of these forums, you might know me. Anwayysss…<br>
Since it’s the Summer, I’ve been wanting to bike lately because I hate sitting inside whilst on my PC during this time of the year. It’s also annoying when I see my friends on Facebook talking about having an awesome day. So yeah, what I’m asking for is if anyone is experienced in biking, and has some tips for me. I’m decent I guess; I have bars, 360’s, 180’s, tuck no-handers, and chase hawks off of a fly out. I’m trying to learn flat 360’s, I get the rotation fine but as soon as I get to the 270 degree spin, the back of my bike drops. -.-<br>
I’ve been told to lean forward once I’m at an 180 degree spin, then force the weight back once I spot my landing. And please don’t tell me to whip the back of the bike, because that’s what makes a biker sloppy, and lastly, don’t tell me to look over my shoulder. I already do that lol.</p>
<p>Any advice?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/does-anyone-here-bike-bmx/449522/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/does-anyone-here-bike-bmx/449522/1</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 13 Jul 2012 17:35:58 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-449522-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/does-anyone-here-bike-bmx/449522.rss">Does anyone here bike? (bmx)</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
