<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Packet Size Mismatch Frustration</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/packet-size-mismatch-frustration/134006</link>
    <description>Alright everyone. This might be a common problem and I&#39;m just not seeing the solution, but, I&#39;ve taken the Testscape PK Script and fashioned it to my liking, putting in all of my custom variables and whatnot.

Now, the problem is that once the first attack is over, ANY CLIENT that can see the attack (in visible range of the players)
has their client crash due to a...

Error packet size mismatch in get player pos: X psize: X, where X is different for each client.

Then Error: T2 - A ton of numbers, including what seems to be the coords of the player who crashed in there as well, so it&#39;s something to do with the players.

I&#39;m not really sure if there&#39;s something I&#39;m missing with updating player positions, but, help would be appreciated![br][size=1]Posted on: August 15, 2007, 12:53:16 PM[/size][hr]Alright, it&#39;s been 8 hours and I&#39;ve only had about 6 views. Perhaps now that traffic is kicking someone could atleast begin to help me with my problem.
[br][size=1]Posted on: August 16, 2007, 11:49:00 AM [/size][hr]Ok, this is rediculous. It&#39;s been an entire day and only 20 or so people have even looked at the problem, and no one has replied. Can anyone even START me looking in the right direction to solve this issue?</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 16 Aug 2007 05:18:05 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/packet-size-mismatch-frustration/134006.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Packet Size Mismatch Frustration</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Archbishop Archbishop]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/archbishop">@Archbishop</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Alright everyone. This might be a common problem and I’m just not seeing the solution, but, I’ve taken the Testscape PK Script and fashioned it to my liking, putting in all of my custom variables and whatnot.</p>
<p>Now, the problem is that once the first attack is over, ANY CLIENT that can see the attack (in visible range of the players)<br>
has their client crash due to a…</p>
<p>Error packet size mismatch in get player pos: X psize: X, where X is different for each client.</p>
<p>Then Error: T2 - A ton of numbers, including what seems to be the coords of the player who crashed in there as well, so it’s something to do with the players.</p>
<p>I’m not really sure if there’s something I’m missing with updating player positions, but, help would be appreciated![br][size=1]Posted on: August 15, 2007, 12:53:16 PM[/size][hr]Alright, it’s been 8 hours and I’ve only had about 6 views. Perhaps now that traffic is kicking someone could atleast begin to help me with my problem.<br>
[br][size=1]Posted on: August 16, 2007, 11:49:00 AM [/size][hr]Ok, this is rediculous. It’s been an entire day and only 20 or so people have even looked at the problem, and no one has replied. Can anyone even START me looking in the right direction to solve this issue?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/packet-size-mismatch-frustration/134006/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/packet-size-mismatch-frustration/134006/1</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 16 Aug 2007 05:18:05 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-134006-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/packet-size-mismatch-frustration/134006.rss">Packet Size Mismatch Frustration</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
