<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>The Q and A from official RSC forums!</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-q-and-a-from-official-rsc-forums/268321</link>
    <description>Sorry, not exactly on-topic, but I thought I should show you this...

Hi, 
I recently received a number of questions from the RuneScape Classic community which I have tried to answer as best I can below  

------------------- 

Q) (Ill Pun Ill) Will RuneScape Classic ever be reopened to the public, If so when and how? 
A) I would love to see RSC open to the public again, whilst now comparatively “retro” in appearance by comparison to the current High Detail version of RuneScape it’s still a great game which posses a unique charm and we are still deeply proud of our ground breaking roots. 
The key problem with opening up the game to the public is the absence of the anti-cheating and macro systems we have built up over the last few years, it is also the case that RSC contains all the features that were causing real world trading and therefore incentivising credit card fraud. 

From above it is clear we simply cannot open the current RSC game to the public without some substantial changes. Our development efforts are almost exclusively focused on evolving the latest version of RuneScape and therefore I suspect it would be years before we could “fix” RuneScape Classic. 

One idea that we are considering is perhaps opening the current RSC game to the public but providing everybody with the cheat codes to set their skills and inventory to whatever they liked. That way everybody could have whatever they wanted in game and there would be no incentive or advantage to cheat or bot. 
Naturally the RSC account would be isolated to RSC worlds and could never interact with the current version of RuneScape. 

------------------------- 

Q) (Ill Pun Ill) Will RuneScape Classic ever be closely moderated again? 
A) No, we currently continue to maintain the existing servers in recognition of our most loyal and ardent fans but all our support and development efforts are around the latest version of RuneScape. 
There is a small but dedicated community of just under 500 active players on RSC, I would expect that unsavoury individuals would quickly become isolated in such a close nit community. 

-------------------------- 

Q) (Caps Lock13) Will the bots be taken care of? 
A) Hopefully implementation of the 1st idea above will negate the purpose of bots. 

-------------------------- 

Q) (Mini Reddish) Will there be any RuneScape Classic events organised by Jagex? 
A) I would love to see more community activity in all parts of the organisation, we are still looking into how we might do this with RSC 

-------------------------- 

Q) (Hit Z) Will we get to have an RSC Cape to wear on RS2 and will we ever be allowed to transfer some of our items over to RS2 again? 
A) Certainly no transfer of items to RuneScape, although I really do like the idea of distinguishing our most loyal players in RuneScape – this ideal is currently on our development opportunities list. 

--------------------------- 

Q) (Legolas435) Will a RS2 item be released to show players still able to play RSC? 
A) Yes as above we are looking at the possibility of a skill cape or another unique item such as a hat perhaps. 

--------------------------- 

Q) (Ill Pun Ill) If avatars are added to the RuneScape, jAGeX forums. Can those of us who can play classic get are own, special avatar icon? 
A) I can’t see why not, it’s a bit of work but I think we could do it  

---------------------------- 

Q) (Ill Pun Ill) Will you dig-up the old RuneScape classic skill guides, world map *wild missing* and other features which were removed? 
A) I’m not sure exactly what the public version of RSC might contain, I would expect it would be rather similar to the current version but I would need to come back to you on this one. 

---------------------------- 

Q) (Ill Pun Ill)Will there ever be in game updates for RuneScape Classic, such as new quests, if no please state why, if yes i think it would be best if World 1 was for the updates world - World 2 stays as it is. 
A) No, all our future development activities are around improving and evolving the latest version of RuneScape 

---------------------------- 

Q) (R4ng3 P0w4) Will there ever be put together a full dedicated team to work with RuneScape Classic, just as with the current RuneScape, FunOrb and the new game MechScape? 
A) No as above our future development activities are around improving and evolving the latest version of our products as well as developing completely new game types for our players as we did with RSC nearly 10 years ago. 

----------------------------- 
Q) Will RuneScape classic ever be welcome on the front page again? 
A) Haha without doubt, as before we are really proud of what we first achieved nearly a decade ago and if we did decide to open it up to the public again we would give all our players the opportunity to check it out. 

----------------------------- 

Q) (Legolas435) Can we have a RuneScape Classic Day? 
A) How do you mean[br][br][size=1]Posted on: March 19, 2009, 08:42:21 am[/size][hr]Other stuff jmods said in the q and a...[br][br][size=1]Posted on: March 19, 2009, 08:43:31 am[/size][hr]So what do you guys think about opening RuneScape Classic to the public again but providing all the cheat codes at the same time? 

Q) (Garibaldo1) Oh and when will we have classic open after all ?1 Month ? 2 ? 3 ? four? five ? 
----------------- 
A) I would expect we could have it up and running in a matter of weeks   
  Mod Mark H 
Jagex Mod

 17-Mar-2009 22:52:16 
Iamlegend, 

What part aren&#39;t you sure about? 

Incidentally, I bet Mod MMG would be better at Runelink or Draughts than I am. I get my butt kicked everytime I play.  

~ MMH ~  

[br][br][size=1]Posted on: March 19, 2009, 08:44:14 am[/size][hr]Ahh okay Iamlegend, 

So, In the Q&amp;A Mod MMG suggests that one way to prevent RWT, cheating, macroing etc would be to open a new RuneScape Classic server, however you would be able to do all sorts of crazy things like J-Mods can do. 

So you could spawn items, set levels etc. 

This would obviously be limited to this new RSC server only.  

~ MMH ~ 

(You would *easily* wipe the floor with me at Runelink. The only board game I am good at is Cluedo) [br][br][size=1]Posted on: March 19, 2009, 08:44:47 am[/size][hr]Q) (Garibaldo1 ) Mod Mmg and Mod Mark H you both my gods now even more that guthix also giving all the cheat codes wouldn* it mean we would have to make a new account on the server since if we logged in a RS2 server we could keep the levels or something ?If i remember correctly if we got xp on a classic we would get it on RS2. But i have to admite having the all cheat codes would by handsome players could try to by in the skin of a high level player at least once and also that would kill for sure most private servers in a single shot! 
------------------ 
A) Hey Garibaldo, 
Yes the RuneScape classic account on the &quot;Public Servers&quot; would be a different account to your current RSC account so there would be NO possibility of skill or wealth transfer into the current version of RuneScape. This would be a isolated service just for Fun! 
I also love the idea of removing the reason for private servers to exist  [br][br][size=1]Posted on: March 19, 2009, 08:45:52 am[/size][hr]Q) (Ill Pun Ill) Would the current Classic players be able to moderate the game for you? 
------------------------- 
A) I think this is a great idea, naturally it would be entirely your choice if you wished to help out or not. 

Q) (Ill Pun Ill) There wouldn&#39;t be any new items just the currently existing Classic items and stats 
------------------------- 
A) No I expect the game would only contain skills and items already available in RuneScape Classic.  
  Mod Mark H 
Jagex Mod

 17-Mar-2009 23:13:38 
Hi Dolfin, 

I think that the RSC Forums would remain for those who use the RuneScape Classic... uhh Classic version. They&#39;re a very loyal community and those have always been their forums. 

What we could do though is add another forum for the free/open RSC.  

That&#39;s just a thought though. Mod MMG may have some scheme already planned.  

~ MMH ~  
[br][br][size=1]Posted on: March 19, 2009, 08:47:20 am[/size][hr]Q) (1dolfinsfan) Would we be able to use the classic forums then? 

------------------------- 
A) Unfortunately not, the classic forums this will remain reserved for the original classic community. 
We will however have a forum where the new RuneScape Classic &quot;Public Servers&quot; can be discussed. 

Q) (Emergency Cc) Ahh, it&#39;s so cool. MMH and MMG here answering questions &amp; talking. ;OOO 

ERMM. 

Oooh! 
Do you think you&#39;ll be accepting people for player support in 2012? And, I&#39;ve had tons of banned accounts, I&#39;ll admit it, and I&#39;ve been rude - does that lower my chances of working for you? (In 3 years time) 

------------------------- 
A) Don&#39;t worry about it Fella, I&#39;ve been rude too and I think turned out OK in the end [br][br][size=1]Posted on: March 19, 2009, 08:48:04 am[/size][hr]Sorry its a bit unorganized but those are all j-mod posts from Mod MMG enjoy! = ]</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 19 Mar 2009 16:14:53 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-q-and-a-from-official-rsc-forums/268321.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>The Q and A from official RSC forums!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Johnisriot Johnisriot]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/johnisriot">@Johnisriot</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Been posted.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-q-and-a-from-official-rsc-forums/268321/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-q-and-a-from-official-rsc-forums/268321/2</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 19 Mar 2009 16:14:53 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-268321-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-q-and-a-from-official-rsc-forums/268321.rss">The Q and A from official RSC forums!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The Q and A from official RSC forums!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@WE1 WE]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/we1">@WE1</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Sorry, not exactly on-topic, but I thought I should show you this…</p>
<p>Hi,<br>
I recently received a number of questions from the RuneScape Classic community which I have tried to answer as best I can below</p>
<hr>
<p>Q) (Ill Pun Ill) Will RuneScape Classic ever be reopened to the public, If so when and how?<br>
A) I would love to see RSC open to the public again, whilst now comparatively “retro” in appearance by comparison to the current High Detail version of RuneScape it’s still a great game which posses a unique charm and we are still deeply proud of our ground breaking roots.<br>
The key problem with opening up the game to the public is the absence of the anti-cheating and macro systems we have built up over the last few years, it is also the case that RSC contains all the features that were causing real world trading and therefore incentivising credit card fraud.</p>
<p>From above it is clear we simply cannot open the current RSC game to the public without some substantial changes. Our development efforts are almost exclusively focused on evolving the latest version of RuneScape and therefore I suspect it would be years before we could “fix” RuneScape Classic.</p>
<p>One idea that we are considering is perhaps opening the current RSC game to the public but providing everybody with the cheat codes to set their skills and inventory to whatever they liked. That way everybody could have whatever they wanted in game and there would be no incentive or advantage to cheat or bot.<br>
Naturally the RSC account would be isolated to RSC worlds and could never interact with the current version of RuneScape.</p>
<hr>
<p>Q) (Ill Pun Ill) Will RuneScape Classic ever be closely moderated again?<br>
A) No, we currently continue to maintain the existing servers in recognition of our most loyal and ardent fans but all our support and development efforts are around the latest version of RuneScape.<br>
There is a small but dedicated community of just under 500 active players on RSC, I would expect that unsavoury individuals would quickly become isolated in such a close nit community.</p>
<hr>
<p>Q) (Caps Lock13) Will the bots be taken care of?<br>
A) Hopefully implementation of the 1st idea above will negate the purpose of bots.</p>
<hr>
<p>Q) (Mini Reddish) Will there be any RuneScape Classic events organised by Jagex?<br>
A) I would love to see more community activity in all parts of the organisation, we are still looking into how we might do this with RSC</p>
<hr>
<p>Q) (Hit Z) Will we get to have an RSC Cape to wear on RS2 and will we ever be allowed to transfer some of our items over to RS2 again?<br>
A) Certainly no transfer of items to RuneScape, although I really do like the idea of distinguishing our most loyal players in RuneScape – this ideal is currently on our development opportunities list.</p>
<hr>
<p>Q) (Legolas435) Will a RS2 item be released to show players still able to play RSC?<br>
A) Yes as above we are looking at the possibility of a skill cape or another unique item such as a hat perhaps.</p>
<hr>
<p>Q) (Ill Pun Ill) If avatars are added to the RuneScape, jAGeX forums. Can those of us who can play classic get are own, special avatar icon?<br>
A) I can’t see why not, it’s a bit of work but I think we could do it</p>
<hr>
<p>Q) (Ill Pun Ill) Will you dig-up the old RuneScape classic skill guides, world map <em>wild missing</em> and other features which were removed?<br>
A) I’m not sure exactly what the public version of RSC might contain, I would expect it would be rather similar to the current version but I would need to come back to you on this one.</p>
<hr>
<p>Q) (Ill Pun Ill)Will there ever be in game updates for RuneScape Classic, such as new quests, if no please state why, if yes i think it would be best if World 1 was for the updates world - World 2 stays as it is.<br>
A) No, all our future development activities are around improving and evolving the latest version of RuneScape</p>
<hr>
<p>Q) (R4ng3 P0w4) Will there ever be put together a full dedicated team to work with RuneScape Classic, just as with the current RuneScape, FunOrb and the new game MechScape?<br>
A) No as above our future development activities are around improving and evolving the latest version of our products as well as developing completely new game types for our players as we did with RSC nearly 10 years ago.</p>
<hr>
<p>Q) Will RuneScape classic ever be welcome on the front page again?<br>
A) Haha without doubt, as before we are really proud of what we first achieved nearly a decade ago and if we did decide to open it up to the public again we would give all our players the opportunity to check it out.</p>
<hr>
<p>Q) (Legolas435) Can we have a RuneScape Classic Day?<br>
A) How do you mean[br][br][size=1]Posted on: March 19, 2009, 08:42:21 am[/size][hr]Other stuff jmods said in the q and a…[br][br][size=1]Posted on: March 19, 2009, 08:43:31 am[/size][hr]So what do you guys think about opening RuneScape Classic to the public again but providing all the cheat codes at the same time?</p>
<h2>Q) (Garibaldo1) Oh and when will we have classic open after all ?1 Month ? 2 ? 3 ? four? five ?</h2>
<p>A) I would expect we could have it up and running in a matter of weeks<br>
Mod Mark H<br>
Jagex Mod</p>
<p>17-Mar-2009 22:52:16<br>
Iamlegend,</p>
<p>What part aren’t you sure about?</p>
<p>Incidentally, I bet Mod MMG would be better at Runelink or Draughts than I am. I get my butt kicked everytime I play.</p>
<p>~ MMH ~</p>
<p>[br][br][size=1]Posted on: March 19, 2009, 08:44:14 am[/size][hr]Ahh okay Iamlegend,</p>
<p>So, In the Q&amp;A Mod MMG suggests that one way to prevent RWT, cheating, macroing etc would be to open a new RuneScape Classic server, however you would be able to do all sorts of crazy things like J-Mods can do.</p>
<p>So you could spawn items, set levels etc.</p>
<p>This would obviously be limited to this new RSC server only.</p>
<p>~ MMH ~</p>
<h2>(You would <em>easily</em> wipe the floor with me at Runelink. The only board game I am good at is Cluedo) [br][br][size=1]Posted on: March 19, 2009, 08:44:47 am[/size][hr]Q) (Garibaldo1 ) Mod Mmg and Mod Mark H you both my gods now even more that guthix also giving all the cheat codes wouldn* it mean we would have to make a new account on the server since if we logged in a RS2 server we could keep the levels or something ?If i remember correctly if we got xp on a classic we would get it on RS2. But i have to admite having the all cheat codes would by handsome players could try to by in the skin of a high level player at least once and also that would kill for sure most private servers in a single shot!</h2>
<h2>A) Hey Garibaldo,<br>
Yes the RuneScape classic account on the “Public Servers” would be a different account to your current RSC account so there would be NO possibility of skill or wealth transfer into the current version of RuneScape. This would be a isolated service just for Fun!<br>
I also love the idea of removing the reason for private servers to exist  [br][br][size=1]Posted on: March 19, 2009, 08:45:52 am[/size][hr]Q) (Ill Pun Ill) Would the current Classic players be able to moderate the game for you?</h2>
<p>A) I think this is a great idea, naturally it would be entirely your choice if you wished to help out or not.</p>
<h2>Q) (Ill Pun Ill) There wouldn’t be any new items just the currently existing Classic items and stats</h2>
<p>A) No I expect the game would only contain skills and items already available in RuneScape Classic.<br>
Mod Mark H<br>
Jagex Mod</p>
<p>17-Mar-2009 23:13:38<br>
Hi Dolfin,</p>
<p>I think that the RSC Forums would remain for those who use the RuneScape Classic… uhh Classic version. They’re a very loyal community and those have always been their forums.</p>
<p>What we could do though is add another forum for the free/open RSC.</p>
<p>That’s just a thought though. Mod MMG may have some scheme already planned.</p>
<p>~ MMH ~<br>
[br][br][size=1]Posted on: March 19, 2009, 08:47:20 am[/size][hr]Q) (1dolfinsfan) Would we be able to use the classic forums then?</p>
<hr>
<p>A) Unfortunately not, the classic forums this will remain reserved for the original classic community.<br>
We will however have a forum where the new RuneScape Classic “Public Servers” can be discussed.</p>
<p>Q) (Emergency Cc) Ahh, it’s so cool. MMH and MMG here answering questions &amp; talking. ;OOO</p>
<p>ERMM.</p>
<p>Oooh!<br>
Do you think you’ll be accepting people for player support in 2012? And, I’ve had tons of banned accounts, I’ll admit it, and I’ve been rude - does that lower my chances of working for you? (In 3 years time)</p>
<hr>
<p>A) Don’t worry about it Fella, I’ve been rude too and I think turned out OK in the end [br][br][size=1]Posted on: March 19, 2009, 08:48:04 am[/size][hr]Sorry its a bit unorganized but those are all j-mod posts from Mod MMG enjoy! = ]</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-q-and-a-from-official-rsc-forums/268321/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-q-and-a-from-official-rsc-forums/268321/1</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 19 Mar 2009 14:41:15 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-268321-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-q-and-a-from-official-rsc-forums/268321.rss">The Q and A from official RSC forums!</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
