<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Need help to fix a few things on a 562 (using rs2hd)</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/need-help-to-fix-a-few-things-on-a-562-using-rs2hd/394147</link>
    <description>As a new coder, I&#39;m actually very bad. So today, I am asking you, Moparscapers, to help me to code a couple of things. If you can find me a tutorial it would be appreciated or you can just tell me how to code if you feel like writing. Please be respectful, I am not english :S. 

[s]Ok, so the first thing that I would like to fix is the combat xp rate. Actually the rate is 4800xp so as you see, it is TOO much high. I wonder how can I slow it.[/s]

[s]After, I wonder how I can enable drops. (actually, when I drop something it disepears.)[/s]

Third, when I shoot any arrows, bolts, or even cannon balls, it doesn&#39;t use the projectiles. How can I make it use the projectiles ?

Fourth: I have the same problem with magic. When I cast a spell, it doesn&#39;t use runes. 

Finally, I wonder how I could add prayer curses. I know that I need sprites but what else? and how to add the effects, the gfx and everything ?

So thanks for replying.

~Jaimelatifa.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 07 May 2011 20:28:45 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Game Development</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/need-help-to-fix-a-few-things-on-a-562-using-rs2hd/394147.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Need help to fix a few things on a 562 (using rs2hd)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@jaimelatifa jaimelatifa]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/jaimelatifa">@jaimelatifa</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>As a new coder, I’m actually very bad. So today, I am asking you, Moparscapers, to help me to code a couple of things. If you can find me a tutorial it would be appreciated or you can just tell me how to code if you feel like writing. Please be respectful, I am not english :S.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-s">Ok, so the first thing that I would like to fix is the combat xp rate. Actually the rate is 4800xp so as you see, it is TOO much high. I wonder how can I slow it.</span></p>
<p><span class="bbcode-s">After, I wonder how I can enable drops. (actually, when I drop something it disepears.)</span></p>
<p>Third, when I shoot any arrows, bolts, or even cannon balls, it doesn’t use the projectiles. How can I make it use the projectiles ?</p>
<p>Fourth: I have the same problem with magic. When I cast a spell, it doesn’t use runes.</p>
<p>Finally, I wonder how I could add prayer curses. I know that I need sprites but what else? and how to add the effects, the gfx and everything ?</p>
<p>So thanks for replying.</p>
<p>~Jaimelatifa.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/need-help-to-fix-a-few-things-on-a-562-using-rs2hd/394147/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/need-help-to-fix-a-few-things-on-a-562-using-rs2hd/394147/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 07 May 2011 20:28:45 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-394147-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/need-help-to-fix-a-few-things-on-a-562-using-rs2hd/394147.rss">Need help to fix a few things on a 562 (using rs2hd)</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
