<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>TheLandofLegends is putting together a team</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/thelandoflegends-is-putting-together-a-team/541464</link>
    <description>[IMG]http://i43.tinypic.com/s3nj0z.png[/img]


I&#39;d like it to be supported by a competent team of developers. I previously worked pretty much alone on all of this with little help from other&#39;s. I devote 12-18 hour&#39;s  a day depending on what goes on that day. I do not sleep much 4-6 hour&#39;s a day when im awake i&#39;m doing thing&#39;s with the project. Through the week I have school where I am out of the house for 4 hour&#39;s but I still keep an eye on thing&#39;s from my Cell phone along with school computer&#39;s .

Server Manager:

I myself manage this  role , I am looking for someone who is qualified to be / CEO  / Sponser and to be able to take care of thing&#39;s when im not around.
Firstly this means somebody to look after the advertisement and  suggestions for development and also this would also include helping fund the server in terms of hosting and VPS, so expenses will be minimal, I&#39;ve put my all into this project so far, And now im looking for a few partner&#39;s to join me. So far ive put $200 of what I had into this project and I continue adding what ever I earn  everything I get goes into the server I take pride in my hard work an would like to continue. This project i&#39;ve spent many long day&#39;s an hour&#39;s working on. 
you will receive a 10%% share of the ownership and donations. And as the success of the server is largely down to your own success in advertisement, you essentially will be  making your own salary here. 

I will take 5% for myself an the other extra 5% will go toward&#39;s the server. I do this mainly for happiyness and enjoyment I have been in the rs community for 10 year&#39;s soon and I am 17 year&#39;s old. Rs has been apart of my life for a long time and im doing this for memorie&#39;s fun an enjoyment i&#39;ve been scaping it since my 8th Birthday 


Website Developer:

You&#39;ll be required to build a website for the server, forums, embedding webclient&#39;s, general website maintenance and additions and have a large role in server to website integration so programming knowledge will be necessary, mainly in databases, sql / php and some java. Not a comprehensive knowledge of PHP and Java is required. You will hold a 10% share of the servers income. I&#39;ve already done most but I am not a proffesional when it come&#39;s to webdesigning so far I&#39;ve done this much of the job. 

Landing Page: http://thelandoflegends.org/
Home: http://thelandoflegends.org/home/

Forums: http://thelandoflegends.org/TheLandofLegends

Webclient: http://www.thelandoflegends.org/webclient.html



Server Developers: (2 Spots to be filled)

You must know Java extensively, and have a relatively good understanding of how RSPS works. It would be beneficial if you had an understanding of any scripting languages, especially Ruby and/or Python as these languages may come into use later down the line of development. Of course content building and upgrading will be required and general debugging in the hosting stages. 10% of all income. Will be split between Developers.

Client Developer: Searching for multiple Client Developer&#39;s to help client developing move along quicker than one person working seperatly alone.

Again pretty much the same requirements as the server developers, you should also be able to effectively modify a Rsps client, edit maps, models, loading screens, creating interfaces. There could also be some communication with the website. You will have a 10% share of the income as well. Will be split between Client Developers


Work is done via dropbox, each developer is required an update log telling change&#39;s, update&#39;s and or work in progress to be finished later. Example shown below.

[IMG]http://i41.tinypic.com/i1k01v.png[/img]

All work is to be kept clean an noted to make thing&#39;s easier to find an be organized example //New Dharok&#39;s axe model

Developer&#39;s are not to argue with one another.

FORMAT:
Skype: Can send via pm if don&#39;t want this show to public
Years in RSPS development:
Must show previous work (include links along with proof):
Age:
Free time:
Desired position (server/client/or website/graphics designer goes under web Developer):

Please post only if you can agree to the terms above.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 23 Mar 2014 18:23:20 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Uncategorized</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/thelandoflegends-is-putting-together-a-team/541464.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>TheLandofLegends is putting together a team</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@TheLandofLegends TheLandofLegends]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/thelandoflegends">@TheLandofLegends</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p><img src="http://i43.tinypic.com/s3nj0z.png" alt width="" height=""></p>
<p>I’d like it to be supported by a competent team of developers. I previously worked pretty much alone on all of this with little help from other’s. I devote 12-18 hour’s  a day depending on what goes on that day. I do not sleep much 4-6 hour’s a day when im awake i’m doing thing’s with the project. Through the week I have school where I am out of the house for 4 hour’s but I still keep an eye on thing’s from my Cell phone along with school computer’s .</p>
<p>Server Manager:</p>
<p>I myself manage this  role , I am looking for someone who is qualified to be / CEO  / Sponser and to be able to take care of thing’s when im not around.<br>
Firstly this means somebody to look after the advertisement and  suggestions for development and also this would also include helping fund the server in terms of hosting and VPS, so expenses will be minimal, I’ve put my all into this project so far, And now im looking for a few partner’s to join me. So far ive put $200 of what I had into this project and I continue adding what ever I earn  everything I get goes into the server I take pride in my hard work an would like to continue. This project i’ve spent many long day’s an hour’s working on.<br>
you will receive a 10%% share of the ownership and donations. And as the success of the server is largely down to your own success in advertisement, you essentially will be  making your own salary here.</p>
<p>I will take 5% for myself an the other extra 5% will go toward’s the server. I do this mainly for happiyness and enjoyment I have been in the rs community for 10 year’s soon and I am 17 year’s old. Rs has been apart of my life for a long time and im doing this for memorie’s fun an enjoyment i’ve been scaping it since my 8th Birthday</p>
<p>Website Developer:</p>
<p>You’ll be required to build a website for the server, forums, embedding webclient’s, general website maintenance and additions and have a large role in server to website integration so programming knowledge will be necessary, mainly in databases, sql / php and some java. Not a comprehensive knowledge of PHP and Java is required. You will hold a 10% share of the servers income. I’ve already done most but I am not a proffesional when it come’s to webdesigning so far I’ve done this much of the job.</p>
<p>Landing Page: <a href="http://thelandoflegends.org/" rel="nofollow noopener">http://thelandoflegends.org/</a><br>
Home: <a href="http://thelandoflegends.org/home/" rel="nofollow noopener">http://thelandoflegends.org/home/</a></p>
<p>Forums: <a href="http://thelandoflegends.org/TheLandofLegends" rel="nofollow noopener">http://thelandoflegends.org/TheLandofLegends</a></p>
<p>Webclient: <a href="http://www.thelandoflegends.org/webclient.html" rel="nofollow noopener">http://www.thelandoflegends.org/webclient.html</a></p>
<p>Server Developers: (2 Spots to be filled)</p>
<p>You must know Java extensively, and have a relatively good understanding of how RSPS works. It would be beneficial if you had an understanding of any scripting languages, especially Ruby and/or Python as these languages may come into use later down the line of development. Of course content building and upgrading will be required and general debugging in the hosting stages. 10% of all income. Will be split between Developers.</p>
<p>Client Developer: Searching for multiple Client Developer’s to help client developing move along quicker than one person working seperatly alone.</p>
<p>Again pretty much the same requirements as the server developers, you should also be able to effectively modify a Rsps client, edit maps, models, loading screens, creating interfaces. There could also be some communication with the website. You will have a 10% share of the income as well. Will be split between Client Developers</p>
<p>Work is done via dropbox, each developer is required an update log telling change’s, update’s and or work in progress to be finished later. Example shown below.</p>
<p><img src="http://i41.tinypic.com/i1k01v.png" alt width="" height=""></p>
<p>All work is to be kept clean an noted to make thing’s easier to find an be organized example //New Dharok’s axe model</p>
<p>Developer’s are not to argue with one another.</p>
<p>FORMAT:<br>
Skype: Can send via pm if don’t want this show to public<br>
Years in RSPS development:<br>
Must show previous work (include links along with proof):<br>
Age:<br>
Free time:<br>
Desired position (server/client/or website/graphics designer goes under web Developer):</p>
<p>Please post only if you can agree to the terms above.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/thelandoflegends-is-putting-together-a-team/541464/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/thelandoflegends-is-putting-together-a-team/541464/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 23 Mar 2014 18:23:20 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-541464-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/thelandoflegends-is-putting-together-a-team/541464.rss">TheLandofLegends is putting together a team</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
