<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Mega Problem - - - Help if you can please. [at least look?]</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/mega-problem-help-if-you-can-please-at-least-look/163926</link>
    <description>[center]Yea , you read right, I am asking for [b]your[/b] help for once. lol. :D well I am in the process of making a new client since my old webclient won&#39;t work and nobody will accept 350k to make me one out of a very basic 317 client with no sprites or models... Forget that though, I am finished editing my new client which has all the new items / gameframe / 377 cache. And I made a jar out of it. Now the jar loads [i]perfectly[/i], it even gets to the login screen, but it will [b][u]never[/u][/b] log me in, no, never. And I have got the IP right, I have the port right, yes I am on Hamachi, wanna know how I know all this for a fact? It lets me login on my non-jarred client. When I open the &quot;run.bat&quot; batch file it lets me login with that one, the jar just wont work, I asked Rob and he said something about init voids?!?! I have no idea what they are. PLease please post telling me what to do. I am not asking for a whole tutorial , please just donate 2 minutes of your time to help me and TobiasScape get back online. There [u]WILL[/u] be a reward for the first two people to help me ...[/center]</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 11 Dec 2007 02:02:01 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/mega-problem-help-if-you-can-please-at-least-look/163926.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Mega Problem - - - Help if you can please. [at least look?]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@tobias222 tobias222]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/tobias222">@tobias222</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[center]Yea , you read right, I am asking for <span class="bbcode-b">your</span> help for once. lol. <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/smiley.png?v=6" title=":smiley:" class="emoji" alt=":smiley:"> well I am in the process of making a new client since my old webclient won’t work and nobody will accept 350k to make me one out of a very basic 317 client with no sprites or models… Forget that though, I am finished editing my new client which has all the new items / gameframe / 377 cache. And I made a jar out of it. Now the jar loads <span class="bbcode-i">perfectly</span>, it even gets to the login screen, but it will <span class="bbcode-b"><span class="bbcode-u">never</span></span> log me in, no, never. And I have got the IP right, I have the port right, yes I am on Hamachi, wanna know how I know all this for a fact? It lets me login on my non-jarred client. When I open the “run.bat” batch file it lets me login with that one, the jar just wont work, I asked Rob and he said something about init voids?!?! I have no idea what they are. PLease please post telling me what to do. I am not asking for a whole tutorial , please just donate 2 minutes of your time to help me and TobiasScape get back online. There <span class="bbcode-u">WILL</span> be a reward for the first two people to help me …[/center]</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/mega-problem-help-if-you-can-please-at-least-look/163926/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/mega-problem-help-if-you-can-please-at-least-look/163926/1</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 11 Dec 2007 02:02:01 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-163926-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/mega-problem-help-if-you-can-please-at-least-look/163926.rss">Mega Problem - - - Help if you can please. [at least look?]</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
