<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>*508* help needed *508*</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/508-help-needed-508/361663</link>
    <description>Ok so i need help doing a few thing and i thought that i would just put into one post.

1.) I need to know how to make NPC&#39;s aggressive, because i want the gods (bandos, armadyle, and zamorok) to auto attack you along with the minions.

2.) I have this kind of bug/glitch to where when people die on my server they won&#39;t lose their stuff and i was wondering if there was a way to change that.

3.) As you prolly already know i&#39;m using Berky-Scape as my base and i need to fix all the glitches that came with it. Like i can&#39;t trade with anyone and i need to know how to make the person stop gaining xp after the inv is full.

If you can help with any of these problems please reply or PM me i really need help.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 24 Sep 2010 16:56:03 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/508-help-needed-508/361663.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>*508* help needed *508*</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@R_A_R_E_S R A R E S]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/r_a_r_e_s">@R_A_R_E_S</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Ok so i need help doing a few thing and i thought that i would just put into one post.</p>
<p>1.) I need to know how to make NPC’s aggressive, because i want the gods (bandos, armadyle, and zamorok) to auto attack you along with the minions.</p>
<p>2.) I have this kind of bug/glitch to where when people die on my server they won’t lose their stuff and i was wondering if there was a way to change that.</p>
<p>3.) As you prolly already know i’m using Berky-Scape as my base and i need to fix all the glitches that came with it. Like i can’t trade with anyone and i need to know how to make the person stop gaining xp after the inv is full.</p>
<p>If you can help with any of these problems please reply or PM me i really need help.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/508-help-needed-508/361663/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/508-help-needed-508/361663/1</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 24 Sep 2010 16:56:03 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-361663-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/508-help-needed-508/361663.rss">*508* help needed *508*</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
