<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>HydraScape - It&#39;s Back! 317, No Customs, Full PK&#39;ing, Most Realistic Private Ser</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/hydrascape-its-back-317-no-customs-full-pking-most-realistic-private-ser/457220</link>
    <description>[center][url=http://www.hydra-scape.org][IMG]http://i49.tinypic.com/2qa0fh4.png[/img][/url]
[COLOR=&quot;#FF0000&quot;]Please Note[/COLOR]: This game requires that you sign up on the Forums before you are allowed access to the game, Sign up using the links below!
[url=http://hydra-scape.org/][img]http://i.imgur.com/hIVuX.png[/img]Click here for Forums![/url]
[url=http://hydra-scape.org/Hydrascape.zip][img]http://i380.photobucket.com/albums/oo245/zamorak_album_2008/webclient.png[/img]Click here to Play![/url]
[url=http://hydra-scape.org/highscore.php][img]http://i.imgur.com/KSIps.gif[/img]Click here for the Highscores![/url]

[SIZE=4][B]What is Hydrascape and what makes it different from any other Server?[/B][/SIZE]
Hydrascape is the most Realistic Runescape Private Server in history, It was once the biggest and Largest Private Server around with over 200 Players on at ALL times and maxing over 500+ players online at one time! It has been running for over 4 years and is now up and running and online and ready for you ALL to play!
Hydrascape features some of the most popular and unique minigames in the history of Runescape Private Servers. Hydrascape doesn’t just use any standard minigames that most servers can rip code from a source, they are all custom coded and UNIQUE to Hydrascape itself. It features “Battle” where you must defend yourself and others against the foul monsters that attack you, and more!

[SIZE=4][B]Take a quick look at this video to find out more about Hydrascape![/B][/SIZE]
[url=http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=1YiAp5Cy-_c&amp;feature=plcp]http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=1YiAp5Cy-_c&amp;feature=plcp[/url]

Hydrascape also features Fully Integrated vBulletin forums which means you must register on the Forums
before you can login to the game, this is required and the game will not allow you to login without doing so!

[B][SIZE=4]—Some of the Features!--[/SIZE][/B]


Integrated vBulletin Forums and Server for added Security!
Highscores integrated on the Forums for ease of Access!
New Training System!
Unique Minigames hand coded!
Fairly Slow XP Rate to keep the game entertaining and challenging!
Great and Fair PK’ing at popular locations!
Achievements to work towards and earn rewards for doing!
A truly awesome and supportive community to help you out whenever you need help!




Those are just some features of Hydrascape, It features many more minigames, events, 
Achievements and milestones to reach in-game and get rewards for doing so!

[SIZE=4][B]Check out these unique achievements you can work towards in-game whilst you are playing![/B][/SIZE]

[img]http://gyazo.com/6d31565234a1a118965336ec81f41d6c.png[/img]
This is just a few of the achievements you can complete in the game, There are always more that can be added and more to achieve, The Server is updated daily to add more features, So feel free to request new achievements if you have any to share!

[img]http://gyazo.com/6e40daaa17ecde2aa22bf0ebf971afce.png?1346175713[/img] 
When you complete an Achievement, The game will send you a message directly to your chatbox telling you have finished and completed the achievement so you do not have to keep checking back at your Achievements tab! When you complete an Achievement, You can withdraw your coins you have been rewarded with the withdraw command “/withdraw”!

[img]http://gyazo.com/64f7e1adc7af4f032f0b745c60b57380.png?1346173050[/img] 
This is one of the longest achievements in the game, It takes a fair while to complete and you are rewarded well for doing so, It also shows how you can look up how far you are through the achievement if you just can’t wait to finish it!

[B]There are so many awesome unique features in hydrascape it is hard to show them all in one advertisement, so why not come and check it out and see all the features for yourself? [url=http://www.hydra-scape.org]Click Here![/url][/B]

Hydrascape also features a new training system, where you must work up through the ranks to slay different types of monsters that drop good items such as the Dark Bow or the more famous Dragon Full Helm. You can track how far you are through the new training system with the simple click of a button to access the Kill Diary!

[img]http://gyazo.com/37e3ea98e5b3515a82bbe7f1afae33c0.png[/img]
This is the Kill Diary in which you can check which monsters you must slay after you have completed the tasks, as you move up through the Training System Ranks you can slay bigger and stronger monsters, but you are rewarded greatly for doing so as they drop some awesome items and weaponary. When completing a Task, You are rewarded with coins, which can inspire you to progress even more!

[img]http://gyazo.com/ca5130e708f37e973e601f56a6bb1c59.png?1346236061[/img]
You must slay your way through the new progressive training system in order to slay the bigger monsters! Start off at the Alkharid Guards, and Finish off at Chaos Elementals, The strongest creature in the Training System!

[img]http://gyazo.com/60083a18850f65c5911358174a890a6c.png?1346176902[/img]

The client is also massively edited to make your viewing and playing experience more entertaining and fun! Check out the Customised Quest Tab as an example! The old Quest Tab has been completely ripped out of the game, and been replaced with this awesome more user friendly Quest Tab which is now used to navigate your way around the game and get help on how to play the game if you are stuck!

[img]http://gyazo.com/94a0619a64f76557d1a7eabc749889b6.png[/img]

[B]As you can see there are just so many awesome features included in Hydrascape I can’t really show you all of them, Just go ahead and check out the server for yourself by [url=http://www.hydra-scape.org]clicking here[/url][/B]

[B][SIZE=4]Hydrascape is not your standard Runescape Private Server[/SIZE][/B]
It is the Most Realistic on the market and nothing can change that. It uses the old 474 revision Graphics which is what I’m guessing made you move from Runescape to Private Servers when they updated the Graphics, so I know for sure you will LOVE hydrascape and what it has to offer.

[img]http://gyazo.com/2726408933c75f3a872f51573ab42959.png?1346233478[/img]

[B][SIZE=4]-Mini Games-[/SIZE][/B]

As I stated before there are many minigames in hydra-scape, I will go through and show you them all, they are all unique to hydrascape and have been 100% coded from hand and a lot of time and effort has been taken to create them and make your playing experience more fun!

[SIZE=4][B]-Last Man Standing-[/B][/SIZE]

This is the Last Man Standing minigame, It is situated in the Duel Arena and is a Free For All, Every man for himself minigame, You are awarded points for winning, runner up and third place. These points are stored and can be used to buy multiple items in the Minigame Store! An Image of this store can be found below!

[img]http://gyazo.com/b5e92d9c99b9b4c5f766b486390af25d.png?1346175557[/img]

[img]http://gyazo.com/06fd5c74dc1fd020d86590d05d62c7fe.png?1346175591[/img]

[B][SIZE=4]-Battle-[/SIZE][/B]

Now this is the first minigame introduced into Hydrascape almost 3 years ago! It is called Battle which I touched up on earlier on in the advertisement, You must defend both you, and your team mates against the foul beasts that come before you and attempt to complete the 8 waves, The waves get harder as you go through them starting off at Wave 1, with Golems and Zombies, and ending with Wave 8 against 4 King Black Dragons! Check out some images of us playing it!

[img]http://gyazo.com/6ab644146fc1993e6c6afe705d644295.png?1346175844[/img]

[img]http://gyazo.com/4f47bc581fcfd113664cc2a058a84592.png?1346176376[/img]


[B][SIZE=4]-Flag Wars-[/SIZE][/B]

There is a third Minigame that is currently still being tested that is very similar to capture the flag, you must capture the flag and hold onto the flag for as long as you can, It is a team based minigame with 2 teams all fighting for the 1 flag that separates the winners, from the losers! It is a very fast and quick paced minigame, So if you enjoy playing things quickly with no waiting, This is the minigame for you! Images will be posted when the minigame is released!

As you can see there are just so many awesome features included in Hydrascape I can’t really show you all of them, Just go ahead and check out the server for yourself by [url=http://www.hydra-scape.org]clicking here[/url]

[B][SIZE=4]-PK&#39;ing-[/SIZE][/B]

Hydrascape also features flawless PK’ing! As for most Private Servers, The main PK’ing spot is at Mage Bank, so we figured we would give you an ease of access teleport by using our custom PK’ing Tab which features 2 teleports to the most popular PK’ing Locations and ease of access to the PK’ing shops.

[img]http://gyazo.com/d71e60fc861da519d703473c5b4c5468.png?1346177152[/img]

When PK’ing you gain points for each kill, Each kill also gives you a Multiplier Bonus, So for every kill after the previous kill, you gain bonus points! Confusing but it is a very helpful and useful system. 

The points are also split up, There are separate points for different PK Locations and also Separate PK Point Shops, As an example, Mage Bank is a Non-Multi PK Location, so each kill gains you Non-Multi PK Points, Varrock is a Multi PK Location and therefore you gain Multi PK Points. Check out some of the items you can gain by using your PK Points, They all vary in the amount of points they cost but are game changing items for PK’ing!

[B]Non-Multi PK Store[/B]

[img]http://gyazo.com/5247117562e2981c69c2569cbef40e79.png?1346177740[/img]

[B]Multi PK Store[/B]

[img]http://gyazo.com/a83ee651af4278844ff595f00c13ab8b.png?1346177756[/img]

[B][SIZE=4]Check out some PK&#39;ing videos from fellow users in the community![/SIZE][/B]

[url=http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=S9V_6635tQc]http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=S9V_6635tQc[/url]
[url=http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=NlUqQy-iCwM]http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=NlUqQy-iCwM[/url]

[B]There are so many awesome unique features in hydrascape it is hard to show them all in one advertisement, so why not come and check it out and see all the features for yourself? [url=http://www.hydra-scape.org]Click Here![/url][/B]

[B][SIZE=4]-Skilling-[/SIZE][/B]

There are 19 perfect skills in Hydrascape that work flawlessly and that you can train!
Check out just some of the skills that work perfectly and flawlessly, there is not any easy way to go about levelling them, such as having a “Skilling Island” it is similar to Runescape where you must manually walk or teleport to the different places to skill! Images below for you to look at!
Perfect Animations and Skill Leveling!

[SIZE=4][B]-Woodcutting-[/B][/SIZE]

[img]http://gyazo.com/27f3993cc359338683bd4e34fa7fdc98.png?1346180525[/img]
The woodcutting works perfectly! You can chop down trees just as you would in Runescape, but with a faster XP Rate, It makes the skill a bit more bearable and fun without being too easy and boring!

[B][SIZE=4]-Fletching-[/SIZE][/B]

[img]http://gyazo.com/a6d89b98851f742923779cca6463f8b2.png?1346180685[/img]
Fletching also works flawlessly, You can fletch just how you would in any other Private Server, but with added options! You can fletch all the way up to magic bows and you can also string your own bows and prepare your own arrows for the battle of your life! But Fletching is not the only way you Rangers can attack monsters, There are plenty of shops scattered around the world of Hydrascape offering you arrows for a fair amount of coins!

[B][SIZE=4]-Fishing-[/SIZE][/B]

[img]http://gyazo.com/1501af4b66459f3bf09055c8e04a67a0.png?1346181631[/img]
Fishing is a great skill and a highly useful skill in Hydrascape, You can create mass amounts of money from fishing as the PK&#39;ers must use Fish and Food to PK with, You can also use it yourself and progress your way through the many Levels in Hydrascape to fish bigger and better fish that heal more health, From Shrimps to Sharks there will always be and need people who have mastered the fishing skill, so don&#39;t miss your chance to make millions in Hydrascape!

[B][SIZE=4]-Thieving-[/SIZE][/B]

[img]http://gyazo.com/f9ce8589daea12e4e4f5cb8dbf22df41.png?1346264377[/img]
On Hydrascape, We try to make the economy as good as we can, and as fair as we can and with that comes thieving, We didn&#39;t want to be like every other single server and give coins when they thieve, So players can sit their and auto click for 24 hours and be a billionaire, We decided it would work out best if items were given, that can be used to level up Crafting, use as food and more, or you could simply trade the items for a fair amount of coins, which won&#39;t ruin the economy!

[B][SIZE=4]-Mining-[/SIZE][/B]

[img]http://gyazo.com/acea9d8361a8937b35211ea5244e0174.png?1346265039[/img]
The Mining also works perfectly, There are multiple ores that you can mine, from Copper or Tin, to Rune for Donators, We even offer everyone the chance to mine Rune Essence, which is brilliant xp and the fastest xp you can get when you are a slow level, We have designated locations for players to mine with hundreds of ores, so you never have to wait for one to respawn!

Those are just some of the features, there are so many more! So come along and [url=http://www.hydra-scape.org]join Hydrascape today![/url] Links to the forums to play where you must sign up first are located near the top of the page!
See you on [url=http://www.hydra-scape.org]Hydrascape![/url][/center]</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 03 Sep 2012 01:58:13 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/hydrascape-its-back-317-no-customs-full-pking-most-realistic-private-ser/457220.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>HydraScape - It&#39;s Back! 317, No Customs, Full PK&#39;ing, Most Realistic Private Ser</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@777slots2 777slots2]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/777slots2">@777slots2</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Seems legit. I think the whole Iraq thing is funny af, dgaf if it’s racist.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/hydrascape-its-back-317-no-customs-full-pking-most-realistic-private-ser/457220/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/hydrascape-its-back-317-no-customs-full-pking-most-realistic-private-ser/457220/4</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 03 Sep 2012 01:58:13 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-457220-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/hydrascape-its-back-317-no-customs-full-pking-most-realistic-private-ser/457220.rss">HydraScape - It&#39;s Back! 317, No Customs, Full PK&#39;ing, Most Realistic Private Ser</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>HydraScape - It&#39;s Back! 317, No Customs, Full PK&#39;ing, Most Realistic Private Ser</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@tisko1 tisko1]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/tisko1">@tisko1</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Yeah don’t join cause they are racist</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/hydrascape-its-back-317-no-customs-full-pking-most-realistic-private-ser/457220/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/hydrascape-its-back-317-no-customs-full-pking-most-realistic-private-ser/457220/3</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 02 Sep 2012 15:08:05 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-457220-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/hydrascape-its-back-317-no-customs-full-pking-most-realistic-private-ser/457220.rss">HydraScape - It&#39;s Back! 317, No Customs, Full PK&#39;ing, Most Realistic Private Ser</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>HydraScape - It&#39;s Back! 317, No Customs, Full PK&#39;ing, Most Realistic Private Ser</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@rooneyscape rooneyscape]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/rooneyscape">@rooneyscape</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Was playing this till i saw this.</p>
<p><img src="http://puu.sh/11hTR" alt width="" height=""></p>
<p>Was playing when i saw this then just logged off.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/hydrascape-its-back-317-no-customs-full-pking-most-realistic-private-ser/457220/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/hydrascape-its-back-317-no-customs-full-pking-most-realistic-private-ser/457220/2</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 02 Sep 2012 11:43:54 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-457220-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/hydrascape-its-back-317-no-customs-full-pking-most-realistic-private-ser/457220.rss">HydraScape - It&#39;s Back! 317, No Customs, Full PK&#39;ing, Most Realistic Private Ser</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>HydraScape - It&#39;s Back! 317, No Customs, Full PK&#39;ing, Most Realistic Private Ser</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@jjbond123 jjbond123]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/jjbond123">@jjbond123</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[center]<a href="http://www.hydra-scape.org" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener"><img src="http://i49.tinypic.com/2qa0fh4.png" alt width="621" height="297"></a><br>
[COLOR="<span class="hashtag">#FF0000</span>"]Please Note[/COLOR]: This game requires that you sign up on the Forums before you are allowed access to the game, Sign up using the links below!<br>
<a href="http://hydra-scape.org/" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener"><img src="http://i.imgur.com/hIVuX.png" alt width="16" height="16">Click here for Forums!</a><br>
<a href="http://hydra-scape.org/Hydrascape.zip" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener"><img src="http://i380.photobucket.com/albums/oo245/zamorak_album_2008/webclient.png" alt width="16" height="16">Click here to Play!</a><br>
<a href="http://hydra-scape.org/highscore.php" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener"><img src="http://i.imgur.com/KSIps.gif" alt width="16" height="16">Click here for the Highscores!</a></p>
<p>[SIZE=4]<span class="bbcode-b">What is Hydrascape and what makes it different from any other Server?</span>[/SIZE]<br>
Hydrascape is the most Realistic Runescape Private Server in history, It was once the biggest and Largest Private Server around with over 200 Players on at ALL times and maxing over 500+ players online at one time! It has been running for over 4 years and is now up and running and online and ready for you ALL to play!<br>
Hydrascape features some of the most popular and unique minigames in the history of Runescape Private Servers. Hydrascape doesn’t just use any standard minigames that most servers can rip code from a source, they are all custom coded and UNIQUE to Hydrascape itself. It features “Battle” where you must defend yourself and others against the foul monsters that attack you, and more!</p>
<p>[SIZE=4]<span class="bbcode-b">Take a quick look at this video to find out more about Hydrascape!</span>[/SIZE]<br>
<a href="http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=1YiAp5Cy-_c&amp;feature=plcp" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=1YiAp5Cy-_c&amp;feature=plcp</a></p>
<p>Hydrascape also features Fully Integrated vBulletin forums which means you must register on the Forums<br>
before you can login to the game, this is required and the game will not allow you to login without doing so!</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">[SIZE=4]—Some of the Features!–[/SIZE]</span></p>
<p>Integrated vBulletin Forums and Server for added Security!<br>
Highscores integrated on the Forums for ease of Access!<br>
New Training System!<br>
Unique Minigames hand coded!<br>
Fairly Slow XP Rate to keep the game entertaining and challenging!<br>
Great and Fair PK’ing at popular locations!<br>
Achievements to work towards and earn rewards for doing!<br>
A truly awesome and supportive community to help you out whenever you need help!</p>
<p>Those are just some features of Hydrascape, It features many more minigames, events,<br>
Achievements and milestones to reach in-game and get rewards for doing so!</p>
<p>[SIZE=4]<span class="bbcode-b">Check out these unique achievements you can work towards in-game whilst you are playing!</span>[/SIZE]</p>
<p><img src="http://gyazo.com/6d31565234a1a118965336ec81f41d6c.png" alt width="242" height="333"><br>
This is just a few of the achievements you can complete in the game, There are always more that can be added and more to achieve, The Server is updated daily to add more features, So feel free to request new achievements if you have any to share!</p>
<p><img src="http://gyazo.com/6e40daaa17ecde2aa22bf0ebf971afce.png?1346175713" alt width="506" height="128"><br>
When you complete an Achievement, The game will send you a message directly to your chatbox telling you have finished and completed the achievement so you do not have to keep checking back at your Achievements tab! When you complete an Achievement, You can withdraw your coins you have been rewarded with the withdraw command “/withdraw”!</p>
<p><img src="http://gyazo.com/64f7e1adc7af4f032f0b745c60b57380.png?1346173050" alt width="511" height="332"><br>
This is one of the longest achievements in the game, It takes a fair while to complete and you are rewarded well for doing so, It also shows how you can look up how far you are through the achievement if you just can’t wait to finish it!</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">There are so many awesome unique features in hydrascape it is hard to show them all in one advertisement, so why not come and check it out and see all the features for yourself? <a href="http://www.hydra-scape.org" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">Click Here!</a></span></p>
<p>Hydrascape also features a new training system, where you must work up through the ranks to slay different types of monsters that drop good items such as the Dark Bow or the more famous Dragon Full Helm. You can track how far you are through the new training system with the simple click of a button to access the Kill Diary!</p>
<p><img src="http://gyazo.com/37e3ea98e5b3515a82bbe7f1afae33c0.png" alt width="511" height="334"><br>
This is the Kill Diary in which you can check which monsters you must slay after you have completed the tasks, as you move up through the Training System Ranks you can slay bigger and stronger monsters, but you are rewarded greatly for doing so as they drop some awesome items and weaponary. When completing a Task, You are rewarded with coins, which can inspire you to progress even more!</p>
<p><img src="http://gyazo.com/ca5130e708f37e973e601f56a6bb1c59.png?1346236061" alt width="" height=""><br>
You must slay your way through the new progressive training system in order to slay the bigger monsters! Start off at the Alkharid Guards, and Finish off at Chaos Elementals, The strongest creature in the Training System!</p>
<p><img src="http://gyazo.com/60083a18850f65c5911358174a890a6c.png?1346176902" alt width="505" height="128"></p>
<p>The client is also massively edited to make your viewing and playing experience more entertaining and fun! Check out the Customised Quest Tab as an example! The old Quest Tab has been completely ripped out of the game, and been replaced with this awesome more user friendly Quest Tab which is now used to navigate your way around the game and get help on how to play the game if you are stuck!</p>
<p><img src="http://gyazo.com/94a0619a64f76557d1a7eabc749889b6.png" alt width="237" height="337"></p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">As you can see there are just so many awesome features included in Hydrascape I can’t really show you all of them, Just go ahead and check out the server for yourself by <a href="http://www.hydra-scape.org" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">clicking here</a></span></p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">[SIZE=4]Hydrascape is not your standard Runescape Private Server[/SIZE]</span><br>
It is the Most Realistic on the market and nothing can change that. It uses the old 474 revision Graphics which is what I’m guessing made you move from Runescape to Private Servers when they updated the Graphics, so I know for sure you will LOVE hydrascape and what it has to offer.</p>
<p><div class="lightbox-wrapper"><a class="lightbox" href="http://gyazo.com/2726408933c75f3a872f51573ab42959.png?1346233478" title="2726408933c75f3a872f51573ab42959.png?1346233478" rel="nofollow noopener"><img src="http://gyazo.com/2726408933c75f3a872f51573ab42959.png?1346233478" alt width="690" height="454"><div class="meta">
<svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-far-image svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#far-image"></use></svg><span class="filename">2726408933c75f3a872f51573ab42959.png?1346233478</span><span class="informations">760×501</span><svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-discourse-expand svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#discourse-expand"></use></svg>
</div></a></div></p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">[SIZE=4]-Mini Games-[/SIZE]</span></p>
<p>As I stated before there are many minigames in hydra-scape, I will go through and show you them all, they are all unique to hydrascape and have been 100% coded from hand and a lot of time and effort has been taken to create them and make your playing experience more fun!</p>
<p>[SIZE=4]<span class="bbcode-b">-Last Man Standing-</span>[/SIZE]</p>
<p>This is the Last Man Standing minigame, It is situated in the Duel Arena and is a Free For All, Every man for himself minigame, You are awarded points for winning, runner up and third place. These points are stored and can be used to buy multiple items in the Minigame Store! An Image of this store can be found below!</p>
<p><div class="lightbox-wrapper"><a class="lightbox" href="http://gyazo.com/b5e92d9c99b9b4c5f766b486390af25d.png?1346175557" title="b5e92d9c99b9b4c5f766b486390af25d.png?1346175557" rel="nofollow noopener"><img src="http://gyazo.com/b5e92d9c99b9b4c5f766b486390af25d.png?1346175557" alt width="690" height="456"><div class="meta">
<svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-far-image svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#far-image"></use></svg><span class="filename">b5e92d9c99b9b4c5f766b486390af25d.png?1346175557</span><span class="informations">765×506</span><svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-discourse-expand svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#discourse-expand"></use></svg>
</div></a></div></p>
<p><div class="lightbox-wrapper"><a class="lightbox" href="http://gyazo.com/06fd5c74dc1fd020d86590d05d62c7fe.png?1346175591" title="06fd5c74dc1fd020d86590d05d62c7fe.png?1346175591" rel="nofollow noopener"><img src="http://gyazo.com/06fd5c74dc1fd020d86590d05d62c7fe.png?1346175591" alt width="690" height="457"><div class="meta">
<svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-far-image svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#far-image"></use></svg><span class="filename">06fd5c74dc1fd020d86590d05d62c7fe.png?1346175591</span><span class="informations">764×507</span><svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-discourse-expand svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#discourse-expand"></use></svg>
</div></a></div></p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">[SIZE=4]-Battle-[/SIZE]</span></p>
<p>Now this is the first minigame introduced into Hydrascape almost 3 years ago! It is called Battle which I touched up on earlier on in the advertisement, You must defend both you, and your team mates against the foul beasts that come before you and attempt to complete the 8 waves, The waves get harder as you go through them starting off at Wave 1, with Golems and Zombies, and ending with Wave 8 against 4 King Black Dragons! Check out some images of us playing it!</p>
<p><div class="lightbox-wrapper"><a class="lightbox" href="http://gyazo.com/6ab644146fc1993e6c6afe705d644295.png?1346175844" title="6ab644146fc1993e6c6afe705d644295.png?1346175844" rel="nofollow noopener"><img src="http://gyazo.com/6ab644146fc1993e6c6afe705d644295.png?1346175844" alt width="690" height="453"><div class="meta">
<svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-far-image svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#far-image"></use></svg><span class="filename">6ab644146fc1993e6c6afe705d644295.png?1346175844</span><span class="informations">767×504</span><svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-discourse-expand svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#discourse-expand"></use></svg>
</div></a></div></p>
<p><div class="lightbox-wrapper"><a class="lightbox" href="http://gyazo.com/4f47bc581fcfd113664cc2a058a84592.png?1346176376" title="4f47bc581fcfd113664cc2a058a84592.png?1346176376" rel="nofollow noopener"><img src="http://gyazo.com/4f47bc581fcfd113664cc2a058a84592.png?1346176376" alt width="690" height="453"><div class="meta">
<svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-far-image svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#far-image"></use></svg><span class="filename">4f47bc581fcfd113664cc2a058a84592.png?1346176376</span><span class="informations">764×502</span><svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-discourse-expand svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#discourse-expand"></use></svg>
</div></a></div></p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">[SIZE=4]-Flag Wars-[/SIZE]</span></p>
<p>There is a third Minigame that is currently still being tested that is very similar to capture the flag, you must capture the flag and hold onto the flag for as long as you can, It is a team based minigame with 2 teams all fighting for the 1 flag that separates the winners, from the losers! It is a very fast and quick paced minigame, So if you enjoy playing things quickly with no waiting, This is the minigame for you! Images will be posted when the minigame is released!</p>
<p>As you can see there are just so many awesome features included in Hydrascape I can’t really show you all of them, Just go ahead and check out the server for yourself by <a href="http://www.hydra-scape.org" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">clicking here</a></p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">[SIZE=4]-PK’ing-[/SIZE]</span></p>
<p>Hydrascape also features flawless PK’ing! As for most Private Servers, The main PK’ing spot is at Mage Bank, so we figured we would give you an ease of access teleport by using our custom PK’ing Tab which features 2 teleports to the most popular PK’ing Locations and ease of access to the PK’ing shops.</p>
<p><img src="http://gyazo.com/d71e60fc861da519d703473c5b4c5468.png?1346177152" alt width="240" height="335"></p>
<p>When PK’ing you gain points for each kill, Each kill also gives you a Multiplier Bonus, So for every kill after the previous kill, you gain bonus points! Confusing but it is a very helpful and useful system.</p>
<p>The points are also split up, There are separate points for different PK Locations and also Separate PK Point Shops, As an example, Mage Bank is a Non-Multi PK Location, so each kill gains you Non-Multi PK Points, Varrock is a Multi PK Location and therefore you gain Multi PK Points. Check out some of the items you can gain by using your PK Points, They all vary in the amount of points they cost but are game changing items for PK’ing!</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Non-Multi PK Store</span></p>
<p><img src="http://gyazo.com/5247117562e2981c69c2569cbef40e79.png?1346177740" alt width="507" height="332"></p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Multi PK Store</span></p>
<p><img src="http://gyazo.com/a83ee651af4278844ff595f00c13ab8b.png?1346177756" alt width="505" height="329"></p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">[SIZE=4]Check out some PK’ing videos from fellow users in the community![/SIZE]</span></p>
<p><a href="http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=S9V_6635tQc" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=S9V_6635tQc</a><br>
<a href="http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=NlUqQy-iCwM" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=NlUqQy-iCwM</a></p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">There are so many awesome unique features in hydrascape it is hard to show them all in one advertisement, so why not come and check it out and see all the features for yourself? <a href="http://www.hydra-scape.org" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">Click Here!</a></span></p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">[SIZE=4]-Skilling-[/SIZE]</span></p>
<p>There are 19 perfect skills in Hydrascape that work flawlessly and that you can train!<br>
Check out just some of the skills that work perfectly and flawlessly, there is not any easy way to go about levelling them, such as having a “Skilling Island” it is similar to Runescape where you must manually walk or teleport to the different places to skill! Images below for you to look at!<br>
Perfect Animations and Skill Leveling!</p>
<p>[SIZE=4]<span class="bbcode-b">-Woodcutting-</span>[/SIZE]</p>
<p><img src="http://gyazo.com/27f3993cc359338683bd4e34fa7fdc98.png?1346180525" alt width="" height=""><br>
The woodcutting works perfectly! You can chop down trees just as you would in Runescape, but with a faster XP Rate, It makes the skill a bit more bearable and fun without being too easy and boring!</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">[SIZE=4]-Fletching-[/SIZE]</span></p>
<p><img src="http://gyazo.com/a6d89b98851f742923779cca6463f8b2.png?1346180685" alt width="" height=""><br>
Fletching also works flawlessly, You can fletch just how you would in any other Private Server, but with added options! You can fletch all the way up to magic bows and you can also string your own bows and prepare your own arrows for the battle of your life! But Fletching is not the only way you Rangers can attack monsters, There are plenty of shops scattered around the world of Hydrascape offering you arrows for a fair amount of coins!</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">[SIZE=4]-Fishing-[/SIZE]</span></p>
<p><img src="http://gyazo.com/1501af4b66459f3bf09055c8e04a67a0.png?1346181631" alt width="" height=""><br>
Fishing is a great skill and a highly useful skill in Hydrascape, You can create mass amounts of money from fishing as the PK’ers must use Fish and Food to PK with, You can also use it yourself and progress your way through the many Levels in Hydrascape to fish bigger and better fish that heal more health, From Shrimps to Sharks there will always be and need people who have mastered the fishing skill, so don’t miss your chance to make millions in Hydrascape!</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">[SIZE=4]-Thieving-[/SIZE]</span></p>
<p><div class="lightbox-wrapper"><a class="lightbox" href="http://gyazo.com/f9ce8589daea12e4e4f5cb8dbf22df41.png?1346264377" title="f9ce8589daea12e4e4f5cb8dbf22df41.png?1346264377" rel="nofollow noopener"><img src="http://gyazo.com/f9ce8589daea12e4e4f5cb8dbf22df41.png?1346264377" alt width="690" height="453"><div class="meta">
<svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-far-image svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#far-image"></use></svg><span class="filename">f9ce8589daea12e4e4f5cb8dbf22df41.png?1346264377</span><span class="informations">766×504</span><svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-discourse-expand svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#discourse-expand"></use></svg>
</div></a></div><br>
On Hydrascape, We try to make the economy as good as we can, and as fair as we can and with that comes thieving, We didn’t want to be like every other single server and give coins when they thieve, So players can sit their and auto click for 24 hours and be a billionaire, We decided it would work out best if items were given, that can be used to level up Crafting, use as food and more, or you could simply trade the items for a fair amount of coins, which won’t ruin the economy!</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">[SIZE=4]-Mining-[/SIZE]</span></p>
<p><img src="http://gyazo.com/acea9d8361a8937b35211ea5244e0174.png?1346265039" alt width="" height=""><br>
The Mining also works perfectly, There are multiple ores that you can mine, from Copper or Tin, to Rune for Donators, We even offer everyone the chance to mine Rune Essence, which is brilliant xp and the fastest xp you can get when you are a slow level, We have designated locations for players to mine with hundreds of ores, so you never have to wait for one to respawn!</p>
<p>Those are just some of the features, there are so many more! So come along and <a href="http://www.hydra-scape.org" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">join Hydrascape today!</a> Links to the forums to play where you must sign up first are located near the top of the page!<br>
See you on <a href="http://www.hydra-scape.org" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">Hydrascape!</a>[/center]</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/hydrascape-its-back-317-no-customs-full-pking-most-realistic-private-ser/457220/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/hydrascape-its-back-317-no-customs-full-pking-most-realistic-private-ser/457220/1</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 29 Aug 2012 23:27:10 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-457220-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/hydrascape-its-back-317-no-customs-full-pking-most-realistic-private-ser/457220.rss">HydraScape - It&#39;s Back! 317, No Customs, Full PK&#39;ing, Most Realistic Private Ser</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
