<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Habbo Retros</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/habbo-retros/134104</link>
    <description>I&#39;ve been playing habbo for about a year. I&#39;ve gotten bored because you cant get coins by earning. You have to pay for them with real money. And im jack broke. So i look for Habbo severs found a few but they were&#39;nt up to date. So I looked for a tutorial but didn&#39;t find any useful ones. So I decided i&#39;d make one. 


Downloads Needed: WinRAR, Hamachi, Server files

Knowledge: Typing, [url=http://www.moparisthebest.org/smf/index.php/topic,185458.0.html]http://www.moparisthebest.org/smf/index.php/topic,185458.0.html[/url], Reading

Difficulty: 1/10

Download WinRAR where ever you can find it, (it&#39;s all over this site)

Download Hamachi at [url=http://hamachi.cc]hamachi.cc[/url]

Download your server files by searching Debbo Project then find one you like and there ya go.

First things first find your server files extract them to any folder you wont forget. Go to you file and open &quot;HTML Loader&quot; or any file like that in WordPad. Search for 127.0.0.1 now open your Hamachi blackbox and replace 127.0.0.1 with what the big numbers on the top are. Make a network by clicking on the triangle in the corner, and click &quot;Create New Network&quot; and fill in the boxes (The name of it should be the name of hotel). You can edit it pretty easily its noob friendly.

Editing: Editing to make your server the best. Make your account admin open your server and make an account first. Then open your file under habbos and click your name and open the... um it has to do with your 
status oh well open it and delete &quot;habbos&quot; and put &quot;admin&quot; and save and your now Admin.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 31 Aug 2007 21:34:12 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Games</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/habbo-retros/134104.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Habbo Retros</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@maru maru]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/maru">@maru</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>What rules is he breaking?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/habbo-retros/134104/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/habbo-retros/134104/3</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 31 Aug 2007 21:34:12 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-134104-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/habbo-retros/134104.rss">Habbo Retros</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Habbo Retros</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@exe626 exe626]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/exe626">@exe626</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Go back to <a href="http://moparisthebest.com/smf" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">Moparscape</a>. Don’t forget to read the <a href="http://moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php/topic,3.0.html" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">Rules</a>.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/habbo-retros/134104/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/habbo-retros/134104/2</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 16 Aug 2007 17:48:07 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-134104-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/habbo-retros/134104.rss">Habbo Retros</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Habbo Retros</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Drew_Scape Drew_Scape]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/drew_scape">@Drew_Scape</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I’ve been playing habbo for about a year. I’ve gotten bored because you cant get coins by earning. You have to pay for them with real money. And im jack broke. So i look for Habbo severs found a few but they were’nt up to date. So I looked for a tutorial but didn’t find any useful ones. So I decided i’d make one.</p>
<p>Downloads Needed: WinRAR, Hamachi, Server files</p>
<p>Knowledge: Typing, <a href="http://www.moparisthebest.org/smf/index.php/topic,185458.0.html" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">http://www.moparisthebest.org/smf/index.php/topic,185458.0.html</a>, Reading</p>
<p>Difficulty: 1/10</p>
<p>Download WinRAR where ever you can find it, (it’s all over this site)</p>
<p>Download Hamachi at <a href="http://hamachi.cc" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">hamachi.cc</a></p>
<p>Download your server files by searching Debbo Project then find one you like and there ya go.</p>
<p>First things first find your server files extract them to any folder you wont forget. Go to you file and open “HTML Loader” or any file like that in WordPad. Search for 127.0.0.1 now open your Hamachi blackbox and replace 127.0.0.1 with what the big numbers on the top are. Make a network by clicking on the triangle in the corner, and click “Create New Network” and fill in the boxes (The name of it should be the name of hotel). You can edit it pretty easily its noob friendly.</p>
<p>Editing: Editing to make your server the best. Make your account admin open your server and make an account first. Then open your file under habbos and click your name and open the… um it has to do with your<br>
status oh well open it and delete “habbos” and put “admin” and save and your now Admin.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/habbo-retros/134104/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/habbo-retros/134104/1</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 16 Aug 2007 14:26:37 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-134104-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/habbo-retros/134104.rss">Habbo Retros</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
