<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Phot</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/phot/275967</link>
    <description>This isn&#39;t really web design, but its PHP so what the heck.[size=10pt][/size]

&#39;Phot&#39; (PHP-bot) is and IRC bot I have spent the last few days building, after speaking with some friends I decided to release it and stick it as a project on sourceforge.

Command-wise the bot doesn&#39;t do much, but the functional capabilities of the bot are endless.
As it stands now the functions that have been made especially for the bot make it possible to parse any piece of data coming from the IRC socket easily. 

Here is the sourceforge project:

[url=http://sourceforge.net/projects/phot/]http://sourceforge.net/projects/phot/[/url]

If you have any questions, or you would like to contact me to speak about a partnership, send an email to [email]admin@phot-irc.co.uk[/email] and I will get back to you as soon as I can.

Phot is protected by the GPL and legal action will be taken against those deciding not to follow the license.


EDIT: The &quot;README&quot; file should be looked over before doing anything related with the bot, it contains a list of functions that the bot has, all the commands that come with the bot and a description on what it is/how to run it.

[size=20pt]THIS IS NOT DESIGNED TO BE A WEB PAGE IT IS FOR COMMAND LINE ONLY[/size]</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 27 Apr 2009 20:05:24 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>General Programming</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/phot/275967.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Phot</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@eczema3 eczema3]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/eczema3">@eczema3</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>This isn’t really web design, but its PHP so what the heck.[size=10pt][/size]</p>
<p>‘Phot’ (PHP-bot) is and IRC bot I have spent the last few days building, after speaking with some friends I decided to release it and stick it as a project on sourceforge.</p>
<p>Command-wise the bot doesn’t do much, but the functional capabilities of the bot are endless.<br>
As it stands now the functions that have been made especially for the bot make it possible to parse any piece of data coming from the IRC socket easily.</p>
<p>Here is the sourceforge project:</p>
<p><a href="http://sourceforge.net/projects/phot/" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">http://sourceforge.net/projects/phot/</a></p>
<p>If you have any questions, or you would like to contact me to speak about a partnership, send an email to <a href="mailto:admin@phot-irc.co.uk" data-bbcode="true">admin@phot-irc.co.uk</a> and I will get back to you as soon as I can.</p>
<p>Phot is protected by the GPL and legal action will be taken against those deciding not to follow the license.</p>
<p>EDIT: The “README” file should be looked over before doing anything related with the bot, it contains a list of functions that the bot has, all the commands that come with the bot and a description on what it is/how to run it.</p>
<p>[size=20pt]THIS IS NOT DESIGNED TO BE A WEB PAGE IT IS FOR COMMAND LINE ONLY[/size]</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/phot/275967/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/phot/275967/1</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 27 Apr 2009 20:05:24 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-275967-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/phot/275967.rss">Phot</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
