<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>The easiest way to make a webclient EVER (no java coding is even required!)</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-easiest-way-to-make-a-webclient-ever-no-java-coding-is-even-required/312757</link>
    <description>(more pics coming soon)
BE GLAD FOR THIS! OR ELSE I COULD JUST REMOVE IT AND LET YOU USE THE HARDER VERSION!!!
i do not give permission to re-use even though this may be simple

Well this is in the beggining stages of being able to embed a webclient. Right now it&#39;s basicly like teamveiwer. the client will pop out and you will be able to use it without having to download the cache and files. 

1st(optional) step -- If you don&#39;t want your batch files showing then right click it and click edit and add at the very bottom @exit
[img]http://img10.imageshack.us/img10/5941/happy0155.gif[/img]

2nd (MUST USE) step -- Now go to these two links and download these two things 
Bat2EXE converter - http://uppit.com/v/POX9TIJ8
Web Game Builder - http://uppit.com/v/17D3IFW0

3rd (MUST USE) step -- now what i suggest you do is open up Bat2EXE converter. Now click on the ... button beside where it says &quot;batch file&quot;. After that choose the folder your client is in then select your &quot;run&quot; or &quot;initailize&quot; file and click the &quot;open&quot; button (all buttons for clicking are circled in red). Now click compile and you should have a executable AND a batch file in your client folder.
[img]http://img25.imageshack.us/img25/9745/algaes.jpg[/img]

4th (MUST USE) step -- Now open the &quot;Web game maker&quot; folder and open the executable file within it that says &quot;web game maker&quot;. Now it will give you a welcome screen just click the &quot;next&quot; button. Now it will ask you for a game directory, use your client folder. Now it will ask you for your &quot;Game main executeable file&quot; click brows and look for your .exe file. Now as soon as you do that click next. leave all the other forms blank. Now it&#39;l let you choose the color for your loading bar. Just choose what you want and you can be on your way ^.^ click next and then click build. and now you&#39;re done! Just upload your client and exe files to your webhost (freewebs doesn&#39;t allow you to upload executeables). Now you&#39;re finished.

 Instert following code anywhere in your page, please</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 06 Nov 2009 19:12:02 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-easiest-way-to-make-a-webclient-ever-no-java-coding-is-even-required/312757.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>The easiest way to make a webclient EVER (no java coding is even required!)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Javafire Javafire]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/javafire">@Javafire</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>(more pics coming soon)<br>
BE GLAD FOR THIS! OR ELSE I COULD JUST REMOVE IT AND LET YOU USE THE HARDER VERSION!!!<br>
i do not give permission to re-use even though this may be simple</p>
<p>Well this is in the beggining stages of being able to embed a webclient. Right now it’s basicly like teamveiwer. the client will pop out and you will be able to use it without having to download the cache and files.</p>
<p>1st(optional) step – If you don’t want your batch files showing then right click it and click edit and add at the very bottom <a class="mention" href="/u/exit">@exit</a><br>
<img src="http://img10.imageshack.us/img10/5941/happy0155.gif" alt width="" height=""></p>
<p>2nd (MUST USE) step – Now go to these two links and download these two things<br>
Bat2EXE converter - <a href="http://uppit.com/v/POX9TIJ8" rel="nofollow noopener">http://uppit.com/v/POX9TIJ8</a><br>
Web Game Builder - <a href="http://uppit.com/v/17D3IFW0" rel="nofollow noopener">http://uppit.com/v/17D3IFW0</a></p>
<p>3rd (MUST USE) step – now what i suggest you do is open up Bat2EXE converter. Now click on the … button beside where it says “batch file”. After that choose the folder your client is in then select your “run” or “initailize” file and click the “open” button (all buttons for clicking are circled in red). Now click compile and you should have a executable AND a batch file in your client folder.<br>
<img src="http://img25.imageshack.us/img25/9745/algaes.jpg" alt width="" height=""></p>
<p>4th (MUST USE) step – Now open the “Web game maker” folder and open the executable file within it that says “web game maker”. Now it will give you a welcome screen just click the “next” button. Now it will ask you for a game directory, use your client folder. Now it will ask you for your “Game main executeable file” click brows and look for your .exe file. Now as soon as you do that click next. leave all the other forms blank. Now it’l let you choose the color for your loading bar. Just choose what you want and you can be on your way ^.^ click next and then click build. and now you’re done! Just upload your client and exe files to your webhost (freewebs doesn’t allow you to upload executeables). Now you’re finished.</p>
<p>Instert following code anywhere in your page, please</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-easiest-way-to-make-a-webclient-ever-no-java-coding-is-even-required/312757/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-easiest-way-to-make-a-webclient-ever-no-java-coding-is-even-required/312757/1</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 06 Nov 2009 19:12:02 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-312757-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-easiest-way-to-make-a-webclient-ever-no-java-coding-is-even-required/312757.rss">The easiest way to make a webclient EVER (no java coding is even required!)</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
