<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>718 players cant equip items</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/718-players-cant-equip-items/546499</link>
    <description>Ok so, on my server there was this one player who was making it so when he wore black claws his character had a wall through him, and it was sort of glitching out. So I reset the server, only to find that I couldnt equip anything.. the inventory still worked because I could still eat food but I could not equip anything, along with a few players.. I have restarted the server multiple times, and now I can equip items, but some other players cannot. If you know whats causing this, please tell me.
The only way they can equip armour at the moment is going into the equipment tab and then equipping it from there.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2014 01:39:34 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/718-players-cant-equip-items/546499.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>718 players cant equip items</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@adamgulka adamgulka]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/adamgulka">@adamgulka</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Ok so, on my server there was this one player who was making it so when he wore black claws his character had a wall through him, and it was sort of glitching out. So I reset the server, only to find that I couldnt equip anything… the inventory still worked because I could still eat food but I could not equip anything, along with a few players… I have restarted the server multiple times, and now I can equip items, but some other players cannot. If you know whats causing this, please tell me.<br>
The only way they can equip armour at the moment is going into the equipment tab and then equipping it from there.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/718-players-cant-equip-items/546499/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/718-players-cant-equip-items/546499/1</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2014 01:39:34 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-546499-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/718-players-cant-equip-items/546499.rss">718 players cant equip items</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
