<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Buffalo plane crash</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/buffalo-plane-crash/261951</link>
    <description>At least 50 people were killed when a commuter plane crashed into a home in suburban Buffalo, New York, moments after it lost contact with air traffic controllers.

The Q400 Bombardier turboprop aircraft operated for Continental Airlines came down suddenly at about 10.20pm yesterday (3.20am GMT), hitting a home in the small town of Clarence Center and bursting into a fireball, according to witnesses.

The crash is the second aviation disaster in less than a month for New York state. In contrast to the January 15 &quot;Miracle on the Hudson&quot;, in which pilot Chesley Sullenberger guided a jet to a water landing and saved the lives of 155 aboard, Continental Connection flight 3407 &quot;seemed to come straight down&quot;, New York&#39;s governor, David Paterson, said, ending in a fierey wreckage that hours later was too hot for investigators to approach.

Television footage showed the tail of the twin-engined propeller plane visible amid the burning wreckage. State police said all 44 passengers and four crew died in the crash, along with one person on the ground. Colgan Air, a Virginia-based regional carrier which was operating the flight on behalf of Continental, said later that an off-duty pilot was also on board. Officials said two people escaped the burning house.

FBI special agent in charge Laurie Bennett said investigators have no evidence the crash was the result of terrorism.

A voice recording of air traffic controllers and the flight&#39;s pilot gave no indication of trouble before contact was lost with the flight at an altitude of 700 metres as it came in to land at Buffalo&#39;s Niagara airport. It had taken off from Newark airport in New Jersey.

A local emergency co-ordinator told reporters that the plane made &quot;a direct hit&quot; on the house. Another 12 homes were evacuated, with some damaged by fire. &quot;It&#39;s remarkable that it only took one house,&quot; said David Bissonette. &quot;It could have easily taken the whole neighbourhood.&quot;

Investigators, who said they had not ruled out any possible causes, have located the flight data recorders and are shipping them to Washington to analysis.

&quot;We don&#39;t have any factual information other than that the airplane went down and it hit a house,&quot; Steve Chealander from the federal National Transportation Safety Board told reporters. &quot;We&#39;re going to be sifting through the evidence, looking for everything.&quot; The wreckage of the plane, including a &quot;relatively intact&quot; section of the tail, was almost completely confined to the land area of the single house, which was destroyed, he said. The crash area contained &quot;a lot of carnage&quot;, he added.

&quot;The whole sky was lit up orange,&quot; said Bob Dworak, who lives less than a mile from the crash site. &quot;All of a sudden there was a big bang and the house shook.&quot;

Another witness, Tony Tatro, said he saw the plane flying low and knew it was in trouble. &quot;It was not spiralling at all. The left wing was a little low,&quot; he told the Buffalo television station, WGRZ-TV.

Authorities did not immediately name any of those killed, although relatives identified several. 

Among the dead was Beverly Eckert, 54, the widow of a businessman killed in the 9/11 attacks. She had been travelling to Buffalo to mark what would have been his 58th birthday, her sister said. Also killed was Rwanda specialist, genocide researcher and MacArthur Fellow Alison Des Forge, Paterson said. 

The weather was cold at the time, with fog and light snow falling, and investigators are likely to concentrate on the possibility of ice build-up on the aircraft. The Q400, which is the latest version of the Dash 8 series of planes, is designed to be flown in such conditions. The 74-seat plane that crashed was delivered new to Colgan Air last April and had flown without any reported incidents.

It is the first fatal crash involving this generation of the Dash 8. In 2007 the Canadian manufacturer advised airlines using the model to temporarily take them out of service to inspect their landing gear after the Scandinavian airline SAS reported landing gear failures.

Kathleen Dworak said she heard the plane&#39;s engines &quot;sputtering&quot; as it passed over her home shortly before the impact. &quot;Then there was a loud noise and it shook our house,&quot; she told CNN. &quot;We opened the door and smelled smoke.&quot;
Dworak said she and her husband arrived at the scene before fire crews but were forced to retreat after another explosion. &quot;It was clear from what we saw that there were not going to be any survivors,&quot; she said.

A US website that records live conversations between aircraft and air traffic control crews posted a recording of air traffic controllers handing the plane over to Buffalo airport&#39;s jurisdiction as it made its final descent before contact was lost without warning. A controller then asked the pilot of a nearby Delta plane: &quot;Delta 1998, look off your right side about five miles for a Dash 8 about 2,300 [feet]. You see anything there?&quot; The Delta pilot replied: &quot;Uh, negative.&quot;

It is the first fatal crash of a commercial airliner in the US since 27 August 2006, when 49 people were killed when a Comair jetliner crashed after take-off in Lexington, Kentucky. Investigators found that the runway chosen was too short for the type of plane.

[url=http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=frl3xVaXiuY]http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=frl3xVaXiuY[/url]</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2009 05:10:21 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>General Discussion</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/buffalo-plane-crash/261951.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Buffalo plane crash</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@jme jme]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/jme">@jme</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p><a href="http://news.yahoo.com/s/ap/20090216/ap_on_re_us/plane_into_home" class="onebox" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">http://news.yahoo.com/s/ap/20090216/ap_on_re_us/plane_into_home</a></p>
<p>Autopilot was on</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/buffalo-plane-crash/261951/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/buffalo-plane-crash/261951/5</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2009 05:10:21 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-261951-5</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/buffalo-plane-crash/261951.rss">Buffalo plane crash</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Buffalo plane crash</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Thornton136 Thornton136]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/thornton136">@Thornton136</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Ineresting story huh?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/buffalo-plane-crash/261951/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/buffalo-plane-crash/261951/4</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2009 09:52:16 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-261951-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/buffalo-plane-crash/261951.rss">Buffalo plane crash</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Buffalo plane crash</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@gothic_queen casey.]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/gothic_queen">@gothic_queen</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote no-group" data-post="2" data-topic="261951">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/bootnecklad/40/5_6bca9977b612b7aeef77ba1ec1cd67b3.png" class="avatar"> bootnecklad:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Oh and how ironic a widow from 9/11 died in the crash</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>idiot</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/buffalo-plane-crash/261951/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/buffalo-plane-crash/261951/3</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2009 21:56:17 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-261951-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/buffalo-plane-crash/261951.rss">Buffalo plane crash</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Buffalo plane crash</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@bootnecklad bootnecklad]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/bootnecklad">@bootnecklad</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>l2quote…</p>
<p>Oh and how ironic a widow from 9/11 died in the crash</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/buffalo-plane-crash/261951/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/buffalo-plane-crash/261951/2</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2009 21:36:15 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-261951-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/buffalo-plane-crash/261951.rss">Buffalo plane crash</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Buffalo plane crash</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Thornton136 Thornton136]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/thornton136">@Thornton136</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>At least 50 people were killed when a commuter plane crashed into a home in suburban Buffalo, New York, moments after it lost contact with air traffic controllers.</p>
<p>The Q400 Bombardier turboprop aircraft operated for Continental Airlines came down suddenly at about 10.20pm yesterday (3.20am GMT), hitting a home in the small town of Clarence Center and bursting into a fireball, according to witnesses.</p>
<p>The crash is the second aviation disaster in less than a month for New York state. In contrast to the January 15 “Miracle on the Hudson”, in which pilot Chesley Sullenberger guided a jet to a water landing and saved the lives of 155 aboard, Continental Connection flight 3407 “seemed to come straight down”, New York’s governor, David Paterson, said, ending in a fierey wreckage that hours later was too hot for investigators to approach.</p>
<p>Television footage showed the tail of the twin-engined propeller plane visible amid the burning wreckage. State police said all 44 passengers and four crew died in the crash, along with one person on the ground. Colgan Air, a Virginia-based regional carrier which was operating the flight on behalf of Continental, said later that an off-duty pilot was also on board. Officials said two people escaped the burning house.</p>
<p>FBI special agent in charge Laurie Bennett said investigators have no evidence the crash was the result of terrorism.</p>
<p>A voice recording of air traffic controllers and the flight’s pilot gave no indication of trouble before contact was lost with the flight at an altitude of 700 metres as it came in to land at Buffalo’s Niagara airport. It had taken off from Newark airport in New Jersey.</p>
<p>A local emergency co-ordinator told reporters that the plane made “a direct hit” on the house. Another 12 homes were evacuated, with some damaged by fire. “It’s remarkable that it only took one house,” said David Bissonette. “It could have easily taken the whole neighbourhood.”</p>
<p>Investigators, who said they had not ruled out any possible causes, have located the flight data recorders and are shipping them to Washington to analysis.</p>
<p>“We don’t have any factual information other than that the airplane went down and it hit a house,” Steve Chealander from the federal National Transportation Safety Board told reporters. “We’re going to be sifting through the evidence, looking for everything.” The wreckage of the plane, including a “relatively intact” section of the tail, was almost completely confined to the land area of the single house, which was destroyed, he said. The crash area contained “a lot of carnage”, he added.</p>
<p>“The whole sky was lit up orange,” said Bob Dworak, who lives less than a mile from the crash site. “All of a sudden there was a big bang and the house shook.”</p>
<p>Another witness, Tony Tatro, said he saw the plane flying low and knew it was in trouble. “It was not spiralling at all. The left wing was a little low,” he told the Buffalo television station, WGRZ-TV.</p>
<p>Authorities did not immediately name any of those killed, although relatives identified several.</p>
<p>Among the dead was Beverly Eckert, 54, the widow of a businessman killed in the 9/11 attacks. She had been travelling to Buffalo to mark what would have been his 58th birthday, her sister said. Also killed was Rwanda specialist, genocide researcher and MacArthur Fellow Alison Des Forge, Paterson said.</p>
<p>The weather was cold at the time, with fog and light snow falling, and investigators are likely to concentrate on the possibility of ice build-up on the aircraft. The Q400, which is the latest version of the Dash 8 series of planes, is designed to be flown in such conditions. The 74-seat plane that crashed was delivered new to Colgan Air last April and had flown without any reported incidents.</p>
<p>It is the first fatal crash involving this generation of the Dash 8. In 2007 the Canadian manufacturer advised airlines using the model to temporarily take them out of service to inspect their landing gear after the Scandinavian airline SAS reported landing gear failures.</p>
<p>Kathleen Dworak said she heard the plane’s engines “sputtering” as it passed over her home shortly before the impact. “Then there was a loud noise and it shook our house,” she told CNN. “We opened the door and smelled smoke.”<br>
Dworak said she and her husband arrived at the scene before fire crews but were forced to retreat after another explosion. “It was clear from what we saw that there were not going to be any survivors,” she said.</p>
<p>A US website that records live conversations between aircraft and air traffic control crews posted a recording of air traffic controllers handing the plane over to Buffalo airport’s jurisdiction as it made its final descent before contact was lost without warning. A controller then asked the pilot of a nearby Delta plane: “Delta 1998, look off your right side about five miles for a Dash 8 about 2,300 [feet]. You see anything there?” The Delta pilot replied: “Uh, negative.”</p>
<p>It is the first fatal crash of a commercial airliner in the US since 27 August 2006, when 49 people were killed when a Comair jetliner crashed after take-off in Lexington, Kentucky. Investigators found that the runway chosen was too short for the type of plane.</p>
<p><a href="http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=frl3xVaXiuY" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=frl3xVaXiuY</a></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/buffalo-plane-crash/261951/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/buffalo-plane-crash/261951/1</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2009 20:03:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-261951-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/buffalo-plane-crash/261951.rss">Buffalo plane crash</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
