<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Xampp</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/xampp/200660</link>
    <description>Is it a good idea to try and make it secure to use it as a production web server? I usually use Linux, and just host my sites with it. Being that it is very secure and uses little CPU. I&#39;m kind of wanting to use a portable version, to take with me. But most places I &#39;hang my hat&#39;, uses Windows. Causing problems for me and hosting. But I have PortableApps, which has Xampp portable, so I was just wondering if it would be safe. I&#39;m not looking for large amounts of traffic, just a very simple web server.  

If you all have any better suggestion. I am open to them. I&#39;m contemplating buying a WD Passport, instead of a Flash Drive. Allowing me to write without shortening the life of my drive.

EDIT: Holy Crap how&#39;d I do that.. Posted in the wrong section. Move to Questions Please?</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 17 Apr 2008 07:32:10 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>General Discussion</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/xampp/200660.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Xampp</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@ThAt0n36Uy Elijah]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/that0n36uy">@ThAt0n36Uy</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Is it a good idea to try and make it secure to use it as a production web server? I usually use Linux, and just host my sites with it. Being that it is very secure and uses little CPU. I’m kind of wanting to use a portable version, to take with me. But most places I ‘hang my hat’, uses Windows. Causing problems for me and hosting. But I have PortableApps, which has Xampp portable, so I was just wondering if it would be safe. I’m not looking for large amounts of traffic, just a very simple web server.</p>
<p>If you all have any better suggestion. I am open to them. I’m contemplating buying a WD Passport, instead of a Flash Drive. Allowing me to write without shortening the life of my drive.</p>
<p>EDIT: Holy Crap how’d I do that… Posted in the wrong section. Move to Questions Please?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/xampp/200660/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/xampp/200660/1</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 17 Apr 2008 07:32:10 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-200660-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/xampp/200660.rss">Xampp</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
