<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Slow news day</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/slow-news-day/410059</link>
    <description>So i thought i would share something i just came across. Shows some great insight into the current RSC community.

The following excerpts are just the ones i found the most interesting, to read the full guide, go to http://www.rscemulation.net/forum/viewtopic.php?id=38375


[b][u]0.0: Introduction[u][/b]

So you want to fit in at the RuneScape Classic Emulation community? It&#39;s hard work. You might even slip and fall a few times, but hopefully with the help of this comprehensive guide, you&#39;ll be on your way to palin&#39; around with all your new buddies. Buddies you&#39;ll meet at RSCE!

[b]1.0: Preparation[/b]

Look, we can&#39;t just go jumping into this whole thing. You need to prepare. You need to build some vocabulary, first off.
[URL=http://imageshack.us/photo/my-images/811/fig1v.jpg/][IMG]http://img811.imageshack.us/img811/7492/fig1v.jpg[/img][/URL]

Figure 1.a: A splendid example of a common exchange between fellow players on RSCE.

As we can see in Figure 1.a, a fantastic basis of discussion can be chimed upon through a simple aggressive command, preferably constructed by arrogance and/or ignorance. Most players will respond.

[b]Addressing Players[/b]
Correctly addressing fellow players sets you apart from the articulate mass of No-Lifers lurking the server. Condescension is key.

[b][i]Noob[/i][/b]- One of the most common terms used. Expect to take &quot;noob&quot; punches thoroughly if you happen to have questions for higher leveled players. The best way to handle being placed in the &quot;noob light&quot; is to immediately attack the assailant&#39;s sexuality, or suggest that he/she has a deviant incestuous relationship with their mother.

[b][i]Kid[/i][/b]- Calling another player &#39;kid&#39; is a great way to assert your superiority and inform said player that you are much more mature and wise than them. Generally, the younger you are IRL the more you should use this term. Also a good way to change the tides of an argument you&#39;re losing.
Some Kid: Shutup dude, you&#39;re an idiot.
You: Look, kid, ive got a good 14 years under my belt, I know alot more then you do.

[b]Phrases[/b]
Some think that arguments should be rational and only involve the topic of discussion that caused the argument, those people are of course filthy no-lifers who live in their parents basement, oh and are virgins.

[b][i]RAGE[/i][/b]- noun, verb, RAGED, RAGEING.
Raging used to be a way to describe someone who was obviously enraged, usually indicated by excess use of CAPITAL LETTERS, however it is becoming acceptable to use this to describe anyone who disagrees with you or has an opinion on something.
RAGER: Dude, death runes AREN&#39;T 1.5K each.
You: LOL rage more bro? 

[b][i]umadbro[/i][/b]- Contrary to popular belief, this little gem definitely isn&#39;t getting old and using it still makes you cool. It is synonymous with RAGE, and can be used to describe anyone who is mad, not mad, happy or generally neutral in disposition.
Can also be used without the &#39;bro&#39; suffix, but that would be varying it up a bit and not be sticking to the tried and true meme that started it several decades ago.
SOMEMADBRO: Dude, death runes AREN&#39;T 1.5K each.
You: LOL  umad bro? 

[b][i]Anything involving the opponents mother.[/i][/b] - Another one that definitely is still funny and original after years of use, is the classic mom jokes. Usually implying that you and the subjects mother had sexual relations of some sort. It&#39;s a good trump card in arguments and shows that you&#39;re not only clever enough to best them in a verbal dispute but you are a real casanova.
your bastard child: Have fun in lumby noob
You: Yeah I will, your mom is there waiting for me.


[b][i]Sockpuppeting[/i][/b]
When your losing an argument because a bunch of no lifers have teamed up on you for supposedly being an &#39;idiot&#39; and told you to &#39;stfu&#39;, a good way to turn the tables is to make several alts and log onto them to agree with yourself.

So I&#39;ve covered the basics of interacting with your fellow players, I suggest you try them all out yourselves and see which ones work for you( I suggest asking people if you can &#39;get some money your new&#39;, and then flaming them when they refuse your very reasonable request. Master these and you will truly be an intellectual force to be reckoned with. Feel free to suggest any other words or phrases I should define in this dictionary of winning.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 17 Aug 2011 04:26:14 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/slow-news-day/410059.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Slow news day</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@lol2011 lol2011]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/lol2011">@lol2011</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote quote-modified" data-post="2" data-topic="410059">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/dexto/40/5_e05bb34c421432ee4d40de30c10af3e5.png" class="avatar"> dexto:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>lol’d</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/slow-news-day/410059/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/slow-news-day/410059/6</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 17 Aug 2011 04:26:14 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-410059-6</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/slow-news-day/410059.rss">Slow news day</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Slow news day</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@nacional nacional]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/nacional">@nacional</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>heh no wonder I didn’t fit in</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/slow-news-day/410059/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/slow-news-day/410059/5</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 14 Aug 2011 14:23:04 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-410059-5</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/slow-news-day/410059.rss">Slow news day</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Slow news day</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@iMubbY iMubbY]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/imubby">@iMubbY</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“Ecko, post:3, topic:410059”][quote]<br>
those people are of course filthy no-lifers who live in their parents basement, oh and are virgins.[/quote][/quote]</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/slow-news-day/410059/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/slow-news-day/410059/4</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 14 Aug 2011 12:34:58 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-410059-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/slow-news-day/410059.rss">Slow news day</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Slow news day</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Ecko Ecko]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/ecko">@Ecko</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <blockquote>those people are of course filthy no-lifers who live in their parents basement, oh and are virgins.</blockquote>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/slow-news-day/410059/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/slow-news-day/410059/3</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 14 Aug 2011 12:27:31 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-410059-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/slow-news-day/410059.rss">Slow news day</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Slow news day</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@dexto dexto]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/dexto">@dexto</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>lol’d</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/slow-news-day/410059/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/slow-news-day/410059/2</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 14 Aug 2011 11:11:14 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-410059-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/slow-news-day/410059.rss">Slow news day</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Slow news day</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@OldSkoolRSC OldSkoolRSC]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/oldskoolrsc">@OldSkoolRSC</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>So i thought i would share something i just came across. Shows some great insight into the current RSC community.</p>
<p>The following excerpts are just the ones i found the most interesting, to read the full guide, go to <a href="http://www.rscemulation.net/forum/viewtopic.php?id=38375" rel="nofollow noopener">http://www.rscemulation.net/forum/viewtopic.php?id=38375</a></p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">[u]0.0: Introduction[u]</span></p>
<p>So you want to fit in at the RuneScape Classic Emulation community? It’s hard work. You might even slip and fall a few times, but hopefully with the help of this comprehensive guide, you’ll be on your way to palin’ around with all your new buddies. Buddies you’ll meet at RSCE!</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">1.0: Preparation</span></p>
<p>Look, we can’t just go jumping into this whole thing. You need to prepare. You need to build some vocabulary, first off.<br>
<a href="http://imageshack.us/photo/my-images/811/fig1v.jpg/" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener"><img src="http://img811.imageshack.us/img811/7492/fig1v.jpg" alt width="" height=""></a></p>
<p>Figure 1.a: A splendid example of a common exchange between fellow players on RSCE.</p>
<p>As we can see in Figure 1.a, a fantastic basis of discussion can be chimed upon through a simple aggressive command, preferably constructed by arrogance and/or ignorance. Most players will respond.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Addressing Players</span><br>
Correctly addressing fellow players sets you apart from the articulate mass of No-Lifers lurking the server. Condescension is key.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b"><span class="bbcode-i">Noob</span></span>- One of the most common terms used. Expect to take “noob” punches thoroughly if you happen to have questions for higher leveled players. The best way to handle being placed in the “noob light” is to immediately attack the assailant’s sexuality, or suggest that he/she has a deviant incestuous relationship with their mother.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b"><span class="bbcode-i">Kid</span></span>- Calling another player ‘kid’ is a great way to assert your superiority and inform said player that you are much more mature and wise than them. Generally, the younger you are IRL the more you should use this term. Also a good way to change the tides of an argument you’re losing.<br>
Some Kid: Shutup dude, you’re an idiot.<br>
You: Look, kid, ive got a good 14 years under my belt, I know alot more then you do.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Phrases</span><br>
Some think that arguments should be rational and only involve the topic of discussion that caused the argument, those people are of course filthy no-lifers who live in their parents basement, oh and are virgins.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b"><span class="bbcode-i">RAGE</span></span>- noun, verb, RAGED, RAGEING.<br>
Raging used to be a way to describe someone who was obviously enraged, usually indicated by excess use of CAPITAL LETTERS, however it is becoming acceptable to use this to describe anyone who disagrees with you or has an opinion on something.<br>
RAGER: Dude, death runes AREN’T 1.5K each.<br>
You: LOL rage more bro?</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b"><span class="bbcode-i">umadbro</span></span>- Contrary to popular belief, this little gem definitely isn’t getting old and using it still makes you cool. It is synonymous with RAGE, and can be used to describe anyone who is mad, not mad, happy or generally neutral in disposition.<br>
Can also be used without the ‘bro’ suffix, but that would be varying it up a bit and not be sticking to the tried and true meme that started it several decades ago.<br>
SOMEMADBRO: Dude, death runes AREN’T 1.5K each.<br>
You: LOL  umad bro?</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b"><span class="bbcode-i">Anything involving the opponents mother.</span></span> - Another one that definitely is still funny and original after years of use, is the classic mom jokes. Usually implying that you and the subjects mother had sexual relations of some sort. It’s a good trump card in arguments and shows that you’re not only clever enough to best them in a verbal dispute but you are a real casanova.<br>
your bastard child: Have fun in lumby noob<br>
You: Yeah I will, your mom is there waiting for me.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b"><span class="bbcode-i">Sockpuppeting</span></span><br>
When your losing an argument because a bunch of no lifers have teamed up on you for supposedly being an ‘idiot’ and told you to ‘stfu’, a good way to turn the tables is to make several alts and log onto them to agree with yourself.</p>
<p>So I’ve covered the basics of interacting with your fellow players, I suggest you try them all out yourselves and see which ones work for you( I suggest asking people if you can ‘get some money your new’, and then flaming them when they refuse your very reasonable request. Master these and you will truly be an intellectual force to be reckoned with. Feel free to suggest any other words or phrases I should define in this dictionary of winning.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/slow-news-day/410059/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/slow-news-day/410059/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 14 Aug 2011 11:07:34 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-410059-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/slow-news-day/410059.rss">Slow news day</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
