<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Combat update</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/combat-update/435082</link>
    <description>i know this might be a bit experienced to explain it in a simple reply... But i&#39;ve been looking for a tut for 2 days now. If any of you can link me to one or if you can explain it that would be great (y)

Basically players combat dont update... the max combat is 138 and that&#39;s because summoning works. but i could get 99 attack in game and still be combat 3, until i log out. why&#39;s this? :s 

when other players look at me it says like combat 50 but when i look at me it says cb 3... until i log out and back in then it says the actual combat? :(</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Mar 2012 10:42:04 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/combat-update/435082.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Combat update</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@V113 V1]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/v113">@V113</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>i know this might be a bit experienced to explain it in a simple reply… But i’ve been looking for a tut for 2 days now. If any of you can link me to one or if you can explain it that would be great (y)</p>
<p>Basically players combat dont update… the max combat is 138 and that’s because summoning works. but i could get 99 attack in game and still be combat 3, until i log out. why’s this? :s</p>
<p>when other players look at me it says like combat 50 but when i look at me it says cb 3… until i log out and back in then it says the actual combat? <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/frowning.png?v=5" title=":frowning:" class="emoji" alt=":frowning:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/combat-update/435082/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/combat-update/435082/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 04 Mar 2012 10:42:04 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-435082-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/combat-update/435082.rss">Combat update</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
