<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>[317] Project Fr0z3n [Delta] [UPDATED] [Video][Special addition to Prodigyscape]</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/317-project-fr0z3n-delta-updated-video-special-addition-to-prodigyscape/313817</link>
    <description>[IMG]http://img21.imageshack.us/img21/4357/mscp.png[/img]


Well since i think i&#39;ll get 20k views on Prodigyscape, i did some last minute touch up&#39;s on it and created Project Fr0z3n. :rolleyes:
[b]
I will sort this topic out more so it&#39;s easier to read and more organized!
[/b]
[b]
Base:Delta 317. (i used prodigyscape, but it&#39;s delta)
Loading Cache: 377
GameFrame: 474?[/b]

[i][b]Client Aspects:[/b][/i]
Loads the Prodigyscape Backround.
Fixed the Gameframe, because it wuz ugly.
Opens your forums (change the link via run.bat, if your using windows, if not simply remove the command line itself to avoid problems).
Has a IpChanger in it, via login screen.
Connects via 127.0.0.1 port 43954 as default.

[b]Side note: Compressed to best quality so it shouldn&#39;t take long to unpack it.[/b]

For Information on how this is an update server to my old one, please visit the topic link here: http://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php/topic,382586.0.html


[u][i][b]Server General Details![/b][/i][/u]

[b]This server was made about 2 months AFTER Prodigyscape, how ever i did a few touch ups
at the same time i&#39;m typing this sentence as i saw the opportunities. I also felt like the people deserve a update to the shit they downloaded (even if this is still shit, it&#39;s better shit &lt;3).[/b]


The main concept of this, was to create a One-Of-A-Kind Godwars + A Stable economy/Leveling system, where leveling is benificial and can be fun, and not over-board economy servers where you&#39;d need say, 99 mining to mine open the entrance to get into bandos, things like those i find are UNFAIR, as players who hate skilling, hate mining, and find that as nothing big, because once they do get 99 mining, they can just keep going back and back, with no more excitement, or the challenge to stay in there as long as possible will keep players wanting to go back. The fact i added ALL gwd minibosses was another thing i felt will attract players to keep trying to get to go to gwd and continue wanting to. I also felt that players SHOULD NOT be able to farcast/range npc&#39;s and get them glitched, or mass clan them, and have people bring level 3&#39;s with food to provide for them, i found this was an economy crasher. So i decided to spend the time on adding a npc Multi Hitting system, where a npc has a 1 in 3 chance it will use it. when it uses this, a emote will VERY QUICKLY show up on the player (feel free to change this, it was just a test emote), and all players within a certain radius will get hit within 0-65 damage (i felt this was neccessary to avoid camping, and as well, corporal beast, which is the npc i used for the damage example, maxes 65 in rs, so i stuck with it), HOW EVER there is one small error with this, when you get hit, the damage that shows up, ISNT the damage you will get hit, as i was cbb to figure out how to have it display the hit and deal the damage, as the basic hitDiff didnt work at all, so at the moment, if it displays a 5, yet your hp drops to half, don&#39;t freak out, take it as a hidden bonus to players that go there, as they won&#39;t know for sure what they will get hit.

[b][u][i]Client Updates![/i][/u][/b]

-A smaller client about 2mb smaller i believe.

-Removed [u][i][b]BASICALLY ALL *CUSTOMS*[/b][/i][/u] as in recolours, this still has things like sigils, hilts etc.

-Added all spirit shields+Sigils+Godswords Hilts+Godsword Blade

-Added 100% ALL GWD Miniboss npc, UNANIMATED, but they have exact names and examine info+correct levels.

-Half the world is SNOW, YAY!?!1111
-A friend told me the snow looks too bright after awile, and deep in the wildy, the black rocks that i cannot remove look disgusting with the white floor, how ever, it&#39;s your opinion.

-This has full godsword stances (Credits to the creator)
-This has All godsword specs (Thanks to the creator)
[s]-The godsword specs need fixing however, there is a slight glitch in the bgs/zgs/and/sgs specs, they repeat themselves, so all you need to do is change the emote i&#39;d back to the old ones, which i might do before i upload the files because i can see terror in this topic from all the help posts. I will LEAVE Ags how ever, as it works flawlessly.[/s]

-This has all pvp armour and weapons+Specs(accurate and hit&#39;s decent, a little to high at the moment i find).
[u][i][b]

[color=red][u][i][b]
Server Updates![/b][/i][/u][/color]
[color=blue][b]
Npc and Npc Spawns:[/b][/color]


-The current Arma Gwd area, IS CODED, how ever, i feel that it is... uhm, not as planned, i decided to put it in the ACTUAL Dagganoth lair, as it was open, and i managed to get it coloured white, for the reason that, since i didn&#39;t need to spawn objects, it creates less lagg, feel free to move it&#39;s current spot.

-i forgot to tell you, to get to gwd, use the portals at home, they have the cords set, just edit your character value points so you can use them.

-Added Corporal Beast hitting ALL PLAYERS within 15 radius(either that or 7 i forget), so players that want to Range instead, can avoid getting hit by this (Read below to see bugs on this).

-Was in the process of adding custom 317 GWD Arena&#39;s, via my tut i released a long time ago under client hacking section about changing the floor colour. So far i have full bandos arena, has  working graardor, and all 3 ACTUAL rs mini bosses, only one of the 3 is coded to attack atm i think, that one happens to range players: (NOTE): The mini bosses are NOT animated as i don&#39;t have the skill to animate, so they stay still sadly.

-Added the Wait Till Beside Npc, thx to Lin :3


[color=blue][b]Economy!
[/b][/color]


-Created a tough econamy and Leveling system;
-lvl 3 start off
-Iron + 100k i believe.
-Exp Rate is set VERY low, i believe 4x the hit, not 100% sure i fixed that ages ago, like 4 months ago lol.
-There are no leveling commands
-Training is north of home, away from spawn spot to avoid clutter
-NPC&#39;s only drop low loot, such as black, mith, Addy(rare), steel.
-Previously the portals you&#39;ll see at home were part of a pk point system/Npc points system, if you had 25 kills you could tele to a medium train in the wildy with monsters that dropped more loot, like rune, but you had to have the risk of pkers, but pkers can&#39;t camp seeming that need to kill npc&#39;s to GET there.
-Shops are incomplete, feel free to change what you want.


[color=blue][b]Weapon Specials![/b][/color]

-Working Dragon Claws ( Actual 4 hitting + randomized hits 90% like rs, just doesn&#39;t have it&#39;s equation to divide the first two hits by two which create the next to hits).
-Fixed ags spec to be more accurate and high hitting (for some reason was only maxing around 50 with full vesta&#39;s etc)
[color=blue][b]
Server Security![/b][/color]

-Has working bans and mutes, although no Anti syi etc, because i never/could host, so i didn&#39;t need these features. A decent way to avoid spam is to change it so the player starts off muted, and once he gains 1 combat level, he can then talk.
should be ALOT [b]less [/b]lagg, i havn&#39;t tested the max players...


COMMANDS ARE(basic ones)-[/b][/i][/u]

::beast (corpbeast tele)
::low(a pk area for 1 def pures)
::med(a pk area for zerkers[45 def])
::food(doesnt work in wildy)
::pots(doesnt work in wildy)
::ownyell (a yell command for the owner displays [OWNER] infront of text)
::quests, auto completes quests, use this to use things like veng, as most quest will not work

-I added a ::kdr command, basically the same functions as a 508 ::kdr
i believe this was something fun as well as helpful to add to the server, as i know when i played 508&#39;s the main goal was to see who could get the best kdr spread, and tbh that was the main reason people played. This adds another goal to players to make them want to play.




[u][i][b]
Pvp drops![/b][/i][/u]

I editted them a tad different compared to Prodigyscape, as prodigyscape i believe the drops were too often etc.

So i changed it to getting drops are alot more uncommon, although when you happen to get good loot, there will be more in the drop than there would have been in Prodigyscape.

- I don&#39;t recall doing anything on drops, other than the basic junk, so you&#39;d have to do this yourself.






[u][i][b]YOUR TURN![/b][/i][/u]

haha, now your like? &quot;oh shit i dun want to read now, i have to do somethings nao D:&quot;, well dw. theres just a few intentional bugs left behind so leechers don&#39;t get 100% privilidges.

As i said before Corp beast doesn&#39;t show it&#39;s proper hits, but you didn&#39;t know that i didnt code the 4 gw monsters to hit all players as well, not really a bug, just a missing piece of data that is vital to a stable gwd system.

I off hand fixed the godsword specs, but i didn&#39;t test, so it&#39;s up to you to tell me IF THEY WORK OR NOT, so if they don&#39;t i can do it the easy way and get my origanal animation id&#39;s back, because i stupidly forgot to save what id&#39;s i was deleting or atleast comment them so i know them for future release. OH WELL

I believe there was a combat glitch furthur down the road, i remember a long time ago i found a problem with timers, and i also didn&#39;t add playerFollowing(didn&#39;t host so i didn&#39;t see why i should at the time). not a bug again, but i suggest you fix those.


Download Links: Missing the 100% correctly updated client, uploading atm dw.

[u][i][b]Server(Fixed gs specs and a few others, this is v1.1):[/b][/i][/u]

http://www.mediafire.com/?migoyvm2mim
http://www.mediafire.com/?migoyvm2mim
http://www.mediafire.com/?migoyvm2mim

Mirror:

http://uppit.com/v/EAL9VIAW
http://uppit.com/v/EAL9VIAW
http://uppit.com/v/EAL9VIAW


[u][i][b]Client(This is the working, cleaner client):[/b][/i][/u]

http://uppit.com/v/T8B1JSNC
http://uppit.com/v/T8B1JSNC
http://uppit.com/v/T8B1JSNC


Video Link: 
http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=fRSbQgynk_0
http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=fRSbQgynk_0


Thanks to all the people who downloaded prodigy, again.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 15 Feb 2012 15:11:47 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>General Discussion</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/317-project-fr0z3n-delta-updated-video-special-addition-to-prodigyscape/313817.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>[317] Project Fr0z3n [Delta] [UPDATED] [Video][Special addition to Prodigyscape]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@tannerdanger tannerdanger]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/tannerdanger">@tannerdanger</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>why are there no NPC’s besides the ones in the starting area, and why is almost nothing interactive? did I set something up wrong?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/317-project-fr0z3n-delta-updated-video-special-addition-to-prodigyscape/313817/19">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/317-project-fr0z3n-delta-updated-video-special-addition-to-prodigyscape/313817/19</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 15 Feb 2012 15:11:47 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-313817-19</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/317-project-fr0z3n-delta-updated-video-special-addition-to-prodigyscape/313817.rss">[317] Project Fr0z3n [Delta] [UPDATED] [Video][Special addition to Prodigyscape]</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[317] Project Fr0z3n [Delta] [UPDATED] [Video][Special addition to Prodigyscape]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Andrew_Ferguson The317Guy]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/andrew_ferguson">@Andrew_Ferguson</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“Ix Soulcist xI, post:17, topic:313817”][quote author=Andrew Ferguson link=topic=410315.msg3413002#msg3413002 date=1290849843]<br>
“2mb smaller client”  Mines 60mb smaller <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=5" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"><br>
[/quote]<br>
So what’s the current size of the client now? I don’t remember if it was on the main post or not.[/quote]<br>
27.0 MB, I had to add in a few files so I could fix the fences <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=5" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"> check it out</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/317-project-fr0z3n-delta-updated-video-special-addition-to-prodigyscape/313817/18">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/317-project-fr0z3n-delta-updated-video-special-addition-to-prodigyscape/313817/18</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 27 Nov 2010 09:27:37 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-313817-18</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/317-project-fr0z3n-delta-updated-video-special-addition-to-prodigyscape/313817.rss">[317] Project Fr0z3n [Delta] [UPDATED] [Video][Special addition to Prodigyscape]</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[317] Project Fr0z3n [Delta] [UPDATED] [Video][Special addition to Prodigyscape]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Ix_Soulcist_xI Soulcist]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/ix_soulcist_xi">@Ix_Soulcist_xI</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote no-group quote-modified" data-post="16" data-topic="313817">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 Andrew Ferguson:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>“2mb smaller client”  Mines 60mb smaller <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=5" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"></p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>So what’s the current size of the client now? I don’t remember if it was on the main post or not.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/317-project-fr0z3n-delta-updated-video-special-addition-to-prodigyscape/313817/17">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/317-project-fr0z3n-delta-updated-video-special-addition-to-prodigyscape/313817/17</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 27 Nov 2010 09:25:15 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-313817-17</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/317-project-fr0z3n-delta-updated-video-special-addition-to-prodigyscape/313817.rss">[317] Project Fr0z3n [Delta] [UPDATED] [Video][Special addition to Prodigyscape]</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[317] Project Fr0z3n [Delta] [UPDATED] [Video][Special addition to Prodigyscape]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Andrew_Ferguson The317Guy]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/andrew_ferguson">@Andrew_Ferguson</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>“2mb smaller client”  Mines 60mb smaller <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=5" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/317-project-fr0z3n-delta-updated-video-special-addition-to-prodigyscape/313817/16">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/317-project-fr0z3n-delta-updated-video-special-addition-to-prodigyscape/313817/16</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 27 Nov 2010 09:24:03 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-313817-16</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/317-project-fr0z3n-delta-updated-video-special-addition-to-prodigyscape/313817.rss">[317] Project Fr0z3n [Delta] [UPDATED] [Video][Special addition to Prodigyscape]</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[317] Project Fr0z3n [Delta] [UPDATED] [Video][Special addition to Prodigyscape]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Jddogg9 Jddogg9]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/jddogg9">@Jddogg9</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Leeching kdr. Thanks. (;</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/317-project-fr0z3n-delta-updated-video-special-addition-to-prodigyscape/313817/15">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/317-project-fr0z3n-delta-updated-video-special-addition-to-prodigyscape/313817/15</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 27 Nov 2010 09:04:54 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-313817-15</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/317-project-fr0z3n-delta-updated-video-special-addition-to-prodigyscape/313817.rss">[317] Project Fr0z3n [Delta] [UPDATED] [Video][Special addition to Prodigyscape]</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[317] Project Fr0z3n [Delta] [UPDATED] [Video][Special addition to Prodigyscape]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@mohammad502 mohammad502]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/mohammad502">@mohammad502</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>mirror uppit</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/317-project-fr0z3n-delta-updated-video-special-addition-to-prodigyscape/313817/14">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/317-project-fr0z3n-delta-updated-video-special-addition-to-prodigyscape/313817/14</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 04 Jun 2010 02:36:58 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-313817-14</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/317-project-fr0z3n-delta-updated-video-special-addition-to-prodigyscape/313817.rss">[317] Project Fr0z3n [Delta] [UPDATED] [Video][Special addition to Prodigyscape]</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[317] Project Fr0z3n [Delta] [UPDATED] [Video][Special addition to Prodigyscape]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@angelfallen angelfallen]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/angelfallen">@angelfallen</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>another gd</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/317-project-fr0z3n-delta-updated-video-special-addition-to-prodigyscape/313817/13">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/317-project-fr0z3n-delta-updated-video-special-addition-to-prodigyscape/313817/13</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 May 2010 00:55:29 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-313817-13</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/317-project-fr0z3n-delta-updated-video-special-addition-to-prodigyscape/313817.rss">[317] Project Fr0z3n [Delta] [UPDATED] [Video][Special addition to Prodigyscape]</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[317] Project Fr0z3n [Delta] [UPDATED] [Video][Special addition to Prodigyscape]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@system system]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/system">@system</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>upit…link…doesnt…work.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/317-project-fr0z3n-delta-updated-video-special-addition-to-prodigyscape/313817/12">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/317-project-fr0z3n-delta-updated-video-special-addition-to-prodigyscape/313817/12</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 May 2010 00:38:32 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-313817-12</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/317-project-fr0z3n-delta-updated-video-special-addition-to-prodigyscape/313817.rss">[317] Project Fr0z3n [Delta] [UPDATED] [Video][Special addition to Prodigyscape]</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[317] Project Fr0z3n [Delta] [UPDATED] [Video][Special addition to Prodigyscape]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Andie Andie]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/andie">@Andie</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I started this up in silab client (I’m using as source for my server) and It got to where you first start out, then froze on me.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/317-project-fr0z3n-delta-updated-video-special-addition-to-prodigyscape/313817/11">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/317-project-fr0z3n-delta-updated-video-special-addition-to-prodigyscape/313817/11</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 23 May 2010 19:00:54 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-313817-11</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/317-project-fr0z3n-delta-updated-video-special-addition-to-prodigyscape/313817.rss">[317] Project Fr0z3n [Delta] [UPDATED] [Video][Special addition to Prodigyscape]</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[317] Project Fr0z3n [Delta] [UPDATED] [Video][Special addition to Prodigyscape]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@the1337legend the1337legend]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/the1337legend">@the1337legend</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“Lewis), post:8, topic:313817”][quote author=Epic Purez link=topic=410315.msg3027388#msg3027388 date=1258117513]<br>
This is actually pretty decent, you’ve been promoted to Run3-Server.<br>
[/quote]</p>
<p>Don’t you mean,</p>
<p>Congratulations! You have reached the level which you can fail at programming and join RS.</p>
<p>No, stick to mopar where you kick ass <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/wink.png?v=5" title=":wink:" class="emoji" alt=":wink:"></p>
<p>Good job, please upload pictures as your old topic has had them removed.[/quote]</p>
<p>yh i’m going to get pics later i guess, i just though a vid was better <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=5" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/317-project-fr0z3n-delta-updated-video-special-addition-to-prodigyscape/313817/10">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/317-project-fr0z3n-delta-updated-video-special-addition-to-prodigyscape/313817/10</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 13 Nov 2009 21:20:42 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-313817-10</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/317-project-fr0z3n-delta-updated-video-special-addition-to-prodigyscape/313817.rss">[317] Project Fr0z3n [Delta] [UPDATED] [Video][Special addition to Prodigyscape]</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[317] Project Fr0z3n [Delta] [UPDATED] [Video][Special addition to Prodigyscape]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@jose3121 jose3121]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/jose3121">@jose3121</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>lol im looking for a source to add all my coded stuff from another source into this 1 <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/smiley.png?v=5" title=":smiley:" class="emoji" alt=":smiley:"> so i guess ill use this <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=5" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"> sounds like a good source</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/317-project-fr0z3n-delta-updated-video-special-addition-to-prodigyscape/313817/9">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/317-project-fr0z3n-delta-updated-video-special-addition-to-prodigyscape/313817/9</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 13 Nov 2009 20:57:14 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-313817-9</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/317-project-fr0z3n-delta-updated-video-special-addition-to-prodigyscape/313817.rss">[317] Project Fr0z3n [Delta] [UPDATED] [Video][Special addition to Prodigyscape]</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[317] Project Fr0z3n [Delta] [UPDATED] [Video][Special addition to Prodigyscape]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Lewis3 Lewis)]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/lewis3">@Lewis3</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote no-group quote-modified" data-post="6" data-topic="313817">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 Epic Purez:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>This is actually pretty decent, you’ve been promoted to Run3-Server.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Don’t you mean,</p>
<p>Congratulations! You have reached the level which you can fail at programming and join RS.</p>
<p>No, stick to mopar where you kick ass <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/wink.png?v=5" title=":wink:" class="emoji" alt=":wink:"></p>
<p>Good job, please upload pictures as your old topic has had them removed.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/317-project-fr0z3n-delta-updated-video-special-addition-to-prodigyscape/313817/8">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/317-project-fr0z3n-delta-updated-video-special-addition-to-prodigyscape/313817/8</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 13 Nov 2009 18:28:13 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-313817-8</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/317-project-fr0z3n-delta-updated-video-special-addition-to-prodigyscape/313817.rss">[317] Project Fr0z3n [Delta] [UPDATED] [Video][Special addition to Prodigyscape]</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[317] Project Fr0z3n [Delta] [UPDATED] [Video][Special addition to Prodigyscape]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@the1337legend the1337legend]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/the1337legend">@the1337legend</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>thanks, and what doyou mean promotedto run3 serveR?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/317-project-fr0z3n-delta-updated-video-special-addition-to-prodigyscape/313817/7">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/317-project-fr0z3n-delta-updated-video-special-addition-to-prodigyscape/313817/7</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 13 Nov 2009 16:50:12 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-313817-7</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/317-project-fr0z3n-delta-updated-video-special-addition-to-prodigyscape/313817.rss">[317] Project Fr0z3n [Delta] [UPDATED] [Video][Special addition to Prodigyscape]</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[317] Project Fr0z3n [Delta] [UPDATED] [Video][Special addition to Prodigyscape]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Epic_Purez Epic Purez]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/epic_purez">@Epic_Purez</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>This is actually pretty decent, you’ve been promoted to Run3-Server.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/317-project-fr0z3n-delta-updated-video-special-addition-to-prodigyscape/313817/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/317-project-fr0z3n-delta-updated-video-special-addition-to-prodigyscape/313817/6</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 13 Nov 2009 13:05:13 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-313817-6</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/317-project-fr0z3n-delta-updated-video-special-addition-to-prodigyscape/313817.rss">[317] Project Fr0z3n [Delta] [UPDATED] [Video][Special addition to Prodigyscape]</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[317] Project Fr0z3n [Delta] [UPDATED] [Video][Special addition to Prodigyscape]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@system system]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/system">@system</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Nice Work <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=5" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/317-project-fr0z3n-delta-updated-video-special-addition-to-prodigyscape/313817/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/317-project-fr0z3n-delta-updated-video-special-addition-to-prodigyscape/313817/5</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 13 Nov 2009 07:50:23 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-313817-5</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/317-project-fr0z3n-delta-updated-video-special-addition-to-prodigyscape/313817.rss">[317] Project Fr0z3n [Delta] [UPDATED] [Video][Special addition to Prodigyscape]</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[317] Project Fr0z3n [Delta] [UPDATED] [Video][Special addition to Prodigyscape]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@danny_508 danny 508]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/danny_508">@danny_508</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>wow nice</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/317-project-fr0z3n-delta-updated-video-special-addition-to-prodigyscape/313817/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/317-project-fr0z3n-delta-updated-video-special-addition-to-prodigyscape/313817/4</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 13 Nov 2009 00:54:23 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-313817-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/317-project-fr0z3n-delta-updated-video-special-addition-to-prodigyscape/313817.rss">[317] Project Fr0z3n [Delta] [UPDATED] [Video][Special addition to Prodigyscape]</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[317] Project Fr0z3n [Delta] [UPDATED] [Video][Special addition to Prodigyscape]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@the1337legend the1337legend]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/the1337legend">@the1337legend</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>thanks &lt;3.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/317-project-fr0z3n-delta-updated-video-special-addition-to-prodigyscape/313817/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/317-project-fr0z3n-delta-updated-video-special-addition-to-prodigyscape/313817/3</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 13 Nov 2009 00:51:47 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-313817-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/317-project-fr0z3n-delta-updated-video-special-addition-to-prodigyscape/313817.rss">[317] Project Fr0z3n [Delta] [UPDATED] [Video][Special addition to Prodigyscape]</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[317] Project Fr0z3n [Delta] [UPDATED] [Video][Special addition to Prodigyscape]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@pk3r_john pk3r john]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/pk3r_john">@pk3r_john</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Great server, good job.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/317-project-fr0z3n-delta-updated-video-special-addition-to-prodigyscape/313817/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/317-project-fr0z3n-delta-updated-video-special-addition-to-prodigyscape/313817/2</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 13 Nov 2009 00:51:19 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-313817-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/317-project-fr0z3n-delta-updated-video-special-addition-to-prodigyscape/313817.rss">[317] Project Fr0z3n [Delta] [UPDATED] [Video][Special addition to Prodigyscape]</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[317] Project Fr0z3n [Delta] [UPDATED] [Video][Special addition to Prodigyscape]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@the1337legend the1337legend]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/the1337legend">@the1337legend</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p><img src="http://img21.imageshack.us/img21/4357/mscp.png" alt width="" height=""></p>
<p>Well since i think i’ll get 20k views on Prodigyscape, i did some last minute touch up’s on it and created Project Fr0z3n. :rolleyes:<br>
<span class="bbcode-b"><br>
I will sort this topic out more so it’s easier to read and more organized!<br>
</span><br>
<span class="bbcode-b"><br>
Base:Delta 317. (i used prodigyscape, but it’s delta)<br>
Loading Cache: 377<br>
GameFrame: 474?</span></p>
<p><span class="bbcode-i"><span class="bbcode-b">Client Aspects:</span></span><br>
Loads the Prodigyscape Backround.<br>
Fixed the Gameframe, because it wuz ugly.<br>
Opens your forums (change the link via run.bat, if your using windows, if not simply remove the command line itself to avoid problems).<br>
Has a IpChanger in it, via login screen.<br>
Connects via 127.0.0.1 port 43954 as default.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Side note: Compressed to best quality so it shouldn’t take long to unpack it.</span></p>
<p>For Information on how this is an update server to my old one, please visit the topic link here: <a href="http://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php/topic,382586.0.html" rel="nofollow noopener">http://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php/topic,382586.0.html</a></p>
<p><span class="bbcode-u"><span class="bbcode-i"><span class="bbcode-b">Server General Details!</span></span></span></p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">This server was made about 2 months AFTER Prodigyscape, how ever i did a few touch ups<br>
at the same time i’m typing this sentence as i saw the opportunities. I also felt like the people deserve a update to the shit they downloaded (even if this is still shit, it’s better shit &lt;3).</span></p>
<p>The main concept of this, was to create a One-Of-A-Kind Godwars + A Stable economy/Leveling system, where leveling is benificial and can be fun, and not over-board economy servers where you’d need say, 99 mining to mine open the entrance to get into bandos, things like those i find are UNFAIR, as players who hate skilling, hate mining, and find that as nothing big, because once they do get 99 mining, they can just keep going back and back, with no more excitement, or the challenge to stay in there as long as possible will keep players wanting to go back. The fact i added ALL gwd minibosses was another thing i felt will attract players to keep trying to get to go to gwd and continue wanting to. I also felt that players SHOULD NOT be able to farcast/range npc’s and get them glitched, or mass clan them, and have people bring level 3’s with food to provide for them, i found this was an economy crasher. So i decided to spend the time on adding a npc Multi Hitting system, where a npc has a 1 in 3 chance it will use it. when it uses this, a emote will VERY QUICKLY show up on the player (feel free to change this, it was just a test emote), and all players within a certain radius will get hit within 0-65 damage (i felt this was neccessary to avoid camping, and as well, corporal beast, which is the npc i used for the damage example, maxes 65 in rs, so i stuck with it), HOW EVER there is one small error with this, when you get hit, the damage that shows up, ISNT the damage you will get hit, as i was cbb to figure out how to have it display the hit and deal the damage, as the basic hitDiff didnt work at all, so at the moment, if it displays a 5, yet your hp drops to half, don’t freak out, take it as a hidden bonus to players that go there, as they won’t know for sure what they will get hit.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b"><span class="bbcode-u"><span class="bbcode-i">Client Updates!</span></span></span></p>
<p>-A smaller client about 2mb smaller i believe.</p>
<p>-Removed <span class="bbcode-u"><span class="bbcode-i"><span class="bbcode-b">BASICALLY ALL <em>CUSTOMS</em></span></span></span> as in recolours, this still has things like sigils, hilts etc.</p>
<p>-Added all spirit shields+Sigils+Godswords Hilts+Godsword Blade</p>
<p>-Added 100% ALL GWD Miniboss npc, UNANIMATED, but they have exact names and examine info+correct levels.</p>
<p>-Half the world is SNOW, YAY!?!1111<br>
-A friend told me the snow looks too bright after awile, and deep in the wildy, the black rocks that i cannot remove look disgusting with the white floor, how ever, it’s your opinion.</p>
<p>-This has full godsword stances (Credits to the creator)<br>
-This has All godsword specs (Thanks to the creator)<br>
<span class="bbcode-s">-The godsword specs need fixing however, there is a slight glitch in the bgs/zgs/and/sgs specs, they repeat themselves, so all you need to do is change the emote i’d back to the old ones, which i might do before i upload the files because i can see terror in this topic from all the help posts. I will LEAVE Ags how ever, as it works flawlessly.</span></p>
<p>-This has all pvp armour and weapons+Specs(accurate and hit’s decent, a little to high at the moment i find).<br>
[u][i][b]</p>
<p>[color=red]<span class="bbcode-u"><span class="bbcode-i"><span class="bbcode-b"><br>
Server Updates!</span></span></span>[/color]<br>
[color=blue]<span class="bbcode-b"><br>
Npc and Npc Spawns:</span>[/color]</p>
<p>-The current Arma Gwd area, IS CODED, how ever, i feel that it is… uhm, not as planned, i decided to put it in the ACTUAL Dagganoth lair, as it was open, and i managed to get it coloured white, for the reason that, since i didn’t need to spawn objects, it creates less lagg, feel free to move it’s current spot.</p>
<p>-i forgot to tell you, to get to gwd, use the portals at home, they have the cords set, just edit your character value points so you can use them.</p>
<p>-Added Corporal Beast hitting ALL PLAYERS within 15 radius(either that or 7 i forget), so players that want to Range instead, can avoid getting hit by this (Read below to see bugs on this).</p>
<p>-Was in the process of adding custom 317 GWD Arena’s, via my tut i released a long time ago under client hacking section about changing the floor colour. So far i have full bandos arena, has  working graardor, and all 3 ACTUAL rs mini bosses, only one of the 3 is coded to attack atm i think, that one happens to range players: (NOTE): The mini bosses are NOT animated as i don’t have the skill to animate, so they stay still sadly.</p>
<p>-Added the Wait Till Beside Npc, thx to Lin :3</p>
<p>[color=blue]<span class="bbcode-b">Economy!<br>
</span>[/color]</p>
<p>-Created a tough econamy and Leveling system;<br>
-lvl 3 start off<br>
-Iron + 100k i believe.<br>
-Exp Rate is set VERY low, i believe 4x the hit, not 100% sure i fixed that ages ago, like 4 months ago lol.<br>
-There are no leveling commands<br>
-Training is north of home, away from spawn spot to avoid clutter<br>
-NPC’s only drop low loot, such as black, mith, Addy(rare), steel.<br>
-Previously the portals you’ll see at home were part of a pk point system/Npc points system, if you had 25 kills you could tele to a medium train in the wildy with monsters that dropped more loot, like rune, but you had to have the risk of pkers, but pkers can’t camp seeming that need to kill npc’s to GET there.<br>
-Shops are incomplete, feel free to change what you want.</p>
<p>[color=blue]<span class="bbcode-b">Weapon Specials!</span>[/color]</p>
<p>-Working Dragon Claws ( Actual 4 hitting + randomized hits 90% like rs, just doesn’t have it’s equation to divide the first two hits by two which create the next to hits).<br>
-Fixed ags spec to be more accurate and high hitting (for some reason was only maxing around 50 with full vesta’s etc)<br>
[color=blue]<span class="bbcode-b"><br>
Server Security!</span>[/color]</p>
<p>-Has working bans and mutes, although no Anti syi etc, because i never/could host, so i didn’t need these features. A decent way to avoid spam is to change it so the player starts off muted, and once he gains 1 combat level, he can then talk.<br>
should be ALOT <span class="bbcode-b">less </span>lagg, i havn’t tested the max players…</p>
<p>COMMANDS ARE(basic ones)-[/b][/i][/u]</p>
<p>::beast (corpbeast tele)<br>
::low(a pk area for 1 def pures)<br>
::med(a pk area for zerkers[45 def])<br>
::food(doesnt work in wildy)<br>
::pots(doesnt work in wildy)<br>
::ownyell (a yell command for the owner displays [OWNER] infront of text)<br>
::quests, auto completes quests, use this to use things like veng, as most quest will not work</p>
<p>-I added a ::kdr command, basically the same functions as a 508 ::kdr<br>
i believe this was something fun as well as helpful to add to the server, as i know when i played 508’s the main goal was to see who could get the best kdr spread, and tbh that was the main reason people played. This adds another goal to players to make them want to play.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-u"><span class="bbcode-i"><span class="bbcode-b"><br>
Pvp drops!</span></span></span></p>
<p>I editted them a tad different compared to Prodigyscape, as prodigyscape i believe the drops were too often etc.</p>
<p>So i changed it to getting drops are alot more uncommon, although when you happen to get good loot, there will be more in the drop than there would have been in Prodigyscape.</p>
<ul>
<li>I don’t recall doing anything on drops, other than the basic junk, so you’d have to do this yourself.</li>
</ul>
<p><span class="bbcode-u"><span class="bbcode-i"><span class="bbcode-b">YOUR TURN!</span></span></span></p>
<p>haha, now your like? “oh shit i dun want to read now, i have to do somethings nao D:”, well dw. theres just a few intentional bugs left behind so leechers don’t get 100% privilidges.</p>
<p>As i said before Corp beast doesn’t show it’s proper hits, but you didn’t know that i didnt code the 4 gw monsters to hit all players as well, not really a bug, just a missing piece of data that is vital to a stable gwd system.</p>
<p>I off hand fixed the godsword specs, but i didn’t test, so it’s up to you to tell me IF THEY WORK OR NOT, so if they don’t i can do it the easy way and get my origanal animation id’s back, because i stupidly forgot to save what id’s i was deleting or atleast comment them so i know them for future release. OH WELL</p>
<p>I believe there was a combat glitch furthur down the road, i remember a long time ago i found a problem with timers, and i also didn’t add playerFollowing(didn’t host so i didn’t see why i should at the time). not a bug again, but i suggest you fix those.</p>
<p>Download Links: Missing the 100% correctly updated client, uploading atm dw.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-u"><span class="bbcode-i"><span class="bbcode-b">Server(Fixed gs specs and a few others, this is v1.1):</span></span></span></p>
<p><aside class="onebox whitelistedgeneric">
  <header class="source">
      <img src="http://www.mediafire.com/images/favicon/download.ico" class="site-icon" width="16" height="16">
      <a href="http://www.mediafire.com/file/migoyvm2mim/Pr0ject+Fr0z3n+Wars+Server+RELEASEV1.1.rar" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">MediaFire</a>
  </header>
  <article class="onebox-body">
    <img src="http://static.mediafire.com/images/filetype/download/zip.jpg" class="thumbnail onebox-avatar" width="250" height="250">

<h3><a href="http://www.mediafire.com/file/migoyvm2mim/Pr0ject+Fr0z3n+Wars+Server+RELEASEV1.1.rar" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Pr0ject Fr0z3n Wars Server RELEASEV1.1.rar</a></h3>

<p>MediaFire is a simple to use free service that lets you put all your photos, documents, music, and video in a single place so you can access them anywhere and share them everywhere.</p>


  </article>
  <div class="onebox-metadata">
    
    
  </div>
  <div style="clear: both"></div>
</aside>
<br>
<aside class="onebox whitelistedgeneric">
  <header class="source">
      <img src="http://www.mediafire.com/images/favicon/download.ico" class="site-icon" width="16" height="16">
      <a href="http://www.mediafire.com/file/migoyvm2mim/Pr0ject+Fr0z3n+Wars+Server+RELEASEV1.1.rar" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">MediaFire</a>
  </header>
  <article class="onebox-body">
    <img src="http://static.mediafire.com/images/filetype/download/zip.jpg" class="thumbnail onebox-avatar" width="250" height="250">

<h3><a href="http://www.mediafire.com/file/migoyvm2mim/Pr0ject+Fr0z3n+Wars+Server+RELEASEV1.1.rar" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Pr0ject Fr0z3n Wars Server RELEASEV1.1.rar</a></h3>

<p>MediaFire is a simple to use free service that lets you put all your photos, documents, music, and video in a single place so you can access them anywhere and share them everywhere.</p>


  </article>
  <div class="onebox-metadata">
    
    
  </div>
  <div style="clear: both"></div>
</aside>
<br>
<aside class="onebox whitelistedgeneric">
  <header class="source">
      <img src="http://www.mediafire.com/images/favicon/download.ico" class="site-icon" width="16" height="16">
      <a href="http://www.mediafire.com/file/migoyvm2mim/Pr0ject+Fr0z3n+Wars+Server+RELEASEV1.1.rar" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">MediaFire</a>
  </header>
  <article class="onebox-body">
    <img src="http://static.mediafire.com/images/filetype/download/zip.jpg" class="thumbnail onebox-avatar" width="250" height="250">

<h3><a href="http://www.mediafire.com/file/migoyvm2mim/Pr0ject+Fr0z3n+Wars+Server+RELEASEV1.1.rar" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Pr0ject Fr0z3n Wars Server RELEASEV1.1.rar</a></h3>

<p>MediaFire is a simple to use free service that lets you put all your photos, documents, music, and video in a single place so you can access them anywhere and share them everywhere.</p>


  </article>
  <div class="onebox-metadata">
    
    
  </div>
  <div style="clear: both"></div>
</aside>
</p>
<p>Mirror:</p>
<p><a href="http://uppit.com/v/EAL9VIAW" class="onebox" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">http://uppit.com/v/EAL9VIAW</a><br>
<a href="http://uppit.com/v/EAL9VIAW" class="onebox" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">http://uppit.com/v/EAL9VIAW</a><br>
<a href="http://uppit.com/v/EAL9VIAW" class="onebox" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">http://uppit.com/v/EAL9VIAW</a></p>
<p><span class="bbcode-u"><span class="bbcode-i"><span class="bbcode-b">Client(This is the working, cleaner client):</span></span></span></p>
<p><a href="http://uppit.com/v/T8B1JSNC" class="onebox" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">http://uppit.com/v/T8B1JSNC</a><br>
<a href="http://uppit.com/v/T8B1JSNC" class="onebox" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">http://uppit.com/v/T8B1JSNC</a><br>
<a href="http://uppit.com/v/T8B1JSNC" class="onebox" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">http://uppit.com/v/T8B1JSNC</a></p>
<p>Video Link:<br>
<div class="lazyYT" data-youtube-id="fRSbQgynk_0" data-youtube-title="" data-width="480" data-height="270" data-parameters="feature=oembed&amp;wmode=opaque"></div><br>
<div class="lazyYT" data-youtube-id="fRSbQgynk_0" data-youtube-title="" data-width="480" data-height="270" data-parameters="feature=oembed&amp;wmode=opaque"></div></p>
<p>Thanks to all the people who downloaded prodigy, again.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/317-project-fr0z3n-delta-updated-video-special-addition-to-prodigyscape/313817/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/317-project-fr0z3n-delta-updated-video-special-addition-to-prodigyscape/313817/1</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 12 Nov 2009 02:15:53 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-313817-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/317-project-fr0z3n-delta-updated-video-special-addition-to-prodigyscape/313817.rss">[317] Project Fr0z3n [Delta] [UPDATED] [Video][Special addition to Prodigyscape]</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
