<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>A whole list</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/a-whole-list/216536</link>
    <description>OK. i took a server from some guy. he said it was ok.. i changed everything BUT i want it to be rare to have phats.. the shop sells them.. so how do i take out shops.. npc drops them.. idk how to take npcs out\ change what they drop.. BIGGER PROBLEM. the shop sells ancient staffs &lt; which i dont know how to take out.. and the ancient staffs hit 99s!! how do i change the stat bonus on ancient staff?? what file do i look in ect.. PLEASE HELP. I know where to look so you dont have to say oooh another noob who doesnt know ****. i just need to know where to look .. some1 please help</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 01 Jul 2008 02:04:10 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/a-whole-list/216536.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>A whole list</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Jarbo Jarbo]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/jarbo">@Jarbo</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>OK. i took a server from some guy. he said it was ok… i changed everything BUT i want it to be rare to have phats… the shop sells them… so how do i take out shops… npc drops them… idk how to take npcs out\ change what they drop… BIGGER PROBLEM. the shop sells ancient staffs &lt; which i dont know how to take out… and the ancient staffs hit 99s!! how do i change the stat bonus on ancient staff?? what file do i look in ect… PLEASE HELP. I know where to look so you dont have to say oooh another noob who doesnt know ****. i just need to know where to look … some1 please help</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/a-whole-list/216536/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/a-whole-list/216536/1</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jul 2008 02:04:10 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-216536-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/a-whole-list/216536.rss">A whole list</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
