<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>I need help</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/i-need-help/201795</link>
    <description>Okay,the part I need help on is how to add stuff to my server. I&#39;ve been wanting to know how to add stuff onto my server. All the other times I had my server I never edited it but I want to edit it now, cause I&#39;ve seen other people post stuff on moparscape serverstatus that says: something on the server is in Construction. When I go to other server&#39;s at the top of the screen it says: Castle Wars in Construction. I want other people to be excited to play my server. The server I have now is just a plain server, I haven&#39;t added nothing to the server. But when I try to add things it never be on the screen or in my server. I can never change the name of screen it says: server created by: Caden but it always says the person that created the source. When I want to add something to my server it never says it on the screen. So when like other people log on my server they can see the updates that I did to the server. But the problem is that I really want to add stuff to my server like Castle Wars and God wars to get god sword&#39;s. If anybody could help me do that I would really appreciate it if they do. but can some people post how to add thing&#39;s to my server.


                                          Here&#39;s Another Thing I Want To Ask:
 



Can someone tell me how to stop me from lagging out of my own server cause:

When I log on my server, &quot;I can&#39;t move&quot;, &quot;I can&#39;t stay logged in&quot;, I only stay logged in for like 1 minute then it says: &quot;Please Wait&quot;, &quot;Waiting To Reestablish&quot;. Why is this happening to me Do I need a new computer or something?


                                                    Please Reply.

                                               Thanks, Colgi</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 22 Apr 2008 10:20:34 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/i-need-help/201795.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>I need help</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@T-R-A-V-I-S T-R-A-V-I-S]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/t-r-a-v-i-s">@T-R-A-V-I-S</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>lol dude this is the simpilist thing</p>
<p>go to client.java<br>
ctrl+f<br>
search for<br>
makeGlobalObject</p>
<p>add what you want find item ids at <a href="http://runelocus.com" rel="nofollow noopener">runelocus.com</a></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/i-need-help/201795/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/i-need-help/201795/2</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 22 Apr 2008 10:20:34 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-201795-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/i-need-help/201795.rss">I need help</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>I need help</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Colgi Colgi]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/colgi">@Colgi</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Okay,the part I need help on is how to add stuff to my server. I’ve been wanting to know how to add stuff onto my server. All the other times I had my server I never edited it but I want to edit it now, cause I’ve seen other people post stuff on moparscape serverstatus that says: something on the server is in Construction. When I go to other server’s at the top of the screen it says: Castle Wars in Construction. I want other people to be excited to play my server. The server I have now is just a plain server, I haven’t added nothing to the server. But when I try to add things it never be on the screen or in my server. I can never change the name of screen it says: server created by: Caden but it always says the person that created the source. When I want to add something to my server it never says it on the screen. So when like other people log on my server they can see the updates that I did to the server. But the problem is that I really want to add stuff to my server like Castle Wars and God wars to get god sword’s. If anybody could help me do that I would really appreciate it if they do. but can some people post how to add thing’s to my server.</p>
<pre><code>                                      Here's Another Thing I Want To Ask:
</code></pre>
<p>Can someone tell me how to stop me from lagging out of my own server cause:</p>
<p>When I log on my server, “I can’t move”, “I can’t stay logged in”, I only stay logged in for like 1 minute then it says: “Please Wait”, “Waiting To Reestablish”. Why is this happening to me Do I need a new computer or something?</p>
<pre><code>                                                Please Reply.

                                           Thanks, Colgi</code></pre>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/i-need-help/201795/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/i-need-help/201795/1</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 22 Apr 2008 03:26:15 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-201795-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/i-need-help/201795.rss">I need help</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
