<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>SvenScap3pk v2</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/svenscap3pk-v2/61375</link>
    <description>Alright here is the problem.

It uses Miss. Silabsofts Server Console.
It let&#39;s me play and other users connect and play.
But randomly, (no certain time), I try and log in and it says, &quot;error connecting to server...&quot; while I can still see other players signed on in my server. I checked the ips.xml for the ban and only 
[glow=red,2,300]127.0.0.1 [/glow] 
and 
[glow=red,2,300]65.34.4.204[/glow]
are banned.
When I first started, they were not there. I removed these, (yes, I know how to do this correctly), and I try to log back in, it&#39;s reset again and still says, &quot;&quot;error connecting to server...&quot; I also tried to access that account from a neighbors house, and it works. Sometimes, it says on the Run Server.Bat Script (yes tried different startup versions *correctly formated ones*), player is already logged in, but it doesn&#39;t show that to me, just the, &quot;error connecting to server&quot;. Also, it sometimes happens to other players, for they have posted on my forums and notified me of this. Please any and all help would be apreciated.

Thanks,

[b][u][glow=red,2,300]bl4ck ra1nb0w[/glow][/u][/b]</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 24 Feb 2007 03:07:49 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/svenscap3pk-v2/61375.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>SvenScap3pk v2</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@bl4ck_ra1nb0w bl4ck ra1nb0w]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/bl4ck_ra1nb0w">@bl4ck_ra1nb0w</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Alright here is the problem.</p>
<p>It uses Miss. Silabsofts Server Console.<br>
It let’s me play and other users connect and play.<br>
But randomly, (no certain time), I try and log in and it says, “error connecting to server…” while I can still see other players signed on in my server. I checked the ips.xml for the ban and only<br>
[glow=red,2,300]127.0.0.1 [/glow]<br>
and<br>
[glow=red,2,300]65.34.4.204[/glow]<br>
are banned.<br>
When I first started, they were not there. I removed these, (yes, I know how to do this correctly), and I try to log back in, it’s reset again and still says, "“error connecting to server…” I also tried to access that account from a neighbors house, and it works. Sometimes, it says on the Run Server.Bat Script (yes tried different startup versions <em>correctly formated ones</em>), player is already logged in, but it doesn’t show that to me, just the, “error connecting to server”. Also, it sometimes happens to other players, for they have posted on my forums and notified me of this. Please any and all help would be apreciated.</p>
<p>Thanks,</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b"><span class="bbcode-u">[glow=red,2,300]bl4ck ra1nb0w[/glow]</span></span></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/svenscap3pk-v2/61375/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/svenscap3pk-v2/61375/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 24 Feb 2007 03:07:49 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-61375-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/svenscap3pk-v2/61375.rss">SvenScap3pk v2</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
