<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Capescape Reborn - Need Ideas</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/capescape-reborn-need-ideas/156013</link>
    <description>Hello, when I started RSPS, I played on a server called Capescape. It was awesome. It was the one server that stuck in my head as a great server with a good balance between PK and NPC based fighting. It also had a good economy. However, at the time, Miss.Silabsoft had only just released her client and the server was lacking somewhat. Well, I&#39;ve decided to remake it, without permission from the unknown owner. So far, I havn&#39;t done that much, but it&#39;s a working progress. I ask anyone that reads this to make a contribution to what you think makes a cool server.

[b]So far:[/b]
 - I&#39;ve added the combat skillcapes. It was made from a basic source so I&#39;ve had to make it Silabs compatible myself. I has, as far as I know, no skills yet. I&#39;m working on adding as many of those as I can.
 - Skillcape emotes. Added all the emotes for the combat skillcapes. Look forward to doing the rest, they we&#39;re fun.
 - Added a few more NPC&#39;s to kill.
 - Added some shops.
 - Added Bandos and Armadyl armour. They have proper stats from Runescape. In the shop, to keep teh economy good, they cost a lot. So that you&#39;ll have to do a lot of NPC killing to get them.
 - Fixed a bug in the PK zone. Otherwise players get trapped in fence when they use ancients.
- Godswords hit properly.

[b]Already added:[/b]
 - God spells were already all working when I got the source, so they&#39;re on there. Other spells all working, I think.
 - Ancient barrage spells all work. This includes multi-target. I&#39;ve seen a massive lack in servers with this added.

I just need some more ideas really. If you don&#39;t have anything constructive to say, don&#39;t post at all please.

[b]Screenies:[/b]
[IMG]http://i226.photobucket.com/albums/dd98/Exgenia/Skillcape.gif[/img]
[IMG]http://i226.photobucket.com/albums/dd98/Exgenia/Godsword.gif[/img]

There are more to come...</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 01 Nov 2007 18:50:08 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/capescape-reborn-need-ideas/156013.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Capescape Reborn - Need Ideas</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@1st_Areo8 1st Areo8]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/1st_areo8">@1st_Areo8</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I have two questions.<br>
1.) How do you add proper attack emotes to NPC’s? I know there was a tut a while ago.</p>
<p>2.) Adding Stats to weapons/armour?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/capescape-reborn-need-ideas/156013/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/capescape-reborn-need-ideas/156013/2</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 01 Nov 2007 18:50:08 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-156013-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/capescape-reborn-need-ideas/156013.rss">Capescape Reborn - Need Ideas</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Capescape Reborn - Need Ideas</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Syrillia Syrillia]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/syrillia">@Syrillia</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Hello, when I started RSPS, I played on a server called Capescape. It was awesome. It was the one server that stuck in my head as a great server with a good balance between PK and NPC based fighting. It also had a good economy. However, at the time, Miss.Silabsoft had only just released her client and the server was lacking somewhat. Well, I’ve decided to remake it, without permission from the unknown owner. So far, I havn’t done that much, but it’s a working progress. I ask anyone that reads this to make a contribution to what you think makes a cool server.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">So far:</span></p>
<ul>
<li>I’ve added the combat skillcapes. It was made from a basic source so I’ve had to make it Silabs compatible myself. I has, as far as I know, no skills yet. I’m working on adding as many of those as I can.</li>
<li>Skillcape emotes. Added all the emotes for the combat skillcapes. Look forward to doing the rest, they we’re fun.</li>
<li>Added a few more NPC’s to kill.</li>
<li>Added some shops.</li>
<li>Added Bandos and Armadyl armour. They have proper stats from Runescape. In the shop, to keep teh economy good, they cost a lot. So that you’ll have to do a lot of NPC killing to get them.</li>
<li>Fixed a bug in the PK zone. Otherwise players get trapped in fence when they use ancients.</li>
<li>Godswords hit properly.</li>
</ul>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Already added:</span></p>
<ul>
<li>God spells were already all working when I got the source, so they’re on there. Other spells all working, I think.</li>
<li>Ancient barrage spells all work. This includes multi-target. I’ve seen a massive lack in servers with this added.</li>
</ul>
<p>I just need some more ideas really. If you don’t have anything constructive to say, don’t post at all please.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Screenies:</span><br>
<img src="http://i226.photobucket.com/albums/dd98/Exgenia/Skillcape.gif" alt width="" height=""><br>
<img src="http://i226.photobucket.com/albums/dd98/Exgenia/Godsword.gif" alt width="" height=""></p>
<p>There are more to come…</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/capescape-reborn-need-ideas/156013/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/capescape-reborn-need-ideas/156013/1</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 01 Nov 2007 17:51:54 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-156013-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/capescape-reborn-need-ideas/156013.rss">Capescape Reborn - Need Ideas</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
