<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>[RuneSource] Password bug [help]</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/runesource-password-bug-help/480443</link>
    <description>Hello, so I have been messing with a RuneSource based source and I have to say that I&#39;m really enjoying using RuneSource. Anyway, so I have been working around with some things and fixing some bugs but for some reason, when I log out i successfully save the character file, but when i log back in I can literally change the password to anything. I know there&#39;s a similar bug on other RuneSource bases that you can log in and log in again and the password changes, but this is even worse that it doesnt actually check the password in the first place. I have tried to fix this but i still find bugs.

In my player.java i have this:
[CODE]        if (username.length() &lt; 1 || username.length() &gt; 12 || password.length() &lt; 5 || password.length() &gt; 20) {
            setReturnCode(Constants.LOGIN_RESPONSE_INVALID_CREDENTIALS);
            return false;[/CODE]
Well basically this checks if your username is under 1 or over 12 characters long, and checks if your password is under 5 or under 20 characters long, Obviously...
Well this works quite well to be honest. I thought to my self, maybe I could add something similar to:
[CODE]if (!player.getPassword().equals(password)) {
setReturnCode(Constants.LOGIN_RESPONSE_INVALID_CREDENTIALS);
return false;[/CODE]
In my mind that should work, right?
But if i add a &quot;System.out.println(player.getPassword());&quot; I get the output of &quot;null&quot;.
So i decided to check in PlayerSave.java in &quot;readFile()&quot;
I added:
[CODE]            System.out.println(&quot;Loaded &quot;+player.getUsername()+ &quot;&#39;s character file with Password: &quot;+password+&quot; from Host: &quot;+connectionHost);[/CODE]
Now this actually outputs the players password from the file correctly.
The &quot;password&quot; is read from this string:
[CODE]            String password = load.readUTF();
 [/CODE]
so i was wondering if i could add something like:
[CODE]            player.setPassword(load.readUTF());[/CODE]
So that I can access the information that is read from the character file and use it in the password check.
I hope this makes sense to someone and could help me fix this. :) Oh and its nothing I&#39;ve done to the source thats caused this, I have used a fresh copy to make sure I didn&#39;t jack something up while modifying :)

Edit: I&#39;ve just realised that this probably wouldn&#39;t work as this is returning your request to false so the players file is not even loaded.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 28 Jan 2013 18:32:39 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/runesource-password-bug-help/480443.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>[RuneSource] Password bug [help]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@ProTayToe ProTayToe]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/protaytoe">@ProTayToe</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Hello, so I have been messing with a RuneSource based source and I have to say that I’m really enjoying using RuneSource. Anyway, so I have been working around with some things and fixing some bugs but for some reason, when I log out i successfully save the character file, but when i log back in I can literally change the password to anything. I know there’s a similar bug on other RuneSource bases that you can log in and log in again and the password changes, but this is even worse that it doesnt actually check the password in the first place. I have tried to fix this but i still find bugs.</p>
<p>In my player.java i have this:</p>
<p><code>        if (username.length() &lt; 1 || username.length() &gt; 12 || password.length() &lt; 5 || password.length() &gt; 20) {
            setReturnCode(Constants.LOGIN_RESPONSE_INVALID_CREDENTIALS);
            return false;</code><br>
Well basically this checks if your username is under 1 or over 12 characters long, and checks if your password is under 5 or under 20 characters long, Obviously…<br>
Well this works quite well to be honest. I thought to my self, maybe I could add something similar to:</p>
<p><code>if (!player.getPassword().equals(password)) {
setReturnCode(Constants.LOGIN_RESPONSE_INVALID_CREDENTIALS);
return false;</code><br>
In my mind that should work, right?<br>
But if i add a “System.out.println(player.getPassword());” I get the output of “null”.<br>
So i decided to check in PlayerSave.java in “readFile()”<br>
I added:</p>
<pre><code class="lang-auto"></code></pre>
<p>Now this actually outputs the players password from the file correctly.<br>
The “password” is read from this string:</p>
<p><code>            String password = load.readUTF();
 </code><br>
so i was wondering if i could add something like:</p>
<pre><code class="lang-auto"></code></pre>
<p>So that I can access the information that is read from the character file and use it in the password check.<br>
I hope this makes sense to someone and could help me fix this. <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=5" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"> Oh and its nothing I’ve done to the source thats caused this, I have used a fresh copy to make sure I didn’t jack something up while modifying <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=5" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
<p>Edit: I’ve just realised that this probably wouldn’t work as this is returning your request to false so the players file is not even loaded.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/runesource-password-bug-help/480443/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/runesource-password-bug-help/480443/1</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 28 Jan 2013 18:32:39 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-480443-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/runesource-password-bug-help/480443.rss">[RuneSource] Password bug [help]</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
