<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>[317/Delta] Spawning Error</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/317-delta-spawning-error/375757</link>
    <description>Alright, well for the passed day or so i&#39;ve &#39;been trying to figure out WHY i can&#39;t add my sword to my server. I&#39;ve tryed to add it on 3 or so different sources with no luck, and even my mate who&#39;s more intelectual then me in java wasn&#39;t able to add it to his.

I&#39;ve searched the forums, looked at a shittonne of guides, but still when i do &quot;::pickup 14832 1&quot; (my swords code, i&#39;ve tryed changing it about 10 times or so, still didn&#39;t do anything) all it does is null my client/account. I&#39;ve tried changing the model numbers, so it doesn&#39;t interfere with others, I&#39;ve tried changing the spawn code, and I&#39;ve  also tried using multiple ints, with still no luck.

I&#39;ve added 5 or so other items with no trouble at all, but this sword, i seem to be having a very hard time with. So what i want to know is, did i do something wrong while making it? Was it made too complex with too many faces or something? If anyone could explain why i&#39;m un-able to add it into my server, so that i could maybe fix the problem, it would be much appreciated. I spent a good 10 hours making this sword, and it would suck to have all that time go to waste.  :|

I also made it .Dat, then Gziped it, and i&#39;ve re-tried to do this a tonne of times, i have no clue why its not working. :/

Ints i used:
[code]if(i == 14783)  // change this if you need to &quot;item number&quot;
{
class8.aStringArray189 = new String[5];
class8.aStringArray189[1] = &quot;Wield&quot;;//New option
class8.anInt174 = 14519; //
class8.aBoolean176 = false;//Stackable
class8.anInt181 = 2000;
class8.anInt190 = 552;
class8.anInt198 = 28;
class8.anInt169 = 0;
class8.anInt194 = 2;
class8.anInt204 = 28;
class8.anInt165 = 14518;//male wearing
class8.anInt200 = 14518;//female wearing
class8.anInt204 = 28;
class8.anInt175 = -1;//Unknown
class8.anInt164 = -1;//Female arms/sleeves
class8.anInt188 = -1;//male arms/sleeves
class8.aBoolean176 = false;//Stackable
class8.aString170 = &quot;CND Blade&quot;;//Name of the new item
class8.aByteArray178 = &quot;Made by Joey&quot;.getBytes();//examin info
}[/code]

CNDbladeW=14518
CNDbladeD=14519


Here it is, if this helps any.
[img]http://www.imagehosting.gr/out.php/i1489882_sword10.jpg[/img]</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 30 Dec 2010 02:02:27 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Game Development</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/317-delta-spawning-error/375757.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>[317/Delta] Spawning Error</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@tehbomb tehbomb]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/tehbomb">@tehbomb</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Alright, well for the passed day or so i’ve 'been trying to figure out WHY i can’t add my sword to my server. I’ve tryed to add it on 3 or so different sources with no luck, and even my mate who’s more intelectual then me in java wasn’t able to add it to his.</p>
<p>I’ve searched the forums, looked at a shittonne of guides, but still when i do “::pickup 14832 1” (my swords code, i’ve tryed changing it about 10 times or so, still didn’t do anything) all it does is null my client/account. I’ve tried changing the model numbers, so it doesn’t interfere with others, I’ve tried changing the spawn code, and I’ve  also tried using multiple ints, with still no luck.</p>
<p>I’ve added 5 or so other items with no trouble at all, but this sword, i seem to be having a very hard time with. So what i want to know is, did i do something wrong while making it? Was it made too complex with too many faces or something? If anyone could explain why i’m un-able to add it into my server, so that i could maybe fix the problem, it would be much appreciated. I spent a good 10 hours making this sword, and it would suck to have all that time go to waste.  <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/expressionless.png?v=5" title=":expressionless:" class="emoji" alt=":expressionless:"></p>
<p>I also made it .Dat, then Gziped it, and i’ve re-tried to do this a tonne of times, i have no clue why its not working. <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/confused.png?v=5" title=":confused:" class="emoji" alt=":confused:"></p>
<p>Ints i used:</p>
<p><code>if(i == 14783)  // change this if you need to "item number"
{
class8.aStringArray189 = new String[5];
class8.aStringArray189[1] = "Wield";//New option
class8.anInt174 = 14519; //
class8.aBoolean176 = false;//Stackable
class8.anInt181 = 2000;
class8.anInt190 = 552;
class8.anInt198 = 28;
class8.anInt169 = 0;
class8.anInt194 = 2;
class8.anInt204 = 28;
class8.anInt165 = 14518;//male wearing
class8.anInt200 = 14518;//female wearing
class8.anInt204 = 28;
class8.anInt175 = -1;//Unknown
class8.anInt164 = -1;//Female arms/sleeves
class8.anInt188 = -1;//male arms/sleeves
class8.aBoolean176 = false;//Stackable
class8.aString170 = "CND Blade";//Name of the new item
class8.aByteArray178 = "Made by Joey".getBytes();//examin info
}</code></p>
<p>CNDbladeW=14518<br>
CNDbladeD=14519</p>
<p>Here it is, if this helps any.<br>
<img src="http://www.imagehosting.gr/out.php/i1489882_sword10.jpg" alt width="" height=""></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/317-delta-spawning-error/375757/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/317-delta-spawning-error/375757/1</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 30 Dec 2010 02:02:27 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-375757-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/317-delta-spawning-error/375757.rss">[317/Delta] Spawning Error</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
