<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>New to this stuff, a few questions regarding clients</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-to-this-stuff-a-few-questions-regarding-clients/529472</link>
    <description>So as the title states I&#39;m new to this private server stuff, I don&#39;t really intend to make one as such for people to play, I&#39;m more of a tinkerer doing my own thing, I&#39;m only interested about the game&#39;s inner workings, however I&#39;m rather confused about something, is the first version of Runescape 2 the latest that can be used for Private Servers? I could have sworn I saw screenshots showing a private server using the revamped version of the game with the current models etc.

Am I just blind or what? So far looking around hasn&#39;t been very helpful as most things are labeled in a way that don&#39;t make it very easy to tell what version the game you&#39;re using, so working out what the client does/doesn&#39;t have isn&#39;t very simple.

If there is a version of the client available that uses most of the current stuff, I would very much appreciate being pointed to it.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 08 Sep 2013 00:01:39 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Game Development</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-to-this-stuff-a-few-questions-regarding-clients/529472.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>New to this stuff, a few questions regarding clients</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Null_Amount N_A]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/null_amount">@Null_Amount</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Everything in the <a href="http://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php/board,49.0.html" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">Server Downloads</a> section is from the RS2 era. The numbers you sometimes see is the revision (317, 474, 525, etc.), the larger the number, the newer the revision. If you’re looking for some of the more modern versions of RuneScape, try looking for revisions that are in the 700s.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-to-this-stuff-a-few-questions-regarding-clients/529472/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-to-this-stuff-a-few-questions-regarding-clients/529472/2</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 08 Sep 2013 00:01:39 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-529472-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-to-this-stuff-a-few-questions-regarding-clients/529472.rss">New to this stuff, a few questions regarding clients</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>New to this stuff, a few questions regarding clients</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Wulfharth Wulfharth]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/wulfharth">@Wulfharth</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>So as the title states I’m new to this private server stuff, I don’t really intend to make one as such for people to play, I’m more of a tinkerer doing my own thing, I’m only interested about the game’s inner workings, however I’m rather confused about something, is the first version of Runescape 2 the latest that can be used for Private Servers? I could have sworn I saw screenshots showing a private server using the revamped version of the game with the current models etc.</p>
<p>Am I just blind or what? So far looking around hasn’t been very helpful as most things are labeled in a way that don’t make it very easy to tell what version the game you’re using, so working out what the client does/doesn’t have isn’t very simple.</p>
<p>If there is a version of the client available that uses most of the current stuff, I would very much appreciate being pointed to it.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-to-this-stuff-a-few-questions-regarding-clients/529472/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-to-this-stuff-a-few-questions-regarding-clients/529472/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 07 Sep 2013 22:26:15 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-529472-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-to-this-stuff-a-few-questions-regarding-clients/529472.rss">New to this stuff, a few questions regarding clients</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
