<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Timers for tru3scape source?</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/timers-for-tru3scape-source/177263</link>
    <description>ok.. i have a tru3scape source and ive tried so many differnt things to stop massing... and the main 1 every one tells me is to change the actiontimer....

ive spent hours change them from 0 - as high as 500 and nothing ever makes a differnce...

is there anything anyone knows that would help me out? to make timers more real like rs instead of being able to spam it...

I don&#39;t need help setting a timer for objects those work when i set them for skills and stuff but....When fighting a player or a npc you can mass and when i change the timer on those it don&#39;t do nothing..

As for the message thing that will just say &quot;Stop massing&quot; I don&#39;t want that. i want it to acually not let you mass o.0.... like on i think it&#39;s called czar you can&#39;t mass while fighting a npc or pvp.


im a bit confussing... sorry but the what i am saying is i want to stop massing for pking and attacking npcs... not objects, or any other skill they all work when i mess with the timers.. any help?</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 31 Jan 2008 05:40:09 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/timers-for-tru3scape-source/177263.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Timers for tru3scape source?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@omgwater omgwater]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/omgwater">@omgwater</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>ok… i have a tru3scape source and ive tried so many differnt things to stop massing… and the main 1 every one tells me is to change the actiontimer…</p>
<p>ive spent hours change them from 0 - as high as 500 and nothing ever makes a differnce…</p>
<p>is there anything anyone knows that would help me out? to make timers more real like rs instead of being able to spam it…</p>
<p>I don’t need help setting a timer for objects those work when i set them for skills and stuff but…When fighting a player or a npc you can mass and when i change the timer on those it don’t do nothing…</p>
<p>As for the message thing that will just say “Stop massing” I don’t want that. i want it to acually not let you mass o.0… like on i think it’s called czar you can’t mass while fighting a npc or pvp.</p>
<p>im a bit confussing… sorry but the what i am saying is i want to stop massing for pking and attacking npcs… not objects, or any other skill they all work when i mess with the timers… any help?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/timers-for-tru3scape-source/177263/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/timers-for-tru3scape-source/177263/1</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jan 2008 05:40:09 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-177263-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/timers-for-tru3scape-source/177263.rss">Timers for tru3scape source?</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
