<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Suicidal Heroism Part 1</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/suicidal-heroism-part-1/340845</link>
    <description>Bill sat down on a wooden crate, exhausted after having escaped from the infected military base. As it turned out, there truly was nowhere to escape to--no one could withstand the wrath of the infected. They were safe now, inside of a safehouse, but how long did that really last? There was always somewhere to run to, always somewhere to go. Couldn&#39;t he finally just be safe, no longer needing to shoot at the enemy? It reminded him too much of his &#39;nam days, terrified every second of the way. He chuckled to himself. At least there ain&#39;t camouflaged pitfalls out here!


Louis came over and handed Bill some nutritional pills. Bill sighed. He hated those pills. They had such a horrible taste, like some kid had taken every sour flavor and mashed them together in a bowl. At least they had a remarkable rejuvenating quality--a single pop could redouble one&#39;s efforts. It had saved him countless times in this hellhole, once even during the escape from the military outpost. A smoker had grabbed him, far away from the survivors. It was constricting him, not relenting no matter how hard he hit it. He could feel his ribs bending; he had to do something. In a stroke of genius, he reached for his pills in his pocket--hopefully there were still there. They HAD to be there! YES! They were there! He quickly unscrewed the lid and grabbed a pill. With a wince, he opened his mouth and downed it, feeling a rush of energy as he did so. In an instant, he had knocked the smoker out with a few quick blows. He ran towards where he thought the other survivors were. Unfortunately, he had gotten turned around, instead going in the opposite direction.


He ran down the hall, yelling their names in fear. It was not good to be alone in this place--there were too many ways he could die. A simple Hunter pounce and it was all over. Suddenly, he heard a high pitched shrieking, unlike any other infected sound he had ever heard. He slowed his run to a slow paced walk, checking every corner for a possible infected attack. Suddenly, from behind him, he heard an odd sound--almost like a spitting noise. Something whistled past his head and hit the wall straight in front of him. It was a green fluid, bubbling viciously. He turned around and, taking almost no time to aim, shot at the infected, killing it where it stood. He smirked. These guys went down easier than those assholes at &#39;nam! Turning around, he want to open the door--and then froze. Where the green fluid had hit, there was absolutely no wall anymore. He staggered back in disbelief. How had that fluid completely corroded the wall?! If that had hit his head...no, best not to think of such things.

He walked through the opening, into a large dining area. It was a mess; tables were overturned, plates were shattered on the floor, utensils were stuck in bodies and pots and pans were scattered everywhere. The smell of death loomed over the area--but then again, where did it not? These days, nowhere was safe. Nothing was sacred to these...these monsters. He explored the dining hall, checking the bodies for weapons. He found nothing, sighing in disappointment. He jerked at the sound of a loud, ominous yelling. It sounded...almost human. Was it german? Oh well. It was best to think of the things that did matter, such as what was making that noise. He looked the side and saw, over at the far end of the dining area, a large figure. It had a massive arm, almost the size of its torso. Its other arm was smaller than a baby&#39;s arm. He shot at it, yelling curses and taunts. It simply brushed the bullets off and then started to charge at him! Bill gasped, unable to move in terror. It screamed a loud, deep scream. 

At the last instance, before the...thing reached Bill, he jumped onto a table to the side. It ran past him, crashing into a table. It flipped over the table and landed on a body that was particularly laden with forks and knives. Even though they were on the dull sides, they cut through its body--killing it slowly, while it screamed in pain. Bill carefully aimed his M4 at it and shot a single bullet, hitting it in the head. He smirked, then stepped off the table and started to walk near the door. As he did so, he heard giggling. He sighed. Not another new creature he thought, readying his weapon. He approached the hallway, checking all his corners. There was nothing there. He then stepped out into the hallway carefully. Nothing. Sighing in relief, he lowered his weapon. As he did so, the giggling repeated--only this time it was coming from his feet! He slowly looked down and saw a hunched over creature the size of a small dog. He attempted to shoot at it, but the creature seized his weapon and threw it against the wall. It jumped at him, landing on his head. Screaming, Bill stumbled around, trying to get the thing off of him. It seemed to be trying to...direct Bill somehow. Suddenly, an immense pain shot through his neck. It felt like his head was being wrenched off of his body! He screamed again, trying to knocked the creature against the wall. As he stumbled around, he heard Zoey yell something in the distance. 
&quot;Help! Something...else has me!!&quot;, he screamed in anxiety and relief. Gunshots sounded, and he heard the whiz of bullets flying past his head. 
&quot;Don&#39;t shoot me!!&quot;, he screamed, terrified of dying not from the infected, but his own friends. Suddenly, the giggling stopped, and the creature fell off his body.
&quot;Oh thank god!&quot; Bill yelled, relieved to be back with his teammates.
&quot;Bill, there&#39;s no time for talking! We found something important--


Bill&#39;s flashback was interrupted by Zoey handing him his gun.
&quot;Come on, old man. It&#39;s time to go&quot;

Bill snatched the gun from her, irritated that she had called him old man. He walked to the safe room door and wrenched off the bar.
&quot;Kill all sons of bitches!&quot;, he said, grinning. He rushed outside, screaming at the infected.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 21 May 2010 14:23:27 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>General Discussion</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/suicidal-heroism-part-1/340845.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Suicidal Heroism Part 1</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@NewbieNewty Newty]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/newbienewty">@NewbieNewty</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Needs more sex</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/suicidal-heroism-part-1/340845/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/suicidal-heroism-part-1/340845/2</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 21 May 2010 14:23:27 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-340845-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/suicidal-heroism-part-1/340845.rss">Suicidal Heroism Part 1</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Suicidal Heroism Part 1</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@geel9 geel9]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/geel9">@geel9</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Bill sat down on a wooden crate, exhausted after having escaped from the infected military base. As it turned out, there truly was nowhere to escape to–no one could withstand the wrath of the infected. They were safe now, inside of a safehouse, but how long did that really last? There was always somewhere to run to, always somewhere to go. Couldn’t he finally just be safe, no longer needing to shoot at the enemy? It reminded him too much of his 'nam days, terrified every second of the way. He chuckled to himself. At least there ain’t camouflaged pitfalls out here!</p>
<p>Louis came over and handed Bill some nutritional pills. Bill sighed. He hated those pills. They had such a horrible taste, like some kid had taken every sour flavor and mashed them together in a bowl. At least they had a remarkable rejuvenating quality–a single pop could redouble one’s efforts. It had saved him countless times in this hellhole, once even during the escape from the military outpost. A smoker had grabbed him, far away from the survivors. It was constricting him, not relenting no matter how hard he hit it. He could feel his ribs bending; he had to do something. In a stroke of genius, he reached for his pills in his pocket–hopefully there were still there. They HAD to be there! YES! They were there! He quickly unscrewed the lid and grabbed a pill. With a wince, he opened his mouth and downed it, feeling a rush of energy as he did so. In an instant, he had knocked the smoker out with a few quick blows. He ran towards where he thought the other survivors were. Unfortunately, he had gotten turned around, instead going in the opposite direction.</p>
<p>He ran down the hall, yelling their names in fear. It was not good to be alone in this place–there were too many ways he could die. A simple Hunter pounce and it was all over. Suddenly, he heard a high pitched shrieking, unlike any other infected sound he had ever heard. He slowed his run to a slow paced walk, checking every corner for a possible infected attack. Suddenly, from behind him, he heard an odd sound–almost like a spitting noise. Something whistled past his head and hit the wall straight in front of him. It was a green fluid, bubbling viciously. He turned around and, taking almost no time to aim, shot at the infected, killing it where it stood. He smirked. These guys went down easier than those assholes at 'nam! Turning around, he want to open the door–and then froze. Where the green fluid had hit, there was absolutely no wall anymore. He staggered back in disbelief. How had that fluid completely corroded the wall?! If that had hit his head…no, best not to think of such things.</p>
<p>He walked through the opening, into a large dining area. It was a mess; tables were overturned, plates were shattered on the floor, utensils were stuck in bodies and pots and pans were scattered everywhere. The smell of death loomed over the area–but then again, where did it not? These days, nowhere was safe. Nothing was sacred to these…these monsters. He explored the dining hall, checking the bodies for weapons. He found nothing, sighing in disappointment. He jerked at the sound of a loud, ominous yelling. It sounded…almost human. Was it german? Oh well. It was best to think of the things that did matter, such as what was making that noise. He looked the side and saw, over at the far end of the dining area, a large figure. It had a massive arm, almost the size of its torso. Its other arm was smaller than a baby’s arm. He shot at it, yelling curses and taunts. It simply brushed the bullets off and then started to charge at him! Bill gasped, unable to move in terror. It screamed a loud, deep scream.</p>
<p>At the last instance, before the…thing reached Bill, he jumped onto a table to the side. It ran past him, crashing into a table. It flipped over the table and landed on a body that was particularly laden with forks and knives. Even though they were on the dull sides, they cut through its body–killing it slowly, while it screamed in pain. Bill carefully aimed his M4 at it and shot a single bullet, hitting it in the head. He smirked, then stepped off the table and started to walk near the door. As he did so, he heard giggling. He sighed. Not another new creature he thought, readying his weapon. He approached the hallway, checking all his corners. There was nothing there. He then stepped out into the hallway carefully. Nothing. Sighing in relief, he lowered his weapon. As he did so, the giggling repeated–only this time it was coming from his feet! He slowly looked down and saw a hunched over creature the size of a small dog. He attempted to shoot at it, but the creature seized his weapon and threw it against the wall. It jumped at him, landing on his head. Screaming, Bill stumbled around, trying to get the thing off of him. It seemed to be trying to…direct Bill somehow. Suddenly, an immense pain shot through his neck. It felt like his head was being wrenched off of his body! He screamed again, trying to knocked the creature against the wall. As he stumbled around, he heard Zoey yell something in the distance.<br>
“Help! Something…else has me!!”, he screamed in anxiety and relief. Gunshots sounded, and he heard the whiz of bullets flying past his head.<br>
“Don’t shoot me!!”, he screamed, terrified of dying not from the infected, but his own friends. Suddenly, the giggling stopped, and the creature fell off his body.<br>
“Oh thank god!” Bill yelled, relieved to be back with his teammates.<br>
"Bill, there’s no time for talking! We found something important–</p>
<p>Bill’s flashback was interrupted by Zoey handing him his gun.<br>
“Come on, old man. It’s time to go”</p>
<p>Bill snatched the gun from her, irritated that she had called him old man. He walked to the safe room door and wrenched off the bar.<br>
“Kill all sons of bitches!”, he said, grinning. He rushed outside, screaming at the infected.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/suicidal-heroism-part-1/340845/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/suicidal-heroism-part-1/340845/1</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 21 May 2010 08:00:42 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-340845-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/suicidal-heroism-part-1/340845.rss">Suicidal Heroism Part 1</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
