<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Please help! (problems)</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/please-help-problems/288478</link>
    <description>i am having some problems with my server and i hope you can help.
here are some of the problem.

[b]mining[/b]
how do i fix mining?
my server will not let me mine...
i would like to be able to mine.

[b]fishing[/b]
how do i put in fishing spots?
when i put them in will they work?
if they dont work, how do i make them work?

[b]cooking[/b]
how do i get cooking to work?
i want to cookthings but when i try it says &quot;nothing intresting happends.&quot;
please help.

[b]fire making[/b]
how do i get firemaking to work?
when i try it doesnt do anything
please help

[b]theiving[/b]
my theiving works but how do i add stalls for lvl 1 theiving?

[b]crafting[/b]
how do i get my crafting to work?
when i try to cut a gem, nothing happends.
please help

[b]slayer[/b]
how do i get slayer to work?
plz help

p.s.
if there are any code.
they will sure come in handy


thank you
::kidd619::</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 13 Jul 2009 06:23:32 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/please-help-problems/288478.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Please help! (problems)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@zyle1992 Zymus]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/zyle1992">@zyle1992</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Mining: Check your ObjectClick1 packet(Can’t remember the packet ID &gt;.&lt;), and then, search for the ID of the rock, and if it doesn’t exist, add a case(Should be a case. not sure what else it would be…), and then make it start an animation, and then when the animation is finished, make it add an Item to the players inventory, and then replace the object.</p>
<p>Fishing: Fishing spots are, believe it or not, Npcs. So you must go into autospawn.cfg, and spawn a fishing spot. Then Go into your NpcOption1 packet, and then repeat the same thing you did for the mining. start animation, and add item.</p>
<p>Cooking: In order to get cooking to work, you have to go into your ItemOnObject Packet, and then go through and then(this all depends on your server), add a case, or an If-else statement that does an animation, and then chooses a random number(or boolean from a boolean[2]), and then, if that random number is 0(or false), it’s burned, if it’s 1(or true) it is successful, and add the item.</p>
<p>Firemaking: Go into your ItemOnItem(Packet 53 i think?) packet, and then make it check if your tinderbox was used on a certain type of logs, and if it was, do an animation, and create a groundobject(should be in your source, it usually is), and then walk 1 square west(or w/e direction you decide)</p>
<p>Thieving: For this, go into your ObjectClick1(or ObjectOption1, whatever it is in your server) packet, then there should be an int in there, that’s something along the lines of objectID, and then hopefully there’s a switch statement. Add a case in there(or if you already have the stalls do something, search for case <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=5" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"> and then, it will probably have something like:</p>
<pre><code class="lang-auto">if(Skills.get("Thieving") &gt;= 5)//change this to a 1 for level 1 thieving</code></pre>
<p>Crafting: Go again into your ItemOnItem packet, and then, depending on your server, check to see if a chisel, is used on a gem, and then depending on the gemID, give the player that item.</p>
<p>Slayer: I do not have a simple explanation for this. The simplest thing I can think of is have a method that writes the NpcID of the slayer monster the player has to kill, and the number they have to kill, and then decrease the requiredKills for each npc they kill.</p>
<p>I hope this helped in some way. It’s almost midnight here, so I’m a bit tired.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/please-help-problems/288478/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/please-help-problems/288478/2</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 13 Jul 2009 06:23:32 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-288478-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/please-help-problems/288478.rss">Please help! (problems)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Please help! (problems)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@kidd619 kidd619]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/kidd619">@kidd619</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>i am having some problems with my server and i hope you can help.<br>
here are some of the problem.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">mining</span><br>
how do i fix mining?<br>
my server will not let me mine…<br>
i would like to be able to mine.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">fishing</span><br>
how do i put in fishing spots?<br>
when i put them in will they work?<br>
if they dont work, how do i make them work?</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">cooking</span><br>
how do i get cooking to work?<br>
i want to cookthings but when i try it says “nothing intresting happends.”<br>
please help.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">fire making</span><br>
how do i get firemaking to work?<br>
when i try it doesnt do anything<br>
please help</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">theiving</span><br>
my theiving works but how do i add stalls for lvl 1 theiving?</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">crafting</span><br>
how do i get my crafting to work?<br>
when i try to cut a gem, nothing happends.<br>
please help</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">slayer</span><br>
how do i get slayer to work?<br>
plz help</p>
<p>p.s.<br>
if there are any code.<br>
they will sure come in handy</p>
<p>thank you<br>
::kidd619::</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/please-help-problems/288478/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/please-help-problems/288478/1</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 13 Jul 2009 05:05:58 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-288478-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/please-help-problems/288478.rss">Please help! (problems)</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
