<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Bush aquits Libby of all charges!</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/bush-aquits-libby-of-all-charges/119257</link>
    <description>Bush aquits Libby of all charges!

I don&#39;t know if anyone keeps up with the news. Most don&#39;t. But Libby is a person who leaked a CIA agent&#39;s identity: Valerie Plame. He only got a 2 and a half year jail term which should have been much longer because now Valerie Plame can&#39;t even work in the CIA anymore because her face and identity is known. Who knows what the other repurcussions of his actions may be. Many of her team&#39;s members, could have been killed because of the leak.

Her husband has been anti-iraq-war since the beginning and to punish Valerie&#39;s husband, the shit official Scotter Libby, intentionally leaked her identity. He should have been jailed for a lot longer than 2 and a half years and he should have never been outted.

All he has to do now is pay a $250,000 fine. For a Bush Official, that is nothing. Especially when his &#39;political friends&#39; will pay most of it as said in the article.

Article: http://news.independent.co.uk/world/americas/article2730498.ece
&lt;blockquote&gt;Bush steps in to commute Libby&#39;s prison term 
By Leonard Doyle in Washington 
Published: 03 July 2007 

President George Bush has used his powers of clemency to spare Lewis &quot;Scooter&quot; Libby - one of his closest advisers in the decision to go to war on Iraq - from a two-and-a-half year prison term. 

The decision yesterday caused widespread anger among Democrats and even dismayed some Republicans. But in keeping Libby out of jail the President may have saved himself from revelations by an embittered former aide. He was also bowing to political pressure from conservative bloggers, talk-radio hosts, and senior Republicans.

Libby, 56, a former chief of staff to Vice-President Dick Cheney, was convicted of lying to prosecutors investigating the leaking in 2003 of CIA official Valerie Plame&#39;s identity.

Mr Cheney supported a pardon but President Bush would not go that far, in part because Mr Libby refused to show any contrition. A pardon by Mr Bush would have been viewed as showing disrespect for the US justice system.

Mr Bush acted after a summit with the Russian President Vladimir Putin in Kennebunkport, Maine, when a court refused to let Libby remain free during his appeal.

&quot;My decision to commute his sentence leaves in place a harsh punishment,&quot; Mr Bush said in a statement. &quot;The consequences of his felony conviction on his former life as a lawyer, public servant and private citizen will be long- lasting.&#39;&#39; He added: &quot;The reputation he gained through his years of public service and professional work in the legal community is forever damaged.&quot;

As a result, Libby&#39;s conviction still stands and he must still pay a $250,000 (£124,000) fine. [b]Political friends have said they will pay much of it.[/b] 

Libby resigned as Mr Cheney&#39;s chief of staff shortly after being charged in 2005. The special US prosecutor Patrick Fitzgerald proved he had lied to investigators over the leaking of Ms Plame&#39;s identity, which ending her undercover career.

Polls found that 69 per cent of Americans opposed a pardon. Only 18 per cent favoured it. The democrats, including the Senate Democratic Leader Harry Reid, demanded that President Bush not pardon Libby.

Libby&#39;s troubles began when a former US ambassador, Joseph Wilson, told The Independent and The New York Times that the Bush administration had twisted intelligence in order to justify the invasion of Iraq.

A senior member of the administration deliberately leaked Ms Plame&#39;s iden-tity to punish her husband. The syndicated columnist Robert Novak testified that the agent&#39;s identity was provided by the Deputy Secretary of State at the time, Richard Armitage, and confirmed by the White House political adviser Karl Rove.

Mr Fitzgerald argued that Libby lied about his knowledge of the leak to protect his job.&lt;/blockquote&gt;

Your thoughts please - If you&#39;re wondering, that is why it&#39;s in the Discussion section of the forum.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 05 Jul 2007 08:47:10 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>General Discussion</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/bush-aquits-libby-of-all-charges/119257.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Bush aquits Libby of all charges!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@moparisthebest Moparisthebest]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/moparisthebest">@moparisthebest</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I think Libby should be lined up in front of a firing squad and shot like the traitor he is.  This makes me like Bush less, but I still believe he was a better choice than John Kerry.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/bush-aquits-libby-of-all-charges/119257/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/bush-aquits-libby-of-all-charges/119257/6</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 05 Jul 2007 08:47:10 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-119257-6</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/bush-aquits-libby-of-all-charges/119257.rss">Bush aquits Libby of all charges!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Bush aquits Libby of all charges!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@therealjdb JDB`]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/therealjdb">@therealjdb</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>565 more days and King Dick and Prince George will be out of office, but then again maybe they’ll declare Marshal Law or something to stay in office longer. Honestly this doesn’t surprise me in the least, you’d think he would have been smart enough to wait until the end of his term to do something this stupid. ahh whatever.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/bush-aquits-libby-of-all-charges/119257/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/bush-aquits-libby-of-all-charges/119257/5</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 05 Jul 2007 00:29:42 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-119257-5</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/bush-aquits-libby-of-all-charges/119257.rss">Bush aquits Libby of all charges!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Bush aquits Libby of all charges!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@xxbestxx xxbestxx]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/xxbestxx">@xxbestxx</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote no-group" data-post="2" data-topic="119257">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/pault/40/5_6259e4fa9dfe0dec282fb0955bb1974c.png" class="avatar"> PaulT:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Very fucked up. Even fake justice is not served. And don’t even get me started on the wacky bear porn that ‘Scooter’ wrote before he started working in the white house. I shit you not, bestiality and neoconservatism go together like romance novels and japanese schoolgirls.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>now u scar me.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/bush-aquits-libby-of-all-charges/119257/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/bush-aquits-libby-of-all-charges/119257/4</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 03 Jul 2007 22:02:36 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-119257-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/bush-aquits-libby-of-all-charges/119257.rss">Bush aquits Libby of all charges!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Bush aquits Libby of all charges!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Ron Ron]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/ron">@Ron</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Paul sometimes it’s hard to take you seriously. :rolleyes:</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/bush-aquits-libby-of-all-charges/119257/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/bush-aquits-libby-of-all-charges/119257/3</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 03 Jul 2007 22:00:45 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-119257-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/bush-aquits-libby-of-all-charges/119257.rss">Bush aquits Libby of all charges!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Bush aquits Libby of all charges!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@PaulT PaulT]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/pault">@PaulT</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Very fucked up. Even fake justice is not served. And don’t even get me started on the wacky bear porn that ‘Scooter’ wrote before he started working in the white house. I shit you not, bestiality and neoconservatism go together like romance novels and japanese schoolgirls.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/bush-aquits-libby-of-all-charges/119257/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/bush-aquits-libby-of-all-charges/119257/2</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 03 Jul 2007 09:10:30 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-119257-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/bush-aquits-libby-of-all-charges/119257.rss">Bush aquits Libby of all charges!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Bush aquits Libby of all charges!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Ron Ron]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/ron">@Ron</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Bush aquits Libby of all charges!</p>
<p>I don’t know if anyone keeps up with the news. Most don’t. But Libby is a person who leaked a CIA agent’s identity: Valerie Plame. He only got a 2 and a half year jail term which should have been much longer because now Valerie Plame can’t even work in the CIA anymore because her face and identity is known. Who knows what the other repurcussions of his actions may be. Many of her team’s members, could have been killed because of the leak.</p>
<p>Her husband has been anti-iraq-war since the beginning and to punish Valerie’s husband, the shit official Scotter Libby, intentionally leaked her identity. He should have been jailed for a lot longer than 2 and a half years and he should have never been outted.</p>
<p>All he has to do now is pay a $250,000 fine. For a Bush Official, that is nothing. Especially when his ‘political friends’ will pay most of it as said in the article.</p>
<p>Article: <a href="http://news.independent.co.uk/world/americas/article2730498.ece" rel="nofollow noopener">http://news.independent.co.uk/world/americas/article2730498.ece</a></p>
<blockquote>Bush steps in to commute Libby's prison term 
By Leonard Doyle in Washington 
Published: 03 July 2007 
<p>President George Bush has used his powers of clemency to spare Lewis “Scooter” Libby - one of his closest advisers in the decision to go to war on Iraq - from a two-and-a-half year prison term.</p>
<p>The decision yesterday caused widespread anger among Democrats and even dismayed some Republicans. But in keeping Libby out of jail the President may have saved himself from revelations by an embittered former aide. He was also bowing to political pressure from conservative bloggers, talk-radio hosts, and senior Republicans.</p>
<p>Libby, 56, a former chief of staff to Vice-President Dick Cheney, was convicted of lying to prosecutors investigating the leaking in 2003 of CIA official Valerie Plame’s identity.</p>
<p>Mr Cheney supported a pardon but President Bush would not go that far, in part because Mr Libby refused to show any contrition. A pardon by Mr Bush would have been viewed as showing disrespect for the US justice system.</p>
<p>Mr Bush acted after a summit with the Russian President Vladimir Putin in Kennebunkport, Maine, when a court refused to let Libby remain free during his appeal.</p>
<p>“My decision to commute his sentence leaves in place a harsh punishment,” Mr Bush said in a statement. "The consequences of his felony conviction on his former life as a lawyer, public servant and private citizen will be long- lasting.’’ He added: “The reputation he gained through his years of public service and professional work in the legal community is forever damaged.”</p>
<p>As a result, Libby’s conviction still stands and he must still pay a $250,000 (£124,000) fine. <span class="bbcode-b">Political friends have said they will pay much of it.</span></p>
<p>Libby resigned as Mr Cheney’s chief of staff shortly after being charged in 2005. The special US prosecutor Patrick Fitzgerald proved he had lied to investigators over the leaking of Ms Plame’s identity, which ending her undercover career.</p>
<p>Polls found that 69 per cent of Americans opposed a pardon. Only 18 per cent favoured it. The democrats, including the Senate Democratic Leader Harry Reid, demanded that President Bush not pardon Libby.</p>
<p>Libby’s troubles began when a former US ambassador, Joseph Wilson, told The Independent and The New York Times that the Bush administration had twisted intelligence in order to justify the invasion of Iraq.</p>
<p>A senior member of the administration deliberately leaked Ms Plame’s iden-tity to punish her husband. The syndicated columnist Robert Novak testified that the agent’s identity was provided by the Deputy Secretary of State at the time, Richard Armitage, and confirmed by the White House political adviser Karl Rove.</p>
<p>Mr Fitzgerald argued that Libby lied about his knowledge of the leak to protect his job.</p>
</blockquote>
<p>Your thoughts please - If you’re wondering, that is why it’s in the Discussion section of the forum.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/bush-aquits-libby-of-all-charges/119257/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/bush-aquits-libby-of-all-charges/119257/1</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 03 Jul 2007 07:10:34 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-119257-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/bush-aquits-libby-of-all-charges/119257.rss">Bush aquits Libby of all charges!</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
