<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Problem connecting to any rsps i&#39;m trying to put online localhost</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/problem-connecting-to-any-rsps-im-trying-to-put-online-localhost/515857</link>
    <description>I&#39;ve been stumped with a problem for a while I am not sure how to fix it. On matrix718 package I&#39;ve got the server to where it connects but when I open the client it stays at 0% and doesn&#39;t load, I&#39;ve already changed the server IP an port  in loader.java to 127.0.0.1 and tried localhost as well and I have the port set to 43594. I&#39;ve port forwarded  43594 and checked it and its good. The error that comes up in cmd while the client is stuck at 0% after 30seconds+ says error_game_js5connect. I&#39;ve also tried on a few other client+source d/l&#39;s I have they usually have similar context saying cannot connect etc. Any help would be GREATLY appreciated. Thanks!</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2013 23:05:25 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/problem-connecting-to-any-rsps-im-trying-to-put-online-localhost/515857.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Problem connecting to any rsps i&#39;m trying to put online localhost</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@ascensi0n ascensi0n]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/ascensi0n">@ascensi0n</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I’ve been stumped with a problem for a while I am not sure how to fix it. On matrix718 package I’ve got the server to where it connects but when I open the client it stays at 0% and doesn’t load, I’ve already changed the server IP an port  in loader.java to 127.0.0.1 and tried localhost as well and I have the port set to 43594. I’ve port forwarded  43594 and checked it and its good. The error that comes up in cmd while the client is stuck at 0% after 30seconds+ says error_game_js5connect. I’ve also tried on a few other client+source d/l’s I have they usually have similar context saying cannot connect etc. Any help would be GREATLY appreciated. Thanks!</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/problem-connecting-to-any-rsps-im-trying-to-put-online-localhost/515857/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/problem-connecting-to-any-rsps-im-trying-to-put-online-localhost/515857/1</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2013 23:05:25 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-515857-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/problem-connecting-to-any-rsps-im-trying-to-put-online-localhost/515857.rss">Problem connecting to any rsps i&#39;m trying to put online localhost</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
