<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Portforwarding Wierd?</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/portforwarding-wierd/419319</link>
    <description>Okay so i have been able to portforward with my verizon router to connect to my old rsps which was hybrid pvp edited since then i shut the server down. now i want to start a new server but i&#39;ve noticed my verizon ports have stopped working? My router says their still active but according to the rsps and open port checkers it isnt. i have tried erasing the ports and reopening them and thats not working either. However i have tried Utorrent to portforward and it seems to work the thing is everytime i restart my cpu i have to portforward with utorrent again. so someone please help me here i want my verizon ports to be working !!!

Extra information:
yes my no-ip is open
yes the server is on my no-ip
yes when i portforward with utorrent my friends can play
and yes when i check open port checker with my utorrent ports open it says the port is open.
I have windows 7

Edit: i dont know if this is in right section but someone please tell me the possible problem why my verizon ports that i opened from logging into my router at 192.168.1.1 arent working.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2011 00:19:50 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Game Development</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/portforwarding-wierd/419319.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Portforwarding Wierd?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@darknessxd darknessxd]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/darknessxd">@darknessxd</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Okay so i have been able to portforward with my verizon router to connect to my old rsps which was hybrid pvp edited since then i shut the server down. now i want to start a new server but i’ve noticed my verizon ports have stopped working? My router says their still active but according to the rsps and open port checkers it isnt. i have tried erasing the ports and reopening them and thats not working either. However i have tried Utorrent to portforward and it seems to work the thing is everytime i restart my cpu i have to portforward with utorrent again. so someone please help me here i want my verizon ports to be working !!!</p>
<p>Extra information:<br>
yes my no-ip is open<br>
yes the server is on my no-ip<br>
yes when i portforward with utorrent my friends can play<br>
and yes when i check open port checker with my utorrent ports open it says the port is open.<br>
I have windows 7</p>
<p>Edit: i dont know if this is in right section but someone please tell me the possible problem why my verizon ports that i opened from logging into my router at 192.168.1.1 arent working.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/portforwarding-wierd/419319/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/portforwarding-wierd/419319/1</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2011 00:19:50 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-419319-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/portforwarding-wierd/419319.rss">Portforwarding Wierd?</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
