<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>VPS Survey</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/vps-survey/347670</link>
    <description>So, its been only just a bit over 24 hours since I launched HydraVM, and already I&#39;ve had more live chats with Moparscapers than anyone else - and I didn&#39;t even post about it here, just put a link in my sig :D Looks like you guys are pretty hot on the idea of Managed VPS.

Unfortunately, since my current offerings are Xen nodes geared towards disk performance etc. for SQL and such, I can&#39;t get the price down to what you guys are used to. However, since there is such an interest, I&#39;ve been thinking of putting together an OpenVZ setup and offering some kind of price cut for you guys, since I love you all so much.

If you&#39;re interested in VPS, or already have a VPS, I&#39;d be super grateful if you could answer a couple of questions:

1) In general, are you happy with a VPS company only offering Linux, no Windows? Bear in mind said VPS company provides full management, so you don&#39;t need to be a Linux nerd, just roughly comfortable.
2) What sort of RAM and CPU requirements do you look for when hosting your servers?
3) Where is the best location for you? US/UK/Somewhere else?</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 Jul 2010 22:08:19 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>General Discussion</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/vps-survey/347670.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>VPS Survey</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Mopman Mopman]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/mopman">@Mopman</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>So, its been only just a bit over 24 hours since I launched HydraVM, and already I’ve had more live chats with Moparscapers than anyone else - and I didn’t even post about it here, just put a link in my sig <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/smiley.png?v=5" title=":smiley:" class="emoji" alt=":smiley:"> Looks like you guys are pretty hot on the idea of Managed VPS.</p>
<p>Unfortunately, since my current offerings are Xen nodes geared towards disk performance etc. for SQL and such, I can’t get the price down to what you guys are used to. However, since there is such an interest, I’ve been thinking of putting together an OpenVZ setup and offering some kind of price cut for you guys, since I love you all so much.</p>
<p>If you’re interested in VPS, or already have a VPS, I’d be super grateful if you could answer a couple of questions:</p>
<ol>
<li>In general, are you happy with a VPS company only offering Linux, no Windows? Bear in mind said VPS company provides full management, so you don’t need to be a Linux nerd, just roughly comfortable.</li>
<li>What sort of RAM and CPU requirements do you look for when hosting your servers?</li>
<li>Where is the best location for you? US/UK/Somewhere else?</li>
</ol>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/vps-survey/347670/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/vps-survey/347670/1</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jul 2010 22:08:19 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-347670-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/vps-survey/347670.rss">VPS Survey</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
