<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Few things</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/few-things/357295</link>
    <description>I want to know how to make the hits in the 100&#39;s like in real rs in delta.  Making the hp higher and stuff.  And is there anyway I could make the combat level go backwards?  Like from 126 to 0.  I know it seems stupid but I took a vote and most peope wanted me to do it.  Now the other thing is people are someone how hacking into my server making themselves mod.  How do I stop that.  And another thing is that my antilag doesn&#39;t work. Lol, sorry for all the questions.  One more thing is that, I want the new emote tab. When I added the images and added it to my client it showed a bunch of blank images when you scrolled over it, it would say the emote and you could still click it.  That should be all.  If there&#39;s anything else I&#39;ll just post in here some more.  OH THE LAST THING IS THAT NPC&#39;S KEEP ON GLITCHING.  WHEN YOU KILL AN NPC THEY LIKE SHAKE OR SOMETHING.  CAN SOMEONE PLEASE SHOW ME HOW TO FIX THIS OR W/E.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 27 Aug 2010 21:59:46 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/few-things/357295.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Few things</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@sageofmali sageofmali]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/sageofmali">@sageofmali</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Can you help me fix them?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/few-things/357295/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/few-things/357295/2</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Aug 2010 21:59:46 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-357295-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/few-things/357295.rss">Few things</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Few things</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@sageofmali sageofmali]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/sageofmali">@sageofmali</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I want to know how to make the hits in the 100’s like in real rs in delta.  Making the hp higher and stuff.  And is there anyway I could make the combat level go backwards?  Like from 126 to 0.  I know it seems stupid but I took a vote and most peope wanted me to do it.  Now the other thing is people are someone how hacking into my server making themselves mod.  How do I stop that.  And another thing is that my antilag doesn’t work. Lol, sorry for all the questions.  One more thing is that, I want the new emote tab. When I added the images and added it to my client it showed a bunch of blank images when you scrolled over it, it would say the emote and you could still click it.  That should be all.  If there’s anything else I’ll just post in here some more.  OH THE LAST THING IS THAT NPC’S KEEP ON GLITCHING.  WHEN YOU KILL AN NPC THEY LIKE SHAKE OR SOMETHING.  CAN SOMEONE PLEASE SHOW ME HOW TO FIX THIS OR W/E.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/few-things/357295/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/few-things/357295/1</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Aug 2010 21:41:37 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-357295-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/few-things/357295.rss">Few things</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
