<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>GOW3 On Playstation 3?</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/gow3-on-playstation-3/166233</link>
    <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;We recently reported on Wedbush Morgan analyst Michael Pachter’s bold prediction that the Mass Effect trilogy will soon appear on the PlayStation 3. That article can be viewed here.
Pachter has stopped there, however, making yet another prediction that a huge Xbox 360 series may be headed to the PS3. In this case, Gears of War was the victim of discussion this time around while in talk with website Game Trailers yet again, where he pointed out that Epic is very open to the PS3 hardware by mentioning, &quot;we pretty much know that Gears of War 3 is probably gonna&#39; come out on PS3.&quot;

Pachter’s basis of testimony was that Microsoft probably inked a deal with Epic which will allow for only the first two games to appear exclusively on the Xbox 360, letting Epic do whatever they wish with the final game, assuming that they will finish the series off exclusively on the Xbox 360.

There’s no doubt that Gears of War 3 on PS3 would be a significant result for Sony. The series is a growing brand, by the time part 3 comes around it will probably be a household name like Halo, and we all know how huge Halo 3 was for the 360. While this is a great topic of debate, it is still too far off as GOW2 is not even out yet. If anything else breaks on this however, PSU will have you informed.
[size=9pt]http://www.psu.com/Analyst--Gears-of-War-3-on-PS3-a-possibility-News--a0002233-p0.php[/size]&lt;/blockquote&gt;

This sounds good. Should be an awesome game, but shame GOW2 hasn&#39;t even been started, lol.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 21 Dec 2007 02:55:05 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Games</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/gow3-on-playstation-3/166233.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>GOW3 On Playstation 3?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Mr.Chris Mr.Chris]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/mr.chris">@Mr.Chris</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <blockquote>We recently reported on Wedbush Morgan analyst Michael Pachter’s bold prediction that the Mass Effect trilogy will soon appear on the PlayStation 3. That article can be viewed here.
Pachter has stopped there, however, making yet another prediction that a huge Xbox 360 series may be headed to the PS3. In this case, Gears of War was the victim of discussion this time around while in talk with website Game Trailers yet again, where he pointed out that Epic is very open to the PS3 hardware by mentioning, "we pretty much know that Gears of War 3 is probably gonna' come out on PS3."
<p>Pachter’s basis of testimony was that Microsoft probably inked a deal with Epic which will allow for only the first two games to appear exclusively on the Xbox 360, letting Epic do whatever they wish with the final game, assuming that they will finish the series off exclusively on the Xbox 360.</p>
<p>There’s no doubt that Gears of War 3 on PS3 would be a significant result for Sony. The series is a growing brand, by the time part 3 comes around it will probably be a household name like Halo, and we all know how huge Halo 3 was for the 360. While this is a great topic of debate, it is still too far off as GOW2 is not even out yet. If anything else breaks on this however, PSU will have you informed.<br>
[size=9pt]<a href="http://www.psu.com/Analyst--Gears-of-War-3-on-PS3-a-possibility-News--a0002233-p0.php%5B/size%5D" rel="nofollow noopener">http://www.psu.com/Analyst--Gears-of-War-3-on-PS3-a-possibility-News--a0002233-p0.php[/size]</a></p>
</blockquote>
<p>This sounds good. Should be an awesome game, but shame GOW2 hasn’t even been started, lol.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/gow3-on-playstation-3/166233/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/gow3-on-playstation-3/166233/1</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 21 Dec 2007 02:55:05 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-166233-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/gow3-on-playstation-3/166233.rss">GOW3 On Playstation 3?</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
