<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>JAR Issue</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/jar-issue/465678</link>
    <description>For some reason when I JAR my client with the IP set as 127.0.0.1 it will load fine, but if I change this to my server IP it won&#39;t do anything. I tried a webclient and just using the JAR on my computer using both IP&#39;s but only 127.0.0.1 does anything.

I don&#39;t know if I&#39;m just unable to load it or changing it messes everything up. I can load the client fine if I set it to my server IP (obviously won&#39;t connect but at least it loads). Not sure if it works and I&#39;ve just been wasting my time or what.

There are no errors when I open it or try to load it as a webclient, it simply doesn&#39;t open anything or shows the Java loading circle thing.

Edit:
Would it be okay if I posted a link to the webclient? Or if you want to test it you can PM me for the link. I just want to make sure it loads, you don&#39;t have to log in.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 01 Nov 2012 05:28:23 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/jar-issue/465678.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>JAR Issue</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@RuneOnline RuneOnline]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/runeonline">@RuneOnline</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>For some reason when I JAR my client with the IP set as 127.0.0.1 it will load fine, but if I change this to my server IP it won’t do anything. I tried a webclient and just using the JAR on my computer using both IP’s but only 127.0.0.1 does anything.</p>
<p>I don’t know if I’m just unable to load it or changing it messes everything up. I can load the client fine if I set it to my server IP (obviously won’t connect but at least it loads). Not sure if it works and I’ve just been wasting my time or what.</p>
<p>There are no errors when I open it or try to load it as a webclient, it simply doesn’t open anything or shows the Java loading circle thing.</p>
<p>Edit:<br>
Would it be okay if I posted a link to the webclient? Or if you want to test it you can PM me for the link. I just want to make sure it loads, you don’t have to log in.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/jar-issue/465678/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/jar-issue/465678/1</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 01 Nov 2012 05:28:23 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-465678-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/jar-issue/465678.rss">JAR Issue</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
