<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Webclient Idea?</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/webclient-idea/390710</link>
    <description>I&#39;ve got an idea which is a bit outside my knowledge, and i&#39;m curious about a few things; 1: is this really even possible? 2: If possible, would it be way to over complicated to implement? and finally, 3: If possible, How can it be done?

Ok, so here goes. I was thinking about how i could get around the need of uploading your .jar file to your domain via ftp program, and the more i thought about this, the more i came to the conclusion that maybe it could be possible when combined with some html compatible java script similar to that of which is used to make the jar&#39;ed client file itself. we all know the process of uploading your cache, creating a cachedownload.java file, etc... but, is it possible to create the same sort of thing for your client.jar as well? so you would have the client and the cache uploaded to wherever, and then your html/javascript on whatever website would first download the client.jar and then run it as an applet within the web page, and then the normal process of the average webclient would take over from there...

i know my idea is raw in detail, this is as fresh as it gets. I just hopped onto mopar forums seeking help with this. As i said, if this is even possible, its way outside my knowledge.

anyone, Help?</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 13 Apr 2011 01:13:35 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Game Development</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/webclient-idea/390710.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Webclient Idea?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@veteran_god_king_ces veteran god: king cesar]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/veteran_god_king_ces">@veteran_god_king_ces</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I’ve got an idea which is a bit outside my knowledge, and i’m curious about a few things; 1: is this really even possible? 2: If possible, would it be way to over complicated to implement? and finally, 3: If possible, How can it be done?</p>
<p>Ok, so here goes. I was thinking about how i could get around the need of uploading your .jar file to your domain via ftp program, and the more i thought about this, the more i came to the conclusion that maybe it could be possible when combined with some html compatible java script similar to that of which is used to make the jar’ed client file itself. we all know the process of uploading your cache, creating a cachedownload.java file, etc… but, is it possible to create the same sort of thing for your client.jar as well? so you would have the client and the cache uploaded to wherever, and then your html/javascript on whatever website would first download the client.jar and then run it as an applet within the web page, and then the normal process of the average webclient would take over from there…</p>
<p>i know my idea is raw in detail, this is as fresh as it gets. I just hopped onto mopar forums seeking help with this. As i said, if this is even possible, its way outside my knowledge.</p>
<p>anyone, Help?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/webclient-idea/390710/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/webclient-idea/390710/1</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 13 Apr 2011 01:13:35 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-390710-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/webclient-idea/390710.rss">Webclient Idea?</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
