<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Clean up your act, Forum-donators</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/clean-up-your-act-forum-donators/70992</link>
    <description>[quote=&quot;lothy, post:83, topic:70563&quot;][quote author=server dude link=topic=103651.msg1050028#msg1050028 date=1174846129]
these forums are for people to have fun, posta few tuts and basically learn stuff from other people ( well maybe for the 733t c0d3z0rs!!) if they restart this board, theres going to be hardly anyong willing to post there tuts [u]again[/u]
[/quote]
Considering what most of the tutorials are about, that wouldn&#39;t be a bad thing.[/quote]

I agree whole-heartedly with this quote. These forums are a complete mess, and many of our good-tutorial-creators have perished, and dont make anymore tutorials. We need to bring this community up, just like Silab says. I believe that silab is the best server-coder out here at the moment, so i say this to her:
HELP US!!!!!
This community definately needs some cleanup, and some more enforced rules. When the rules began to be enforced,  i dislilked it greatly. But now that i am more mature, i realize, that this commmunity needs... The devil&#39;s grip... to keep it together. We need strictly enforced rules, and not just &#39;locking&#39; them. There should be a trash bin, where you move and lock them. So that they arent hogging up a part of the forum that should be only used for giving stuff to people. We need to BEAT the people who keep making this forum bad. And alot of the threads, are very similar, but not similar enough to get locked. All of these spell tutorials and other tuts like that are making this section noob-like, because there are too many tuts that have the same base. Also, i believe that we should just have sub-forums for each category of tutorial, which will keep alot of this mess organised.

     This is the big reason that i am making all of these text-based tutorials. We NEED something different. When everything is alike, it is not fun anymore.

     I remember when i was a ignorant server noob, looking through the tutorials, adding what i wanted. Even then, i had enough respect to post on nearly every thread i looked at. Now, i am ashamed of looking through these, because i usually cant think of a positive reply. If somebody replies to your thread about it being &quot;unique&quot;, that should be the best compliment. Because, nothing here seems to be unique. Everything is the same. All of these &#39;nooby&#39; tuts, are just a waste of everybody&#39;s time. The only people who add these tuts, are selfish people who want every single feature in their server, and cant code by themselves

I will leave it there
~ThatOneServer

[i]note:[/i] I will be editing this thread later.

I have written more in this thread, than i write in my 7th grade (Most advanced Middle-school classes in The los angeles district) essays. Respect that.
but then again, i have an F in english.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 25 Mar 2007 21:20:01 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/clean-up-your-act-forum-donators/70992.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Clean up your act, Forum-donators</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@MMcgrady1 MMcgrady1]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/mmcgrady1">@MMcgrady1</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>im 12 <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=6" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"> you dont see me spamming, plus, I understand most of this stuff.   MOST</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/clean-up-your-act-forum-donators/70992/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/clean-up-your-act-forum-donators/70992/2</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 25 Mar 2007 21:20:01 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-70992-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/clean-up-your-act-forum-donators/70992.rss">Clean up your act, Forum-donators</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Clean up your act, Forum-donators</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@ThatOneServer Mike_]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/thatoneserver">@ThatOneServer</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“lothy, post:83, topic:70563”][quote author=server dude link=topic=103651.msg1050028#msg1050028 date=1174846129]<br>
these forums are for people to have fun, posta few tuts and basically learn stuff from other people ( well maybe for the 733t c0d3z0rs!!) if they restart this board, theres going to be hardly anyong willing to post there tuts <span class="bbcode-u">again</span><br>
[/quote]<br>
Considering what most of the tutorials are about, that wouldn’t be a bad thing.[/quote]</p>
<p>I agree whole-heartedly with this quote. These forums are a complete mess, and many of our good-tutorial-creators have perished, and dont make anymore tutorials. We need to bring this community up, just like Silab says. I believe that silab is the best server-coder out here at the moment, so i say this to her:<br>
HELP US!!!<br>
This community definately needs some cleanup, and some more enforced rules. When the rules began to be enforced,  i dislilked it greatly. But now that i am more mature, i realize, that this commmunity needs… The devil’s grip… to keep it together. We need strictly enforced rules, and not just ‘locking’ them. There should be a trash bin, where you move and lock them. So that they arent hogging up a part of the forum that should be only used for giving stuff to people. We need to BEAT the people who keep making this forum bad. And alot of the threads, are very similar, but not similar enough to get locked. All of these spell tutorials and other tuts like that are making this section noob-like, because there are too many tuts that have the same base. Also, i believe that we should just have sub-forums for each category of tutorial, which will keep alot of this mess organised.</p>
<pre><code> This is the big reason that i am making all of these text-based tutorials. We NEED something different. When everything is alike, it is not fun anymore.

 I remember when i was a ignorant server noob, looking through the tutorials, adding what i wanted. Even then, i had enough respect to post on nearly every thread i looked at. Now, i am ashamed of looking through these, because i usually cant think of a positive reply. If somebody replies to your thread about it being "unique", that should be the best compliment. Because, nothing here seems to be unique. Everything is the same. All of these 'nooby' tuts, are just a waste of everybody's time. The only people who add these tuts, are selfish people who want every single feature in their server, and cant code by themselves
</code></pre>
<p>I will leave it there<br>
~ThatOneServer</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-i">note:</span> I will be editing this thread later.</p>
<p>I have written more in this thread, than i write in my 7th grade (Most advanced Middle-school classes in The los angeles district) essays. Respect that.<br>
but then again, i have an F in english.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/clean-up-your-act-forum-donators/70992/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/clean-up-your-act-forum-donators/70992/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 25 Mar 2007 19:38:41 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-70992-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/clean-up-your-act-forum-donators/70992.rss">Clean up your act, Forum-donators</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
