<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Some Questions</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/some-questions/353143</link>
    <description>Hey guys,
so I&#39;m trying to code my own server now.
It&#39;s delta based.
Well, I&#39;d be happy, if you could answer me all or atleast some of these questions.

1.) How can I add more playerRights + image in game, for example, playerRights 5 with a moderator crown, or a crown which I want to add myself

2.) How can I add new Npc, items, object etc, everywhere I read &quot;add the models&quot;, but where? o_O

3.) I downloaded a source named &#39;ParadiseX&#39;, and I have to use no-Ip if I want it to be online, I&#39;ve searched the port but didn&#39;t find it, does anybody know where it is? :)

4.) My gs specs are glitched, when I use a spec on a npc and run away, the gfx moves with me. &gt;.&gt;
Is there any way, that you cannot run while doing a spec or something like that? 

5.) Agility is glitched at my source, you cannot see the gnome course, and when I spawn the agility objects, you cannot go over it, I could simply add, that if you click on the object, that you&#39;re getting teleported to the other side of the object, but that&#39;s sad.

6.) The passwords in the character files aren&#39;t hidden, any ideas how to change that?

7.) I want to add a TempBan/TempMute/TempIpMute/TempIpBan command, which Bans/Mutes/IpMutes/IpBans a player for 2days, any ideas?


That should be enough at first, thanks guys! :)
I&#39;m happy to be a part of the Mopar-Scape community now. :)</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 05 Aug 2010 21:36:58 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/some-questions/353143.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Some Questions</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Ferity Ferity]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/ferity">@Ferity</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Hey guys,<br>
so I’m trying to code my own server now.<br>
It’s delta based.<br>
Well, I’d be happy, if you could answer me all or atleast some of these questions.</p>
<p>1.) How can I add more playerRights + image in game, for example, playerRights 5 with a moderator crown, or a crown which I want to add myself</p>
<p>2.) How can I add new Npc, items, object etc, everywhere I read “add the models”, but where? o_O</p>
<p>3.) I downloaded a source named ‘ParadiseX’, and I have to use no-Ip if I want it to be online, I’ve searched the port but didn’t find it, does anybody know where it is? <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=5" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
<p>4.) My gs specs are glitched, when I use a spec on a npc and run away, the gfx moves with me. &gt;.&gt;<br>
Is there any way, that you cannot run while doing a spec or something like that?</p>
<p>5.) Agility is glitched at my source, you cannot see the gnome course, and when I spawn the agility objects, you cannot go over it, I could simply add, that if you click on the object, that you’re getting teleported to the other side of the object, but that’s sad.</p>
<p>6.) The passwords in the character files aren’t hidden, any ideas how to change that?</p>
<p>7.) I want to add a TempBan/TempMute/TempIpMute/TempIpBan command, which Bans/Mutes/IpMutes/IpBans a player for 2days, any ideas?</p>
<p>That should be enough at first, thanks guys! <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=5" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"><br>
I’m happy to be a part of the Mopar-Scape community now. <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=5" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/some-questions/353143/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/some-questions/353143/1</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 05 Aug 2010 21:36:58 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-353143-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/some-questions/353143.rss">Some Questions</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
