<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Some questions</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/some-questions/433038</link>
    <description>I couldn&#39;t find any board where I could post this, that&#39;s why I am posting this here.
Basically, I&#39;m quite a noob when it comes to a RSPS, I&#39;ve been working on PI bases alot, changing/removing objects, teleports, etc. The basic stuffs.
I noticed most of the Tutorials in the Tutorials that I want to add on my server are for 317 Delta&#39;s. So I would like to know if it&#39;s a good choice for me to move to Delta, and if someone knows a good starting thing for me to work on. I&#39;ve tried several sources and clients and I prefer one with no skills, except for combat. I downloaded a blank one, but it had no objectclicking. So whenever you open the bank, nothing happens. And I don&#39;t know (yet) how to make that work.

I also like the old gameframe (old icons, etc.) about Delta. Another reason to move to Delta for me.

To make a long story short, does anyone know a good source+client I can start off with?
When I started PI, I downloaded the source and client from the &quot;Complete noob project insanity guide&quot;, something like that for example, but then for 317 delta.

Regards,
Derpington</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 15 Feb 2012 10:07:22 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/some-questions/433038.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Some questions</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Derpington Derpington]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/derpington">@Derpington</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I couldn’t find any board where I could post this, that’s why I am posting this here.<br>
Basically, I’m quite a noob when it comes to a RSPS, I’ve been working on PI bases alot, changing/removing objects, teleports, etc. The basic stuffs.<br>
I noticed most of the Tutorials in the Tutorials that I want to add on my server are for 317 Delta’s. So I would like to know if it’s a good choice for me to move to Delta, and if someone knows a good starting thing for me to work on. I’ve tried several sources and clients and I prefer one with no skills, except for combat. I downloaded a blank one, but it had no objectclicking. So whenever you open the bank, nothing happens. And I don’t know (yet) how to make that work.</p>
<p>I also like the old gameframe (old icons, etc.) about Delta. Another reason to move to Delta for me.</p>
<p>To make a long story short, does anyone know a good source+client I can start off with?<br>
When I started PI, I downloaded the source and client from the “Complete noob project insanity guide”, something like that for example, but then for 317 delta.</p>
<p>Regards,<br>
Derpington</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/some-questions/433038/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/some-questions/433038/1</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 15 Feb 2012 10:07:22 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-433038-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/some-questions/433038.rss">Some questions</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
