<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>For anyone interested in making fast GPs</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/for-anyone-interested-in-making-fast-gps/3182</link>
    <description>Basically all I need is a person (being a member on runescape) who has at least started the &quot;Recipe for Disaster&quot; quest, basically as to those who the above apply may know grapes cost 1 gp each from the buy food option on the &quot;Culinomancer Chest&quot; I am paying 10-20 gp per grape people get by world hopping (pricing varies depending on amount which you sell). And Theres virtually no limit to the amount which I would buy... (I need quite alot of them). 

TYVM in advance -  anyone who may be interested contact me by any means that you know how: l3eta</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 22 May 2006 22:22:32 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/for-anyone-interested-in-making-fast-gps/3182.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>For anyone interested in making fast GPs</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@l3etal3lade l3etal3lade]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/l3etal3lade">@l3etal3lade</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Basically all I need is a person (being a member on runescape) who has at least started the “Recipe for Disaster” quest, basically as to those who the above apply may know grapes cost 1 gp each from the buy food option on the “Culinomancer Chest” I am paying 10-20 gp per grape people get by world hopping (pricing varies depending on amount which you sell). And Theres virtually no limit to the amount which I would buy… (I need quite alot of them).</p>
<p>TYVM in advance -  anyone who may be interested contact me by any means that you know how: l3eta</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/for-anyone-interested-in-making-fast-gps/3182/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/for-anyone-interested-in-making-fast-gps/3182/1</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 22 May 2006 22:22:32 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-3182-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/for-anyone-interested-in-making-fast-gps/3182.rss">For anyone interested in making fast GPs</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
