<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Subwoofer Help</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/subwoofer-help/530770</link>
    <description>Alright, so I just got two infinity 12&quot; subs, and I have a persisting issue.

When I start up the truck, my left sub doesn&#39;t hit. However, after waiting 5min~, it cuts on and works for the remainder of the time it&#39;s on. My RCA cables are slightly damaged, the positive jack is broken on them, so I have a split running off of the negative. This may seem to be the problem, but it doesn&#39;t explain why it starts to work after 5min. All my connections are good, solders are secure. I&#39;m not sure what to do, of course by instinct, my first reaction is to go buy a new RCA cable, but frankly I don&#39;t have the money to take chances.. (I have enough for one purchase) Any ideas?</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2013 23:03:47 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>General Discussion</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/subwoofer-help/530770.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Subwoofer Help</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@system system]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/system">@system</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Alright, so I just got two infinity 12" subs, and I have a persisting issue.</p>
<p>When I start up the truck, my left sub doesn’t hit. However, after waiting 5min~, it cuts on and works for the remainder of the time it’s on. My RCA cables are slightly damaged, the positive jack is broken on them, so I have a split running off of the negative. This may seem to be the problem, but it doesn’t explain why it starts to work after 5min. All my connections are good, solders are secure. I’m not sure what to do, of course by instinct, my first reaction is to go buy a new RCA cable, but frankly I don’t have the money to take chances… (I have enough for one purchase) Any ideas?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/subwoofer-help/530770/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/subwoofer-help/530770/1</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2013 23:03:47 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-530770-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/subwoofer-help/530770.rss">Subwoofer Help</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
