<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Server help</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/server-help/530803</link>
    <description>what the best rsps source and client 317 with no dupes ! please help and look like rs not old</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2013 11:21:04 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/server-help/530803.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Server help</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Flame3 John]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/flame3">@Flame3</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>This isn’t a section for requesting a server, so I’m afraid I’ll have to lock this topic. However, Sk8rdude461 pointed you to the right place to request a download, found <a href="http://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php/board,257.0.html" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">here</a>.<br>
Good luck.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/server-help/530803/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/server-help/530803/3</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2013 11:21:04 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-530803-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/server-help/530803.rss">Server help</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Server help</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@sk8rdude461 sk8rdude461]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/sk8rdude461">@sk8rdude461</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Let me break this down for you nice and simple.</p>
<ol>
<li>
<p>You’re asking in the wrong section. Ask <a href="http://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php/board,257.0.html" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">here</a>.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>317 is over 400 revisions old compared to runescape (Runescape is at least on revision 760+). If you want something that looks like runescape, or a more current revision, you’re going to want something higher than revision 600. Or you can find a 317 client that has 600+/700+ data crammed into it, and make it work with a 317 server.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>No dupes? You’re looking at the most widely used, and most exploited revision of rsps. You’re going to have to do most of the patches yourself.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>There is no ‘best 317’ 9/10 are crap. Trisidia and Deathlypvpz are the most common because of all the shit (literally shit) crammed into them, but they also have the most errors. Find a blank source and start from there.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Honestly, I don’t see why you’re working with rsps. All I see you doing here is asking simple questions over and over without doing any research. You need to google a lot before you come to here for help. Chances are your answer is already out there (Read <span class="hashtag">#3</span>). If you have a legitimate question, or don’t get how something works, that’s completely fine to post about, but coming here and asking for code, and not steps on how to, you aren’t showing any will to learn. And if you don’t learn, you’re just going to keep pestering for answers.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Make sure you’re getting into RSPS because you want to code, not because you want to own/host a rsps. You’d be surprised how many programmers (Some go by ‘coders’) ask for a dedicated hoster. If you want to be an owner, then be a hoster for someone and get co-owner out of it. But if you really want to learn the dynamics behind it, and write the code, then by all means continue.</p>
</li>
</ol>
<p>I’m not trying to be an ass, nor rude, but it’s going to sound like that. and I’m sorry, but honestly, you don’t want to waste your time on this to find out you don’t want it.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/server-help/530803/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/server-help/530803/2</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2013 02:33:07 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-530803-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/server-help/530803.rss">Server help</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Server help</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@i_pwn_u11 i_pwn_u1]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/i_pwn_u11">@i_pwn_u11</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>what the best rsps source and client 317 with no dupes ! please help and look like rs not old</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/server-help/530803/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/server-help/530803/1</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2013 02:06:39 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-530803-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/server-help/530803.rss">Server help</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
