<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Need a partner</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/need-a-partner/540920</link>
    <description>Opener
Well the official &quot;business plan&quot;, so to speak, is not composed yet. So the plan as of right now is very flexible. I am looking for someone to start a server with me. I want someone who will be equally as dedicated as myself. You have to be ready to take on the challenge of starting a server from square one with me and continue to strive for success through the whole process. Your job will be to help run the server and help with programming whatever content we decide on.
 
Option 1:
Reopen my previous server called Energized which was ran for nearly a year. It had around 50 concurrent players. The server has some very original content and was well liked by most new players. I still have the website back up which has thousands of posts which would help with looking like an active server. The server has a great automatic vote, donation system, and highscores. 
 
Option 2:
Do a near-reality remake but change the server a lot (not trying to sound like the average leecher even though it pretty much is). You can&#39;t deny that the gameplay of near-reality was well loved by thousands of players and it is well coded. We could easily change it to be original and could easily bring in a hefty player base and plenty of donations to ensure plenty of advertising and paid bills.
 
What I have to offer:
-Dedication
-Active
-Profesional
-IPB license
-Server coding experience
-Good grammar (appealing to players)
-Experience with running a decent sized server
-Great with managing server
-More if interested
 
Application
Name:
Programming Experience:
Available Time:
Previous Work:
Skype:
 
:D</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 07 Mar 2014 22:05:59 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/need-a-partner/540920.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Need a partner</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@General_Z General Z]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/general_z">@General_Z</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>add me on skype: areyou.mad</p>
<p>ill show u my works + im 100% good at server/client</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/need-a-partner/540920/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/need-a-partner/540920/2</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 07 Mar 2014 22:05:59 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-540920-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/need-a-partner/540920.rss">Need a partner</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Need a partner</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Galennn Galennn]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/galennn">@Galennn</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Opener<br>
Well the official “business plan”, so to speak, is not composed yet. So the plan as of right now is very flexible. I am looking for someone to start a server with me. I want someone who will be equally as dedicated as myself. You have to be ready to take on the challenge of starting a server from square one with me and continue to strive for success through the whole process. Your job will be to help run the server and help with programming whatever content we decide on.</p>
<p>Option 1:<br>
Reopen my previous server called Energized which was ran for nearly a year. It had around 50 concurrent players. The server has some very original content and was well liked by most new players. I still have the website back up which has thousands of posts which would help with looking like an active server. The server has a great automatic vote, donation system, and highscores.</p>
<p>Option 2:<br>
Do a near-reality remake but change the server a lot (not trying to sound like the average leecher even though it pretty much is). You can’t deny that the gameplay of near-reality was well loved by thousands of players and it is well coded. We could easily change it to be original and could easily bring in a hefty player base and plenty of donations to ensure plenty of advertising and paid bills.</p>
<p>What I have to offer:<br>
-Dedication<br>
-Active<br>
-Profesional<br>
-IPB license<br>
-Server coding experience<br>
-Good grammar (appealing to players)<br>
-Experience with running a decent sized server<br>
-Great with managing server<br>
-More if interested</p>
<p>Application<br>
Name:<br>
Programming Experience:<br>
Available Time:<br>
Previous Work:<br>
Skype:</p>
<p><img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/smiley.png?v=5" title=":smiley:" class="emoji" alt=":smiley:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/need-a-partner/540920/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/need-a-partner/540920/1</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 05 Mar 2014 21:24:12 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-540920-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/need-a-partner/540920.rss">Need a partner</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
