<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Problem when installing</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/problem-when-installing/253648</link>
    <description>Today I tried to install Ubuntu, because i had nothing else to do, and thought i would try it out.

I partitioned my C: using Paragon Partition Manager 9 which restarted my computer after i tried to create the first partition, so i accepted.

When it was booting up, it came up and said &quot;Resizing Partition&quot; and said how long to go and what it was doing ect. It went fairly fast for the first few minuets, but then it stopped, and i assumed it had crashed, it said you could exit by pressing esc or ctrl-c, but it didn&#39;t work.

So when i restarted it now says &quot; Interrupted operation : Insert the Recovery CD or other Recovery Media and reboot your PC, and i don&#39;t have a recovery CD, so i&#39;m a bit lost on what to do now ?

I&#39;m wondering if i could use the laptop i&#39;m posting from now to create a recovery CD and then just use it in my desktop.

I know this isn&#39;t really about Linux, but i got this problem when trying to partition so that i could install Linux, so i posted it here. 

Has anyone else had this problem, or heard of any ways to fix it? I don&#39;t have a windows boot CD, but i have Ubuntu on a disc, so i could install, but that would mean i would loose everything that i had on windows, no ?

Thanks
-Kaza

EDIT : I have now made a recoverable disk, but looks like i have nothing to recover, and i can&#39;t find a way to restore without being asked for an image where everything was.

[s]If i try and boot without the disk, it says MBR error, which means i&#39;m fucked, no ?[/s]

I fixed the MBR error, but now it says i have to boot from system disk, so looks like i&#39;ll have to go find a windows disk.

Bah :(</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2008 05:11:24 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Technology</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/problem-when-installing/253648.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Problem when installing</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@pk4pk pk4pk]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/pk4pk">@pk4pk</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“Kaza, post:1, topic:253648”]Today I tried to install Ubuntu, because i had nothing else to do, and thought i would try it out.</p>
<p>I partitioned my C: using Paragon Partition Manager 9 which restarted my computer after i tried to create the first partition, so i accepted.</p>
<p>When it was booting up, it came up and said “Resizing Partition” and said how long to go and what it was doing ect. It went fairly fast for the first few minuets, but then it stopped, and i assumed it had crashed, it said you could exit by pressing esc or ctrl-c, but it didn’t work.</p>
<p>So when i restarted it now says " Interrupted operation : Insert the Recovery CD or other Recovery Media and reboot your PC, and i don’t have a recovery CD, so i’m a bit lost on what to do now ?</p>
<p>I’m wondering if i could use the laptop i’m posting from now to create a recovery CD and then just use it in my desktop.</p>
<p>I know this isn’t really about Linux, but i got this problem when trying to partition so that i could install Linux, so i posted it here.</p>
<p>Has anyone else had this problem, or heard of any ways to fix it? I don’t have a windows boot CD, but i have Ubuntu on a disc, so i could install, but that would mean i would loose everything that i had on windows, no ?</p>
<p>Thanks<br>
-Kaza</p>
<p>EDIT : I have now made a recoverable disk, but looks like i have nothing to recover, and i can’t find a way to restore without being asked for an image where everything was.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-s">If i try and boot without the disk, it says MBR error, which means i’m fucked, no ?</span></p>
<p>I fixed the MBR error, but now it says i have to boot from system disk, so looks like i’ll have to go find a windows disk.</p>
<p>Bah :([/quote]<br>
Just torrent windows 95 if you wanted ubuntu for faster running, or win xp</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/problem-when-installing/253648/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/problem-when-installing/253648/2</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2008 05:11:24 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-253648-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/problem-when-installing/253648.rss">Problem when installing</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Problem when installing</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@kaza Kaza]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/kaza">@kaza</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Today I tried to install Ubuntu, because i had nothing else to do, and thought i would try it out.</p>
<p>I partitioned my C: using Paragon Partition Manager 9 which restarted my computer after i tried to create the first partition, so i accepted.</p>
<p>When it was booting up, it came up and said “Resizing Partition” and said how long to go and what it was doing ect. It went fairly fast for the first few minuets, but then it stopped, and i assumed it had crashed, it said you could exit by pressing esc or ctrl-c, but it didn’t work.</p>
<p>So when i restarted it now says " Interrupted operation : Insert the Recovery CD or other Recovery Media and reboot your PC, and i don’t have a recovery CD, so i’m a bit lost on what to do now ?</p>
<p>I’m wondering if i could use the laptop i’m posting from now to create a recovery CD and then just use it in my desktop.</p>
<p>I know this isn’t really about Linux, but i got this problem when trying to partition so that i could install Linux, so i posted it here.</p>
<p>Has anyone else had this problem, or heard of any ways to fix it? I don’t have a windows boot CD, but i have Ubuntu on a disc, so i could install, but that would mean i would loose everything that i had on windows, no ?</p>
<p>Thanks<br>
-Kaza</p>
<p>EDIT : I have now made a recoverable disk, but looks like i have nothing to recover, and i can’t find a way to restore without being asked for an image where everything was.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-s">If i try and boot without the disk, it says MBR error, which means i’m fucked, no ?</span></p>
<p>I fixed the MBR error, but now it says i have to boot from system disk, so looks like i’ll have to go find a windows disk.</p>
<p>Bah <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/frowning.png?v=6" title=":frowning:" class="emoji" alt=":frowning:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/problem-when-installing/253648/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/problem-when-installing/253648/1</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2008 21:25:21 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-253648-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/problem-when-installing/253648.rss">Problem when installing</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
