<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Actual A+ essentials exam questions and answers</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/actual-a-essentials-exam-questions-and-answers/270137</link>
    <description>So guys as of today I am finally A+ certified, yay go me and I thought that you guys might like to try to get certified too so Im going to post some of the questions and answers I encountered during the exam I didn&#39;t have a bunch of time to make this list so they are separated by questions and answers they are all numbered accordingly 

these answers will be huge advantage because all the site out there today are questions that are likely to be on the test and are usually worded differently, these are the questions I personally ran into with original wording as seen on the A+ essentials test on march 19th, 2009

[code]

Questions

1.)	A laptop runs out of power and shuts down after a few minutes operating on battery only. This happens even when the battery initially shows a full charge.

What is most likely the problem?

2.)	A Windows XP computer on a TCP/IP network can use the ping command to communicate with other computers by IP address, but not by the computer&#39;s name. This is the only computer on the network having this problem.

What is most likely wrong?

3.) 	Which of the following are acceptable means of disposing of hardware? (Choose two.)

4.)	How should you clean a CRT monitor&#39;s screen?

5.)	Which term describes the ability for a portable PC&#39;s power adapter to change its rated input voltage?

6.)	Windows gives you an &quot;Invalid Page Fault&quot; error message.

What could be the cause of this? (Choose two.)

7.)	Your company purchases laptop computers for users. Some laptops are as much as five years old. All of the laptops have an integrated (built-in) wireless networking interface. All of the laptops are running either Microsoft Windows XP Professional or Windows 2000 Professional. Operating system service packs are up-to-date on all computers.

The office network is currently wired for 100 megabits per second (Mbps) Ethernet. You want to convert the office to a wireless network. You want to use wireless technology that is compatible with all of the laptops currently in use. You also want to optimize network performance.

What type of wireless access should you install?

8.)	Which backup types back up selected files and clear the archive bit in Windows Backup? (Choose two.)

9.)	While he is attempting to fix a problem, a customer makes the problem worse by introducing new issues. The customer claims that he did not do anything other than call you to report the problem.

What should you do?

10.)	Which CPU technology allows an operating system to treat a single processor as two logical processors?

11.)	Why should an MSDS be kept with or near the hazardous material it describes? (Choose two.)

12.)	You are cleaning a laptop computer. You plan to use compressed air where appropriate.

For which of the following is compressed air the recommended cleaning method for the device? (Choose three.)

13.)	What is the preferred method for disposing of a toner cartridge?

14.)	NWLink is a protocol designed for compatibility with which network operating system?

15.)	How does a laser printer put images on paper?

16.)	What is the potential risk when disposing of laptop batteries in a landfill?

17.)	A customer is having printer problems. The customer says, &quot;The printout was bad.&quot;

Which of the following is an example of a clarifying question?

18.)	What form factor is typically used for hard disk drives for laptop computers?

19.)	You need to install a network in your office location, which has a suspended overhead ceiling. You will be running the cable into the ceiling and between the walls.

What type of cable should you purchase?

20.) 	What device increases the number of PCI slots on a motherboard?

21.)	Why is it important to document and report accidents? (Choose two.)

22.)	You are working on a laptop. When you plug in the AC adapter, the power LED and the battery charge LED light up. You press the power button and the laptop will not start. You cannot hear any activity from the hard drive, cooling fan or the DVD drive.

Which of the following steps are necessary to diagnose the problem? (Choose three.)

23.)	At what point in the laser printer printing process is toner transferred to the drum?

24.)	A laptop computer has an external 68-pin slot that is 5 mm thick.

What type of expansion slot is this?

25.)	A customer downloads an updated device driver as an executable file from a display adapter manufacturer&#39;s Web site. The file runs, but the user is prevented by Windows XP from installing the device driver because of insufficient privileges.

What is the best way to correct this problem without giving the user excessive permissions?

26.)	You are helping a small business set up a network. The users want to be able to share printers that are hooked up to their computers. They also want to share folders on users&#39; computers. They do not require central management of user accounts.

What network model should you implement?

27.)	You have been asked to evaluate a 1 gigabyte (GB) PC2100 DDR SDRAM module that a remote user is describing to you over the phone.

The user tells you that it has 18 chips arranged in two rows (ranks).

Which statement about that memory module is most likely correct?

28.)	A customer installs an ink-jet printer on a computer running Windows XP. The printer uses a USB connection to the computer. The printer&#39;s self-test prints correctly, but documents sent from any application print unrecognizable garbage.

What is the most likely cause?

29.)    A computer running Windows XP is configured with the default Start menu.

How can you determine if updates are available?

30.)	Your laptop does not provide sufficient I/O ports to meet your needs. You are trying to decide whether a docking station or port replicator is more appropriate to your needs.

What additional hardware support is provided by both a docking station and a port replicator? (Choose two.)

31.)	Which parts of a laptop computer should be cleaned with a soft cloth dampened with water? (Choose two.)

32.)	What should you avoid wearing when working on a monitor? (Choose two.)

33.)	What is a female DB-25 connector (also called a 25-pin &quot;D&quot; connector) most often used for?

34.)	Which file displays the startup menu for a computer running Windows XP or Windows 2000?

35.)	A computer running Microsoft Windows 2000 Server currently has Service Pack 2 (SP2) applied. You need to apply SP4. You have already downloaded the service pack from Microsoft.

What is the most efficient way to apply SP4?

36.)	What is the potential risk from using a vacuum to clean circuit boards?

37.)	You have installed a new sound card in a Windows computer and have just finished running the driver installation program. The driver installation program indicates that the driver was installed successfully. 

38.)	Which type of display device typically uses resolution and lumens to describe the quality of the device?

39.)	You are trying to determine the name and IP address of the DNS server on a customer&#39;s network.

What command should you use?

40.) A user complains that a laptop&#39;s LCD screen stopped working suddenly. The user was typing when the LCD screen went dark. The laptop has a port that supports an external VGA monitor.

You want to talk the user through correcting the problem over the phone, if possible. The user is concerned about losing unsaved work on the computer.

What is the first thing you should have the user try?



Answers




1.) The laptop has a Nickel Cadmium (NiCad) battery suffering from memory effect.

2.) The computer&#39;s Primary DNS server address is configured incorrectly.

3.) Selling, Cannibalizing

4.) Spray a soft cloth with glass cleaner and wipe the screen.

5.) Auto-Switching

6.) The virtual memory becomes unstable due to a shortage of free RAM.,The virtual memory becomes unstable due to a shortage of free disk space.

7.) 802.11g

8.) Incremental, Normal

9.) Say nothing about the added problem, focus on the task at hand, and troubleshoot and fix the problem.

10.) Hyper-threading

11.) The MSDS describes health effects and first aid procedures. ,The MSDS describes proper handling and storage procedures.

12.) Keyboard, Fans, and USB ports

13.) Send the cartridge in for refill and recycling.

14.) Novell NetWare

15.) A laser creates an electric image on the drum (called Registration), which attracts toner particles that are pressed onto the page.

16.) The batteries contain hazardous heavy metals.

17.) Were the characters blurry?

18.) 2.5-inch

19.) Plenum grade

20.) Riser Card

21.) To meet Occupational Safety and Health Administration (OSHA) requirements, For worker&#39;s compensation and insurance claims

22.) Reseat the memory, Take out the laptop components (battery, PC cards, etc.) and plug them back in, Test the adapter output with a voltmeter.

23.) Developing

24.) PCMCIA Type II

25.) Allow the user to install device drivers through the Local Security settings.

26.) Peer-to-peer

27.) It is an ECC module.

28.) Windows XP selected the wrong device driver for the printer during installation.

29.) Connect to the Internet, run Start | All Programs | Windows Update and scan for updates.

30.) USB port, Serial interface connector

31.) Case, Touchpad

32.) Jewelry, Antistatic wrist strap

33.) Parallel port

34.) NTLDR

35.) Install SP4 on the computer as is.

36.) Static discharge

37.) Check to see whether sounds are audible, Check Device Manager to see if the device is functioning correctly.

38.) Projector

39.) nslookup

40.) Hold the function (Fn) key and toggle the LCD screen key

[/code]</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 30 Mar 2009 08:16:30 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>General Discussion</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/actual-a-essentials-exam-questions-and-answers/270137.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Actual A+ essentials exam questions and answers</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@newguy45 newguy45]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/newguy45">@newguy45</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>So guys as of today I am finally A+ certified, yay go me and I thought that you guys might like to try to get certified too so Im going to post some of the questions and answers I encountered during the exam I didn’t have a bunch of time to make this list so they are separated by questions and answers they are all numbered accordingly</p>
<p>these answers will be huge advantage because all the site out there today are questions that are likely to be on the test and are usually worded differently, these are the questions I personally ran into with original wording as seen on the A+ essentials test on march 19th, 2009</p>
<pre><code class="lang-auto">
Questions

1.)	A laptop runs out of power and shuts down after a few minutes operating on battery only. This happens even when the battery initially shows a full charge.

What is most likely the problem?

2.)	A Windows XP computer on a TCP/IP network can use the ping command to communicate with other computers by IP address, but not by the computer's name. This is the only computer on the network having this problem.

What is most likely wrong?

3.) 	Which of the following are acceptable means of disposing of hardware? (Choose two.)

4.)	How should you clean a CRT monitor's screen?

5.)	Which term describes the ability for a portable PC's power adapter to change its rated input voltage?

6.)	Windows gives you an "Invalid Page Fault" error message.

What could be the cause of this? (Choose two.)

7.)	Your company purchases laptop computers for users. Some laptops are as much as five years old. All of the laptops have an integrated (built-in) wireless networking interface. All of the laptops are running either Microsoft Windows XP Professional or Windows 2000 Professional. Operating system service packs are up-to-date on all computers.

The office network is currently wired for 100 megabits per second (Mbps) Ethernet. You want to convert the office to a wireless network. You want to use wireless technology that is compatible with all of the laptops currently in use. You also want to optimize network performance.

What type of wireless access should you install?

8.)	Which backup types back up selected files and clear the archive bit in Windows Backup? (Choose two.)

9.)	While he is attempting to fix a problem, a customer makes the problem worse by introducing new issues. The customer claims that he did not do anything other than call you to report the problem.

What should you do?

10.)	Which CPU technology allows an operating system to treat a single processor as two logical processors?

11.)	Why should an MSDS be kept with or near the hazardous material it describes? (Choose two.)

12.)	You are cleaning a laptop computer. You plan to use compressed air where appropriate.

For which of the following is compressed air the recommended cleaning method for the device? (Choose three.)

13.)	What is the preferred method for disposing of a toner cartridge?

14.)	NWLink is a protocol designed for compatibility with which network operating system?

15.)	How does a laser printer put images on paper?

16.)	What is the potential risk when disposing of laptop batteries in a landfill?

17.)	A customer is having printer problems. The customer says, "The printout was bad."

Which of the following is an example of a clarifying question?

18.)	What form factor is typically used for hard disk drives for laptop computers?

19.)	You need to install a network in your office location, which has a suspended overhead ceiling. You will be running the cable into the ceiling and between the walls.

What type of cable should you purchase?

20.) 	What device increases the number of PCI slots on a motherboard?

21.)	Why is it important to document and report accidents? (Choose two.)

22.)	You are working on a laptop. When you plug in the AC adapter, the power LED and the battery charge LED light up. You press the power button and the laptop will not start. You cannot hear any activity from the hard drive, cooling fan or the DVD drive.

Which of the following steps are necessary to diagnose the problem? (Choose three.)

23.)	At what point in the laser printer printing process is toner transferred to the drum?

24.)	A laptop computer has an external 68-pin slot that is 5 mm thick.

What type of expansion slot is this?

25.)	A customer downloads an updated device driver as an executable file from a display adapter manufacturer's Web site. The file runs, but the user is prevented by Windows XP from installing the device driver because of insufficient privileges.

What is the best way to correct this problem without giving the user excessive permissions?

26.)	You are helping a small business set up a network. The users want to be able to share printers that are hooked up to their computers. They also want to share folders on users' computers. They do not require central management of user accounts.

What network model should you implement?

27.)	You have been asked to evaluate a 1 gigabyte (GB) PC2100 DDR SDRAM module that a remote user is describing to you over the phone.

The user tells you that it has 18 chips arranged in two rows (ranks).

Which statement about that memory module is most likely correct?

28.)	A customer installs an ink-jet printer on a computer running Windows XP. The printer uses a USB connection to the computer. The printer's self-test prints correctly, but documents sent from any application print unrecognizable garbage.

What is the most likely cause?

29.)    A computer running Windows XP is configured with the default Start menu.

How can you determine if updates are available?

30.)	Your laptop does not provide sufficient I/O ports to meet your needs. You are trying to decide whether a docking station or port replicator is more appropriate to your needs.

What additional hardware support is provided by both a docking station and a port replicator? (Choose two.)

31.)	Which parts of a laptop computer should be cleaned with a soft cloth dampened with water? (Choose two.)

32.)	What should you avoid wearing when working on a monitor? (Choose two.)

33.)	What is a female DB-25 connector (also called a 25-pin "D" connector) most often used for?

34.)	Which file displays the startup menu for a computer running Windows XP or Windows 2000?

35.)	A computer running Microsoft Windows 2000 Server currently has Service Pack 2 (SP2) applied. You need to apply SP4. You have already downloaded the service pack from Microsoft.

What is the most efficient way to apply SP4?

36.)	What is the potential risk from using a vacuum to clean circuit boards?

37.)	You have installed a new sound card in a Windows computer and have just finished running the driver installation program. The driver installation program indicates that the driver was installed successfully. 

38.)	Which type of display device typically uses resolution and lumens to describe the quality of the device?

39.)	You are trying to determine the name and IP address of the DNS server on a customer's network.

What command should you use?

40.) A user complains that a laptop's LCD screen stopped working suddenly. The user was typing when the LCD screen went dark. The laptop has a port that supports an external VGA monitor.

You want to talk the user through correcting the problem over the phone, if possible. The user is concerned about losing unsaved work on the computer.

What is the first thing you should have the user try?



Answers




1.) The laptop has a Nickel Cadmium (NiCad) battery suffering from memory effect.

2.) The computer's Primary DNS server address is configured incorrectly.

3.) Selling, Cannibalizing

4.) Spray a soft cloth with glass cleaner and wipe the screen.

5.) Auto-Switching

6.) The virtual memory becomes unstable due to a shortage of free RAM.,The virtual memory becomes unstable due to a shortage of free disk space.

7.) 802.11g

8.) Incremental, Normal

9.) Say nothing about the added problem, focus on the task at hand, and troubleshoot and fix the problem.

10.) Hyper-threading

11.) The MSDS describes health effects and first aid procedures. ,The MSDS describes proper handling and storage procedures.

12.) Keyboard, Fans, and USB ports

13.) Send the cartridge in for refill and recycling.

14.) Novell NetWare

15.) A laser creates an electric image on the drum (called Registration), which attracts toner particles that are pressed onto the page.

16.) The batteries contain hazardous heavy metals.

17.) Were the characters blurry?

18.) 2.5-inch

19.) Plenum grade

20.) Riser Card

21.) To meet Occupational Safety and Health Administration (OSHA) requirements, For worker's compensation and insurance claims

22.) Reseat the memory, Take out the laptop components (battery, PC cards, etc.) and plug them back in, Test the adapter output with a voltmeter.

23.) Developing

24.) PCMCIA Type II

25.) Allow the user to install device drivers through the Local Security settings.

26.) Peer-to-peer

27.) It is an ECC module.

28.) Windows XP selected the wrong device driver for the printer during installation.

29.) Connect to the Internet, run Start | All Programs | Windows Update and scan for updates.

30.) USB port, Serial interface connector

31.) Case, Touchpad

32.) Jewelry, Antistatic wrist strap

33.) Parallel port

34.) NTLDR

35.) Install SP4 on the computer as is.

36.) Static discharge

37.) Check to see whether sounds are audible, Check Device Manager to see if the device is functioning correctly.

38.) Projector

39.) nslookup

40.) Hold the function (Fn) key and toggle the LCD screen key
</code></pre>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/actual-a-essentials-exam-questions-and-answers/270137/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/actual-a-essentials-exam-questions-and-answers/270137/1</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 30 Mar 2009 08:16:30 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-270137-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/actual-a-essentials-exam-questions-and-answers/270137.rss">Actual A+ essentials exam questions and answers</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
