<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Welp. it&#39;s being done again (x10hositng horror story)</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/welp-its-being-done-again-x10hositng-horror-story/529803</link>
    <description>As i&#39;ve made a post before, I used x10hosting for the sake of that it was easy to run my website on with their cpanel and free features.

I had built a site for runescape and ontop of that I had a side website for christmas cards I made to friends and family (which was now lost because of x10&#39;s bull crap). I was banned for having cache stored on my website in which users used for the webclient to be able to play it. They searched my site without me knowing and checked my files invading my personal privacy with this method and completely banned my account for having the cache. x10hosting also refuses to delete the items for you and re-enable your account. Once it is banned, it is banned, they don&#39;t have to tell you why, they don&#39;t have to tell you which files, and they certainly do not have to help you get your account back and let you off with a warning.



Today it happened again. After 2 straight years of not having an issue with x10, hosting ALL my files that revolved around the client or the cache or anything to do with the server, was hosted on third party sources such as uppit and mega.co.nz. Today I was banned for illegal content hosted on my website.


Now the only thing I have on my website is: Christmas cards, Valentine&#39;s day cards, My main site for my runescape private server, and a forum to go with my website (mybb). 

The only thing that can be struck as copyrighted material is two pictures that I had re-edited in photoshop. Two runescape characters re-painted.

x10hosting has now have my account banned again once more for no reason as I do not host any files regarding runescape on my site. (even the php for the webclient is on my own computer that is not apart of the site hosted on x10hositng). 

Now if x10hosting is having a &quot;bad day&quot;, I&#39;m going to loose all my content, never get it agian, and will not get a copy of what I had on those files as the account is suspened and they will not let you access the files unless you get unbanned.


~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~


This is an outrage, and I suggest everyone NEVER use x10hosting services, and do NOT pay for their services as they will take it and ruin your site with a flick of a finger.


I wish I could take further action into this issue, but sadly there is nothing I can do personally to bring justice to their door step.

However, this is a warning for all server hosters who are looking for a webhost to put their site on.



~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~

UPDATE!

Apparently now you can be banned for having a LINK that MAY or MAY NOT contain copyright material.


&lt;blockquote&gt;Hello,

Thank you for submitting an appeal against the suspension imposed upon your x10Hosting free web hosting account. We have
reviewed your account and the information included within your appeal. Unfortunately after careful consideration the
information submitted with your appeal does not adequately justify removal of the suspension. I can confirm that your
website was indeed providing links to a Runescape Private Server Client, which is being redistributed in violation of the
Runescape EULA and Terms of Use, which also means it&#39;s violating their copyright. This is not an action we allow in any way,
shape, or form.

In accordance with the x10Hosting Terms of Service and Acceptable Use Policy agreed to upon registration the suspension will
remain permanently. This decision is final.

At this time, data backups are not available as detailed in sections 6 and 8 of the x10Hosting Terms of Service.

http://x10hosting.com/terms

Best regards,
The x10Hosting Abuse Team&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&quot; I can confirm that your
website was indeed providing links to a Runescape Private Server Client, which is being redistributed in violation of the
Runescape EULA and Terms of Use, which also means it&#39;s violating their copyright. This is not an action we allow in any way,
shape, or form.&quot;


So a redirect to mega.co.nz is a bannable offense. as well as a redirect to a webclient php.



~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~

UPDATE:


Now they banned EVERY single account I had that was not related to RuneScape at all. (good news is they messed up and i got EVERYTHING backed up :P so cheers!)</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2013 22:21:41 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/welp-its-being-done-again-x10hositng-horror-story/529803.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Welp. it&#39;s being done again (x10hositng horror story)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Doobage Doobage]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/doobage">@Doobage</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>As i’ve made a post before, I used x10hosting for the sake of that it was easy to run my website on with their cpanel and free features.</p>
<p>I had built a site for runescape and ontop of that I had a side website for christmas cards I made to friends and family (which was now lost because of x10’s bull crap). I was banned for having cache stored on my website in which users used for the webclient to be able to play it. They searched my site without me knowing and checked my files invading my personal privacy with this method and completely banned my account for having the cache. x10hosting also refuses to delete the items for you and re-enable your account. Once it is banned, it is banned, they don’t have to tell you why, they don’t have to tell you which files, and they certainly do not have to help you get your account back and let you off with a warning.</p>
<p>Today it happened again. After 2 straight years of not having an issue with x10, hosting ALL my files that revolved around the client or the cache or anything to do with the server, was hosted on third party sources such as uppit and mega.co.nz. Today I was banned for illegal content hosted on my website.</p>
<p>Now the only thing I have on my website is: Christmas cards, Valentine’s day cards, My main site for my runescape private server, and a forum to go with my website (mybb).</p>
<p>The only thing that can be struck as copyrighted material is two pictures that I had re-edited in photoshop. Two runescape characters re-painted.</p>
<p>x10hosting has now have my account banned again once more for no reason as I do not host any files regarding runescape on my site. (even the php for the webclient is on my own computer that is not apart of the site hosted on x10hositng).</p>
<p>Now if x10hosting is having a “bad day”, I’m going to loose all my content, never get it agian, and will not get a copy of what I had on those files as the account is suspened and they will not let you access the files unless you get unbanned.</p>
<pre><code class="lang-auto">

This is an outrage, and I suggest everyone NEVER use x10hosting services, and do NOT pay for their services as they will take it and ruin your site with a flick of a finger.


I wish I could take further action into this issue, but sadly there is nothing I can do personally to bring justice to their door step.

However, this is a warning for all server hosters who are looking for a webhost to put their site on.



~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~

UPDATE!

Apparently now you can be banned for having a LINK that MAY or MAY NOT contain copyright material.


&lt;blockquote&gt;Hello,

Thank you for submitting an appeal against the suspension imposed upon your x10Hosting free web hosting account. We have
reviewed your account and the information included within your appeal. Unfortunately after careful consideration the
information submitted with your appeal does not adequately justify removal of the suspension. I can confirm that your
website was indeed providing links to a Runescape Private Server Client, which is being redistributed in violation of the
Runescape EULA and Terms of Use, which also means it's violating their copyright. This is not an action we allow in any way,
shape, or form.

In accordance with the x10Hosting Terms of Service and Acceptable Use Policy agreed to upon registration the suspension will
remain permanently. This decision is final.

At this time, data backups are not available as detailed in sections 6 and 8 of the x10Hosting Terms of Service.

http://x10hosting.com/terms

Best regards,
The x10Hosting Abuse Team&lt;/blockquote&gt;

" I can confirm that your
website was indeed providing links to a Runescape Private Server Client, which is being redistributed in violation of the
Runescape EULA and Terms of Use, which also means it's violating their copyright. This is not an action we allow in any way,
shape, or form."


So a redirect to mega.co.nz is a bannable offense. as well as a redirect to a webclient php.



~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~

UPDATE:


Now they banned EVERY single account I had that was not related to RuneScape at all. (good news is they messed up and i got EVERYTHING backed up :P so cheers!)</code></pre>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/welp-its-being-done-again-x10hositng-horror-story/529803/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/welp-its-being-done-again-x10hositng-horror-story/529803/1</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2013 22:21:41 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-529803-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/welp-its-being-done-again-x10hositng-horror-story/529803.rss">Welp. it&#39;s being done again (x10hositng horror story)</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
