<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Client Connection IP</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/client-connection-ip/524791</link>
    <description>Well, to start off, I don&#39;t have a VPS and I&#39;m in the early stages of development for my RSPS. We don&#39;t have an official client yet and we&#39;d all like to connect to the server to test dupes, bugs, and glitches. I can connect fine with localhost, but I&#39;d have to open my ports etc. for my team members to connect and then when they&#39;re hosting they&#39;d have to do the same thing and we&#39;d have to change client IP&#39;s to connect to them. So I was wondering this: would it be possible to make a domain as the server IP? We could keep the IP the same forever inside of the client and just change where the domain points. Is this possible? If it is, what do I have to do? Is there another way to solve this problem?


A VPS is out of the question for right now as we&#39;re all scrounging up money at the moment. Our budget is like $30 and we want a good VPS, we don&#39;t want to waste it on a cheap one now and not have the money later or buy a good one now and not have money when it&#39;s time to release.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 14 Jul 2013 20:49:51 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Game Development</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/client-connection-ip/524791.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Client Connection IP</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Shorty626 Shorty626]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/shorty626">@Shorty626</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>All you need to do is set the IP inside the client to a DNS name. Like <a href="http://example.com" rel="nofollow noopener">example.com</a> then change the DNS to point to the team member you have hosting the project. Tbh though if you are working with multiple people, you’d be better off just creating a repository and having one person compile and run the server when changes are made rather than decide who will host and what parts of your code have changed. Then you eliminate all of those problems in the first place.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/client-connection-ip/524791/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/client-connection-ip/524791/2</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 14 Jul 2013 20:49:51 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-524791-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/client-connection-ip/524791.rss">Client Connection IP</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Client Connection IP</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@DaGamerChild DaGamerChild]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/dagamerchild">@DaGamerChild</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Well, to start off, I don’t have a VPS and I’m in the early stages of development for my RSPS. We don’t have an official client yet and we’d all like to connect to the server to test dupes, bugs, and glitches. I can connect fine with localhost, but I’d have to open my ports etc. for my team members to connect and then when they’re hosting they’d have to do the same thing and we’d have to change client IP’s to connect to them. So I was wondering this: would it be possible to make a domain as the server IP? We could keep the IP the same forever inside of the client and just change where the domain points. Is this possible? If it is, what do I have to do? Is there another way to solve this problem?</p>
<p>A VPS is out of the question for right now as we’re all scrounging up money at the moment. Our budget is like $30 and we want a good VPS, we don’t want to waste it on a cheap one now and not have the money later or buy a good one now and not have money when it’s time to release.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/client-connection-ip/524791/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/client-connection-ip/524791/1</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 12 Jul 2013 22:35:14 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-524791-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/client-connection-ip/524791.rss">Client Connection IP</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
