<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Haha Republicans Lost and Democrats Own EVERYTHING!</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/haha-republicans-lost-and-democrats-own-everything/23325</link>
    <description>Haha Republicans Lost and Democrats Own EVERYTHING!!!

Yes. Democrats have a majority in the House and it&#39;s VERY close majority in the Senate. In the Senate, Democrats have 50% and Republicans have 49%, everybody is waiting on that last percent.

Finally the Military Commissions Act, can be rejected hopefully. The Patriot act can go fuck itself and Bush won&#39;t be able to take away any more of our rights (hopefully). Just two more years.... just two more years. :D

If anyone wants to read about the Bush Human Torture act I was talking about. [url=http://www.nytimes.com/2006/09/28/opinion/28thu1.html?ei=5088&amp;en=3eb3b23c27944ff9&amp;ex=1317096000&amp;adxnnl=1&amp;partner=rssnyt&amp;emc=rss&amp;adxnnlx=1163030486]Refer to this article.[/url]

If anyone wants to argue what the [url=http://www.epic.org/privacy/terrorism/hr3162.html]patriot act[/url] [i]really[/i] does, read the act and see what it does first. Oh by the way, it&#39;s called the patriot act, so that if any one is against it, then they are supposedly unpatriotic. Fuck them if you think so. Anyone not against this law is unpatriotic and a terrorist (someone causing terror. You don&#39;t have to be blowing up bombs to cause terror).

~Ron

PS: I&#39;m so fucking happy.  :D

Edit: Democrats one majority in congress too! WOO HOO! Now they got the job, hopefully they can do it right. War is not over yet. Oh and I found the name of the act that let bush torture whoever he wanted on any premises. It&#39;s called &quot;Military Commissions Act&quot;.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 10 Nov 2006 17:39:10 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>General Discussion</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/haha-republicans-lost-and-democrats-own-everything/23325.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Haha Republicans Lost and Democrats Own EVERYTHING!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@O_M_F_G O M F G]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/o_m_f_g">@O_M_F_G</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Also plain BOMBS…(the ones droped by BOMBERS, if you can’t find a link between theese 2 I feel sorry for you)</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/haha-republicans-lost-and-democrats-own-everything/23325/45">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/haha-republicans-lost-and-democrats-own-everything/23325/45</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 Nov 2006 17:39:10 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-23325-45</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/haha-republicans-lost-and-democrats-own-everything/23325.rss">Haha Republicans Lost and Democrats Own EVERYTHING!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Haha Republicans Lost and Democrats Own EVERYTHING!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@bumblescum bumblescum]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/bumblescum">@bumblescum</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>“Actually it’s still his country. Why don’t you go to china and preach your little laws with the emperor.”</p>
<p>The People’s Republic of China is a communist-controlled country where they have little freedoms.</p>
<p>“I’d like to see what you think of their opinion when your head is on a stick.”</p>
<p>Even if I were killed, it would have been done covertly. They have concentration camps you know. <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=9" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"></p>
<p>“China is part of the UN too, you know?”</p>
<p>And your point is? I never excused China of any wrong-doing.</p>
<p>“Um it doesn’t matter who put him in power”</p>
<p>This is true, however, the U.S. still played a large part by supporting the Ba’ath party.</p>
<p>“it doesn’t even matter that the US and Iraq were allies”</p>
<p>When did I say they were ever allies?</p>
<p>“Just because someone put him in power does not mean they own that person and whatever territory he keeps.”</p>
<p>This is also true, however, illegitimate. He obtained power illegally.</p>
<p>“Defend ourselves? Are you fucking kidding? No American died when he gassed the curds.”</p>
<p>True, but let’s take a look at the Gulf War (which never really ended anyway, considering Saddam was totally negligent during the U.N. peace process. I might also add that, we never really declared war on Iraq. Some would argue war was already declared due to Saddam’s violations.)</p>
<p>The number of coalition wounded in combat seems to have been less than 1,000. However, as of the year 2000, 183,000 U.S. veterans of the Gulf War, more than a quarter of the U.S. troops who participated in the War, have been declared permanently disabled by the Department of Veterans Affairs [1]. About 30% of the 700,000 men and women who served in U.S. forces in the Gulf War still suffer an array of serious symptoms whose causes are not fully understood [2].</p>
<p>"So why are you saying we “have a right to take up arms and defend ourselves”</p>
<p>If the country is hostile against the U.S. and our allies?</p>
<p>“Do you know why people went into the election in such a anti-republican way? Because of the Iraq war.”</p>
<p>Anti-Republican? It was a close race. The democrat strategy is insult, attack &amp; triumph. They have no real strategy for Iraq. All they are going to do these last two years is attack Bush and make him look unsuitable for the nation, which, trust me; will not gain any leverage for the democrats in the '08 election. The people do not want to hear of how much of a failure their leader is, they want to hear progress in Iraq, social policies as well as foreign policies. Will the democrats give them these things? Of course not. They’ll avoid it at all costs. JUST TO make the republican president look badly.</p>
<p>“If you still favor the iraq war, then I consider that unethical cause that’s our people dying there for no reason.”</p>
<p>How can you say such a thing? There is no reason? Are you blind? The impending civil war will be the immediate death of millions of people, and you say it’s not worth it?</p>
<p>“You really are fascist aren’t you?”</p>
<p>What? What does fascism have to do with this? <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=9" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"></p>
<p>“I was being radical to prove my point.”</p>
<p>Sorry, I failed to catch the sarcasm. <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=9" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"></p>
<p>“You’re saying it was the business of Canada and Britain to go and fight them?”</p>
<p>How about Israel? The Ba’athist rule of Iraq was radically socialist &amp; Islamic, hence the deaths of hundreds of thousands of secular Kurdish people in Southern Iraq. They would not conform to their radical belief, thus they die. Sad world isn’t it?</p>
<p>“Your ignorance is exponential. Bush admitted that there were no WMDs (nuclear weapons in their definition) and said intelligence failed.”</p>
<p>Could you back up this statement with a source? If what you say is true, then it invalidates my entire argument.</p>
<p>“Do you think Bush even gave a shit what the cost was?”</p>
<p>Considering the amount of money that pours into Iraq effects the people’s opinion of him, I’d say so.</p>
<p>“He thought he could just jump in there, take saddam down, everyone would be happy, and then we could get out.”</p>
<p>I’m sure everyone thought this.</p>
<p>“You are wrong. Look it up. Once again, Bush admitted it in public.”</p>
<p>He may have admitted to it, but intelligence does not lie, we have found mass stockpiles of Chemical weapons &amp; agents. It’s common fact. Perhaps it was not part of their original agenda, but it is still a smack in the face to those who don’t believe any good has come out of Iraq. Saddam was supposed to immediately dispose of all chemical weapons in accordance with the U.N., this just proves how negligent he really is.</p>
<p>You can’t ignore the global community, it keeps the world ticking, even if it is a wishy-washy organization.</p>
<p>“What the fuck? That doesn’t even make sense. Please prove your statements, don’t just rant about stuff you can’t back up.”</p>
<p>Here’s a good list of the U.N.'s failures. This list includes what I’m ranting about. <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=9" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"></p>
<p>"Other serious security failures include:</p>
<pre><code>* Failure to prevent the 1994 Rwandan genocide, which resulted in the killings of nearly a million people, due to the refusal of the security council members to approve any necessary military action.[21]
* Failure by MONUC (UNSC Resolution 1291) to effectively intervene during the Second Congo War, which claimed nearly five million people in the Democratic Republic of Congo (DRC), 1998-2002 (with fighting reportedly continuing), and in carrying out and distributing humanitarian aid.
* Failure to intervene in the 1995 Srebrenica massacre, despite the fact that the UN designated Srebrenica a "safe haven" for refugees and assigned 600 Dutch peacekeepers to protect it.
* Failure to successfully deliver food to starving people in Somalia; the food was instead usually seized by local warlords. A U.S./UN attempt to apprehend the warlords seizing these shipments resulted in the 1993 Battle of Mogadishu.
* Sexual abuse by UN peacekeepers. Peacekeepers from several nations have been repatriated from UN peacekeeping operations for sexually abusing and exploiting girls as young as 8 in a number of different peacekeeping missions. This abuse is ongoing despite many revelations and probes by the UN Office of Internal Oversight Services.[22][23] A 2005 internal UN investigation found that sexual exploitation and abuse has been reported in at least five countries where UN peacekeepers have been deployed, including the Democratic Republic of Congo, Haiti, Burundi, Côte d'Ivoire, and Liberia. [27] The BBC carried a similar report, and also cited a member of the World Food Programme as an offender.[24]"
</code></pre>
<p>“He doubled the deficit! We’re the biggest debtors in the entire world”</p>
<p>And, what reform plan do you have in mind that can fix this?</p>
<p>“??? We had foreign friends such as Canada, Mexico, Germany, France, and many more.”</p>
<p>Canada, again, Canada can’t not be our friend under NAFTA. They need us.</p>
<p>Mexico? Oh of course, their opposition to immigration reform is really helping us out. That’s their biggest source of income.</p>
<p>Germany? See NATO.</p>
<aside class="onebox wikipedia">
  <header class="source">
      <a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/NATO" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">en.wikipedia.org</a>
  </header>
  <article class="onebox-body">
    <div class="aspect-image" style="--aspect-ratio:150/78;"><img src="//upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/thumb/5/55/NATO_OTAN_landscape_logo.svg/150px-NATO_OTAN_landscape_logo.svg.png" class="thumbnail"></div>

<h3><a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/NATO" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">NATO</a></h3>

<p>
 



 The North Atlantic Treaty Organization (NATO /ˈneɪtoʊ/; French: Organisation du traité de l'Atlantique nord; OTAN), also called the North Atlantic Alliance, is an intergovernmental military alliance between 29 North American and European countries. The organization implements the North Atlantic Treaty that was signed on 4 April 1949. NATO constitutes a system of collective defence whereby its independent member states agree to mutual defence in response to an attack by any external party. ...</p>

  </article>
  <div class="onebox-metadata">
    
    
  </div>
  <div style="clear: both"></div>
</aside>

<p>France? See NATO.</p>
<p>“Ever since the Iraq war, a lot of people didn’t back up the US at first, so Bush openly called them names, etc.”</p>
<p>Where’s your source for this? <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=9" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"></p>
<p>“That pissed them off and Canada + Britain entered the war and Canada withdrew their soldiers”</p>
<p>Britain is still in Iraq.</p>
<p>“So far America has almost no foreign friends.”</p>
<p>Yes, we’re so anti-social. <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/frowning.png?v=9" title=":frowning:" class="emoji" alt=":frowning:"></p>
<p>“How would you like it if they brought back the draft,”</p>
<p>They don’t need to reinstate the draft, we have enough volunteer soldiers in Iraq. <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=9" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"></p>
<p>"and you would get sent there fighting the war and you can laugh at someone cutting off your balls. "</p>
<p>Such confrontations are highly rare, indeed, most warfare is now fought with suicide bombs, roadside bombs &amp; car bombs.</p>
<p>EDIT: I’d like to apologize for the sloppy format, your quoting system confuses me greatly. <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/frowning.png?v=9" title=":frowning:" class="emoji" alt=":frowning:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/haha-republicans-lost-and-democrats-own-everything/23325/44">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/haha-republicans-lost-and-democrats-own-everything/23325/44</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 Nov 2006 14:53:05 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-23325-44</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/haha-republicans-lost-and-democrats-own-everything/23325.rss">Haha Republicans Lost and Democrats Own EVERYTHING!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Haha Republicans Lost and Democrats Own EVERYTHING!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@cruel cruel]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/cruel">@cruel</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>^Yeah, sry.<br>
He mentions a draft later on… redirect that comment there. <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/wink.png?v=9" title=":wink:" class="emoji" alt=":wink:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/haha-republicans-lost-and-democrats-own-everything/23325/43">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/haha-republicans-lost-and-democrats-own-everything/23325/43</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 Nov 2006 12:56:46 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-23325-43</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/haha-republicans-lost-and-democrats-own-everything/23325.rss">Haha Republicans Lost and Democrats Own EVERYTHING!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Haha Republicans Lost and Democrats Own EVERYTHING!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@googlethis googlethis]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/googlethis">@googlethis</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“cruel, post:41, topic:23325”][quote author=Ron link=topic=35494.msg431565#msg431565 date=1163155078]<br>
Do you know why people went into the election in such a anti-republican way? Because of the Iraq war. If you still favor the iraq war, then I consider that unethical cause that’s our people dying there for no reason. If you sign up for the war, which I bet you won’t, then you can say what you wish while a guy with an AK 47 is shooting at you and your own blood breaks your fall when your legs collapse.[/quote]<br>
There won’t be a draft rofl, we won’t need it. So of course I won’t join the military (not to mention I agree with John Kerry that the military is for uneducated folk [and criminals]… :D)<br>
We can just fire up our practically infinite arsenal or long-range weapons if it gets to that point.[/quote]<br>
He never said anything about a draft. Oh, and think about it… Firing a weapon at the middle east is a bad idea. It would be worse than Hiroshima and Nagasaki because 1. It’ll just anger people further. 2. Bombing the middle east would probably hurt Israel too. 3. It’s not government-condoned, bombing the place would only create more terrorists.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/haha-republicans-lost-and-democrats-own-everything/23325/42">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/haha-republicans-lost-and-democrats-own-everything/23325/42</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 Nov 2006 12:28:36 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-23325-42</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/haha-republicans-lost-and-democrats-own-everything/23325.rss">Haha Republicans Lost and Democrats Own EVERYTHING!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Haha Republicans Lost and Democrats Own EVERYTHING!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@cruel cruel]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/cruel">@cruel</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote no-group quote-modified" data-post="40" data-topic="23325">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/ron/40/5_6259e4fa9dfe0dec282fb0955bb1974c.png" class="avatar"> Ron:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Actually it’s still his country. Why don’t you go to china and preach your little laws with the emperor. I’d like to see what you think of their opinion when your head is on a stick. China is part of the UN too, you know?</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Hrmm… didn’t know there was a genocide going on in China. Which one is that now?</p>
<aside class="quote no-group quote-modified" data-post="40" data-topic="23325">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/ron/40/5_6259e4fa9dfe0dec282fb0955bb1974c.png" class="avatar"> Ron:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Defend ourselves? Are you fucking kidding? No American died when he gassed the curds. He didn’t gas the Americans. So why are you saying we “have a right to take up arms and defend ourselves”.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Americans are the only people that matter? You’re quite clearly saying this.<br>
How about you stop being a selfish cunt and start caring about the lives of foreigners. Believe it or not, they are actual people too… or so I have read.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group quote-modified" data-post="40" data-topic="23325">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/ron/40/5_6259e4fa9dfe0dec282fb0955bb1974c.png" class="avatar"> Ron:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Do you know why people went into the election in such a anti-republican way? Because of the Iraq war. If you still favor the iraq war, then I consider that unethical cause that’s our people dying there for no reason. If you sign up for the war, which I bet you won’t, then you can say what you wish while a guy with an AK 47 is shooting at you and your own blood breaks your fall when your legs collapse.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>There won’t be a draft rofl, we won’t need it. So of course I won’t join the military (not to mention I agree with John Kerry that the military is for uneducated folk [and criminals]… :D)<br>
We can just fire up our practically infinite arsenal or long-range weapons if it gets to that point.<br>
And this war has saved lives… so I don’t know what you’re going on about:<br>
<a href="http://www.weeklystandard.com/Content/Public/Articles/000/000/003/889tngrz.asp" class="onebox" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">http://www.weeklystandard.com/Content/Public/Articles/000/000/003/889tngrz.asp</a><br>
The roughtly 3000 american lives over the past 5 years is nothing compared to the sometimes 1000 lives per day that were being executed. Come on… try using your head?<br>
But of course… American lives are the only ones that matter. :rolleyes:</p>
<p>[quote=“Ron, post:40, topic:23325”][quote]<br>
“THERE WERE NO FUCKING WEAPONS! IT WAS A FACT!”<br>
Refer to my article bub. You are quite wrong. <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=9" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"><br>
[/quote]<br>
You are wrong. Look it up. Once again, Bush admitted it in public.[/quote]<br>
Ermm…<br>
<aside class="onebox whitelistedgeneric">
  <header class="source">
      <img src="https://www.newsmax.com/App_Themes/Newsmax/images/favicon.ico" class="site-icon" width="16" height="16">
      <a href="https://www.newsmax.com" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Newsmax</a>
  </header>
  <article class="onebox-body">
    <div class="aspect-image" style="--aspect-ratio:690/362;"><img src="https://www.newsmax.com/App_Themes/NewsmaxNew/images/NM01.png" class="thumbnail"></div>

<h3><a href="https://www.newsmax.com" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Newsmax.com - Breaking news from around the globe</a></h3>

<p>Newsmax.com reports today’s news headlines, live news stream, news videos from Americans and global readers
seeking the latest in current events, politics, U.S., world news, health, finance, and more.</p>


  </article>
  <div class="onebox-metadata">
    
    
  </div>
  <div style="clear: both"></div>
</aside>
<br>
One of many reports of weapons. But as far as WMDs, I suppose not.</p>
<p>[quote=“Ron, post:40, topic:23325”][quote]<br>
“The U.N. is helping a ton on keeping the world together”</p>
<p>By raping innocent women &amp; children in poverty stricken areas? Oh, of course.<br>
[/quote]<br>
What the fuck? That doesn’t even make sense. Please prove your statements, don’t just rant about stuff you can’t back up.[/quote]<br>
He’s most likely talking about the fact that the UN doesn’t do much for countries under mass killing regimes. The Saddam regime is just one example.<br>
But of course… that pointless to bring up since you don’t care about the lives of others.<br>
Fuck those millions of jews, we should never have gotten into WWII except to take out Japan to ouor defense… :rollseyes:</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-post="40" data-topic="23325">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/ron/40/5_6259e4fa9dfe0dec282fb0955bb1974c.png" class="avatar"> Ron:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Why do you think Hugo Chavez called him the Anti Christ? How senile are you?</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Because he’s a retard.<br>
(honestly)</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/haha-republicans-lost-and-democrats-own-everything/23325/41">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/haha-republicans-lost-and-democrats-own-everything/23325/41</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 Nov 2006 11:26:13 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-23325-41</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/haha-republicans-lost-and-democrats-own-everything/23325.rss">Haha Republicans Lost and Democrats Own EVERYTHING!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Haha Republicans Lost and Democrats Own EVERYTHING!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Ron Ron]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/ron">@Ron</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“bumblescum, post:33, topic:23325”]“Saddam can do whatever he wants.”</p>
<p>Actually, he has to correspond with some set of U.N. guidelines. Mass killing of innocent people isn’t too favored in the global community. :P[/quote]<br>
Actually it’s still his country. Why don’t you go to china and preach your little laws with the emperor. I’d like to see what you think of their opinion when your head is on a stick. China is part of the UN too, you know?</p>
<blockquote>"It's his country."
<p>No it wasn’t? He came to power due to a military coup that was supported by the U.S. So, essentially, it’s our country; had we not helped during this military coup, Saddam would be a sitting duck. <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=9" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"></p>
</blockquote><br>
Um it doesn’t matter who put him in power, it doesn’t even matter that the US and Iraq were allies, what matters is who was controlling the country. He was a dictator, and that was his country. Just because someone put him in power does not mean they own that person and whatever territory he keeps.
<blockquote>"Who the fuck died and left America in charge?"
<p>No one did, but when an establishment that is bent on peace actively fails at securing our nation’s interests, as well as the interests of our allies, then we have a right to take up arms and defend ourselves. Do you know why Germany, France &amp; Russia were opposed to the War in Iraq? Germany had oil ties with Iraq, which is a complete violation of U.N. imposed sanctions, France the same as Germany, and Russia was covertly selling MUNITIONS to Iraq. Yay for the opposition. <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=9" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"></p>
</blockquote><br>
Defend ourselves? Are you fucking kidding? No American died when he gassed the curds. He didn’t gas the Americans. So why are you saying we “have a right to take up arms and defend ourselves”. Do you know why people went into the election in such a anti-republican way? Because of the Iraq war. If you still favor the iraq war, then I consider that unethical cause that’s our people dying there for no reason. If you sign up for the war, which I bet you won’t, then you can say what you wish while a guy with an AK 47 is shooting at you and your own blood breaks your fall when your legs collapse.
<blockquote>"If someone came into my home, I would tell them to fuck off. If they still didn't then I would have them killed."
<p>Refer back to your own civil rights mumbo-jumbo.</p>
</blockquote><br>
You really are fascist aren’t you? Civil Rights mumbo jumbo. You really are demented. Do you like having rights? If you don’t, I suggest you go to N. Korea and have an orgy.
<blockquote>"I'm surprised he didn't kill the UN inspectors"
<p>Uh, because he had some form of intelligence? He would’ve been in such deep shit if he did that.</p>
</blockquote><br>
I was being radical to prove my point.
<blockquote>"Again, it was not our business."
<p>Okay, but it WAS the business of our allies. <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=9" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"></p>
</blockquote><br>
You’re saying it was the business of Canada and Britain to go and fight them? That doesn’t even make sense. but at least you admitted that it wasn’t our business. Some progress there…
<blockquote>"He didn't have nuclear weapons"
<p>That was never the original debate in the first place, it was his capability of W.M.D.'s</p>
</blockquote><br>
No kidding.
<blockquote>And according to Wikipedia, a W.M.D. can be defined as the following:
<p>“Terms used in a military context include atomic, biological, and chemical warfare (ABC warfare), nuclear, biological, and chemical (NBC) after the invention of the hydrogen bomb, and chemical, biological, radiological, and nuclear (CBRN), recognizing the threat of non-explosive radiological weapons.”</p>
</blockquote><br>
And according to reality, when Rumsfield was talking about WMD’s, he was talking about Nuclear Weapons. No one is going nitty gritty into the definitions.
<blockquote>We have found stockpiles of Chemical weapons &amp; agents. If you had read the article I had posted, your ignorance would have dwindled by just a bit. ;)</blockquote>
Your ignorance is exponential. Bush admitted that there were no WMDs (nuclear weapons in their definition) and said intelligence failed. 
<blockquote>"Him gassing the curds didn't have anything to do with us."
<p>Refer back to your Civil Rights mumbo-jumbo. <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=9" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"></p>
</blockquote><br>
Again mumbo jumbo civil rights. Take your facist ass back to Nazi Germany man.
<blockquote>"We just pretended that we felt bad for them just to get an excuse to invade the country."
<p>And lose $400,000,000,000 in the mix. Oh yes, we’re quite the war-mongering country. <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=9" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"></p>
</blockquote><br>
Do you think Bush even gave a shit what the cost was? He’s just thinking one day, oh hey, I’m going to spend 400 billion dollars on a war. No he wasn’t thinking that. He thought he could just jump in there, take saddam down, everyone would be happy, and then we could get out. Everyone though it would be a half year war until the shit hit the fan.
<blockquote>"THERE WERE NO FUCKING WEAPONS! IT WAS A FACT!"
<p>Refer to my article bub. You are quite wrong. <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=9" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"></p>
</blockquote><br>
You are wrong. Look it up. Once again, Bush admitted it in public.
<blockquote>"The U.N. is helping a ton on keeping the world together"
<p>By raping innocent women &amp; children in poverty stricken areas? Oh, of course.</p>
</blockquote><br>
What the fuck? That doesn’t even make sense. Please prove your statements, don’t just rant about stuff you can’t back up.
<blockquote>"Bush came and fucked it up"
<p>How, exactly? By invading one country, the U.S. has seemed to disrupt all world politics? Please…</p>
</blockquote><br>
He doubled the deficit! We’re the biggest debtors in the entire world and you’re jerking off to this whole thing? He did fuck it up. Why do you think people call him the worst president in the world? Why do you think Hugo Chavez called him the Anti Christ? How senile are you?
<blockquote>"Did you know, our foreign friends of the US has diminished to almost nothing?"
<p>Like?</p>
</blockquote><br>
??? We had foreign friends such as Canada, Mexico, Germany, France, and many more. Ever since the Iraq war, a lot of people didn’t back up the US at first, so Bush openly called them names, etc. That pissed them off and Canada + Britain entered the war and Canada withdrew their soldiers. So far America has almost no foreign friends.
<blockquote>"Canada was pissed off because US withdrew a lot of there troops from Afghanistan and Canada was stuck there fighting the war,"
<p>Haha, it doesn’t really matter if Canada was pissed, they’re still bound to NAFTA. So really, we haven’t lost a great friend.</p>
</blockquote><br>
You would laugh about that? How would you like it if they brought back the draft, and you would get sent there fighting the war and you can laugh at someone cutting off your balls.
<p>~Ron</p>
<p>Edit: I forgot to mention. Democrats one majority in Congress too. Yay!</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/haha-republicans-lost-and-democrats-own-everything/23325/40">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/haha-republicans-lost-and-democrats-own-everything/23325/40</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 Nov 2006 10:37:58 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-23325-40</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/haha-republicans-lost-and-democrats-own-everything/23325.rss">Haha Republicans Lost and Democrats Own EVERYTHING!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Haha Republicans Lost and Democrats Own EVERYTHING!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Pyro Pyro]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/pyro">@Pyro</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>sometimes i truley think i live in the best country in the world <em>(New Zealand)</em> i mean we seem to keep out of all this crap by a mile. I think a person with half a brain would have thoguht saddam had WMDS. I mean hindsight sure is great isnt it. Way back when invasion started im sure you guys would have had your mouths securley zipped. But now that its gone and past. You can all say o yess i thought that all along. Its like when a sports team wins in a national league that you dont neccesarily support. Then your like o yes i suppoest them through and through.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/haha-republicans-lost-and-democrats-own-everything/23325/39">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/haha-republicans-lost-and-democrats-own-everything/23325/39</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 Nov 2006 09:00:17 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-23325-39</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/haha-republicans-lost-and-democrats-own-everything/23325.rss">Haha Republicans Lost and Democrats Own EVERYTHING!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Haha Republicans Lost and Democrats Own EVERYTHING!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@bumblescum bumblescum]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/bumblescum">@bumblescum</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>“We still got Osama 2 worry about…”</p>
<p>He never had any power in Iraq.</p>
<p>“(the internet represents you and the internet, while Firefox represents Firefox and me)”</p>
<p>I use Opera/Firefox. &gt;_&gt;</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/haha-republicans-lost-and-democrats-own-everything/23325/38">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/haha-republicans-lost-and-democrats-own-everything/23325/38</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 Nov 2006 08:47:55 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-23325-38</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/haha-republicans-lost-and-democrats-own-everything/23325.rss">Haha Republicans Lost and Democrats Own EVERYTHING!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Haha Republicans Lost and Democrats Own EVERYTHING!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@O_M_F_G O M F G]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/o_m_f_g">@O_M_F_G</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“bumblescum, post:36, topic:23325”]“however it’s a country we are going to war with, not just Sadam!”</p>
<p>The war’s over &amp; Saddam’s regime abolished.[/quote]<br>
We still got Osama 2 worry about…<br>
P.S.<br>
<img src="http://smileys.sur-la-toile.com/repository/Firefox/firefox25.gif" alt width="" height=""><br>
(the internet represents you and the internet, while Firefox represents Firefox and me)</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/haha-republicans-lost-and-democrats-own-everything/23325/37">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/haha-republicans-lost-and-democrats-own-everything/23325/37</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 Nov 2006 08:30:37 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-23325-37</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/haha-republicans-lost-and-democrats-own-everything/23325.rss">Haha Republicans Lost and Democrats Own EVERYTHING!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Haha Republicans Lost and Democrats Own EVERYTHING!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@bumblescum bumblescum]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/bumblescum">@bumblescum</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>“however it’s a country we are going to war with, not just Sadam!”</p>
<p>The war’s over &amp; Saddam’s regime abolished.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/haha-republicans-lost-and-democrats-own-everything/23325/36">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/haha-republicans-lost-and-democrats-own-everything/23325/36</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 Nov 2006 07:09:33 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-23325-36</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/haha-republicans-lost-and-democrats-own-everything/23325.rss">Haha Republicans Lost and Democrats Own EVERYTHING!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Haha Republicans Lost and Democrats Own EVERYTHING!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@O_M_F_G O M F G]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/o_m_f_g">@O_M_F_G</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote no-group" data-post="21" data-topic="23325">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/pyro/40/5_6259e4fa9dfe0dec282fb0955bb1974c.png" class="avatar"> Pyro:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Im going to have to disagree with you there ron. Even though i dont live in US i still know that saddam was a crazy and relentless torturer. He is not getting hanged because we invaded his country. He is getting hanged because he murdered 100s of people. They have found torture chambers with live cables hanging from the ceilings. Ready to shock the crap out of some civilian.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I must agree, but I’m also sure that Bush wouldn’t mind taking control of their oil iether, however it’s a country we are going to war with, not just Sadam!</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/haha-republicans-lost-and-democrats-own-everything/23325/35">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/haha-republicans-lost-and-democrats-own-everything/23325/35</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 Nov 2006 07:06:08 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-23325-35</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/haha-republicans-lost-and-democrats-own-everything/23325.rss">Haha Republicans Lost and Democrats Own EVERYTHING!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Haha Republicans Lost and Democrats Own EVERYTHING!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@bullzeye95 bullzeye]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/bullzeye95">@bullzeye95</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“moparisthebest, post:32, topic:23325”]Oh well, it probably won’t last for long when the american people see how bad the democrats screw them over.  I voted almost straight republican (personally I am an independent and vote for whomever I think to be the better person), but at least the minimum wage issue and smoking ban passed in my state, so I am partially happy. :)[/quote]<img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/smiley.png?v=9" title=":smiley:" class="emoji" alt=":smiley:"></p>
<p>mopar and bumblescum are cool.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/haha-republicans-lost-and-democrats-own-everything/23325/34">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/haha-republicans-lost-and-democrats-own-everything/23325/34</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 Nov 2006 06:30:30 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-23325-34</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/haha-republicans-lost-and-democrats-own-everything/23325.rss">Haha Republicans Lost and Democrats Own EVERYTHING!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Haha Republicans Lost and Democrats Own EVERYTHING!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@bumblescum bumblescum]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/bumblescum">@bumblescum</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>“So you think it’s ok to take someone away for any reason no matter what it is?”</p>
<p>Never did I hint at such a thing, stop putting words in my mouth.</p>
<p>“Turn off Fox News and wake up.”</p>
<p>I don’t watch Fox News, and shame on you for assuming so. <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=9" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"></p>
<p>“If you don’t believe in civil rights,”</p>
<p>Quite the master of at putting words into other’s mouths. <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=9" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"></p>
<p>“Saddam can do whatever he wants.”</p>
<p>Actually, he has to correspond with some set of U.N. guidelines. Mass killing of innocent people isn’t too favored in the global community. <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=9" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"></p>
<p>“It’s his country.”</p>
<p>No it wasn’t? He came to power due to a military coup that was supported by the U.S. So, essentially, it’s our country; had we not helped during this military coup, Saddam would be a sitting duck. <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=9" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"></p>
<p>“Who the fuck died and left America in charge?”</p>
<p>No one did, but when an establishment that is bent on peace actively fails at securing our nation’s interests, as well as the interests of our allies, then we have a right to take up arms and defend ourselves. Do you know why Germany, France &amp; Russia were opposed to the War in Iraq? Germany had oil ties with Iraq, which is a complete violation of U.N. imposed sanctions, France the same as Germany, and Russia was covertly selling MUNITIONS to Iraq. Yay for the opposition. <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=9" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"></p>
<p>“If someone came into my home, I would tell them to fuck off. If they still didn’t then I would have them killed.”</p>
<p>Refer back to your own civil rights mumbo-jumbo.</p>
<p>“I’m surprised he didn’t kill the UN inspectors”</p>
<p>Uh, because he had some form of intelligence? He would’ve been in such deep shit if he did that.</p>
<p>“Again, it was not our business.”</p>
<p>Okay, but it WAS the business of our allies. <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=9" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"></p>
<p>“He didn’t have nuclear weapons”</p>
<p>That was never the original debate in the first place, it was his capability of W.M.D.'s</p>
<p>And according to Wikipedia, a W.M.D. can be defined as the following:</p>
<p>“Terms used in a military context include atomic, biological, and chemical warfare (ABC warfare), nuclear, biological, and chemical (NBC) after the invention of the hydrogen bomb, and chemical, biological, radiological, and nuclear (CBRN), recognizing the threat of non-explosive radiological weapons.”</p>
<p>We have found stockpiles of Chemical weapons &amp; agents. If you had read the article I had posted, your ignorance would have dwindled by just a bit. <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/wink.png?v=9" title=":wink:" class="emoji" alt=":wink:"></p>
<p>“Him gassing the curds didn’t have anything to do with us.”</p>
<p>Refer back to your Civil Rights mumbo-jumbo. <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=9" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"></p>
<p>“We just pretended that we felt bad for them just to get an excuse to invade the country.”</p>
<p>And lose $400,000,000,000 in the mix. Oh yes, we’re quite the war-mongering country. <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=9" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"></p>
<p>“THERE WERE NO FUCKING WEAPONS! IT WAS A FACT!”</p>
<p>Refer to my article bub. You are quite wrong. <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=9" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"></p>
<p>“The U.N. is helping a ton on keeping the world together”</p>
<p>By raping innocent women &amp; children in poverty stricken areas? Oh, of course.</p>
<p>“Bush came and fucked it up”</p>
<p>How, exactly? By invading one country, the U.S. has seemed to disrupt all world politics? Please…</p>
<p>“Did you know, our foreign friends of the US has diminished to almost nothing?”</p>
<p>Like?</p>
<p>“Canada was pissed off because US withdrew a lot of there troops from Afghanistan and Canada was stuck there fighting the war,”</p>
<p>Haha, it doesn’t really matter if Canada was pissed, they’re still bound to NAFTA. So really, we haven’t lost a great friend.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/haha-republicans-lost-and-democrats-own-everything/23325/33">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/haha-republicans-lost-and-democrats-own-everything/23325/33</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 Nov 2006 06:24:55 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-23325-33</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/haha-republicans-lost-and-democrats-own-everything/23325.rss">Haha Republicans Lost and Democrats Own EVERYTHING!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Haha Republicans Lost and Democrats Own EVERYTHING!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@moparisthebest Moparisthebest]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/moparisthebest">@moparisthebest</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Oh well, it probably won’t last for long when the american people see how bad the democrats screw them over.  I voted almost straight republican (personally I am an independent and vote for whomever I think to be the better person), but at least the minimum wage issue and smoking ban passed in my state, so I am partially happy. <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=9" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/haha-republicans-lost-and-democrats-own-everything/23325/32">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/haha-republicans-lost-and-democrats-own-everything/23325/32</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 Nov 2006 06:01:57 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-23325-32</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/haha-republicans-lost-and-democrats-own-everything/23325.rss">Haha Republicans Lost and Democrats Own EVERYTHING!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Haha Republicans Lost and Democrats Own EVERYTHING!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Ron Ron]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/ron">@Ron</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“bumblescum, post:16, topic:23325”]“You can be one of those ‘dissappearing people’ we heard about”</p>
<p>There are twelve thousand Georgians missing from Russia, is there any public outcry against<br>
that? Oh of course not. Always targeting it at the big guy.[/quote]<br>
So you think it’s ok to take someone away for any reason no matter what it is? Turn off Fox News and wake up. If you don’t believe in civil rights, then you sir are a terrorist and I won’t even bother reading whatever you say. I don’t want to be contaminated with bubble scum.</p>
<p>[quote=“bumblescum, post:20, topic:23325”]“and we did just use 9/11 as an excuse to go into another mans country. we were never having problems with him or anything.”</p>
<p>So, Saddam kicking U.N. weapon’s inspectors out of his country for no apparent reason? It’s been an ongoing battle with Saddam, he was totally negligent during the U.N. peace process.[/quote]<br>
Saddam can do whatever he wants. It’s his country. We have no right to go into another man’s home and tell him what to do. Who the fuck died and left America in charge? If someone came into my home, I would tell them to fuck off. If they still didn’t then I would have them killed. I’m surprised he didn’t kill the UN inspectors.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-post="21" data-topic="23325">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/pyro/40/5_6259e4fa9dfe0dec282fb0955bb1974c.png" class="avatar"> Pyro:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Im going to have to disagree with you there ron. Even though i dont live in US i still know that saddam was a crazy and relentless torturer. He is not getting hanged because we invaded his country. He is getting hanged because he murdered 100s of people. They have found torture chambers with live cables hanging from the ceilings. Ready to shock the crap out of some civilian.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Again, it was not our business. He didn’t have nuclear weapons. Him gassing the curds didn’t have anything to do with us. We just pretended that we felt bad for them just to get an excuse to invade the country. Like I said before, nobody died and left America in charge of the world.</p>
<p>[quote=“BobDole81, post:23, topic:23325”]Yep, I’m glad we have democratic control now.  We were celebrating yesterday over the senatorial win and the resignation of Rumsfeld <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=9" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"></p>
<p>No doubts there, of course Saddam committed many crimes in the past.  But it was in the past.  Making him accountable for his acts was never the issue, it was going into Iraq under false pretenses.  We went in because of threats of weapons of mass destruction and involvement with 9/11, not because he was a bad person.  Why not get UN assistance to have his regime overthrown and let him be tried by the international court?  The UN only refused to invade because of insufficient evidence of WMD’s…so I don’t disagree that he should be hanged, just the way we went about doing it.[/quote]<br>
Exactly! BobDole, you’re very smart. And that comment isn’t given in terms of politics in ignoramus country.</p>
<p>[quote=“bumblescum, post:24, topic:23325”]“The UN only refused to invade because of insufficient evidence of WMD’s”</p>
<p>Insufficient? Okay sure, their weapon’s inspectors getting forcibly removed from the country, yeah, there’s nothing going on there.[/quote]<br>
THERE WERE NO FUCKING WEAPONS! IT WAS A FACT!</p>
<p>The Bush administration, when questioned, said “Intelligence Failed” when they were asked “Why did we attack Iraq when there was no evidence of Weapons of Mass destruction”. Fuck you, intelligence didn’t fail. They lied. And Saddam shouldn’t be hung. The administration should be! AND ALSO! The whole war was illegal! Congress didn’t even give Bush the right to do it, and that retarded jack ass did it any way. That man should be impeached and imprisoned until he suffers the consequences of of ass fucking the USA.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-post="24" data-topic="23325">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/bumblescum/40/5_6259e4fa9dfe0dec282fb0955bb1974c.png" class="avatar"> bumblescum:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>The U.N. Is a failed establishment, much like the League of Nations.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Are you serious? The U.N. is helping a ton on keeping the world together until Bush came and fucked it up. Did you know, our foreign friends of the US has diminished to almost nothing? Our only friends now is Kazakhstan and Britain. Canada was pissed off because US withdrew a lot of there troops from Afghanistan and Canada was stuck there fighting the war, much like when we went into Vietnam because of the French, and the French pulled out.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group quote-modified" data-post="28" data-topic="23325">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/mjordan/40/5_6259e4fa9dfe0dec282fb0955bb1974c.png" class="avatar"> mjordan:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>yeah i think thats pretty damn hilarious that the reason we claimed to go over there is because of WMD’s and where are they now?? there never was any ROFL. poor poor Bush, i feel sorry for you…NOT!!!</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p><img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/smiley.png?v=9" title=":smiley:" class="emoji" alt=":smiley:"></p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-post="29" data-topic="23325">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/thiefmn6092/40/5_6259e4fa9dfe0dec282fb0955bb1974c.png" class="avatar"> thiefmn6092:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>I think someone woke up on the wrong side of the rock?</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>You have no point and your entire statement doesn’t make any sense. Please don’t post unless you have a brain. I should make that a disclaimer in all my posts.</p>
<p>~Ron</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/haha-republicans-lost-and-democrats-own-everything/23325/31">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/haha-republicans-lost-and-democrats-own-everything/23325/31</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 Nov 2006 05:38:18 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-23325-31</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/haha-republicans-lost-and-democrats-own-everything/23325.rss">Haha Republicans Lost and Democrats Own EVERYTHING!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Haha Republicans Lost and Democrats Own EVERYTHING!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@mjordan mjordan]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/mjordan">@mjordan</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>or not. maybe some of us are just democrats thiefmn</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/haha-republicans-lost-and-democrats-own-everything/23325/30">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/haha-republicans-lost-and-democrats-own-everything/23325/30</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 Nov 2006 05:05:43 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-23325-30</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/haha-republicans-lost-and-democrats-own-everything/23325.rss">Haha Republicans Lost and Democrats Own EVERYTHING!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Haha Republicans Lost and Democrats Own EVERYTHING!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@thiefmn6092 thiefmn6092]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/thiefmn6092">@thiefmn6092</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“Ron, post:1, topic:23325”]Haha Republicans Lost and Democrats Own EVERYTHING!!!</p>
<p>Yes. Democrats have a majority in the House and it’s VERY close majority in the Senate. In the Senate, Democrats have 50% and Republicans have 49%, everybody is waiting on that last percent.</p>
<p>Finally the Bush Humon Torture act (The act doesn’t have a name so I just call it that), can be rejected hopefully. The Patriot act can go fuck itself and Bush won’t be able to take away any more of our rights (hopefully). Just two more years… just two more years. <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/smiley.png?v=9" title=":smiley:" class="emoji" alt=":smiley:"></p>
<p>If anyone wants to read about the Bush Human Torture act I was talking about. <a href="http://www.nytimes.com/2006/09/28/opinion/28thu1.html?ei=5088&amp;en=3eb3b23c27944ff9&amp;ex=1317096000&amp;adxnnl=1&amp;partner=rssnyt&amp;emc=rss&amp;adxnnlx=1163030486" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">Refer to this article.</a></p>
<p>If anyone wants to argue what the <a href="http://www.epic.org/privacy/terrorism/hr3162.html" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">patriot act</a> <span class="bbcode-i">really</span> does, read the act and see what it does first. Oh by the way, it’s called the patriot act, so that if any one is against it, then they are supposively unpatriotic. Fuck them if you think so. Anyone not against this law is unpatriotic and a terrorist (someone causing terror. You don’t have to be blowing up bombs to cause terror).</p>
<p>~Ron</p>
<p>PS: I’m so fucking happy.  :D[/quote]</p>
<p>I think someone woke up on the wrong side of the rock?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/haha-republicans-lost-and-democrats-own-everything/23325/29">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/haha-republicans-lost-and-democrats-own-everything/23325/29</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 Nov 2006 04:29:12 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-23325-29</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/haha-republicans-lost-and-democrats-own-everything/23325.rss">Haha Republicans Lost and Democrats Own EVERYTHING!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Haha Republicans Lost and Democrats Own EVERYTHING!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@mjordan mjordan]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/mjordan">@mjordan</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>yeah i think thats pretty damn hilarious that the reason we claimed to go over there is because of WMD’s and where are they now?? there never was any ROFL. poor poor Bush, i feel sorry for you…NOT!!!</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/haha-republicans-lost-and-democrats-own-everything/23325/28">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/haha-republicans-lost-and-democrats-own-everything/23325/28</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 Nov 2006 03:51:06 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-23325-28</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/haha-republicans-lost-and-democrats-own-everything/23325.rss">Haha Republicans Lost and Democrats Own EVERYTHING!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Haha Republicans Lost and Democrats Own EVERYTHING!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@cruel cruel]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/cruel">@cruel</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Yeah, this was my face:</p>
<p><img src="http://www.grahmann.com/Gallery%2008%201978-1979/images/051%20This%20shocked-%20scared-%20terrified-looking%20boy%20is%20_______.jpg" alt width="374" height="53"></p>
<p><img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/smiley.png?v=9" title=":smiley:" class="emoji" alt=":smiley:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/haha-republicans-lost-and-democrats-own-everything/23325/27">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/haha-republicans-lost-and-democrats-own-everything/23325/27</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 Nov 2006 02:36:07 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-23325-27</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/haha-republicans-lost-and-democrats-own-everything/23325.rss">Haha Republicans Lost and Democrats Own EVERYTHING!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Haha Republicans Lost and Democrats Own EVERYTHING!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@bumblescum bumblescum]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/bumblescum">@bumblescum</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>It certainly worked, didn’t it Cruel? <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=9" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/haha-republicans-lost-and-democrats-own-everything/23325/26">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/haha-republicans-lost-and-democrats-own-everything/23325/26</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 Nov 2006 02:15:57 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-23325-26</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/haha-republicans-lost-and-democrats-own-everything/23325.rss">Haha Republicans Lost and Democrats Own EVERYTHING!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Haha Republicans Lost and Democrats Own EVERYTHING!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@cruel cruel]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/cruel">@cruel</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Yes, the UN has no spine, that’s why.<br>
Here’s a list of resolution violations:<br>
<a href="http://www.whitehouse.gov/infocus/iraq/decade/sect2.html" class="onebox" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">http://www.whitehouse.gov/infocus/iraq/decade/sect2.html</a></p>
<p>Not to mention Saddam himself claimed to have WMDs… but perhaps just to try to scare ppl. :rolleyes:</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/haha-republicans-lost-and-democrats-own-everything/23325/25">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/haha-republicans-lost-and-democrats-own-everything/23325/25</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 Nov 2006 02:11:03 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-23325-25</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/haha-republicans-lost-and-democrats-own-everything/23325.rss">Haha Republicans Lost and Democrats Own EVERYTHING!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Haha Republicans Lost and Democrats Own EVERYTHING!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@bumblescum bumblescum]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/bumblescum">@bumblescum</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>“The UN only refused to invade because of insufficient evidence of WMD’s”</p>
<p>Insufficient? Okay sure, their weapon’s inspectors getting forcibly removed from the country, yeah, there’s nothing going on there.</p>
<p>The U.N. Is a failed establishment, much like the League of Nations.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/haha-republicans-lost-and-democrats-own-everything/23325/24">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/haha-republicans-lost-and-democrats-own-everything/23325/24</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 Nov 2006 02:05:50 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-23325-24</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/haha-republicans-lost-and-democrats-own-everything/23325.rss">Haha Republicans Lost and Democrats Own EVERYTHING!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Haha Republicans Lost and Democrats Own EVERYTHING!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@BobDole81 BobDole81]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/bobdole81">@BobDole81</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Yep, I’m glad we have democratic control now.  We were celebrating yesterday over the senatorial win and the resignation of Rumsfeld <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=9" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"></p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-post="21" data-topic="23325">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/pyro/40/5_6259e4fa9dfe0dec282fb0955bb1974c.png" class="avatar"> Pyro:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Im going to have to disagree with you there ron. Even though i dont live in US i still know that saddam was a crazy and relentless torturer. He is not getting hanged because we invaded his country. He is getting hanged because he murdered 100s of people. They have found torture chambers with live cables hanging from the ceilings. Ready to shock the crap out of some civilian.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>No doubts there, of course Saddam committed many crimes in the past.  But it was in the past.  Making him accountable for his acts was never the issue, it was going into Iraq under false pretenses.  We went in because of threats of weapons of mass destruction and involvement with 9/11, not because he was a bad person.  Why not get UN assistance to have his regime overthrown and let him be tried by the international court?  The UN only refused to invade because of insufficient evidence of WMD’s…so I don’t disagree that he should be hanged, just the way we went about doing it.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/haha-republicans-lost-and-democrats-own-everything/23325/23">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/haha-republicans-lost-and-democrats-own-everything/23325/23</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 Nov 2006 01:08:36 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-23325-23</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/haha-republicans-lost-and-democrats-own-everything/23325.rss">Haha Republicans Lost and Democrats Own EVERYTHING!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Haha Republicans Lost and Democrats Own EVERYTHING!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@bullzeye95 bullzeye]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/bullzeye95">@bullzeye95</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I like Pyro and cruel &lt;3</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/haha-republicans-lost-and-democrats-own-everything/23325/22">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/haha-republicans-lost-and-democrats-own-everything/23325/22</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 Nov 2006 00:47:01 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-23325-22</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/haha-republicans-lost-and-democrats-own-everything/23325.rss">Haha Republicans Lost and Democrats Own EVERYTHING!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Haha Republicans Lost and Democrats Own EVERYTHING!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Pyro Pyro]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/pyro">@Pyro</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Im going to have to disagree with you there ron. Even though i dont live in US i still know that saddam was a crazy and relentless torturer. He is not getting hanged because we invaded his country. He is getting hanged because he murdered 100s of people. They have found torture chambers with live cables hanging from the ceilings. Ready to shock the crap out of some civilian.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/haha-republicans-lost-and-democrats-own-everything/23325/21">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/haha-republicans-lost-and-democrats-own-everything/23325/21</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 Nov 2006 00:40:01 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-23325-21</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/haha-republicans-lost-and-democrats-own-everything/23325.rss">Haha Republicans Lost and Democrats Own EVERYTHING!</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
