<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Sick Board - Post your current illness!</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/sick-board-post-your-current-illness/542028</link>
    <description>I have the flu</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2014 11:36:14 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>General Discussion</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/sick-board-post-your-current-illness/542028.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Sick Board - Post your current illness!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@TabbyKiller TabbyKiller]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/tabbykiller">@TabbyKiller</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p><a class="mention" href="/u/mopman">@mopman</a><br>
So from what I’m understanding is that depression starts off as a typical illness where the patient starts to feel sad, where dopemine and serotonin levels decrease, this causes a chemical imbalance where cells start to die and which then, eventually causes depression to become a disease by changing the structure? I have a hard time comprehending things so mind don’t mind me if I’m not getting the point across. It sounds really interesting and I’ll definitely discuss this with my psych teacher if we ever come in contact again. Thanks for the lesson</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/sick-board-post-your-current-illness/542028/70">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/sick-board-post-your-current-illness/542028/70</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2014 11:36:14 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-542028-70</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/sick-board-post-your-current-illness/542028.rss">Sick Board - Post your current illness!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Sick Board - Post your current illness!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@eXemplar eXemplar]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/exemplar">@eXemplar</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p><a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=qLrnkK2YEcE" class="onebox" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=qLrnkK2YEcE</a></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/sick-board-post-your-current-illness/542028/69">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/sick-board-post-your-current-illness/542028/69</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2014 11:18:26 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-542028-69</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/sick-board-post-your-current-illness/542028.rss">Sick Board - Post your current illness!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Sick Board - Post your current illness!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Mopman Mopman]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/mopman">@Mopman</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>It’s not really correct. There’s far more going on in a depressed brain than ‘too little dopamine’. I’m really the wrong person to talk about it, I’m not a neuroscientist either haha. Just a crazy person with an interest. But, basically, yes, we did once think that too low or high levels of neurotransmitters like dopamine and serotonin were the cause of depression (though even that was more complicated than just ‘not enough of them’) - this was something called the monoamine hypothesis. It’s now discredited, because we’ve realised that it’s far more complicated than that.</p>
<p>We arrived at the monoamine hypothesis basically because, while working on some drugs to treat other stuff (Tuberculosis was a big one, I forget the others) we found that the way these drugs inhibited MAOI’s (basically, the chemicals that break down dopamine, serotonin, adrenaline etc. and remove it from the brain) also helped a lot of people with depression and other diseases that were thought to be purely psychological, like anxiety disorders etc. This led to a sort of big breakthrough moment in medicine where we went 'oh shit, so these depressed people actually have chemical imbalances in the brain? Well that’s easy then, we can fix that with science!’ and we developed drugs like Prozac specifically to target these monoamines and prevent their reuptake (leave more of them lying around in the brain for longer).</p>
<p>Unfortunately, after we started using these drugs on people we realised that they aren’t the wonder pill we thought they were. And this basically proved the monoamine hypothesis wrong. If we think of another disease that everyone is familiar with that results from a ‘lack of’ something in the body - say, Diabetes Type 1 (body dramatically reduces production of insulin) or primary hypothyroidism (thyroid gland sucks dick at producing thyroxin) - we can a) measure the deficit, everybody who has these diseases has a measurable lack of something in the body and b) if we replace what they’re missing, with insulin or levothyroxine, we can then measure the improvement - and the patient gets better.</p>
<p>This doesn’t happen with depression and antidepressant drugs (by the way, before someone points out that thyroxine replacement and SSRI’s are not really the same - that’s totally true - serotonin doesn’t really readily/efficiently cross the blood brain barrier, so we can’t just stick serotonin in peoples brains, we have to do fancy things like prevent its reuptake - the brain is sometimes a big of a black box like that. We do the same thing with Parkinsons sometimes, with drugs that inhibit reuptake of dopamine or with MAOI’s) - sometimes people on antidepressants get better, sometimes they don’t, sometimes they get worse, sometimes nothing happens at all. So it’s fairly clear now, that ‘too little serotonin’ or similar statements is not enough to explain the cause. It’s fairly evident that they are a symptom of the ‘actual’ cause - one which may also contribute to further deterioration in a sort of ‘cascade’ effect, but not the ‘root’ cause, if that makes sense. A bit like how if you broke your leg in the desert and were in pain, and then got dehydrated, you’d be in more pain, but lack of water didn’t put you there, the broken leg did… that’s a terrible analogy but I can’t think of a better one right now.</p>
<p>So where does this leave us? The current consensus is that depression is not one disease, but the result of many different things that can go wrong in the brain, and importantly, it’s a process that once started and untreated, leads to chemical and importantly <em>structural</em> changes that continue the progression of the disease - like a death spiral. There are measurable structural (‘physical’) changes in the brains of people with chronic depression, for example the hypothalamus shrinks, neurons die and lose their ability to interact with neurotransmitters properly, and pathways in the brain change and form new functions and behaviours. In a way, depression is a kind of ‘brain damage’, I guess you could say, though I’d be wary of using that term… <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=5" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"></p>
<p>Importantly, these changes have been shown to undo themselves with treatment, <em>and that doesn’t only include drug therapy, but other therapies too</em>. So it’s also not correct to just give up and say ‘oh shit, it’s brain damage, well that guy is fucked’. But it’s clear at this point that it is definitely a ‘disease’.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/sick-board-post-your-current-illness/542028/68">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/sick-board-post-your-current-illness/542028/68</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2014 10:56:09 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-542028-68</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/sick-board-post-your-current-illness/542028.rss">Sick Board - Post your current illness!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Sick Board - Post your current illness!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@TabbyKiller TabbyKiller]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/tabbykiller">@TabbyKiller</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I wont argue with that because I barely recall half of the key terms I’m supposed to remember so yeah it’s a huge mess. But the jist of what I was saying is that depression is caused by a low concentration of dopamine and schizophrenia is a cause of too much dopemine, which I’m pretty sure is correct minus the terms I’m using in-between.</p>
<p>Also could you care to explain a little more about what I got wrong with the neuro system. I know little about the nervous system, all I really know is the structures and cells involved and what they do.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/sick-board-post-your-current-illness/542028/67">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/sick-board-post-your-current-illness/542028/67</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2014 10:35:52 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-542028-67</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/sick-board-post-your-current-illness/542028.rss">Sick Board - Post your current illness!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Sick Board - Post your current illness!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Mopman Mopman]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/mopman">@Mopman</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote" data-post="51" data-topic="542028">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/tabbykiller/40/5_e05bb34c421432ee4d40de30c10af3e5.png" class="avatar"> TabbyKiller:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Depression is a chemical imbalance in the brain which involves dopamine so don’t try to say it has nothing to do with depression</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Sure, it ‘involves’ Dopamine - because so does basically every other neurological process. That’s like saying every disease ‘involves blood’ - technically correct, but still a bullshit statement. Also, what you said was it’s a ‘drop in dopamine production’ not just ‘involves dopamine’ - which isn’t true at all. That’s Parkinson’s (and related diseases).</p>
<p>You kind of have a good point hidden in the mess, but tone it down on the pop neurology talk &lt;3</p>
<p>EDIT: I should be clearer because that post looks mean - I dig your support for behavioural therapy, but your simplification of the super complex neuro stuff involved with depression is dangerous (and very wrong)</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/sick-board-post-your-current-illness/542028/66">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/sick-board-post-your-current-illness/542028/66</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2014 10:10:54 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-542028-66</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/sick-board-post-your-current-illness/542028.rss">Sick Board - Post your current illness!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Sick Board - Post your current illness!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@xx_matty_xx Justin Bieber]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/xx_matty_xx">@xx_matty_xx</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I started by having a rational debate with you until you called me a massive prick and resorted to knee jerk reactions and random flailing. Clearly none of us can change <span class="bbcode-i">your</span> views, but I think we’ve all made our points and probably convinced people who were on the fence about how “real” depression is.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/sick-board-post-your-current-illness/542028/65">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/sick-board-post-your-current-illness/542028/65</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2014 08:59:19 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-542028-65</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/sick-board-post-your-current-illness/542028.rss">Sick Board - Post your current illness!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Sick Board - Post your current illness!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@TabbyKiller TabbyKiller]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/tabbykiller">@TabbyKiller</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>So I guess the thousands of thousands of cognitive psychologist everywhere do their part just for the hell of it? I assume they study these things to make no progress at all? Again, I’ve listen to your point that is supported by facts. But you should know that in psychology there isn’t just one answer, an example of this is nature vs nurture, another is every single approach from behavioral, cognitive, biological, behavioral and humanistic. All psychologist believe in different approach if not all. I pitty your ignorance because you fail to see that psychologists will and forever will disagree. What we’re having right now is some sort of mini Darwin vs Lamarck discussion on my part, and a flame war on yours.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/sick-board-post-your-current-illness/542028/64">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/sick-board-post-your-current-illness/542028/64</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2014 08:54:21 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-542028-64</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/sick-board-post-your-current-illness/542028.rss">Sick Board - Post your current illness!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Sick Board - Post your current illness!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@xx_matty_xx Justin Bieber]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/xx_matty_xx">@xx_matty_xx</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>lol if you’re backing up controversial points with actual studies you should probably cite them</p>
<p>This Just In - Numerous Studies Across the United States of the America Prove That Homosexuality Is Caused By Satan</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/sick-board-post-your-current-illness/542028/63">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/sick-board-post-your-current-illness/542028/63</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2014 08:38:02 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-542028-63</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/sick-board-post-your-current-illness/542028.rss">Sick Board - Post your current illness!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Sick Board - Post your current illness!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@TabbyKiller TabbyKiller]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/tabbykiller">@TabbyKiller</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>If you actually read my comment earlier I did say I had a misconception between illness and disease, meaning I was confused between the two thinking one was the other. Knowing that an illness is a lot less dramatic than a disease (i have a feeling that comment will break into a discussion). I was originally thinking of depression as a disease which is why I was so strong on the point saying people don’t get it as common as people think. But really, I don’t think you guys are understanding what i mean because I’m going over everything I’m saying with facts and backups from studies and research, yet you continue to keep a closed mind belittling everything I say.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/sick-board-post-your-current-illness/542028/62">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/sick-board-post-your-current-illness/542028/62</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2014 08:28:02 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-542028-62</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/sick-board-post-your-current-illness/542028.rss">Sick Board - Post your current illness!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Sick Board - Post your current illness!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Vain1 Vain_]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/vain1">@Vain1</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>tabby. I really hope you further your knowledge on depression because everything (opinion or not) you have said is wrong. depression is an illness - which is what this thread is about - not a poor choice. and if you cannot agree or see to it that this is an illness, then you should stop posting your “opinions” in this topic.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/sick-board-post-your-current-illness/542028/61">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/sick-board-post-your-current-illness/542028/61</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2014 08:21:05 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-542028-61</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/sick-board-post-your-current-illness/542028.rss">Sick Board - Post your current illness!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Sick Board - Post your current illness!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@TabbyKiller TabbyKiller]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/tabbykiller">@TabbyKiller</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>please explain all mighty</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/sick-board-post-your-current-illness/542028/60">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/sick-board-post-your-current-illness/542028/60</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2014 07:50:16 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-542028-60</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/sick-board-post-your-current-illness/542028.rss">Sick Board - Post your current illness!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Sick Board - Post your current illness!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@xx_matty_xx Justin Bieber]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/xx_matty_xx">@xx_matty_xx</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>the irony in that post is unbelievable</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/sick-board-post-your-current-illness/542028/59">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/sick-board-post-your-current-illness/542028/59</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2014 07:45:48 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-542028-59</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/sick-board-post-your-current-illness/542028.rss">Sick Board - Post your current illness!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Sick Board - Post your current illness!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@TabbyKiller TabbyKiller]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/tabbykiller">@TabbyKiller</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Well you’re doing a really bad job at it, child. After a little bit of research I’ve found that I’m not the only person who has thought of this. Many psychologist have carried out studies and experiments looking into controlling your own thoughts in hopes it will help to improve your depression, personalities, health and well-being,  and overall generally making you a nicer person. You should look into this because it seems sif’ you need it. But I don’t care. If you want to stay closed minded then be my guest because I get a kick out of your ignorance.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/sick-board-post-your-current-illness/542028/58">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/sick-board-post-your-current-illness/542028/58</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2014 07:25:28 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-542028-58</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/sick-board-post-your-current-illness/542028.rss">Sick Board - Post your current illness!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Sick Board - Post your current illness!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@xx_matty_xx Justin Bieber]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/xx_matty_xx">@xx_matty_xx</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I was mocking you. ha ha ha ha</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/sick-board-post-your-current-illness/542028/57">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/sick-board-post-your-current-illness/542028/57</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2014 07:18:07 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-542028-57</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/sick-board-post-your-current-illness/542028.rss">Sick Board - Post your current illness!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Sick Board - Post your current illness!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@TabbyKiller TabbyKiller]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/tabbykiller">@TabbyKiller</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Now you result in insults because you have nothing left to say to tip the balance on your side. Something I’d expect from a child, but hey, my opinion. At least we know who the man-child is here</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/sick-board-post-your-current-illness/542028/56">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/sick-board-post-your-current-illness/542028/56</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2014 07:08:39 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-542028-56</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/sick-board-post-your-current-illness/542028.rss">Sick Board - Post your current illness!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Sick Board - Post your current illness!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@xx_matty_xx Justin Bieber]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/xx_matty_xx">@xx_matty_xx</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>in my opinion tabby is a moron. NO DISCUSSION ABOUT IT PLS, ITS MY OPINION FFS</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/sick-board-post-your-current-illness/542028/55">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/sick-board-post-your-current-illness/542028/55</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2014 06:45:14 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-542028-55</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/sick-board-post-your-current-illness/542028.rss">Sick Board - Post your current illness!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Sick Board - Post your current illness!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@TabbyKiller TabbyKiller]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/tabbykiller">@TabbyKiller</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I remember learning about Schizophrenia in class and I think it was a cause of too much dopamine, I’ll look through my book later on but I’m sure there’s a difference. I might have been getting mixed up between dopamine and serotonin. You will see quite a bit of information if you type dopeamine and depression in the same search though. You might notice a simple context that says 3 ways to increase dopamine, it follows food/diet, lifestyle and even meds. The meds are to increase the level of dopamine (i cant remember a name) and there are meds, key name dopamine blockers that lowers the production of dopamine so it helps Schizophrenia. I’m a little rusty because this is all last years learning so things might be jumbled up a bit but I’m sure what I’ve said is accurate.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/sick-board-post-your-current-illness/542028/54">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/sick-board-post-your-current-illness/542028/54</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2014 04:21:07 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-542028-54</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/sick-board-post-your-current-illness/542028.rss">Sick Board - Post your current illness!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Sick Board - Post your current illness!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Vain1 Vain_]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/vain1">@Vain1</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>not very book smart, so have no idea whether that’s true or not. but a quick google of dopamine brought up schizophrenia, Parkinson’s, pain, rls, ADHD, and lack of motivation. etc etc. nowhere did it bring up depression. because depression isn’t just one chemical imbalance. psychological disorders don’t just happen. there are triggers. and nobody know what may trigger it for someone. depression isn’t magically cured by “being happy” or “doing stuff” like you seem to want to believe.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/sick-board-post-your-current-illness/542028/53">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/sick-board-post-your-current-illness/542028/53</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2014 04:10:29 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-542028-53</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/sick-board-post-your-current-illness/542028.rss">Sick Board - Post your current illness!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Sick Board - Post your current illness!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Travas Travas]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/travas">@Travas</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>It has nothing to do with depression.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/sick-board-post-your-current-illness/542028/52">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/sick-board-post-your-current-illness/542028/52</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2014 04:08:25 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-542028-52</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/sick-board-post-your-current-illness/542028.rss">Sick Board - Post your current illness!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Sick Board - Post your current illness!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@TabbyKiller TabbyKiller]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/tabbykiller">@TabbyKiller</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote" data-post="49" data-topic="542028">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 Vain_:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>in every post you make, you say the word opinion. you say it’s your opinion that you believe one can stop themselves from being depressed. this is false. there’s no opinion to it. everything is factual, not opinionated. psychological disorders are real, and should be dealt with accordingly. they cannot choose to be happy. they need help.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I’ve given you what depression is, it’s a drop in dopamine production in the brain. I’ve said how I think it can be resolved, through simulation of producing happy thoughts which produces dopamine. How is that something to continue post after post to go against as? So if you’re going against what I’m saying then you’re saying we have no control over our brain.</p>
<p>EDIT:<br>
Depression is a chemical imbalance in the brain which involves dopamine so don’t try to say it has nothing to do with depression</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/sick-board-post-your-current-illness/542028/51">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/sick-board-post-your-current-illness/542028/51</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2014 04:01:43 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-542028-51</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/sick-board-post-your-current-illness/542028.rss">Sick Board - Post your current illness!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Sick Board - Post your current illness!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@RUNE-PK RUNE-PK]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/rune-pk">@RUNE-PK</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Insane heartburn every hour for everyday since I was 12</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/sick-board-post-your-current-illness/542028/50">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/sick-board-post-your-current-illness/542028/50</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2014 03:46:56 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-542028-50</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/sick-board-post-your-current-illness/542028.rss">Sick Board - Post your current illness!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Sick Board - Post your current illness!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Vain1 Vain_]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/vain1">@Vain1</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>in every post you make, you say the word opinion. you say it’s your opinion that you believe one can stop themselves from being depressed. this is false. there’s no opinion to it. everything is factual, not opinionated. psychological disorders are real, and should be dealt with accordingly. they cannot choose to be happy. they need help.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/sick-board-post-your-current-illness/542028/49">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/sick-board-post-your-current-illness/542028/49</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2014 03:46:12 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-542028-49</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/sick-board-post-your-current-illness/542028.rss">Sick Board - Post your current illness!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Sick Board - Post your current illness!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@TabbyKiller TabbyKiller]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/tabbykiller">@TabbyKiller</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Things change all the time, we find out that some things are wrong everyday, we change and build off of ideas based on opinion. But I guess every opinion that was made to prove another thing wrong/right or build on was never actually an opinion, right? Now you’re just contradicting everything I’m trying to say.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/sick-board-post-your-current-illness/542028/48">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/sick-board-post-your-current-illness/542028/48</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2014 03:38:19 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-542028-48</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/sick-board-post-your-current-illness/542028.rss">Sick Board - Post your current illness!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Sick Board - Post your current illness!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Vain1 Vain_]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/vain1">@Vain1</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>there’s no such thing as opinions when it comes to psychological disorders.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/sick-board-post-your-current-illness/542028/47">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/sick-board-post-your-current-illness/542028/47</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2014 03:09:52 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-542028-47</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/sick-board-post-your-current-illness/542028.rss">Sick Board - Post your current illness!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Sick Board - Post your current illness!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@TabbyKiller TabbyKiller]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/tabbykiller">@TabbyKiller</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“Vain_, post:45, topic:542028”][quote author=TabbyKiller link=topic=660902.msg4420182#msg4420182 date=1398042264]<br>
I had a misconception between illness and disease which is why I used that term in an earlier post. But I do stand by saying that Depression is easily treated. From what I’ve learnt in last years psychology, if there’s not enough dopemine released into our brains then you feel the effects of depression. All I see is that it’s a simple self control method, by steering your mind into a more happier, bright course then you might be able to control your initial thoughts. Though this might be hugely effected by our personalities or behavioral bring up. Of course there are other methods like happy pills, or chocolate but that’s just too cliche. Again, this is all opinionated and even the greatest minds had their own theories.</p>
<p>All I am saying is that I don’t understand why you people are so sad. I myself have all the reasons to claim my depression with the 99 problems I have but I don’t want to be seen in that way, and I actually don’t think I do deserve to be depressed. So much stuff is going on around us so I’d rather be a happy man with sadness than a sad man without happiness.<br>
[/quote]you clearly don’t understand what depression is, how it’s caused, or the effects. depression isn’t <span class="bbcode-b">easily cured.</span> and whatever medium you got that information from is beyond retarded. you think just because so much stuff is going on around you, means you cannot - or should not - be depressed? depression is psychological, it doesn’t matter what the hell is happening around you.[/quote]<br>
Oh my god read the rest of what I’ve said if you’re so defensive, I’ve filled in any plot holes you fuckers are complaining about. This “medium” you’re talking about is valid information, and as I have said a billion times already, it’s an opinion, a theory. Jesus Christ if this is the amount of bull shit I’m getting from this small opinion, I hate to see what every other science or psych theorist gets for their opinion. If you cant understand the fact that I’m trying to explain an option and not actually teach you fuckers something then maybe, just maybe you’d comprehend an open mind. But no, you’re stuck to exactly what you read on the Internet or learn at school.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/sick-board-post-your-current-illness/542028/46">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/sick-board-post-your-current-illness/542028/46</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2014 02:00:22 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-542028-46</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/sick-board-post-your-current-illness/542028.rss">Sick Board - Post your current illness!</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
