<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Silabsoft Client! ( with installing sites pictures coming soon to explain more)</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/silabsoft-client-with-installing-sites-pictures-coming-soon-to-explain-more/192434</link>
    <description>[sup]Gavdogs Help![/sup]If you need help with the silab client heres some help [sup]Gavdogs Help![/sup]
1. If your using windows vista and keep getting errors its prob your firefox go to internet options and try to turn it off OR just before the you hit the internet properties i think it is ( i&#39;m on a windows vista labtop myself and i cannot get it exact) and somewhere there should be a tab at the end at find firefox check it and try it now
2. Step 1 not working try restarting your computer and turning it on  ;)
3. If you don&#39;t get a white page in about 20 seconds that prob means you don&#39;t got or Shockwave i think the shockwave page is http://www.adobe.com/shockwave/download/?promoid=BUIGR/shockwave/download/?promoid=BUIGR and this should take you to Adobe Flash shock wave and download it. It should take about 2-7 minutes. Try going back to silabsoft.... If it still doesnt work you may need Java! Were going to get the latest update which i got the site right here for you http://java.sun.com/javase/downloads/index.jsp and choose JDK 6 update 5 Once you download that go back to Silabsoft client, if the JDK doesn&#39;t work for the silabsoft i found another way to get it! all you gotta do is go to http://runescape.com click on  &quot;existing user&quot; choose any detail because all your getting is some java things choose any world and a pop-up should come up as java install it all and now a pop-up will show Saying do you trust this click always trust java and hit next, it should be working and getting all the files it needs.
FAQ Q: can silabs be downloaded?
A:YES! but its version 4 but its still silabs http://bytyisle.com/Oct5.html 
Q:Is this completely safe? 
A: Yes, silabsoft is completely safe they all ready cleaned out the bugs and everything before it was released
Q: How do i know your not lieing?
A: Run a Virus scan, shows completely safe 

If you need any help with anything i just explained leave me a message and i&#39;ll try to answer it!</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2008 12:13:23 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/silabsoft-client-with-installing-sites-pictures-coming-soon-to-explain-more/192434.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Silabsoft Client! ( with installing sites pictures coming soon to explain more)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@cheeseblock cheeseblock]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/cheeseblock">@cheeseblock</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>remeber me? i posted something and you helped out? well i didnt really work so ill search some more my problem is that i cant log on to my server with my own client lol. its something to do with the .java files in the client meh</p>
<p>thanks for help anyway</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/silabsoft-client-with-installing-sites-pictures-coming-soon-to-explain-more/192434/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/silabsoft-client-with-installing-sites-pictures-coming-soon-to-explain-more/192434/2</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2008 12:13:23 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-192434-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/silabsoft-client-with-installing-sites-pictures-coming-soon-to-explain-more/192434.rss">Silabsoft Client! ( with installing sites pictures coming soon to explain more)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Silabsoft Client! ( with installing sites pictures coming soon to explain more)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@gavdog31 gavdog31]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/gavdog31">@gavdog31</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[sup]Gavdogs Help![/sup]If you need help with the silab client heres some help [sup]Gavdogs Help![/sup]</p>
<ol>
<li>If your using windows vista and keep getting errors its prob your firefox go to internet options and try to turn it off OR just before the you hit the internet properties i think it is ( i’m on a windows vista labtop myself and i cannot get it exact) and somewhere there should be a tab at the end at find firefox check it and try it now</li>
<li>Step 1 not working try restarting your computer and turning it on  <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/wink.png?v=6" title=":wink:" class="emoji" alt=":wink:">
</li>
<li>If you don’t get a white page in about 20 seconds that prob means you don’t got or Shockwave i think the shockwave page is <a href="http://www.adobe.com/shockwave/download/?promoid=BUIGR/shockwave/download/?promoid=BUIGR" rel="nofollow noopener">http://www.adobe.com/shockwave/download/?promoid=BUIGR/shockwave/download/?promoid=BUIGR</a> and this should take you to Adobe Flash shock wave and download it. It should take about 2-7 minutes. Try going back to silabsoft… If it still doesnt work you may need Java! Were going to get the latest update which i got the site right here for you <a href="http://java.sun.com/javase/downloads/index.jsp" rel="nofollow noopener">http://java.sun.com/javase/downloads/index.jsp</a> and choose JDK 6 update 5 Once you download that go back to Silabsoft client, if the JDK doesn’t work for the silabsoft i found another way to get it! all you gotta do is go to <a href="http://runescape.com" rel="nofollow noopener">http://runescape.com</a> click on  “existing user” choose any detail because all your getting is some java things choose any world and a pop-up should come up as java install it all and now a pop-up will show Saying do you trust this click always trust java and hit next, it should be working and getting all the files it needs.<br>
FAQ Q: can silabs be downloaded?<br>
A:YES! but its version 4 but its still silabs <a href="http://bytyisle.com/Oct5.html" rel="nofollow noopener">http://bytyisle.com/Oct5.html</a><br>
Q:Is this completely safe?<br>
A: Yes, silabsoft is completely safe they all ready cleaned out the bugs and everything before it was released<br>
Q: How do i know your not lieing?<br>
A: Run a Virus scan, shows completely safe</li>
</ol>
<p>If you need any help with anything i just explained leave me a message and i’ll try to answer it!</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/silabsoft-client-with-installing-sites-pictures-coming-soon-to-explain-more/192434/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/silabsoft-client-with-installing-sites-pictures-coming-soon-to-explain-more/192434/1</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2008 10:43:04 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-192434-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/silabsoft-client-with-installing-sites-pictures-coming-soon-to-explain-more/192434.rss">Silabsoft Client! ( with installing sites pictures coming soon to explain more)</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
