<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>[508] Server Help</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/508-server-help/329836</link>
    <description>Hello, I need some help with my server...

For some reason, I can&#39;t connect to the server. I used 3 [b]Different[/b] 508 clients, and i&#39;ve tested them both to connect to 127.0.01, and then 0.0.0.0, but they will NOT connect to my server for some reason. Yes, the server is 508...Although it&#39;s [b]Not[/b] the clients, because they work on other servers...


Can someone help? Perhaps it&#39;s something wrong with the sockets, but i&#39;ve been trying so long now to fix it, and can&#39;t. Help?


P.S: I tested some sort of thing out. I turn on a different server, then connect to the server until the client is at the Login Screen. Then I exit the server, and switch back to my server that I need help with. And when I login, I get a client error saying &quot;Unexected Server Response. Please try a different world.&quot;..</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 18 Feb 2010 02:03:44 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/508-server-help/329836.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>[508] Server Help</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@QuestMaster_2K10 QuestMaster 2K10]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/questmaster_2k10">@QuestMaster_2K10</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Hello, I need some help with my server…</p>
<p>For some reason, I can’t connect to the server. I used 3 <span class="bbcode-b">Different</span> 508 clients, and i’ve tested them both to connect to 127.0.01, and then 0.0.0.0, but they will NOT connect to my server for some reason. Yes, the server is 508…Although it’s <span class="bbcode-b">Not</span> the clients, because they work on other servers…</p>
<p>Can someone help? Perhaps it’s something wrong with the sockets, but i’ve been trying so long now to fix it, and can’t. Help?</p>
<p>P.S: I tested some sort of thing out. I turn on a different server, then connect to the server until the client is at the Login Screen. Then I exit the server, and switch back to my server that I need help with. And when I login, I get a client error saying “Unexected Server Response. Please try a different world.”…</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/508-server-help/329836/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/508-server-help/329836/1</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 18 Feb 2010 02:03:44 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-329836-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/508-server-help/329836.rss">[508] Server Help</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
