<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>AutoCast #4</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/autocast-4/156482</link>
    <description>Okay, 4th post now, and still no success.

I&#39;ve used some tuts off rune-server, to try and get 1 autocasting spell. Then, from that i can work on the others...

Soooo.... I&#39;ve got it to do the Gfx, and the hitdiff.. Problem is that, before i attack my oponent, when i click the spell to autocast with.. It attacks normal, like a weapon...

In the fight, when i click the spell book, then the spell again.. It activates the case.. Right?.. So it does the method called..

In that case, i put my method. E.G.
[code]
AutoCasting();
[/code]

But it doesn&#39;t loop... 

Does anyone have a working loop that will make it cast over and over again?..

I&#39;m not too bothered how many times it does it.. It can be a simple for loop, that does it 500 times with a timer.. I just need it to attack over and over.. Without me have to keep clicking the spell every time i attack -.-..

Please, much apreciated.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 03 Nov 2007 19:12:13 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/autocast-4/156482.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>AutoCast #4</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@X-J-K-X X-J-K-X]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/x-j-k-x">@X-J-K-X</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Okay, 4th post now, and still no success.</p>
<p>I’ve used some tuts off rune-server, to try and get 1 autocasting spell. Then, from that i can work on the others…</p>
<p>Soooo… I’ve got it to do the Gfx, and the hitdiff… Problem is that, before i attack my oponent, when i click the spell to autocast with… It attacks normal, like a weapon…</p>
<p>In the fight, when i click the spell book, then the spell again… It activates the case… Right?.. So it does the method called…</p>
<p>In that case, i put my method. E.G.</p>
<pre><code class="lang-auto">AutoCasting();</code></pre>
<p>But it doesn’t loop…</p>
<p>Does anyone have a working loop that will make it cast over and over again?..</p>
<p>I’m not too bothered how many times it does it… It can be a simple for loop, that does it 500 times with a timer… I just need it to attack over and over… Without me have to keep clicking the spell every time i attack -.-…</p>
<p>Please, much apreciated.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/autocast-4/156482/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/autocast-4/156482/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 03 Nov 2007 19:12:13 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-156482-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/autocast-4/156482.rss">AutoCast #4</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
