<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Server design?</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/server-design/388544</link>
    <description>I plan on asking my teacher tomorrow about it if I remember. My question is in general how do u go about programming a server? The concepts that need to be implimented, things you should think of to design it and stuff. The reason I ask is I want to start developing a game or two. I&#39;m wanting to know where to start in this journey. I know I want the game to have server and client communication, and multiplayer. The first I want to work on is a simple fps game that can later evolve into something serious if I. Decide to farther devlope it. The other I have in mind is a far more complex game, it actually involves concepts from other games but basically a civilization based game. Both games will be 3d and I&#39;m also focused on anti hacking with these games. The reason for the fps is a learning experience and the fact the free fps I currently play is ok but its shit when it comes to preventing hacking. I played a ffa match today(it seems like they released a patch within the past 2 days) and I would have to say at least half the ppl had some kind of hack whether it was an aimbot, or 1 hit kill, or a combo of shot through walls and aimbot(hundreds of kills a match its f*n bs b/c they are almost untouchable). Idk if the hacks are injecting packets which makes them work or if they are stupid enough to handle whether the damage ur bullets do a set client-side.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 09 Apr 2011 04:45:07 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>General Programming</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/server-design/388544.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Server design?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Sanctum1 Sanctum-]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/sanctum1">@Sanctum1</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[Back on topic]</p>
<p>Let’s put it this way, I’m guessing your an adolescent thinking game development is pretty darn cool (which it is), however, coding in general is becoming ever so advanced, and the concepts of game development are being driven by world leading industries in game development (e.g. SONY) that strive for perfection, so it’s unlikely that you will be making the new “perfect” Call Of Duty game.</p>
<p>Now, don’t get me wrong, all game developers started from somewhere, but not without the fundamental basics that are needed to succeed in making a decent game.</p>
<p>Perhaps your wondering what the hell I’m talking about? Well, in order to make a successful game (in your case, an FPS) than you will need most of these things:</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b"><span class="bbcode-u">Knowledge:</span> </span></p>
<ul>
<li>The basic knowledge of general coding; the most popular gaming code languages are C++, and JAVA, so I’d start learning these thoroughly before attempting to draw guns on GIMP.</li>
<li>Understanding servers and clients.</li>
<li>Understanding how IDE’s save time and efficiently construct the base of your game.</li>
</ul>
<p><span class="bbcode-b"><span class="bbcode-u">Team’s:</span></span><br>
Have you considered the effort needed to develop a game, no? A major company such as Infinity Ward usually takes 8-14 months to successfully develop a game (e.g. Modern Warfare 2). Now let me tell you, Infinity Ward is not run by one person, it is a <span class="bbcode-b">company</span> of several teams working day-by-day consistently. Imagine trying to accomplish what 50 people can do by yourself. That would take you a <span class="bbcode-b">VERY</span> long time. So you will need to come up with a team, which then brings me to my next topic.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-u"><span class="bbcode-b">Cost:</span></span><br>
You will need to provide for your development team, this means an office, multiple computers; hundreds of thousands of dollars will be needed in the development stages of your game.</p>
<p>I hope I have enlightened your mind of what game development consists of; not just cool animations or graphics, but the determination to create something amazing. Please, i hope i haven’t effected on your dreams in the future, but keep in mind that game development is only attempted by the determined, not script kiddies who know how to make themselves spawn items on a Runescape private server.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/server-design/388544/16">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/server-design/388544/16</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 09 Apr 2011 04:45:07 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-388544-16</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/server-design/388544.rss">Server design?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Server design?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@_s11 s1gma]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/_s11">@_s11</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“blakeman8192, post:12, topic:388544”]_s pretty much hit it dead-on.</p>
<p>In order to figure out how to write any program, you need to break it down into the problems that it needs to solve.</p>
<p>What does a server need to do?<br>
Accept incoming connections<br>
Handle the I/O of each client<br>
etc.</p>
<p>This approach is brought forth with the concept that all computers, and computer programs, exist to solve problems.  Once you have broken down your software into the problems that it needs to solve, you start planning out a design (the most important thing you can do) that solves all of these problems in the simplest and most efficient way possible.  The greatest thing that separates amateur programmers from expert programmers is the ability to plan out a design and execute it.  Some people can design things all in their head, others like to use pencil and paper, others like to use modeling languages like UML.</p>
<p>I learned in college classes that you need to plan everything out before you even write one line of code.  This is especially important in collaborative projects.  From my personal experience, things always work out better if you plan ahead.  You don’t see construction crews just slapping down a multi-million-dollar bridge without planning anything - they use blueprints, they plan every inch out meticulously.  Software engineering isn’t all that different from architectural engineering.</p>
<p>Weeks of coding can save you hours of planning![/quote]</p>
<p>in addition to this, a good tip for the future is to solve each problem separately. a modular and decoupled architecture is seldom a bad one and each module should abide by the <a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Unix_philosophy" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">Unix philosophy</a> of doing one thing and doing it well (Eric Raymond’s design rules are something i abide to religiously). also, with modularity comes the inevitable possibility of code reuse. look at libraries like netty for Java and libev &amp; libevent for C/C++, they’re very flexible and were created with adaptability and modularity in mind as well as being applicable in nearly every project where IO is a factor to consider in design. look at the way they strive to achieve the goal, use them as an example and write all of your modules to be applicable in nearly every context, just like they are. blake said that software engineering isn’t all that different from architectural engineering, i can only reiterate upon his notion to a greater extremity. software engineering barely differs from architectural engineering, you plan and build, the only differences are the concepts used in planning and the tools and materials used to build.</p>
<p>tl;dr - realise one thing: <span class="bbcode-i">software engineering is an art.</span></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/server-design/388544/15">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/server-design/388544/15</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 06 Apr 2011 18:38:22 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-388544-15</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/server-design/388544.rss">Server design?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Server design?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@xryz xryz]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/xryz">@xryz</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>ok. thx. we have been learning that in school. even though the most we have done is php pages… when i get time i will try planning stuff out. but when im free from school work i need to go out and find a job then that limits my time even more. we installed axosoft ontime that could help me keep track of planning and progress. i need to work on brainstorming all the parts that are needed, then getting the stuff on paper or w/e. right now i make a flow chart and follow it, and then im like i need to add so thing or remove something. but in the end everything works like i planned it. when i get time i need to take a look at the links mendorphins posted.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/server-design/388544/14">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/server-design/388544/14</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 06 Apr 2011 18:00:02 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-388544-14</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/server-design/388544.rss">Server design?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Server design?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@IlikeArrays IlikeArrays]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/ilikearrays">@IlikeArrays</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <blockquote>Weeks of planning can save you hours of coding!</blockquote>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/server-design/388544/13">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/server-design/388544/13</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 06 Apr 2011 17:41:24 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-388544-13</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/server-design/388544.rss">Server design?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Server design?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@system system]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/system">@system</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>_s pretty much hit it dead-on.</p>
<p>In order to figure out how to write any program, you need to break it down into the problems that it needs to solve.</p>
<p>What does a server need to do?</p>
<p>[ul][<em>]Accept incoming connections<br>
[</em>]Handle the I/O of each client<br>
[*]etc.[/ul]</p>
<p>This approach is brought forth with the concept that all computers, and computer programs, exist to solve problems.  Once you have broken down your software into the problems that it needs to solve, you start <span class="bbcode-b">planning out a design</span> (the most important thing you can do) that solves all of these problems in the <span class="bbcode-u">simplest</span> and <span class="bbcode-u">most efficient</span> way possible.  The greatest thing that separates amateur programmers from expert programmers is the ability to plan out a design and execute it.  Some people can design things all in their head, others like to use pencil and paper, others like to use modeling languages like <a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Unified_Modeling_Language" data-bbcode="true">UML</a>.</p>
<p>I learned in college classes that you need to plan <span class="bbcode-i">everything</span> out before you even write one line of code.  This is especially important in collaborative projects.  From my personal experience, things always work out better if you plan ahead.  You don’t see construction crews just slapping down a multi-million-dollar bridge without planning anything - they use blueprints, they plan every inch out meticulously.  Software engineering isn’t all that different from architectural engineering.</p>
<p>Weeks of coding can save you hours of planning!</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/server-design/388544/12">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/server-design/388544/12</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 06 Apr 2011 17:23:55 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-388544-12</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/server-design/388544.rss">Server design?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Server design?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@xryz xryz]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/xryz">@xryz</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote="_s, post:10, topic:388544"][quote author=xx matty xx link=topic=484365.msg3553903#msg3553903 date=1301735354]</p>
<aside class="quote">
<blockquote>
<p>Ok. I remember seeing a tut on making a server with some concepts but I don’t remember the names to. I remember there were 3 parts to this server design(one that listens for and sends packets, and I can’t remember what the other 2 did but the communicated with each other.<br>
[/quote]The server has a listener which accepts new connections. In a simple thread per client server, a new thread is created when this connection is accepted and a socket is opened between the server and the client. You can then open the io streams which allow you to read and write data to the socket.</p>
<p>Better design involves thread pools or NIO, but learn the basics first.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>when talking about general server design, NIO is a term that annoys me as it refers to Java’s NIO API; the correct term would be asynchronous IO. ask a purely C and C++ programmer about NIO and he’ll have probably never heard of the term before, let asynchronous IO roll off of your tongue and he’ll baffle on endlessly. sorry for my nitpicking, but it has to be said.</p>
<p>also, in an ideal world, i’d recommend not educating him as to what thread-per-client even is, it’s a blasphemous and hideous practice that makes anyone with a brain look down upon the user. it’s a shame it’s pretty much the de-facto standard for teaching people how to handle multiple clients in a server, and so is probably unavoidable.</p>
<p>OP, i’m assuming you want to use Java for this and so the logical first step is to gain a good grasp of the language itself. then, research into basic sockets and communication and learn a little bit about how it all works internally. try to understand everything, and also allow yourself to realise the flaws of thread-per-client on your own; thinking about something yourself is always the best route to a partial revelation. look at the Java NIO API and asynchronicity as a whole as well as looking at patterns like the reactor and the proactor which the NIO API hands itself well to. then i’d strongly advise on looking at design patterns in general, a place where the Gang of Four book becomes a complete godsend. rinse and repeat your standard and practice and ultimately realise that your dream is not as far off as it may seem, although… if you want to make a functional first person shooter you’re also going to have to learn a lot about graphics and game development as a whole, i’d recommend just sticking with being a back-end developer.</p>
<p>and may i iterate that this is probably going to take a long time, concurrency and networking is not a topic that you can become very familiar with in a matter of hours.[/quote]</p>
<p>ok thank you for reply it is helpful.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/server-design/388544/11">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/server-design/388544/11</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 06 Apr 2011 16:48:24 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-388544-11</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/server-design/388544.rss">Server design?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Server design?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@_s11 s1gma]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/_s11">@_s11</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“xx matty xx, post:9, topic:388544”][quote author=xryz link=topic=484365.msg3549033#msg3549033 date=1301369940]<br>
Ok. I remember seeing a tut on making a server with some concepts but I don’t remember the names to. I remember there were 3 parts to this server design(one that listens for and sends packets, and I can’t remember what the other 2 did but the communicated with each other.<br>
[/quote]The server has a listener which accepts new connections. In a simple thread per client server, a new thread is created when this connection is accepted and a socket is opened between the server and the client. You can then open the io streams which allow you to read and write data to the socket.</p>
<p>Better design involves thread pools or NIO, but learn the basics first.[/quote]<br>
when talking about general server design, NIO is a term that annoys me as it refers to Java’s NIO API; the correct term would be asynchronous IO. ask a purely C and C++ programmer about NIO and he’ll have probably never heard of the term before, let asynchronous IO roll off of your tongue and he’ll baffle on endlessly. sorry for my nitpicking, but it has to be said.</p>
<p>also, in an ideal world, i’d recommend not educating him as to what thread-per-client even is, it’s a blasphemous and hideous practice that makes anyone with a brain look down upon the user. it’s a shame it’s pretty much the de-facto standard for teaching people how to handle multiple clients in a server, and so is probably unavoidable.</p>
<p>OP, i’m assuming you want to use Java for this and so the logical first step is to gain a good grasp of the language itself. then, research into basic sockets and communication and learn a little bit about how it all works internally. try to understand everything, and also allow yourself to realise the flaws of thread-per-client on your own; thinking about something yourself is always the best route to a partial revelation. look at the Java NIO API and asynchronicity as a whole as well as looking at patterns like the reactor and the proactor which the NIO API hands itself well to. then i’d strongly advise on looking at design patterns in general, a place where the Gang of Four book becomes a complete godsend. rinse and repeat your standard and practice and ultimately realise that your dream is not as far off as it may seem, although… if you want to make a functional first person shooter you’re also going to have to learn a lot about graphics and game development as a whole, i’d recommend just sticking with being a back-end developer.</p>
<p>and may i iterate that this is probably going to take a long time, concurrency and networking is not a topic that you can become very familiar with in a matter of hours.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/server-design/388544/10">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/server-design/388544/10</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 06 Apr 2011 16:39:08 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-388544-10</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/server-design/388544.rss">Server design?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Server design?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@xx_matty_xx Justin Bieber]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/xx_matty_xx">@xx_matty_xx</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“xryz, post:3, topic:388544”]Ok. I remember seeing a tut on making a server with some concepts but I don’t remember the names to. I remember there were 3 parts to this server design(one that listens for and sends packets, and I can’t remember what the other 2 did but the communicated with each other.[/quote]The server has a listener which accepts new connections. In a simple thread per client server, a new thread is created when this connection is accepted and a socket is opened between the server and the client. You can then open the io streams which allow you to read and write data to the socket.</p>
<p>Better design involves thread pools or NIO, but learn the basics first.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/server-design/388544/9">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/server-design/388544/9</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 02 Apr 2011 09:09:14 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-388544-9</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/server-design/388544.rss">Server design?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Server design?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@SETO SETO]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/seto">@SETO</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>it might not be as easy, it took us (team of 3) @ uni and 4 months and alot of bitching to develop a video storage server,</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/server-design/388544/8">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/server-design/388544/8</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 02 Apr 2011 02:53:07 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-388544-8</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/server-design/388544.rss">Server design?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Server design?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@xryz xryz]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/xryz">@xryz</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Ok thx I will look at it when I can. I’m on my phone so ya.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/server-design/388544/7">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/server-design/388544/7</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 29 Mar 2011 04:32:35 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-388544-7</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/server-design/388544.rss">Server design?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Server design?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@NewbieNewty Newty]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/newbienewty">@NewbieNewty</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>If you want to find out more about client --&gt; server communication using java then I suggest taking a look at:<br>
<a href="http://download.oracle.com/javase/tutorial/networking/sockets/clientServer.html" class="onebox" target="_blank">http://download.oracle.com/javase/tutorial/networking/sockets/clientServer.html</a></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/server-design/388544/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/server-design/388544/6</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 29 Mar 2011 04:24:09 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-388544-6</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/server-design/388544.rss">Server design?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Server design?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@xryz xryz]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/xryz">@xryz</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I know. And that means they need to work on their servers since all of those issues are in the fps I play. Some of them I haven’t seen in a little bit but the major one that seem like all it would take is a simple easy fix aren’t not fixed(like shooting thru walls, and the amount of damage ur bullets do; I’m pretty sure if I knew how to make a hack. For this game all I would have to do is make it were my bullets were 1.5-2.0 times more powerful and no one would know I was hacking and I could use it until they decided to fix that problem)…</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/server-design/388544/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/server-design/388544/5</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 29 Mar 2011 03:58:05 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-388544-5</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/server-design/388544.rss">Server design?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Server design?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@davidi2 Davidi2]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/davidi2">@davidi2</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Slave Scyth is correct, you want the client to handle as little as possible. When you look at server that don’t check things server-sided, no clip, item spawning and such all become issues.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/server-design/388544/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/server-design/388544/4</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 29 Mar 2011 03:49:15 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-388544-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/server-design/388544.rss">Server design?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Server design?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@xryz xryz]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/xryz">@xryz</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Ok. I remember seeing a tut on making a server with some concepts but I don’t remember the names to. I remember there were 3 parts to this server design(one that listens for and sends packets, and I can’t remember what the other 2 did but the communicated with each other.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/server-design/388544/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/server-design/388544/3</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 29 Mar 2011 03:39:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-388544-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/server-design/388544.rss">Server design?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Server design?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Slave_Scyth Slave Scyth]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/slave_scyth">@Slave_Scyth</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Hacks are easy to prevent so long as you make the server check EVERYTHING. You can’t stop people from intercepting your packets. Eventually, someone will figure them out and their meanings. You just have to make sure you don’t give too much power to the client side of things.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/server-design/388544/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/server-design/388544/2</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 29 Mar 2011 03:31:58 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-388544-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/server-design/388544.rss">Server design?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Server design?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@xryz xryz]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/xryz">@xryz</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I plan on asking my teacher tomorrow about it if I remember. My question is in general how do u go about programming a server? The concepts that need to be implimented, things you should think of to design it and stuff. The reason I ask is I want to start developing a game or two. I’m wanting to know where to start in this journey. I know I want the game to have server and client communication, and multiplayer. The first I want to work on is a simple fps game that can later evolve into something serious if I. Decide to farther devlope it. The other I have in mind is a far more complex game, it actually involves concepts from other games but basically a civilization based game. Both games will be 3d and I’m also focused on anti hacking with these games. The reason for the fps is a learning experience and the fact the free fps I currently play is ok but its shit when it comes to preventing hacking. I played a ffa match today(it seems like they released a patch within the past 2 days) and I would have to say at least half the ppl had some kind of hack whether it was an aimbot, or 1 hit kill, or a combo of shot through walls and aimbot(hundreds of kills a match its f*n bs b/c they are almost untouchable). Idk if the hacks are injecting packets which makes them work or if they are stupid enough to handle whether the damage ur bullets do a set client-side.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/server-design/388544/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/server-design/388544/1</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 29 Mar 2011 03:28:04 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-388544-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/server-design/388544.rss">Server design?</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
