<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Zyphyr - Looking for Lead Coder - Retiring from RSPS</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/zyphyr-looking-for-lead-coder-retiring-from-rsps/542358</link>
    <description>Well, it&#39;s that time. I&#39;m sorry you guys, but I have to move from Zyphyr. College is around the corner, I will be applying next year, and I need to do more things with my life. I just don&#39;t have the time to run a server, and I realized this in my struggles to do college visits, extra curriculars, working on my gpa, all while trying to get daily coding in. It has just come to the point where I have time for one thing: either continueing rsps or straightening out my life by maintaining my social life and focusing on college. I of course will not stop coding, as AP Computer Science is still part of my curriculum and I am developing open source projects on Github, and I still have time to work on my Gielinor project, there is just not enough time to run a server with the fact that its not just coding, its also managing, interacting, advertising, and everything. It is just taking too much of my time and is something I can&#39;t handle.

Does this mean Zyphyr is closing? 
Of course not! Motherboard is still here standing strong, but I will need someone to fill in my position as a coder. Yup, this means that I am finally looking for a coder, but keep in mind that there are requirements to even apply. This is a serious position and I don&#39;t want to hire the wrong person. The reason that these requirements are tough is because I obviously care a lot about the server, it has been something I have been passionate about for 3 years, and that I don&#39;t want to be spammed with applications like always. I am sorry, but in the past, when I was looking for a coder I have had 100+ people in one day spam me with applications and then they couldn&#39;t even explain what the difference between a double and an int. So, if you are interested, don&#39;t hesitate to contact me. But know that you must meet the following requirements and why they are important for this role:

-A Great Understanding of Java-
You don&#39;t need to be a Java prodigy or the best coder this planet has, but you need a large understanding of Java. About 90% of the community claims that they are &quot;good&quot;, &quot;experienced&quot; and &quot;expert&quot; coders in the rsps business because they can do blah blah blah. I&#39;m sorry to break it to you, but if you don&#39;t know the fundamentals of Java, you really aren&#39;t a coder. Everything is based off of the basics, and if you have the founding knowledge of Java, you can literally code anything. Even complicated things such as Construction, all of it is based off of anything a regular Java coder would know or understand. Please, if you don&#39;t even know what an object is or how it works (no not rsps objects, Java is an object-oriented language), don&#39;t even bother applying.

-Ability to Work Well With Communities-
There are great coders out there, and I have had the privelege to work with some of the best the internet had to offer. Some people I never even thought I would be able to speak to over the years have been in some sort of development with me, however, it doesn&#39;t get you the job if you are only a good coder. You need to be able to interact with the community, having the ability to speak with players, help people out, understand and listen to ideas with a sense of maturity, etc. I will in no way hire someone who is rude and doesn&#39;t know how to treat the community properly. You need to be a fair and mature person who loves to be active in the scene. Sure you can have your laughs here and there, but you need to know how to be professional.

-You Need Time-
When I did run the server, I had about 5 hours on a weekday and 8 hours on a weekend, on average. Now I don&#39;t expect other people to have the dedication that I had, but I am looking for someone who has a similar sense of dedication. I want to see that you can spend a decent amount of hours on weekdays and a good chunk on weekends. I don&#39;t need an inactive person on the team, sorry!

Now there are other things such as the fact that you need creativitiy, listening skills, etc. But the ones listed above were the most important to me. I very much want the legacy of the server to carry on as theres a lot of people that care about it. Again, do not hesitate if you think you are up for the position. There is no application format, so use your mind and create an approach that you think would be appropriate. If I do think that you are good for the job, I will interview you on skype. If you have any questions, feel free to pm me on here or on skype.

Skype: mabrox97</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 02 May 2014 01:22:21 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/zyphyr-looking-for-lead-coder-retiring-from-rsps/542358.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Zyphyr - Looking for Lead Coder - Retiring from RSPS</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Chimerica Chimerica]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/chimerica">@Chimerica</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Good luck <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/open_mouth.png?v=5" title=":open_mouth:" class="emoji" alt=":open_mouth:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/zyphyr-looking-for-lead-coder-retiring-from-rsps/542358/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/zyphyr-looking-for-lead-coder-retiring-from-rsps/542358/2</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2014 01:22:21 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-542358-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/zyphyr-looking-for-lead-coder-retiring-from-rsps/542358.rss">Zyphyr - Looking for Lead Coder - Retiring from RSPS</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Zyphyr - Looking for Lead Coder - Retiring from RSPS</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@hottys2good4 hottys2good4]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/hottys2good4">@hottys2good4</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Well, it’s that time. I’m sorry you guys, but I have to move from Zyphyr. College is around the corner, I will be applying next year, and I need to do more things with my life. I just don’t have the time to run a server, and I realized this in my struggles to do college visits, extra curriculars, working on my gpa, all while trying to get daily coding in. It has just come to the point where I have time for one thing: either continueing rsps or straightening out my life by maintaining my social life and focusing on college. I of course will not stop coding, as AP Computer Science is still part of my curriculum and I am developing open source projects on Github, and I still have time to work on my Gielinor project, there is just not enough time to run a server with the fact that its not just coding, its also managing, interacting, advertising, and everything. It is just taking too much of my time and is something I can’t handle.</p>
<p>Does this mean Zyphyr is closing?<br>
Of course not! Motherboard is still here standing strong, but I will need someone to fill in my position as a coder. Yup, this means that I am finally looking for a coder, but keep in mind that there are requirements to even apply. This is a serious position and I don’t want to hire the wrong person. The reason that these requirements are tough is because I obviously care a lot about the server, it has been something I have been passionate about for 3 years, and that I don’t want to be spammed with applications like always. I am sorry, but in the past, when I was looking for a coder I have had 100+ people in one day spam me with applications and then they couldn’t even explain what the difference between a double and an int. So, if you are interested, don’t hesitate to contact me. But know that you must meet the following requirements and why they are important for this role:</p>
<p>-A Great Understanding of Java-<br>
You don’t need to be a Java prodigy or the best coder this planet has, but you need a large understanding of Java. About 90% of the community claims that they are “good”, “experienced” and “expert” coders in the rsps business because they can do blah blah blah. I’m sorry to break it to you, but if you don’t know the fundamentals of Java, you really aren’t a coder. Everything is based off of the basics, and if you have the founding knowledge of Java, you can literally code anything. Even complicated things such as Construction, all of it is based off of anything a regular Java coder would know or understand. Please, if you don’t even know what an object is or how it works (no not rsps objects, Java is an object-oriented language), don’t even bother applying.</p>
<p>-Ability to Work Well With Communities-<br>
There are great coders out there, and I have had the privelege to work with some of the best the internet had to offer. Some people I never even thought I would be able to speak to over the years have been in some sort of development with me, however, it doesn’t get you the job if you are only a good coder. You need to be able to interact with the community, having the ability to speak with players, help people out, understand and listen to ideas with a sense of maturity, etc. I will in no way hire someone who is rude and doesn’t know how to treat the community properly. You need to be a fair and mature person who loves to be active in the scene. Sure you can have your laughs here and there, but you need to know how to be professional.</p>
<p>-You Need Time-<br>
When I did run the server, I had about 5 hours on a weekday and 8 hours on a weekend, on average. Now I don’t expect other people to have the dedication that I had, but I am looking for someone who has a similar sense of dedication. I want to see that you can spend a decent amount of hours on weekdays and a good chunk on weekends. I don’t need an inactive person on the team, sorry!</p>
<p>Now there are other things such as the fact that you need creativitiy, listening skills, etc. But the ones listed above were the most important to me. I very much want the legacy of the server to carry on as theres a lot of people that care about it. Again, do not hesitate if you think you are up for the position. There is no application format, so use your mind and create an approach that you think would be appropriate. If I do think that you are good for the job, I will interview you on skype. If you have any questions, feel free to pm me on here or on skype.</p>
<p>Skype: mabrox97</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/zyphyr-looking-for-lead-coder-retiring-from-rsps/542358/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/zyphyr-looking-for-lead-coder-retiring-from-rsps/542358/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 20 Apr 2014 14:46:22 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-542358-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/zyphyr-looking-for-lead-coder-retiring-from-rsps/542358.rss">Zyphyr - Looking for Lead Coder - Retiring from RSPS</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
