<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Small project consists of programs</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/small-project-consists-of-programs/296985</link>
    <description>[center][b]Wales 00&#39;s project[/b][/center]

After being on IRC for a few days and making a new modification for Taharok&#39;s forums I decided to create a little server in the mean time while I get bored. This project may not go through but I shall release the finished project if I get bored ect.

[center][b]Server information[/b][/center]
I ain&#39;t going to make a server from scratch, it&#39;s just a waste of time and I wouldn&#39;t use it much at all, therefore I will be using something a little more advanced than the servers out there now, every person will get some sort of credit for my finished project and hopefully I can release a good server for people to use.

I will be hardcoding for some reasons; one is I really have no clue on how to do it any more, it has been so long since the last time I made a model and added to my server it&#39;s unbelievable, even though it&#39;s really easy to do I guess I can learn a few more things about client related things. I will not be adding any custom items, I will just be finding new ways on how to add models and other things and then advance off that.

I am not going to a goal on this project, there is a difference between goals and achievements therefore everything I add I will class it as a achievement.

[center][b]Pictures[/b][/center]
I am not going to provide any pictures [b]yet[/b], the development is really early and I don&#39;t want to waste time taking screen shots of nothing.

[b]Programs[/b]
I may or may not put any custom programs on this project, if I am bored and have nothing further to do with my time then I will start on a graphical user interface for some educational purposes (Using Visual basic).

[b]Comments[/b]
Don&#39;t ask for pictures.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 26 Aug 2009 22:08:37 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/small-project-consists-of-programs/296985.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Small project consists of programs</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Fission Fission]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/fission">@Fission</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Not much info, but, Good luck on your journey mate.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/small-project-consists-of-programs/296985/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/small-project-consists-of-programs/296985/3</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 26 Aug 2009 22:08:37 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-296985-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/small-project-consists-of-programs/296985.rss">Small project consists of programs</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Small project consists of programs</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Leetviper Leetviper]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/leetviper">@Leetviper</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Is this iSoft devolpment?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/small-project-consists-of-programs/296985/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/small-project-consists-of-programs/296985/2</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 26 Aug 2009 21:18:56 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-296985-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/small-project-consists-of-programs/296985.rss">Small project consists of programs</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Small project consists of programs</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@wales_00 wales 00]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/wales_00">@wales_00</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[center]<span class="bbcode-b">Wales 00’s project</span>[/center]</p>
<p>After being on IRC for a few days and making a new modification for Taharok’s forums I decided to create a little server in the mean time while I get bored. This project may not go through but I shall release the finished project if I get bored ect.</p>
<p>[center]<span class="bbcode-b">Server information</span>[/center]<br>
I ain’t going to make a server from scratch, it’s just a waste of time and I wouldn’t use it much at all, therefore I will be using something a little more advanced than the servers out there now, every person will get some sort of credit for my finished project and hopefully I can release a good server for people to use.</p>
<p>I will be hardcoding for some reasons; one is I really have no clue on how to do it any more, it has been so long since the last time I made a model and added to my server it’s unbelievable, even though it’s really easy to do I guess I can learn a few more things about client related things. I will not be adding any custom items, I will just be finding new ways on how to add models and other things and then advance off that.</p>
<p>I am not going to a goal on this project, there is a difference between goals and achievements therefore everything I add I will class it as a achievement.</p>
<p>[center]<span class="bbcode-b">Pictures</span>[/center]<br>
I am not going to provide any pictures <span class="bbcode-b">yet</span>, the development is really early and I don’t want to waste time taking screen shots of nothing.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Programs</span><br>
I may or may not put any custom programs on this project, if I am bored and have nothing further to do with my time then I will start on a graphical user interface for some educational purposes (Using Visual basic).</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Comments</span><br>
Don’t ask for pictures.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/small-project-consists-of-programs/296985/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/small-project-consists-of-programs/296985/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2009 21:57:44 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-296985-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/small-project-consists-of-programs/296985.rss">Small project consists of programs</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
