<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Project-Tweeny I&#39;m very new at Java First major project</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/project-tweeny-im-very-new-at-java-first-major-project/298260</link>
    <description>Well, I decided to start a new project. I&#39;m not very good at Java, I only really know the basics. But I do know ALOT of C++ C# some mysql, And I&#39;m very good with Visual basic. I really don&#39;t know what base to use for my project, but I&#39;ve been sticking with a 474. I just joined a day or two ago, But I&#39;ve been playing Servers for a long time. But Almost every server I go to seems the same. Theres Deltascape pk, All these servers are all the same.. And each and everyone of them is boring. I&#39;m really honestly am sick of rsps. Same goes for all rsps websites I have never found a server That truly Is fun to play. So... This is why I&#39;m developing a new base. This may take months, years. I don&#39;t know. But I think that when I&#39;m done People will have new ideas of what a FUN server is like. My list of things on a server that I would play are...

1.Stable No lagg, 24/7
2.Fun things to do such as mini games to keep people from getting bored. Not just things like Pest control.
3.Players If there&#39;s 4 players online There no Fun? For me anywase..
4.Some kind of player VS player So You can fight people around your skill level and gain something from it.
5.A good economy. Hard training, not as hard as Runescape but hard enough so that it takes time to achieve your goals.
6.Some Cool features such as Better graphics I&#39;m planning on working on a 474. I recently got a 474 base, That someone was nice enough to release. I&#39;ve been working on that learning more and more. But I have other things in my life too. So I can&#39;t be programming all day. But I have been trying hard to get better at this. 
I also have been trying to Make a client from Visual Basic. But so far it is extremely hard and way to complicated for myself to do. But so far I have got the basic game frame and set up some other mapdata. Now don&#39;t complain or flame me Just give suggestions or say what I can Improve on. Remember I&#39;m still learning  ;)

I promise I will add Pics for the client as soon as I get back from my Grandpas house.

Well I will edit this as I go along the base for 474 that I&#39;m using is this..

http://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php/topic,334652.0.html

I&#39;ve added some basic things..
Finished Equipment tab
I fixed sending messages
Added Some basic Npcs (Man, Goblin, Woman)
Teleporting now works, When you spawn runes.
I will add pics asap.

I Really hope I get alot of ideas for this project.
I&#39;m not one of those people who say I will do this project and it turns out to be some junk and is hosted for 1-2 weeks then shut down. I have vps already so When I&#39;m ready for beta I will tell you guys.  :)
And this may not seem this good to you. But to me Its hard work and I think It will turn out good.

-Ryan (Tweeny x)</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 27 Aug 2009 23:54:13 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/project-tweeny-im-very-new-at-java-first-major-project/298260.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Project-Tweeny I&#39;m very new at Java First major project</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Tweeny_x Tweeny x]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/tweeny_x">@Tweeny_x</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Thanks Guys, I really would like some help. I need it =/ It will take less time to make and be out quicker. Also we will have more ideas. If you two really want to help I’m okay with it.</p>
<p>-Ryan</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/project-tweeny-im-very-new-at-java-first-major-project/298260/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/project-tweeny-im-very-new-at-java-first-major-project/298260/4</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 27 Aug 2009 23:54:13 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-298260-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/project-tweeny-im-very-new-at-java-first-major-project/298260.rss">Project-Tweeny I&#39;m very new at Java First major project</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Project-Tweeny I&#39;m very new at Java First major project</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Chiizu Chiizu]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/chiizu">@Chiizu</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>If u need more help just pm me <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/smiley.png?v=5" title=":smiley:" class="emoji" alt=":smiley:"> i’m ok with coding… i usta code servers and post and get like 20 ppl to play untill i couldnt find sources stable enough to be a good as close to runescape server type thing ya know? anyway need help just pm me</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/project-tweeny-im-very-new-at-java-first-major-project/298260/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/project-tweeny-im-very-new-at-java-first-major-project/298260/3</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 27 Aug 2009 23:30:11 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-298260-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/project-tweeny-im-very-new-at-java-first-major-project/298260.rss">Project-Tweeny I&#39;m very new at Java First major project</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Project-Tweeny I&#39;m very new at Java First major project</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@jeddac jeddac]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/jeddac">@jeddac</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>If you need any help just ask, i’m not the best coder but im willing to help out with testing or the simpler coding ( ill write shops and shit for you (aslong as theyre the same syntax as 317s :))</p>
<p>Add <a href="mailto:Jeddac@hotmail.com">Jeddac@hotmail.com</a></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/project-tweeny-im-very-new-at-java-first-major-project/298260/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/project-tweeny-im-very-new-at-java-first-major-project/298260/2</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 27 Aug 2009 20:34:55 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-298260-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/project-tweeny-im-very-new-at-java-first-major-project/298260.rss">Project-Tweeny I&#39;m very new at Java First major project</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Project-Tweeny I&#39;m very new at Java First major project</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Tweeny_x Tweeny x]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/tweeny_x">@Tweeny_x</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Well, I decided to start a new project. I’m not very good at Java, I only really know the basics. But I do know ALOT of C++ C# some mysql, And I’m very good with Visual basic. I really don’t know what base to use for my project, but I’ve been sticking with a 474. I just joined a day or two ago, But I’ve been playing Servers for a long time. But Almost every server I go to seems the same. Theres Deltascape pk, All these servers are all the same… And each and everyone of them is boring. I’m really honestly am sick of rsps. Same goes for all rsps websites I have never found a server That truly Is fun to play. So… This is why I’m developing a new base. This may take months, years. I don’t know. But I think that when I’m done People will have new ideas of what a FUN server is like. My list of things on a server that I would play are…</p>
<p>1.Stable No lagg, 24/7<br>
2.Fun things to do such as mini games to keep people from getting bored. Not just things like Pest control.<br>
3.Players If there’s 4 players online There no Fun? For me anywase…<br>
4.Some kind of player VS player So You can fight people around your skill level and gain something from it.<br>
5.A good economy. Hard training, not as hard as Runescape but hard enough so that it takes time to achieve your goals.<br>
6.Some Cool features such as Better graphics I’m planning on working on a 474. I recently got a 474 base, That someone was nice enough to release. I’ve been working on that learning more and more. But I have other things in my life too. So I can’t be programming all day. But I have been trying hard to get better at this.<br>
I also have been trying to Make a client from Visual Basic. But so far it is extremely hard and way to complicated for myself to do. But so far I have got the basic game frame and set up some other mapdata. Now don’t complain or flame me Just give suggestions or say what I can Improve on. Remember I’m still learning  <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/wink.png?v=6" title=":wink:" class="emoji" alt=":wink:"></p>
<p>I promise I will add Pics for the client as soon as I get back from my Grandpas house.</p>
<p>Well I will edit this as I go along the base for 474 that I’m using is this…</p>
<aside class="onebox whitelistedgeneric">
  <header class="source">
      <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/uploads/default/original/2X/1/1f0dc167bcf798bdbd70b03bf0fd1bc836e54e1a.png" class="site-icon" width="32" height="32">
      <a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/" target="_blank">moparisthebest.com</a>
  </header>
  <article class="onebox-body">
    <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/uploads/default/original/2X/4/41fecb6185fddc2758aeba68c3f8c9c78e26e4ff.png" class="thumbnail onebox-avatar" width="500" height="500">

<h3><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/" target="_blank">moparisthebest.com</a></h3>

<p>programming, irc, cars</p>


  </article>
  <div class="onebox-metadata">
    
    
  </div>
  <div style="clear: both"></div>
</aside>

<p>I’ve added some basic things…<br>
Finished Equipment tab<br>
I fixed sending messages<br>
Added Some basic Npcs (Man, Goblin, Woman)<br>
Teleporting now works, When you spawn runes.<br>
I will add pics asap.</p>
<p>I Really hope I get alot of ideas for this project.<br>
I’m not one of those people who say I will do this project and it turns out to be some junk and is hosted for 1-2 weeks then shut down. I have vps already so When I’m ready for beta I will tell you guys.  <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=6" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"><br>
And this may not seem this good to you. But to me Its hard work and I think It will turn out good.</p>
<p>-Ryan (Tweeny x)</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/project-tweeny-im-very-new-at-java-first-major-project/298260/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/project-tweeny-im-very-new-at-java-first-major-project/298260/1</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 27 Aug 2009 19:45:15 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-298260-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/project-tweeny-im-very-new-at-java-first-major-project/298260.rss">Project-Tweeny I&#39;m very new at Java First major project</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
