<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Shop help</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/shop-help/363440</link>
    <description>I&#39;ve come to a conclusion, after a long battle with trying to spawn items in a 317 I give up, can&#39;t make my moparscape do it. So now I need help with item prices and new shops for player-rights = 0-3... I want to put claws, bgs, ags, sgs, zgs, bandos, sol, and fire cape, into one shop all priced at 0 gold pieces, problem is i don&#39;t know how. So now i need your help with the following, (server is called  MTP V2 - Turmoil/Perfect Pking/Minigames - Best Pking source ever! this server can be found on the server downloads list, i advise you to download the server before posting because the code is a little different. Example: on client.java, loginmessage1 and 2 are all original runescape code, I can&#39;t find where to post different a log in message, because the old owner has a different login message that i want to change.) i want to know, which folder do i go to, to add a new shop, also how do i add items and how do i code in new prices into the (shop)?
This will help so much so please feel free to post, this isn&#39;t a server source advertisement! I&#39;m just telling others to inform them about the difference in coding!
Please help, thanks.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 09 Oct 2010 01:49:25 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/shop-help/363440.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Shop help</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@help_with_my_server help with my server]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/help_with_my_server">@help_with_my_server</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I’ve come to a conclusion, after a long battle with trying to spawn items in a 317 I give up, can’t make my moparscape do it. So now I need help with item prices and new shops for player-rights = 0-3… I want to put claws, bgs, ags, sgs, zgs, bandos, sol, and fire cape, into one shop all priced at 0 gold pieces, problem is i don’t know how. So now i need your help with the following, (server is called  MTP V2 - Turmoil/Perfect Pking/Minigames - Best Pking source ever! this server can be found on the server downloads list, i advise you to download the server before posting because the code is a little different. Example: on client.java, loginmessage1 and 2 are all original runescape code, I can’t find where to post different a log in message, because the old owner has a different login message that i want to change.) i want to know, which folder do i go to, to add a new shop, also how do i add items and how do i code in new prices into the (shop)?<br>
This will help so much so please feel free to post, this isn’t a server source advertisement! I’m just telling others to inform them about the difference in coding!<br>
Please help, thanks.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/shop-help/363440/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/shop-help/363440/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 09 Oct 2010 01:49:25 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-363440-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/shop-help/363440.rss">Shop help</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
