<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Help setting up SRL scripts</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/help-setting-up-srl-scripts/3581</link>
    <description>In most SRL scripts you get a setup that looks similar to this :
[code] Players[0].Name := &#39;&#39;;
     Players[0].Pass := &#39;&#39;;
     Players[0].Nick := &#39;&#39;;
     Players[0].Active:=True;[/code]

Ive searched everywhere and dont know how to set this up. Obviously name and pass i can set up but what is Nick and Active code for? Also you also get the same code as above for 4 or more lines with Players[2] for example. Can someone please explain how this works?</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 08 Jun 2006 23:29:37 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/help-setting-up-srl-scripts/3581.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Help setting up SRL scripts</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Dankness Dankness]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/dankness">@Dankness</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>When in Doubt Read the SRL Manual, I Know Benland, Freddy and Fawki have put mad time into this Manual just for people who don’t understand a function or somehing anything you want to know can be found there <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=9" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"></p>
<p>[php]<br>
The Player Array</p>
<p>Main philosophy behind SRL is to play with many player, not with one! These players are all lined up, they play for a short time, and then they log out to make way for the next player. This approach has a number of advantages.</p>
<ul>
<li>It is much less obvious you are autoing.</li>
<li>Better profite because scripts generally run much longer.</li>
<li>the number of randoms your Player encounters dramatically goes down.</li>
</ul>
<p>The Player Array is easy to set up, but you will need to know a bit about Arrays to fully comprehend it.</p>
<pre><code> HowManyPlayers  :=6;             
 NumberOfPlayers(HowManyPlayers);  
 CurrentPlayer:=0;       

 Players[0].Name :='yourname';
 Players[0].Pass :='yourpass';
 Players[0].Nick :='urna';
 Players[0].Loc  :='yourloc';
 Players[0].Skill:='yourskill';
 Players[0].Active:=True;
</code></pre>
<p>You set HowManyPlayers.  It determines the amount of players you have.<br>
You call NumberOfPlayers(HowManyPlayers); to set the array length and initialize the StartPlayer.<br>
The global CurrentPlayer contains the ArrayIndex. Players[CurrentPlayer] is the one playing.</p>
<p>You set the Players Name, Pass and Nick. The first two are obvious, the third one needs some explanation.<br>
SRL checks for randoms by scanning the yellow text from the mainscreen. If you encounter a Random, your name always appears on the mainscreen. That is what we scan for in Nick. Nick doesnt need your whole name. Take two, three or four letters from it and put it in Nick. Example: if your runescape is Qwertyuiop,  good Nicks would be: tyu, erty, uio or iop. Note however that nick should NOT contain the First Letter Of Your RuneScapeName, Since These Are Always capitalised.</p>
<p>loc is used to store the Players location. You will need to set this location manually. If,  for instance, you are sure you are at location Brumlidge, you set Players[CurrentPlayer].loc :=‘Brumlidge’; You can now safely log out.</p>
<p>skill is an optional parameter allowing you to assign different tasks to each Player. For mining for instance, you might set this to ‘copper’ for Player1 and ‘iron’ for Player2.</p>
<p>active determines the Player state. If active is True, then our Player is fine and standing at a known place in our script. If active is False, this means that our Player has unexpectedly logged out. active is set in the procedure NextPlayer(active; Boolean),  Warning: if you set active to False at script startup, the Player will be inactive.</p>
<p>type<br>
TUser = record<br>
Name:   String;<br>
Pass:   String;<br>
Nick:   String;<br>
Active: Boolean;<br>
Loc:    String;<br>
Skill:  String;<br>
AttackLevel: Integer;<br>
StrengthLevel: Integer;<br>
DefenceLevel: Integer;<br>
HitPointLevel: Integer;<br>
MiningLevel: Integer;<br>
SmithingLevel: Integer;<br>
CraftingLevel: Integer;<br>
MagicLevel: Integer;<br>
WoodCuttingLevel: Integer;<br>
Ore:    String;<br>
Fight:  Boolean;<br>
Worked: Integer;<br>
Banked: Integer;<br>
Killed: Integer;<br>
end;</p>
<p>var Players : array of TUser; The User Record stores all sorts of data about our player.<br>
Name contains the Login name of the player.<br>
Pass contains the Password of the player.<br>
Nick contains the ScreenName of the player for use with AntiRandom protection.<br>
Active holds the playerstate. Set Active to False if the player is lost, leave to True if he is on track. Active is toggled using NextPlayer(Active; Boolean); see for more info: “using the Player Array”<br>
Loc holds the player Location. Usefull for determining the whereabouts of our Player.<br>
Skill is a general purpose parameter usefull for storing skills, e.g. ‘steel’ or ‘copper’  for melting scripts  or ‘clay’ or ‘iron’ for mining scripts.<br>
…Level holds the skilllevels of our player, useful for autoresponding and general statistical purpose.<br>
Ore general purpose, can hold anything.<br>
Fight contains a flag that determines if our player is capabel of random fights.<br>
Worked stores the Time theplayer had worked.<br>
Banked stores the amount of banks the player has performed.<br>
Killed stores the number of kills the player has made.</p>
<p>Using the Player Array</p>
<p>A player is activated (loggedin) using the LoginPlayer command. LoginPlayer does not require any arguments. It will simply log you in.<br>
The Player continues running the script until any of three conditions are met:</p>
<ol>
<li>It has done its task. (for instance: It has banked three times)</li>
<li>It is logged out because of an emergency.</li>
<li>It is lost and logged out.</li>
</ol>
<p>In the first case, you call NextPlayer(True). This logs out our Player, sets its state to True (he will return the next round) and logs in the next Player.<br>
In the second case you call NextPlayer(True). provided you know where our Player is. You can set its location in the loc variable ( Players[CurrentPlayer].loc:=‘Brumlidge’ )<br>
In the third case our Player is lost and will not return. You call NextPlayer(False), thus effectively removing the Player from the Player Array and log in a new Player. You will need to set the Player back to his starting position.<br>
Your script will continue running until all Players are False.</p>
<p>Main Loop</p>
<p>repeat</p>
<p>if Players[CurrentPlayer].loc=‘Dalafor’ then<br>
begin<br>
WalkToMine;<br>
end;</p>
<p>if Players[CurrentPlayer].Loc=‘Timmingron’ then<br>
begin<br>
repeat<br>
Mine;<br>
if (not(Loggedin)) then break;<br>
until(InventoryFull)</p>
<pre><code>   WalkToDalafor;
   Bank;
   ProgressReport;
</code></pre>
<p>end;</p>
<p>if ((LoggedIn) and (Players[CurrentPlayer].Banked mod Loads = 0)) then<br>
begin<br>
SetChat(‘off’, 1);<br>
repeat<br>
Wait(1000);<br>
FindRandoms;<br>
until(not(LoggedIn));<br>
NextPlayer(true);<br>
end;</p>
<p>if (not(Loggedin)) then NextPlayer(false);<br>
until(false);</p>
<p>This is a typical example of how you might want to setup a mainloop using SRL. The first two are simple: walk-mine-walk-bank. But notice the use of if (not(Loggedin)) then break; inside this loop:</p>
<p>repeat<br>
Mine;<br>
if (not(Loggedin)) then break;<br>
until(InventoryFull)</p>
<p>This is essential.</p>
<p>You have to break out of every loop. Let me say that again, only louder this time:<br>
YOU HAVE TO BREAK OUT OF EVERY LOOP. In SRL there are no endless loops. All functions or procedures break one way or the other. It is vital for proper SRL scripting. Do not use:</p>
<p>repeat<br>
until(false);</p>
<p>but break, preferably when logged out.</p>
<p>Now, notice the last line: if (not(Loggedin)) then NextPlayer(false);This is the final instruction of the script. Something went wrong and we where logged out for some reason. The Player is False. We pass this to NextPlayer, thus setting Players.active to False. It is removed from the list and the next True Player is logged in.</p>
<p>Everybody has his own programmatic logic. What I have presented you here, is merely one way of doing things. Some programmers strongly oppose to the way I program, and they are prolly right<br>
[/php]</p>
<p>-Dankness<br>
SRL Admin</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/help-setting-up-srl-scripts/3581/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/help-setting-up-srl-scripts/3581/4</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jun 2006 23:29:37 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-3581-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/help-setting-up-srl-scripts/3581.rss">Help setting up SRL scripts</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Help setting up SRL scripts</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@seifer225 seifer225]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/seifer225">@seifer225</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Ok thanks inferno, now im going to take a shot at making my first SRL script. + rep</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/help-setting-up-srl-scripts/3581/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/help-setting-up-srl-scripts/3581/3</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jun 2006 21:07:53 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-3581-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/help-setting-up-srl-scripts/3581.rss">Help setting up SRL scripts</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Help setting up SRL scripts</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@inferno inferno]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/inferno">@inferno</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Name and Pass obvious like you said. Nick is three of four letters from your name (this is used in random detection) be careful not to use the first letter though as that is capitalized. Active is whether you want to use the char or not, you shouldn’t really have to change this.</p>
<p>Ok so now that is set up you have one char loaded into the srl script ready to auto on. You can add more chars though by following the same method but with Players[1], Players[2] etc. With more than one character, the script will auto for a while on one then move onto the next and keeps repeating this.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/help-setting-up-srl-scripts/3581/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/help-setting-up-srl-scripts/3581/2</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jun 2006 17:37:30 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-3581-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/help-setting-up-srl-scripts/3581.rss">Help setting up SRL scripts</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Help setting up SRL scripts</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@seifer225 seifer225]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/seifer225">@seifer225</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>In most SRL scripts you get a setup that looks similar to this :</p>
<p><code> Players[0].Name := '';
     Players[0].Pass := '';
     Players[0].Nick := '';
     Players[0].Active:=True;</code></p>
<p>Ive searched everywhere and dont know how to set this up. Obviously name and pass i can set up but what is Nick and Active code for? Also you also get the same code as above for 4 or more lines with Players[2] for example. Can someone please explain how this works?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/help-setting-up-srl-scripts/3581/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/help-setting-up-srl-scripts/3581/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jun 2006 19:06:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-3581-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/help-setting-up-srl-scripts/3581.rss">Help setting up SRL scripts</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
