<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Should Scientists</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/should-scientists/537214</link>
    <description>There are many issues in American Democracy, one of many being genetically engineering.
Should Scientists genetically engineer embryos to benefit ill people?
Heres a one sided point:
http://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/worldnews/asia/1368902/Genetically-selected-test-tube-baby-born-to-save-sisters-life.html</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2014 09:13:34 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>General Discussion</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/should-scientists/537214.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Should Scientists</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Svitkona Svitkona]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/svitkona">@Svitkona</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>If you look at it objectively it’s pretty much the same thing</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/should-scientists/537214/20">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/should-scientists/537214/20</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2014 09:13:34 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-537214-20</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/should-scientists/537214.rss">Should Scientists</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Should Scientists</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@the_wanderer The Wanderer]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/the_wanderer">@the_wanderer</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote" data-post="6" data-topic="537214">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/svitkona/40/5_e05bb34c421432ee4d40de30c10af3e5.png" class="avatar"> Svitkona:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Why is growing a human to be slaughtered different from growing animals to be slaughtered?</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Because humans give humans more rights than animals. Blame societal standards. I’m sure there’s some people who would say killing animals is worse but in general I would feel safe to assume people would feeling killing a human is worse than killing an animal. But the whole situation can be avoided if we could just create organs.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/should-scientists/537214/19">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/should-scientists/537214/19</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2014 19:41:28 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-537214-19</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/should-scientists/537214.rss">Should Scientists</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Should Scientists</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@jc22493 Jc22493]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/jc22493">@jc22493</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote" data-post="9" data-topic="537214">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/amy_webb/40/5_e05bb34c421432ee4d40de30c10af3e5.png" class="avatar"> amy_webb:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Have any of you ever thought of what your life would be like if you were born for the soul purpose of harvesting? Could you watch as others lived life, not knowing their fate when you know yours?</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>What about animals? Unless you abstain from consuming animals and animal products, this point adds no value to the conversation. If you in fact do practice this abstention, then kudos to you.</p>
<p>Sorry for posting in an old topic.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/should-scientists/537214/18">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/should-scientists/537214/18</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 08 Dec 2014 15:41:49 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-537214-18</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/should-scientists/537214.rss">Should Scientists</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Should Scientists</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@ruzylo Ruzylo]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/ruzylo">@ruzylo</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I suppose. But still.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/should-scientists/537214/17">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/should-scientists/537214/17</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2014 22:48:14 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-537214-17</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/should-scientists/537214.rss">Should Scientists</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Should Scientists</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@amy_webb1 amy_webb]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/amy_webb1">@amy_webb1</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>She wanted to give her parts because she loved her sister, however she still suffered. She wasn’t given a choice at the beginning because the mother pressured her, the reason she didn’t refuse because she knew her sister would die.</p>
<p>I understand that it is just a movie, but all ideas are based of something. The movie reflects events that may have or soon happen, we can use them as a reference to the future because it is as close as we’ve seen to the truth so far.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/should-scientists/537214/16">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/should-scientists/537214/16</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 02 Feb 2014 00:37:07 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-537214-16</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/should-scientists/537214.rss">Should Scientists</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Should Scientists</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@ruzylo Ruzylo]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/ruzylo">@ruzylo</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Sad movies… But keep in mind that the girl wanted to still give her parts, but the cancerous sister finally said no, showing the good side of humans. If there was a point it could be used and they both could live, it will never be achieved without trying.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/should-scientists/537214/15">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/should-scientists/537214/15</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 02 Feb 2014 00:21:15 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-537214-15</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/should-scientists/537214.rss">Should Scientists</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Should Scientists</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@amy_webb1 amy_webb]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/amy_webb1">@amy_webb1</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>They’re being used for cells currently, however, as The Wanderer mentioned with My Sisters Keeper, that situation is already taking place.<br>
It said in the news post that the child would need a bone marrow transplant, are they going to get that from a fetus or baby?</p>
<p>In these cases where the use of marrow or cells or small organs are taken, yes they survive but they still suffer when they shouldn’t have to.<br>
In other cases like i pointed out where the whole being is used entirely for organ harvesting, that is when they don’t survive. If you haven’t already, watch the two movies suggested in above posts because i am referring to these types of situations as an outcome of this practice.</p>
<p>I’m not saying it is my personal opinion that doesn’t allow it, i said it was societies with a majority view.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/should-scientists/537214/14">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/should-scientists/537214/14</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 02 Feb 2014 00:18:22 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-537214-14</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/should-scientists/537214.rss">Should Scientists</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Should Scientists</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Vain1 Vain_]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/vain1">@Vain1</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>amy these beings are being grown to increase survival for others. not to be used as ‘spare parts’</p>
<p>the embryos have no knowledge of what they are being used for/how they were conceived. the link in the op: the test-tube baby cured the first born’s disease, and the baby lived as well.</p>
<p>who are you to say this can’t be allowed?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/should-scientists/537214/13">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/should-scientists/537214/13</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 02 Feb 2014 00:04:48 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-537214-13</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/should-scientists/537214.rss">Should Scientists</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Should Scientists</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@ruzylo Ruzylo]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/ruzylo">@ruzylo</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>This goes back to my idea of genetically engineering US rather then making duplicates. Make our bodies stronger by recreating dna or whatever needs to be done, and litteraly make “Super-Humans” But on a world wide basis. Force our species to evolve to live longer understand knowledge better and to also have better reaction times, increase or muscle mass and the rate of increase.  We may be far from it, but the idea seems outstanding.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/should-scientists/537214/12">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/should-scientists/537214/12</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 01 Feb 2014 23:47:28 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-537214-12</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/should-scientists/537214.rss">Should Scientists</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Should Scientists</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@amy_webb1 amy_webb]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/amy_webb1">@amy_webb1</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <blockquote>please show evidence of one person living that long after being used.
these 'organisms' are grown to save another organism which has already developed a mindset. these fetuses have no knowledge of existence or anything. especially being genetically engineered in a laboratory, rather than actually bred (mating for additional offspring to save the first born) it is less inhumane</blockquote>
I wasn't talking about living after being used, i was talking about the build up to it. 
So what you're saying is these beings will be raised away from society in science labs without any contact? You don't know how others think, how are you to know what they accept or understand when they observe others? I'm sorry, isn't being genetically selected and born for the purpose of being used what we're talking about rather then being a captive?
<blockquote>nobody was brought up in this world being taught that everything is fair. and you have the same chance as one another. rather the complete opposite. life isn't fair, and to receive something, you must take it. life doesn't hand you what you want. you have to go out and get it. i'd love to see you preach equality to the world, because sure we're 'equal' in terms of race or religion, but no two people are equal when compared.</blockquote>
<p>Actually, it might be a cultural difference but i’ve been told throughout my child hood i could be anything i want to be. I have the opportunity to be, just as anyone else. Life isn’t fair because of the bias it is viewed from, for these lab beings it would not seem fair because they don’t have the chance. You say like doesn’t hand you want you want but at least us “free” humans would have the right to the opportunity. Where as these other being, by your explanation, have no ability to do so at all. How can they “go out and get it” when they’re locked up? You want to know why the world isn’t considered equal, it is because of understandings such as yours.</p>
<blockquote>society doesn't determine what scientists dedicate their time to testing. governments don't tell all research facilities what to study. these tests were up to the discretion of the facility. not society. these facilities don't tell the hospitals to perform transplants to those who need them</blockquote>
<p>No it does, but it does have a say in what science practices with the evidence it finds. If the facilities are studying something beyond reason the government of the country has the ability to stop it, just because they don’t it doesn’t mean they can’t. If the majority disagree with the practice, the government is obligated to stop it.</p>
<blockquote>you want to preach equality, go try to convince the world that everyone deserves the transplant, regardless of wealth. they all deserve the same opportunity to live life.</blockquote>
<p>Yes, that is what i want to do. I believe everyone should live on the same level, or at least have the same opportunities and you try and degrade me for that. What gives wealthy people the right to own another being with their own thoughts, beliefs and understandings of life?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/should-scientists/537214/11">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/should-scientists/537214/11</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 01 Feb 2014 23:41:19 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-537214-11</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/should-scientists/537214.rss">Should Scientists</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Should Scientists</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Vain1 Vain_]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/vain1">@Vain1</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“amy_webb, post:9, topic:537214”]Have any of you ever thought of what your life would be like if you were born for the soul purpose of harvesting? Could you watch as others lived life, not knowing their fate when you know yours?[/quote]please show evidence of one person living that long after being used.<br>
these ‘organisms’ are grown to save another organism which has already developed a mindset. these fetuses have no knowledge of existence or anything. especially being genetically engineered in a laboratory, rather than actually bred (mating for additional offspring to save the first born) it is less inhumane.</p>
<aside class="quote" data-post="9" data-topic="537214">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/amy_webb/40/5_e05bb34c421432ee4d40de30c10af3e5.png" class="avatar"> amy_webb:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>We base life on a system of fairness and equality, at least we like to think so. You’re brought up in this world believing you have just as good of a chance as anyone, that you are equal to the people around you. Knowing you are equal to everyone you still diminish others because “they”, not you, are no different to animals.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>nobody was brought up in this world being taught that everything is fair. and you have the same chance as one another. rather the complete opposite. life isn’t fair, and to receive something, you must take it. life doesn’t hand you what you want. you have to go out and get it. i’d love to see you preach equality to the world, because sure we’re ‘equal’ in terms of race or religion, but no two people are equal when compared.</p>
<p>[quote=“amy_webb, post:9, topic:537214”]Just mentioning the idea of organ harvesting with genetic engineering shows society isn’t ready for it. Society has already decided that an engineered being is less of those who are dying and need an organ transplant. Society has already accepted that one being is worth saving over another because of their purpose or nature of birth.[/quote]society doesn’t determine what scientists dedicate their time to testing. governments don’t tell all research facilities what to study. these tests were up to the discretion of the facility. not society. these facilities don’t tell the hospitals to perform transplants to those who need them.</p>
<p>you want to preach equality, go try to convince the world that everyone deserves the transplant, regardless of wealth. they all deserve the same opportunity to live life. blah blah</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/should-scientists/537214/10">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/should-scientists/537214/10</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 01 Feb 2014 23:15:37 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-537214-10</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/should-scientists/537214.rss">Should Scientists</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Should Scientists</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@amy_webb1 amy_webb]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/amy_webb1">@amy_webb1</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Have any of you ever thought of what your life would be like if you were born for the soul purpose of harvesting? Could you watch as others lived life, not knowing their fate when you know yours? There is a movie that expresses this idea called Never Let Me Go (2010), and if you’ve ever seen it then you’ll understand why it is a horrible idea.</p>
<p>We base life on a system of fairness and equality, at least we like to think so. You’re brought up in this world believing you have just as good of a chance as anyone, that you are equal to the people around you. Knowing you are equal to everyone you still diminish others because “they”, not you, are no different to animals.</p>
<p>You sit around and think “No, that is fine” because it isn’t happening to you, put yourself in the shoes of the other person. Use your empathy for one minute so understand the situation, this isn’t strictly scientific, this is the life and well-being of another human. This effects the life of many others, their feelings, their beliefs, and here you are thinking you’ve a right to decide what happens to them.</p>
<p>Just mentioning the idea of organ harvesting with genetic engineering shows society isn’t ready for it. Society has already decided that an engineered being is less of those who are dying and need an organ transplant. Society has already accepted that one being is worth saving over another because of their purpose or nature of birth.</p>
<p>It saddens me to see the arguments of this topic, but reality is as it is. If you would like to see a possible outcome of genetic engineering then you should look up the work of Patricia Piccinini. She is an artist who expresses her ideas in genetic engineering through lifelike sculptures. You may think that she is just an artist, however she has experience in her topic’s field and shows a realistic outcome of the future when it comes to engineering.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/should-scientists/537214/9">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/should-scientists/537214/9</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 01 Feb 2014 23:06:46 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-537214-9</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/should-scientists/537214.rss">Should Scientists</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Should Scientists</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Vain1 Vain_]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/vain1">@Vain1</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>^ it actually is a 3d printer. not all make plastic casts.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/should-scientists/537214/8">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/should-scientists/537214/8</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 01 Feb 2014 21:45:50 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-537214-8</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/should-scientists/537214.rss">Should Scientists</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Should Scientists</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@naseem142 naseem142]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/naseem142">@naseem142</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote" data-post="6" data-topic="537214">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/svitkona/40/5_e05bb34c421432ee4d40de30c10af3e5.png" class="avatar"> Svitkona:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Why is growing a human to be slaughtered different from growing animals to be slaughtered?</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I don’t get that too , poor animals we took control of them and made advantage of it  <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/frowning.png?v=5" title=":frowning:" class="emoji" alt=":frowning:"></p>
<p>But seriosly , There is actually a machine that creates organ tissues but really slowly and cureently being tested and improved , The idea came from that 3D printer that prints 3D plastic objects , i saw that all on discovery science chanel  <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/expressionless.png?v=5" title=":expressionless:" class="emoji" alt=":expressionless:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/should-scientists/537214/7">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/should-scientists/537214/7</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 01 Feb 2014 21:43:24 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-537214-7</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/should-scientists/537214.rss">Should Scientists</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Should Scientists</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Svitkona Svitkona]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/svitkona">@Svitkona</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Why is growing a human to be slaughtered different from growing animals to be slaughtered?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/should-scientists/537214/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/should-scientists/537214/6</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 01 Feb 2014 21:37:32 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-537214-6</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/should-scientists/537214.rss">Should Scientists</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Should Scientists</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@the_wanderer The Wanderer]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/the_wanderer">@the_wanderer</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Have you seen the movie My Sister’s Keeper? Pretty sad. I think we should wait a little bit until we can genetically grow the organs rather than grow a human to be slaughtered. We have rights as human’s defined by human’s, so you cannot take away their rights to benefit others. It will never be allowed in the US. However growing some heart tissue that was genetically engineered, sure.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/should-scientists/537214/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/should-scientists/537214/5</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 01 Feb 2014 21:29:23 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-537214-5</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/should-scientists/537214.rss">Should Scientists</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Should Scientists</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@T41 t4]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/t41">@T41</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>sure, who gives a fuck. we eat gmo’s all day</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/should-scientists/537214/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/should-scientists/537214/4</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2014 20:06:07 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-537214-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/should-scientists/537214.rss">Should Scientists</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Should Scientists</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Tutorial Tutorial]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/tutorial">@Tutorial</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>The only problem I think that this would cause is those that practice a more religious way of living, which means they let natures take it course, which isn’t very practical in some cases.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/should-scientists/537214/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/should-scientists/537214/3</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2014 04:23:53 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-537214-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/should-scientists/537214.rss">Should Scientists</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Should Scientists</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@ruzylo Ruzylo]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/ruzylo">@ruzylo</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Why not. Evolution is for survival. If you can use genetically engineering to increse the speed of evolution, the idea is just overwhelmingly amazing. Imagine living for 400+ years. Being at one point alaive during the civil war, and another during 9-11. You can see anything and everything, how things change and not only that but your knowledge would always increase. Put being alive longer testing something longer. The idea can advance civilization, not how we are now but faster. One day mp3, one month later ipod. The world would change with forced evolution.</p>
<p>On your point. If a baby is made in a lab, and is used to save a life. Whats the full harm. That baby would have never been born in the first place if there wasn’t a reason for it. &lt;&lt; I didn’t read the article but I’ve heard of such things.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/should-scientists/537214/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/should-scientists/537214/2</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2014 04:11:07 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-537214-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/should-scientists/537214.rss">Should Scientists</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Should Scientists</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@chillwitm888 chillwitm888]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/chillwitm888">@chillwitm888</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>There are many issues in American Democracy, one of many being genetically engineering.<br>
Should Scientists genetically engineer embryos to benefit ill people?<br>
Heres a one sided point:<br>
<a href="http://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/worldnews/asia/1368902/Genetically-selected-test-tube-baby-born-to-save-sisters-life.html" class="onebox" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">http://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/worldnews/asia/1368902/Genetically-selected-test-tube-baby-born-to-save-sisters-life.html</a></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/should-scientists/537214/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/should-scientists/537214/1</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2013 05:26:26 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-537214-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/should-scientists/537214.rss">Should Scientists</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
