<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Guidelines &amp; Rules</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/guidelines-rules/521016</link>
    <description>Well, you&#39;re a writer or editor for the Mopar Monthly. Now what? This board was created for the Mopar Monthly team to discuss the article&#39;s nominations, potential members, and setup for future editions.
Outlined in this thread will be the guidelines - such as our vision and things to think about - and the rules of the Mopar Monthly.

[u][b]Guidelines:[/b][/u]
[ul][li][u]The Vision:[/u] I&#39;ve started this &#39;project&#39; for the simple purpose of trying to bring some potential activity to the blog on our homepage. Seeing as it didn&#39;t take off as it was hoped to, I was thinking that a blog post series like this could spark some community engagement and/or hopefully give new ideas to other members to post blog entries.[/li]
[li][u]What Your Job Is:[/u] Your job is to write, edit, and suggest articles to add to each edition. Because you are a part of the team, your suggestions are the first to be seen. When you first joined the team as a writer or editor, you were assigned a section(s) to manage. If you haven&#39;t already been assigned somehow, please contact me.[/li]
[li][u]What To Do If You Don&#39;t Finish In Time:[/u] Sit down and relax. This is a volunteer job, meaning that you aren&#39;t obligated to do anything. If you don&#39;t have anything submitted by the time allotted, then nothing will happen. When I assign a date by which I want  the sections that you are managing, I usually will have the due date be somewhere in the range of one week before I plan to submit.[/li]
[li][u]How You Will Be Removed:[/u] The only way I will ever remove you from the writing team: if you are handing out copies of the Mopar Monthly, or any parts of it, before the edition is published and public. As I said earlier, you are not required to submit the area that you are managing, as this is volunteer work and I understand if you are busy.[/li][/ul]

[b][u]The Rules:[/u][/b]
[ul][li]Seeing as we are a part of Mopar, we are to follow the [url=http://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php/topic,342270.0.html]Global Rules[/url] of the forums. Infringement on these rules will be left to staff decision.[/li]
[li]My standards are very easy to reach, simply put. If I see that you&#39;re putting effort into the work I&#39;m receiving, I&#39;ll use it (with re-reads and edits as necessary, of course). I don&#39;t require you to do any work for the month at all, you just won&#39;t have your name mentioned in the author&#39;s tab.[/li]
[li]You are to keep all drafts of the Mopar Monthly to this board only. Sharing previews with friends isn&#39;t an exception. If you do, I will not use that article for the month and write my own, and you will promptly be removed from the team.[/li]
[li]Cite all work that you include which isn&#39;t yours. You will not be allowed to contribute to the following month&#39;s edition should I discover that you don&#39;t properly accredit original creators.[/li]
[li]Enjoy yourself. As I said previously, this is volunteer work. Have a good time, and keep the community interested.[/li][/ul]</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2013 03:16:17 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Community Suggestions</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/guidelines-rules/521016.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Guidelines &amp; Rules</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Flame3 John]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/flame3">@Flame3</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Something as trivial as a Mopar Monthly nomination is fine, I suppose. I’d prefer if you didn’t include interview nominations though, considering that those users might be interviewed in the future.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/guidelines-rules/521016/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/guidelines-rules/521016/3</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2013 03:16:17 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-521016-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/guidelines-rules/521016.rss">Guidelines &amp; Rules</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Guidelines &amp; Rules</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Ambokile Ambokile]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/ambokile">@Ambokile</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote quote-modified" data-post="1" data-topic="521016">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 Flame_:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>[ul][li]<span class="bbcode-u">How You Will Be Removed:</span> The only way I will ever remove you from the writing team: if you are handing out copies of the Mopar Monthly, or any parts of it, before the edition is published and public. As I said earlier, you are not required to submit the area that you are managing, as this is volunteer work and I understand if you are busy.[/li][/ul]</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Regarding the above rule, is it acceptable to tell people who the nominations were <span class="bbcode-b">after</span> the issue has been published?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/guidelines-rules/521016/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/guidelines-rules/521016/2</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2013 12:48:01 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-521016-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/guidelines-rules/521016.rss">Guidelines &amp; Rules</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Guidelines &amp; Rules</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Flame3 John]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/flame3">@Flame3</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Well, you’re a writer or editor for the Mopar Monthly. Now what? This board was created for the Mopar Monthly team to discuss the article’s nominations, potential members, and setup for future editions.<br>
Outlined in this thread will be the guidelines - such as our vision and things to think about - and the rules of the Mopar Monthly.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-u"><span class="bbcode-b">Guidelines:</span></span><br>
[ul][li]<span class="bbcode-u">The Vision:</span> I’ve started this ‘project’ for the simple purpose of trying to bring some potential activity to the blog on our homepage. Seeing as it didn’t take off as it was hoped to, I was thinking that a blog post series like this could spark some community engagement and/or hopefully give new ideas to other members to post blog entries.[/li]<br>
[li]<span class="bbcode-u">What Your Job Is:</span> Your job is to write, edit, and suggest articles to add to each edition. Because you are a part of the team, your suggestions are the first to be seen. When you first joined the team as a writer or editor, you were assigned a section(s) to manage. If you haven’t already been assigned somehow, please contact me.[/li]<br>
[li]<span class="bbcode-u">What To Do If You Don’t Finish In Time:</span> Sit down and relax. This is a volunteer job, meaning that you aren’t obligated to do anything. If you don’t have anything submitted by the time allotted, then nothing will happen. When I assign a date by which I want  the sections that you are managing, I usually will have the due date be somewhere in the range of one week before I plan to submit.[/li]<br>
[li]<span class="bbcode-u">How You Will Be Removed:</span> The only way I will ever remove you from the writing team: if you are handing out copies of the Mopar Monthly, or any parts of it, before the edition is published and public. As I said earlier, you are not required to submit the area that you are managing, as this is volunteer work and I understand if you are busy.[/li][/ul]</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b"><span class="bbcode-u">The Rules:</span></span><br>
[ul][li]Seeing as we are a part of Mopar, we are to follow the <a href="http://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php/topic,342270.0.html" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">Global Rules</a> of the forums. Infringement on these rules will be left to staff decision.[/li]<br>
[li]My standards are very easy to reach, simply put. If I see that you’re putting effort into the work I’m receiving, I’ll use it (with re-reads and edits as necessary, of course). I don’t require you to do any work for the month at all, you just won’t have your name mentioned in the author’s tab.[/li]<br>
[li]You are to keep all drafts of the Mopar Monthly to this board only. Sharing previews with friends isn’t an exception. If you do, I will not use that article for the month and write my own, and you will promptly be removed from the team.[/li]<br>
[li]Cite all work that you include which isn’t yours. You will not be allowed to contribute to the following month’s edition should I discover that you don’t properly accredit original creators.[/li]<br>
[li]Enjoy yourself. As I said previously, this is volunteer work. Have a good time, and keep the community interested.[/li][/ul]</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/guidelines-rules/521016/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/guidelines-rules/521016/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 08 Jun 2013 00:21:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-521016-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/guidelines-rules/521016.rss">Guidelines &amp; Rules</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
