<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Leeching [READ NOW OR BE AT RISK FOR A WARN OR WORSE]</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/leeching-read-now-or-be-at-risk-for-a-warn-or-worse/254091</link>
    <description>It appears many people are accusing others of &#39;leeching&#39;, or stealing and re-releasing without credit, other people&#39;s work. This applies to the following sections primarily:

[url=http://moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php/board,49.0.html]RS2 Server Downloads[/url]
[url=http://moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php/board,51.0.html]RS2 Server Tutorials[/url]
[url=http://moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php/board,129.0.html]Models[/url]

Leeching is strictly forbidden and will result in a lock of the topic charged with leeching. Excessive leeching will result in a ban, so do not try it. You [i]can[/i] post another person&#39;s server [b]if and only if the person has given credit and is appropriately accredited[/b]. Failure to comply with this will result in a lock of the charged topic.

[b]Note to all people accusing someone else of leeching: [/b] do NOT accuse someone else of leeching unless you have [b]ABSOLUTE PROOF[/b]. Failure to do this can result in a warning or worse for you, considering it is very annoying looking at people accusing others of leeching with zero proof.

Finally, this new rule can be bent heavily depending on the discretion of the moderator. The punishment for leeching will result from a locked topic to a ban, depending on the level of leeching and whether it was excessive. People accusing others of leeching can also be punished from a warning to a mute depending on the discretion of the moderator.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2008 20:34:06 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Community Suggestions</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/leeching-read-now-or-be-at-risk-for-a-warn-or-worse/254091.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Leeching [READ NOW OR BE AT RISK FOR A WARN OR WORSE]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@mod_taharok Taharok]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/mod_taharok">@mod_taharok</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>It appears many people are accusing others of ‘leeching’, or stealing and re-releasing without credit, other people’s work. This applies to the following sections primarily:</p>
<p><a href="http://moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php/board,49.0.html" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">RS2 Server Downloads</a><br>
<a href="http://moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php/board,51.0.html" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">RS2 Server Tutorials</a><br>
<a href="http://moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php/board,129.0.html" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">Models</a></p>
<p>Leeching is strictly forbidden and will result in a lock of the topic charged with leeching. Excessive leeching will result in a ban, so do not try it. You <span class="bbcode-i">can</span> post another person’s server <span class="bbcode-b">if and only if the person has given credit and is appropriately accredited</span>. Failure to comply with this will result in a lock of the charged topic.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Note to all people accusing someone else of leeching: </span> do NOT accuse someone else of leeching unless you have <span class="bbcode-b">ABSOLUTE PROOF</span>. Failure to do this can result in a warning or worse for you, considering it is very annoying looking at people accusing others of leeching with zero proof.</p>
<p>Finally, this new rule can be bent heavily depending on the discretion of the moderator. The punishment for leeching will result from a locked topic to a ban, depending on the level of leeching and whether it was excessive. People accusing others of leeching can also be punished from a warning to a mute depending on the discretion of the moderator.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/leeching-read-now-or-be-at-risk-for-a-warn-or-worse/254091/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/leeching-read-now-or-be-at-risk-for-a-warn-or-worse/254091/1</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2008 20:34:06 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-254091-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/leeching-read-now-or-be-at-risk-for-a-warn-or-worse/254091.rss">Leeching [READ NOW OR BE AT RISK FOR A WARN OR WORSE]</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
