<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Threats To Internet Freedom All Too Real</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/threats-to-internet-freedom-all-too-real/30949</link>
    <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;Threats To Internet Freedom All Too Real
Cyberspace police state dismissed by some, yet agenda for regulated, controlled, patrolled &quot;Internet 2&quot; advances

Paul Joseph Watson
Prison Planet
Thursday, November 30, 2006

The Internet is the last true unregulated outpost of freedom of speech but moves are afoot to stifle, suffocate and control the world wide web. These threats are not hidden nor are they hard to deduce and yet a significant minority of truth seekers and activists remain naive as to their scope.

Following our publication of yesterday&#39;s article, RIAA Legal Ruling Could Shut Down The Internet, we received a mixed response. Many were aware of the imminent dangers that threaten to change the face of the Internet but others were more hostile to the supposition that the world wide web could be devastated by landmark copyright case rulings as well as plans to develop &quot;Internet 2.&quot;

Some accused us of yellow journalism and scaremongering yet the warning that the Elektra vs. Barker case could criminalize the very mechanism that characterizes the Internet was not concocted by Alex Jones or Paul Joseph Watson, it was a statement made by the very lawyer fighting the case, Ray Beckerman.

It was a danger also reported on by one of the UK&#39;s biggest technology news websites, the Inquirer, which also yesterday highlighted the frightening development in an article entitled, RIAA wants the Internet shut down.

The RIAA&#39;s argument is that defendant Tenise Barker downloaded music files and made them available for distribution by placing them in a shared folder. Though Barker paid for the files and downloaded them legally, and the files were not copied by anyone, the RIAA&#39;s motion states that simply making the files available constitutes copyright infringement.

As Beckerman points out, the entire Internet is nothing more than a giant network of hyperlinks making files &#39;available&#39; to other people. If we link to CNN.com, we are making the file that constitutes the CNN homepage &#39;available&#39; to other users. We don&#39;t own the copyright to any of CNN&#39;s material therefore if the RIAA&#39;s argument is accepted, by simply making that CNN file available from our website, even if no one clicks on the link, we are committing a breach of copyright.

At no point in our article did we suggest that the ruling definitely would shut down the Internet, we highlighted the fact that hundreds of transnational corporations like Amazon.com who solely rely on Internet trade would scream bloody murder. But what the ruling would grease the skids for is the move towards a strictly regulated Internet whereby government permission would be required to run a website and that website would be subject to censoring and deletion if it violated any &quot;terms of use.&quot;

The example I highlighted yesterday on the Alex Jones Show was that running a blog would be like having a You Tube account - any politically sensitive or controversial information that the owners dislike would immediately be removed as it is frequently on You Tube.

In addition, the slide towards a licensed Internet that will be sold using fear of identity and credit card fraud could lead to mandatory biometric thumb or finger scanning simply to access the world wide web.

This is hardly a stretch of the imagination, since numerous public services and functions of society are increasingly accessible only through providing some form of biometric identification. Credit passes for travel, ATM terminals and access to theme parks like Disneyland are just a few of the many services we use that are shifting towards mandatory biometric gatekeeping.

Furthermore, Pay By Touch Online and other companies have already developed and launched keyboard biometric finger scanning terminals that require users to submit their biometric print before they can access the Internet or buy online.

Piggybacking the net neutrality debate, Internet 2 is being shaped to replace the old Internet, which will be allowed to self-destruct as it labors under the pressures of being relegated to slower and slower pipes and users will simply desert a painstaking system.

Earlier this year under the headline, The End of the Internet?, The Nation magazine reported,

&quot;The nation&#39;s largest telephone and cable companies are crafting an alarming set of strategies that would transform the free, open and nondiscriminatory Internet of today to a privately run and branded service that would charge a fee for virtually everything we do online.&quot;

&quot;Verizon, Comcast, Bell South and other communications giants are developing strategies that would track and store information on our every move in cyberspace in a vast data-collection and marketing system, the scope of which could rival the National Security Agency. According to white papers now being circulated in the cable, telephone and telecommunications industries, those with the deepest pockets--corporations, special-interest groups and major advertisers--would get preferred treatment. Content from these providers would have first priority on our computer and television screens, while information seen as undesirable, such as peer-to-peer communications, could be relegated to a slow lane or simply shut out.&quot;

Internet 2 is being billed as the next generation of the world wide web and it has already set global speed records in terms of data transfer, far outstripping the old Internet.

One of the fathers of the Internet, David Clark, who served as chief protocol architect for the government&#39;s internet development initiative in the 1980s, has been given $200,000 by the National Science Foundation to covertly work on a &quot;whole new infrastructure to replace today&#39;s global network,&quot; according to Wired Magazine.

Clark has vowed to create a &quot;brave new world&quot; in designing the new Internet, characterizing what he wanted for the new network to be &quot;a coherent security architecture.&quot;

Dovetailing the onset of Internet 2 are government propaganda campaigns to demonize the existing Internet as a wild backwater for hate crime, child pornography and a terrorist recruiting ground.

Establishment kingpins and their cheerleaders have increased their level of vitriolic rhetoric against the Internet in recent months, as legislation in both the U.S. and Europe to regulate, stifle and license the Internet moves forward.

The White House&#39;s own recently de-classified strategy for &quot;winning the war on terror&quot; targets Internet conspiracy theories as a recruiting ground for terrorists and threatens to &quot;diminish&quot; their influence.

In addition, the Pentagon recently announced its effort to infiltrate the Internet and propagandize for the war on terror.

In a speech last month, Homeland Security director Michael Chertoff identified the web as a &quot;terror training camp,&quot; through which &quot;disaffected people living in the United States&quot; are developing &quot;radical ideologies and potentially violent skills.&quot;

Chertoff pledged to dispatch Homeland Security agents to local police departments in order to aid in the apprehension of domestic terrorists who use the Internet as a political tool.

The European Union, led by former Stalinist and potential future British Prime Minister John Reid, has also vowed to shut down &quot;terrorists&quot; who use the Internet to spread propaganda.

The dangers to the freedom and very existence of the Internet as we know it are all too real and the way to counteract these developments is to get involved and get the word out. Simply burying our heads in the sand and being apathetic and naive about the threat is only going to aid those who wish to see the last outpost of freedom of speech shut off forever.&lt;/blockquote&gt;[url=http://prisonplanet.com/articles/november2006/301106internetfreedom.htm]From Here[/url]

What do you think about that?</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2006 22:28:59 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>General Discussion</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/threats-to-internet-freedom-all-too-real/30949.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Threats To Internet Freedom All Too Real</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@theliberator theliberator]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/theliberator">@theliberator</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“flamed fury1, post:4, topic:30949”]All i’m saying about shutting the internet down is… GOOD LUCK![/quote] yea do they honestly think they could actually do that there are way to many people that access the internet its impossible to shut it down.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/threats-to-internet-freedom-all-too-real/30949/21">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/threats-to-internet-freedom-all-too-real/30949/21</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2006 22:28:59 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-30949-21</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/threats-to-internet-freedom-all-too-real/30949.rss">Threats To Internet Freedom All Too Real</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Threats To Internet Freedom All Too Real</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@pookey71 Pookey71]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/pookey71">@pookey71</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>TLDR</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/threats-to-internet-freedom-all-too-real/30949/20">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/threats-to-internet-freedom-all-too-real/30949/20</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2006 19:30:15 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-30949-20</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/threats-to-internet-freedom-all-too-real/30949.rss">Threats To Internet Freedom All Too Real</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Threats To Internet Freedom All Too Real</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@pko pko]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/pko">@pko</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Impossible. Would be way to many lawsuits, and other legal battles.</p>
<p>They may shut down some things, but not anything huge.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/threats-to-internet-freedom-all-too-real/30949/19">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/threats-to-internet-freedom-all-too-real/30949/19</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2006 19:11:23 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-30949-19</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/threats-to-internet-freedom-all-too-real/30949.rss">Threats To Internet Freedom All Too Real</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Threats To Internet Freedom All Too Real</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Annex Annex]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/annex">@Annex</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>It is a flawed idea it would simply cost too much to have policing for port 80 alone. Also how would they access people who block their ips from connecting?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/threats-to-internet-freedom-all-too-real/30949/18">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/threats-to-internet-freedom-all-too-real/30949/18</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2006 05:43:19 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-30949-18</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/threats-to-internet-freedom-all-too-real/30949.rss">Threats To Internet Freedom All Too Real</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Threats To Internet Freedom All Too Real</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@DeadBird DeadBird]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/deadbird">@DeadBird</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>The next civil war?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/threats-to-internet-freedom-all-too-real/30949/17">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/threats-to-internet-freedom-all-too-real/30949/17</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2006 05:27:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-30949-17</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/threats-to-internet-freedom-all-too-real/30949.rss">Threats To Internet Freedom All Too Real</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Threats To Internet Freedom All Too Real</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@KyleGut3 KyleGut3]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/kylegut3">@KyleGut3</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Lets not worry about this now, first we have to keep ATT and other phone companies from taking control of or beloved interwebz. <a href="http://www.savetheinternet.com/" rel="nofollow noopener">http://www.savetheinternet.com/</a></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/threats-to-internet-freedom-all-too-real/30949/16">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/threats-to-internet-freedom-all-too-real/30949/16</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2006 04:47:09 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-30949-16</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/threats-to-internet-freedom-all-too-real/30949.rss">Threats To Internet Freedom All Too Real</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Threats To Internet Freedom All Too Real</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Taylor Taylor]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/taylor">@Taylor</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>the Internet is complete freedom!</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/threats-to-internet-freedom-all-too-real/30949/15">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/threats-to-internet-freedom-all-too-real/30949/15</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2006 04:46:28 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-30949-15</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/threats-to-internet-freedom-all-too-real/30949.rss">Threats To Internet Freedom All Too Real</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Threats To Internet Freedom All Too Real</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Javacisnotrecognized _^_]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/javacisnotrecognized">@Javacisnotrecognized</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Just because someone is deemed the ‘correct authority’ doesn’t mean they have power. The internet evolves through the work of thousands of people around the clock and around the World.</p>
<p>They obviously will be unable to modify it <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=6" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/threats-to-internet-freedom-all-too-real/30949/14">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/threats-to-internet-freedom-all-too-real/30949/14</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2006 04:36:39 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-30949-14</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/threats-to-internet-freedom-all-too-real/30949.rss">Threats To Internet Freedom All Too Real</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Threats To Internet Freedom All Too Real</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@The_Un-Named The Un-Named]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/the_un-named">@The_Un-Named</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote no-group quote-modified" data-post="12" data-topic="30949">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/javacisnotrecognized/40/5_6259e4fa9dfe0dec282fb0955bb1974c.png" class="avatar"> Javacisnotrecognized:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Maybe some, but they wouldn’t be able to make any actual changes to the intenet overall. It is going to be pretty comical watching them try <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/wink.png?v=6" title=":wink:" class="emoji" alt=":wink:"></p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>If they have enough evidence that a server/multiple servers are being used to share illegal files then yes, they will use the correct authority’s.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/threats-to-internet-freedom-all-too-real/30949/13">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/threats-to-internet-freedom-all-too-real/30949/13</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2006 04:33:32 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-30949-13</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/threats-to-internet-freedom-all-too-real/30949.rss">Threats To Internet Freedom All Too Real</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Threats To Internet Freedom All Too Real</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Javacisnotrecognized _^_]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/javacisnotrecognized">@Javacisnotrecognized</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Maybe some, but they wouldn’t be able to make any actual changes to the intenet overall. It is going to be pretty comical watching them try <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/wink.png?v=6" title=":wink:" class="emoji" alt=":wink:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/threats-to-internet-freedom-all-too-real/30949/12">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/threats-to-internet-freedom-all-too-real/30949/12</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2006 04:27:34 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-30949-12</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/threats-to-internet-freedom-all-too-real/30949.rss">Threats To Internet Freedom All Too Real</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Threats To Internet Freedom All Too Real</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@The_Un-Named The Un-Named]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/the_un-named">@The_Un-Named</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“Javacisnotrecognized, post:10, topic:30949”][quote author=The Un-Named link=topic=45208.msg551446#msg551446 date=1164945714]<br>
The RIAA have a lot of power.<br>
[/quote]</p>
<p>Your pretty funny yourself :)[/quote]</p>
<p>Seriously, I’m sure they could take down a lot of copy write material if they wanted to.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/threats-to-internet-freedom-all-too-real/30949/11">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/threats-to-internet-freedom-all-too-real/30949/11</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2006 04:25:46 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-30949-11</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/threats-to-internet-freedom-all-too-real/30949.rss">Threats To Internet Freedom All Too Real</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Threats To Internet Freedom All Too Real</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Javacisnotrecognized _^_]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/javacisnotrecognized">@Javacisnotrecognized</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote no-group" data-post="9" data-topic="30949">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 The Un-Named:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>The RIAA have a lot of power.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Your pretty funny yourself <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=6" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/threats-to-internet-freedom-all-too-real/30949/10">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/threats-to-internet-freedom-all-too-real/30949/10</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2006 04:04:06 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-30949-10</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/threats-to-internet-freedom-all-too-real/30949.rss">Threats To Internet Freedom All Too Real</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Threats To Internet Freedom All Too Real</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@The_Un-Named The Un-Named]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/the_un-named">@The_Un-Named</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“Javacisnotrecognized, post:7, topic:30949”][quote author=The Un-Named link=topic=45208.msg551404#msg551404 date=1164945370]<br>
A lot of the internet is legit material for LEARNING PURPOSES.<br>
[/quote]</p>
<p>You act like they actually have a chance at doing anything :P[/quote]</p>
<p>The RIAA have a lot of power.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/threats-to-internet-freedom-all-too-real/30949/9">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/threats-to-internet-freedom-all-too-real/30949/9</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2006 04:01:54 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-30949-9</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/threats-to-internet-freedom-all-too-real/30949.rss">Threats To Internet Freedom All Too Real</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Threats To Internet Freedom All Too Real</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@White_Castle White Castle]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/white_castle">@White_Castle</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>FUCK THE MAN! REBEL!</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/threats-to-internet-freedom-all-too-real/30949/8">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/threats-to-internet-freedom-all-too-real/30949/8</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2006 04:00:17 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-30949-8</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/threats-to-internet-freedom-all-too-real/30949.rss">Threats To Internet Freedom All Too Real</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Threats To Internet Freedom All Too Real</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Javacisnotrecognized _^_]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/javacisnotrecognized">@Javacisnotrecognized</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote no-group" data-post="6" data-topic="30949">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 The Un-Named:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>A lot of the internet is legit material for LEARNING PURPOSES.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>You act like they actually have a chance at doing anything <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=6" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/threats-to-internet-freedom-all-too-real/30949/7">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/threats-to-internet-freedom-all-too-real/30949/7</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2006 03:57:47 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-30949-7</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/threats-to-internet-freedom-all-too-real/30949.rss">Threats To Internet Freedom All Too Real</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Threats To Internet Freedom All Too Real</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@The_Un-Named The Un-Named]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/the_un-named">@The_Un-Named</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>A lot of the internet is legit material for LEARNING PURPOSES.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/threats-to-internet-freedom-all-too-real/30949/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/threats-to-internet-freedom-all-too-real/30949/6</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2006 03:56:10 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-30949-6</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/threats-to-internet-freedom-all-too-real/30949.rss">Threats To Internet Freedom All Too Real</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Threats To Internet Freedom All Too Real</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@g00dg0d g00dg0d]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/g00dg0d">@g00dg0d</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Lol if they ever do that I would laugh for awhile then realize what they did and cry.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/threats-to-internet-freedom-all-too-real/30949/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/threats-to-internet-freedom-all-too-real/30949/5</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2006 03:50:59 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-30949-5</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/threats-to-internet-freedom-all-too-real/30949.rss">Threats To Internet Freedom All Too Real</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Threats To Internet Freedom All Too Real</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@flamed_fury1 flamed fury1]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/flamed_fury1">@flamed_fury1</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>All i’m saying about shutting the internet down is… GOOD LUCK!</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/threats-to-internet-freedom-all-too-real/30949/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/threats-to-internet-freedom-all-too-real/30949/4</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2006 01:21:15 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-30949-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/threats-to-internet-freedom-all-too-real/30949.rss">Threats To Internet Freedom All Too Real</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Threats To Internet Freedom All Too Real</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Javacisnotrecognized _^_]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/javacisnotrecognized">@Javacisnotrecognized</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>It’s pretty funny <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=6" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/threats-to-internet-freedom-all-too-real/30949/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/threats-to-internet-freedom-all-too-real/30949/3</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2006 01:15:32 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-30949-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/threats-to-internet-freedom-all-too-real/30949.rss">Threats To Internet Freedom All Too Real</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Threats To Internet Freedom All Too Real</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@flamed_fury1 flamed fury1]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/flamed_fury1">@flamed_fury1</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>THE INTERNET RULES!!!</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/threats-to-internet-freedom-all-too-real/30949/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/threats-to-internet-freedom-all-too-real/30949/2</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2006 01:14:03 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-30949-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/threats-to-internet-freedom-all-too-real/30949.rss">Threats To Internet Freedom All Too Real</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Threats To Internet Freedom All Too Real</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@therealjdb JDB`]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/therealjdb">@therealjdb</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <blockquote>Threats To Internet Freedom All Too Real
Cyberspace police state dismissed by some, yet agenda for regulated, controlled, patrolled "Internet 2" advances
<p>Paul Joseph Watson<br>
Prison Planet<br>
Thursday, November 30, 2006</p>
<p>The Internet is the last true unregulated outpost of freedom of speech but moves are afoot to stifle, suffocate and control the world wide web. These threats are not hidden nor are they hard to deduce and yet a significant minority of truth seekers and activists remain naive as to their scope.</p>
<p>Following our publication of yesterday’s article, RIAA Legal Ruling Could Shut Down The Internet, we received a mixed response. Many were aware of the imminent dangers that threaten to change the face of the Internet but others were more hostile to the supposition that the world wide web could be devastated by landmark copyright case rulings as well as plans to develop “Internet 2.”</p>
<p>Some accused us of yellow journalism and scaremongering yet the warning that the Elektra vs. Barker case could criminalize the very mechanism that characterizes the Internet was not concocted by Alex Jones or Paul Joseph Watson, it was a statement made by the very lawyer fighting the case, Ray Beckerman.</p>
<p>It was a danger also reported on by one of the UK’s biggest technology news websites, the Inquirer, which also yesterday highlighted the frightening development in an article entitled, RIAA wants the Internet shut down.</p>
<p>The RIAA’s argument is that defendant Tenise Barker downloaded music files and made them available for distribution by placing them in a shared folder. Though Barker paid for the files and downloaded them legally, and the files were not copied by anyone, the RIAA’s motion states that simply making the files available constitutes copyright infringement.</p>
<p>As Beckerman points out, the entire Internet is nothing more than a giant network of hyperlinks making files ‘available’ to other people. If we link to <a href="http://CNN.com" rel="nofollow noopener">CNN.com</a>, we are making the file that constitutes the CNN homepage ‘available’ to other users. We don’t own the copyright to any of CNN’s material therefore if the RIAA’s argument is accepted, by simply making that CNN file available from our website, even if no one clicks on the link, we are committing a breach of copyright.</p>
<p>At no point in our article did we suggest that the ruling definitely would shut down the Internet, we highlighted the fact that hundreds of transnational corporations like <a href="http://Amazon.com" rel="nofollow noopener">Amazon.com</a> who solely rely on Internet trade would scream bloody murder. But what the ruling would grease the skids for is the move towards a strictly regulated Internet whereby government permission would be required to run a website and that website would be subject to censoring and deletion if it violated any “terms of use.”</p>
<p>The example I highlighted yesterday on the Alex Jones Show was that running a blog would be like having a You Tube account - any politically sensitive or controversial information that the owners dislike would immediately be removed as it is frequently on You Tube.</p>
<p>In addition, the slide towards a licensed Internet that will be sold using fear of identity and credit card fraud could lead to mandatory biometric thumb or finger scanning simply to access the world wide web.</p>
<p>This is hardly a stretch of the imagination, since numerous public services and functions of society are increasingly accessible only through providing some form of biometric identification. Credit passes for travel, ATM terminals and access to theme parks like Disneyland are just a few of the many services we use that are shifting towards mandatory biometric gatekeeping.</p>
<p>Furthermore, Pay By Touch Online and other companies have already developed and launched keyboard biometric finger scanning terminals that require users to submit their biometric print before they can access the Internet or buy online.</p>
<p>Piggybacking the net neutrality debate, Internet 2 is being shaped to replace the old Internet, which will be allowed to self-destruct as it labors under the pressures of being relegated to slower and slower pipes and users will simply desert a painstaking system.</p>
<p>Earlier this year under the headline, The End of the Internet?, The Nation magazine reported,</p>
<p>“The nation’s largest telephone and cable companies are crafting an alarming set of strategies that would transform the free, open and nondiscriminatory Internet of today to a privately run and branded service that would charge a fee for virtually everything we do online.”</p>
<p>“Verizon, Comcast, Bell South and other communications giants are developing strategies that would track and store information on our every move in cyberspace in a vast data-collection and marketing system, the scope of which could rival the National Security Agency. According to white papers now being circulated in the cable, telephone and telecommunications industries, those with the deepest pockets–corporations, special-interest groups and major advertisers–would get preferred treatment. Content from these providers would have first priority on our computer and television screens, while information seen as undesirable, such as peer-to-peer communications, could be relegated to a slow lane or simply shut out.”</p>
<p>Internet 2 is being billed as the next generation of the world wide web and it has already set global speed records in terms of data transfer, far outstripping the old Internet.</p>
<p>One of the fathers of the Internet, David Clark, who served as chief protocol architect for the government’s internet development initiative in the 1980s, has been given $200,000 by the National Science Foundation to covertly work on a “whole new infrastructure to replace today’s global network,” according to Wired Magazine.</p>
<p>Clark has vowed to create a “brave new world” in designing the new Internet, characterizing what he wanted for the new network to be “a coherent security architecture.”</p>
<p>Dovetailing the onset of Internet 2 are government propaganda campaigns to demonize the existing Internet as a wild backwater for hate crime, child pornography and a terrorist recruiting ground.</p>
<p>Establishment kingpins and their cheerleaders have increased their level of vitriolic rhetoric against the Internet in recent months, as legislation in both the U.S. and Europe to regulate, stifle and license the Internet moves forward.</p>
<p>The White House’s own recently de-classified strategy for “winning the war on terror” targets Internet conspiracy theories as a recruiting ground for terrorists and threatens to “diminish” their influence.</p>
<p>In addition, the Pentagon recently announced its effort to infiltrate the Internet and propagandize for the war on terror.</p>
<p>In a speech last month, Homeland Security director Michael Chertoff identified the web as a “terror training camp,” through which “disaffected people living in the United States” are developing “radical ideologies and potentially violent skills.”</p>
<p>Chertoff pledged to dispatch Homeland Security agents to local police departments in order to aid in the apprehension of domestic terrorists who use the Internet as a political tool.</p>
<p>The European Union, led by former Stalinist and potential future British Prime Minister John Reid, has also vowed to shut down “terrorists” who use the Internet to spread propaganda.</p>
<p>The dangers to the freedom and very existence of the Internet as we know it are all too real and the way to counteract these developments is to get involved and get the word out. Simply burying our heads in the sand and being apathetic and naive about the threat is only going to aid those who wish to see the last outpost of freedom of speech shut off forever.</p>
</blockquote><a href="http://prisonplanet.com/articles/november2006/301106internetfreedom.htm" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">From Here</a>
<p>What do you think about that?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/threats-to-internet-freedom-all-too-real/30949/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/threats-to-internet-freedom-all-too-real/30949/1</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2006 00:53:38 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-30949-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/threats-to-internet-freedom-all-too-real/30949.rss">Threats To Internet Freedom All Too Real</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
