<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>*</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/topic/395712</link>
    <description>the god damn grammer police got me</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 20 May 2011 14:36:08 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>General Discussion</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/topic/395712.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>*</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Svitkona Svitkona]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/svitkona">@Svitkona</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I agree with you wholeheartedly. A few weeks ago, I lived an experience that I thought I’d never retell, but your obviously heartfelt post has prompted me into revealing this shocking piece of evidence pertaining to what you have posted. You see, one day I had to hail a cab (which I do everyday, actually) so I could go to my training. I spent hours of waiting because each cab would mysteriously ignore me, yet grab that couple standing next to me instantly! Naturally, I was very irked by this predicament. A few hours later, a cab actually stopped! However, there was something wrong with this cab. It generated an aura of darkness around it that even drivers seemed to sense and stay away from. I ignored all my screaming instincts however, because they just seemed stupid. I mean, a cab emanating a dark aura? Hah! Have you even heard of such a thing?</p>
<p>Let me stop here to tell you some background information about me. I am a recently turned 15 year old guy who lives in Egypt. Now let me tell you that Egypt isn’t the best of places. Our dictator has been controlling our daily lives so bad we weren’t even able to see a grain of hope. However, we managed to overthrow him, and that event is still shrouded in mystery. What sparked the revolution? Was it really a spur of the moment event, or was it planned over the years when Mubaraks intent to stay was made clear? This is something that will never be known. However, hopefully Egypt will start becoming a better place now that we’ve gotten rid of him. Hopefully…</p>
<p>Back to my story. Ignoring all my natural human instincts, I got in the cab. Inside the cab I had the strangest feeling of vertigo, and the feeling of unease only intensified as I saw the inside of the cab. It appeared to be dark, with all light rays attempting to pierce the cloud of darkness failing at that. “I’d like to stop at the Zohour Sporting Club”, I said.</p>
<p>“Of course, young lad!” he replied.</p>
<p>As we drove through the streets, I had another flash of vertigo - and suddenly I blacked out. I awoke later at a strange place filled with the color “white”. I tried to move but found out I was strapped to a chair not unlike the one at the dentist. I saw a few scientists bending over me. “He’s awake”, one remarked. What a remarkable person, I thought. He was able to see that I was awake!</p>
<p>What followed next was a series of horrible events I’d like to skip over. I will instead, jump to the bone of the subject. A few hours later, they started opening me up. Literally opening me up. They took my internal organs out and left me in a state that should have marked me as dead - then they replaced it all and sealed it up lie there was no opening up at all! It would have been amazing had it not been me in that situation. I later found out that they had only wanted to extract my DNA to help in creating the ultimate 3 species creature, which makes me wholeheartedly lean to the truths found within your post. Keep up the good work, and remember - awareness is just the first step!</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/topic/395712/9">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/topic/395712/9</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 20 May 2011 14:36:08 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-395712-9</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/topic/395712.rss">*</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>*</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@n10si_t n10si t]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/n10si_t">@n10si_t</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote="`Alec, post:1, topic:395727"]Oh god… I could comment on the horrible grammar and spelling like the other people, but instead I think I should recommend you get some help as you are obviously not the brightest crayon in the box. Furthermore, n10si t didn’t fix all of your errors. The spelling indicates that you are just above a fourth grade writing level, congratulations.</p>
<p>[quote author=iz3 legend link=topic=492907.msg3603562#msg3603562 date=1305853614]<br>
I believe the government influences our daily lives in many ways.</p>
<ul>
<li>Horrible way to start your prompt.</li>
</ul>
<p>One way the government influences our lives is by keeping secrets from us. They are so caring they want to keep us on our toes all the time. To do this, they pay the media to freak us out with movies and T.V shows. By doing this they can really keep us unaware of the big plot behind this all.</p>
<ul>
<li>
<p>Any proof that isn’t absolutely fucking retarded? You realize creating writing isn’t just you shitting out words onto your computer, don’t you?</p>
<p>The big plot is so important that they have actually given us hints but never an answer. Remember the movie Ice Age? With the retarded sloth and the overweight mammoth? That was a very big hint. We the people have reason to believe the government wants to breed 3 species together to form one ultimate species. If given the chance they will breed sloth’s, mammoth’s, and people to create one dominate species. This species will be called… the SLUM!</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>I think that the only way the people of America would have reason to believe the government wants to breed 3 species together to form an ultimate specie would be if everyone in this country was as retarded as you, thus proving <a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Flynn_effect" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">the Flynn effect</a> horribly wrong.</p>
<p>To keep this project top secret they have to keep us stupid. To do this they infect our water with chemicals to lower brain activity, they always said we only used 10% of our brain now we know its true. The only way to filter this water is through the human body. While we are told pee is toxic it is actually chemical free water.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Obviously they are doing a good job at “keeping us stupid” judging by this prompt.</p>
</li>
</ul>
<aside class="quote">
<blockquote>
<p>Urine is not toxic.[5] However, being a waste product, it does contain compounds undesirable to the body and can be irritating to skin and eyes.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>We are not even told that “pee is toxic”.</p>
<pre><code> The government tells us it is toxic to keep us from drinking it. If we start drinking our own pee then we won't drink the polluted water. So the main plot behind this is that drinking piss will actually make you smarter.
 So as the American people I think we need to ban together against this new world that is being created underneath our feet.
</code></pre>
<ul>
<li>Oh really, drinking urine will “make you smarter”? I think that if everybody on this planet pissed into your mouth at one moment in time you would still be inferior to my cat.<br>
[/quote][/quote]</li>
</ul>
<p>I tried to fix his grammar without rewriting the whole thing :\</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/topic/395712/8">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/topic/395712/8</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 20 May 2011 03:12:27 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-395712-8</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/topic/395712.rss">*</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>*</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@reyx7 reyx7]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/reyx7">@reyx7</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Americans don’t use 10% of their brain.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/topic/395712/7">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/topic/395712/7</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 20 May 2011 02:38:09 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-395712-7</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/topic/395712.rss">*</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>*</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@the_elve_age the elve age]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/the_elve_age">@the_elve_age</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“iz3 legend, post:4, topic:395712”]lawl ik its bad as i said it was a rough copy i had on my computer, this was before i edited it at all this was like the first version :)[/quote]And…? You can at least have better grammar.</p>
<p>Here. </p><blockquote>I believe the government influences our daily lives in many ways. One way the government influences our lives is by keeping secrets from us. They care so much, they want to keep us on our toes all the time. To do this, they pay the media to make us freak out with certain movies and T.V shows. By doing this they can make us completely unaware of whats actually going.<br>
The big plot is so important that they have actually given us hints but never an answer.<br>
Remember the movie Ice Age? With the sloth and the giant mammoth? That was a huge hint. We the people have reason to believe the government wants to breed 3 species together to form one ultimate species.  If given the chance, they will breed sloths, mammoths, and people to create one dominate species. This species will be called… the SLUM!<br>
To keep this project top secret they have to keep us stupid. To do this, they infect our water with chemicals to lower brain activity. They have always said we only used 10% of our brain, and now we know its true. The only true natural way to filter water is through the human body. While we are told urine has some acidic properties, it is actually chemical free water, and fine to drink. The government does not want us drinking our urine. If we start drinking our own pee than we won’t drink the polluted water. So the main plot behind this is that drinking urine will actually make you smarter.<br>
So as an American citizen I think we the people need to take a stand against the new world that is being thrown at us.</blockquote>
<p>Tips: don’t use piss, retarded, and discriminating things in a paper.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/topic/395712/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/topic/395712/6</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 20 May 2011 02:31:05 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-395712-6</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/topic/395712.rss">*</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>*</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@reyx7 reyx7]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/reyx7">@reyx7</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Sounds like 6th grade work.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/topic/395712/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/topic/395712/5</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 20 May 2011 02:22:53 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-395712-5</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/topic/395712.rss">*</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>*</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@iz3_legend iz3 legend]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/iz3_legend">@iz3_legend</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>lawl ik its bad as i said it was a rough copy i had on my computer, this was before i edited it at all this was like the first version <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=5" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/topic/395712/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/topic/395712/4</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 20 May 2011 01:54:14 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-395712-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/topic/395712.rss">*</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>*</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@n10si_t n10si t]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/n10si_t">@n10si_t</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“iz3 legend, post:1, topic:395712”]prompt: how do you think the government influences our daily lives.</p>
<pre><code> I [b]believe[/b] the government influences our daily lives in many ways. One way the government influences our lives is by keeping secrets from us. They are so caring they want to keep us on our toes all the time. To do this, they pay the media to freak us out with movies and T.V shows. By doing this they can really keep us unaware of the big plot behind [b]all of this[/b].
 The big plot is so important that they have actually given us hints but never an [b]answer[/b]. [b]Remember[/b] the movie Ice Age? With the retarded sloth and the overweight mammoth? That was a very big hint. We the people have reason to [b]believe[/b] the government wants to breed 3 species [b]together[/b] to form one ultimate species. If given the chance[b],[/b] they will breed [b]sloths, mammoths[/b], and people to create one dominate species. This species will be called... the SLUM!
 To keep this project top secret they have to keep us stupid. To do this[b],[/b] they infect our water with chemicals to lower brain activity[b]. They have[/b] always said we only used 10% of our brain[b], and[/b] now we know its true. The only way to filter this water is through the human body. While we are told pee is toxic[b],[/b] it is actually chemical free water.
 The government tells us it is toxic to keep us from drinking it. If we start drinking our own pee then we won't drink the polluted water. So the main plot behind this is that drinking piss will actually make you smarter.
 So as the [b]A[/b]merican people I think we need to ban [b]together[/b] against this new world that is being created underneath our feet.
</code></pre>
<p>yeah I wrote this its pretty creative so im expecting a good grade. Tell me what you think <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=5" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"><br>
for all the people out there this is made up and i have no problem with the government it’s just that when my creative juices start going that cant be stopped. I know the grammars a bit off this was a rough draft on my computer enjoy :)[/quote]</p>
<p>fixed your spelling and grammar, btw… what? That’s messed up. I was really hoping you just made this up, which I see you did. It’s okay. Kind of stupid and short.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/topic/395712/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/topic/395712/3</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 20 May 2011 01:30:53 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-395712-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/topic/395712.rss">*</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>*</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@davidi2 Davidi2]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/davidi2">@davidi2</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Very bad writing conventions, grammar, and punctuation</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/topic/395712/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/topic/395712/2</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 20 May 2011 01:28:04 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-395712-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/topic/395712.rss">*</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>*</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@iz3_legend iz3 legend]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/iz3_legend">@iz3_legend</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>the god damn grammer police got me</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/topic/395712/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/topic/395712/1</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 20 May 2011 01:06:54 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-395712-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/topic/395712.rss">*</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
