<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Introducing NEW crown</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/introducing-new-crown/281776</link>
    <description>im wanting to add a crown for playerRights 8 like Blurr&#39;s client has.. but a dif client than his since i dont like his much... i have tired folowing these tuts but none say about adding a NEW crown to the existing ones that i could find.. how can i add a new crown with the title of it KenIcon.png? ive already got it drawn up and stuff[br][br][size=1]Posted on: June 02, 2009, 01:02:27 pm[/size][hr]so honestly NOBODY knows how in the 14 people that looked? i have use Z-FileSearcher on blurrs client to find the icon but it comes up with nothing.. so i know its possible and there are plenty of people that can.. just HOW...</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 02 Jun 2009 06:39:26 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Game Development</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/introducing-new-crown/281776.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Introducing NEW crown</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@CoonHunter CoonHunter]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/coonhunter">@CoonHunter</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>im wanting to add a crown for playerRights 8 like Blurr’s client has… but a dif client than his since i dont like his much… i have tired folowing these tuts but none say about adding a NEW crown to the existing ones that i could find… how can i add a new crown with the title of it KenIcon.png? ive already got it drawn up and stuff[br][br][size=1]Posted on: June 02, 2009, 01:02:27 pm[/size][hr]so honestly NOBODY knows how in the 14 people that looked? i have use Z-FileSearcher on blurrs client to find the icon but it comes up with nothing… so i know its possible and there are plenty of people that can… just HOW…</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/introducing-new-crown/281776/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/introducing-new-crown/281776/1</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 02 Jun 2009 06:39:26 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-281776-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/introducing-new-crown/281776.rss">Introducing NEW crown</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
