<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>[Team_Rocket] The first thread since the return [CREATIVE]</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/team-rocket-the-first-thread-since-the-return-creative/516328</link>
    <description>   Well, as some of you may know, I left for a while. Shortly after my departure, I went away for a while. Now that I&#39;m back, I&#39;m designing and developing again. The more I thought about it, the more I realized that this is straying too far away to call it a R.S.P.S. even though it still has many core elements and aspects that are the same as a R.S.P.S.

   I wasn&#39;t going to release these, but I don&#39;t see a valid reason for me not to. So here&#39;s some things for you guys to peruse. I was also unable to post the entirety of this, due to the character limit of 20,000.



[b]It&#39;s sort of like RuneScape meets Arcanum: of Steamworks and Magic Obscura meets D&amp;D.


Here&#39;s some background information so you won&#39;t be confused or wondering when you read certain parts of this:

&lt;blockquote&gt;attack = Assault
strength = Power
defence = Guard
ranged = Archery
prayer = Faith
magic = Thaumaturgy
runecrafting = Ritualism
hitpoints = Health
agility = Grace
herblore = Herblaw
thieving = Pilfering
crafting = Creation
fletching = Bow-Crafting
slayer = Executionist
mining = Prospecting
smithing = Forging
fishing = Trawling
cooking = Culinary
firemaking/Woodcutting = Survival
farming = Agriculture&lt;/blockquote&gt;


&lt;blockquote&gt;[u]Negative Attributes:[/u]
- Poison: Inflicts 1-9 Hitpoint damage every 20 seconds. (Green Hitsplat)

- Burn: Inflicts 5-15 Hitpoint damage every 10 seconds. (Orange Hitsplat)

- Drench: Inflicts 1-5 Hitpoint damage every 5 seconds. Reduces Energy renegeneration by 50%. Energy also drains 25% faster. (Purple Hitsplat)

- Fatigue: Lowers Agility level to 0. Weight Carried is increased by 50-500lbs. (Yellow Hitsplat)

- Soul-Corruption: Drains 1-3 Prayer Points and 1 Hitpoint every 2-10 seconds.&lt;/blockquote&gt;


&lt;blockquote&gt;Offensive Statistics:

Assault = Attack Bonuses/Chance to hit
Powerful = Strength Bonuses/Max hit
Thaumaturgy = Magic accuracy/Max hit
Archery = Ranged accuracy/max hit

Defensive Statistics:

Assault = Defence against how often you are hit by melee
Archery = Defence against how often you are hit by ranged/Max hit
Guard = Defence aganst enemy max hits and also game-breaker boss attacks
Thaumaturgy = Defence against enemy magic and how often they splash

Balanced Statistics:

Faith = The rate at which your Faith drains
Health = The rate and variation of which negative attributes effect you.&lt;/blockquote&gt;


Now that we&#39;ve gotten that out of the way, here&#39;s what I&#39;ve been designing in the short time that I&#39;ve been back.

&lt;blockquote&gt;Character Background: Upon creation of a new Character, the Player-Character can choose their Background from a pre-generated list of options. There are quite a lot of choices, many of them are very useful, some of them are more for utility, a few of them are permanent, and a couple may only increase your material wealth. Whatever your choice may be, this is what your Character spent their time doing, or how they lived their life... before the Great War, Collapse, and Awakening of Cynosure.

Backgrounds:

Raised by Monks - You were raised by Monks in a monestary from birth, and spent your childhood learning your purpose. You recieve a permanent bonus to your Faith statistic of 10.

Bookworm - You spent all of the free time you had reading any book which you could get your hands on. You are very well educated, and begin the game with 10 levels in all Skills.

Military Enlistment - When the Great War of Cynosure came about, you signed up to fight for your homeland. You were injured before being assigned to the field (-5 Guard Statistic [DEFENSIVE]), but your training remained intact. All Combat stats are raised to 25.

Son of a Hero - Your Father passed away when you were younger, but before leaving this world, he left you with his tactic of enslaving beasts. You are completely immune to any and all Game-Breaker Special Attacks inflicted by Raid Bosses.

Spoiled Child - Being sheltered as a child and spoiled at every opportunity, you are not as battle-hardened as others (-5 to Thaumaturgy and Archery [DEFENSIVE]), however, your parents left you the family fortune in their will. You begin the game with 50,000 pieces of Gold.

Merlin&#39;s Relative - Not only are you related to Merlin, the great wizard, by blood, but you are also his favorite Nephew/Niece (WILL BE DIALOGUE-DEPENDANT BASED UPON GENDER CHOSEN). You have a permanent + 5 bonus to Thaumaturgy.

Sickly Childhood - You become sick easily and had a weak immune system as a child. You are stricken with a permanent weakness to negative attributes (poison, burn, drench, fatigue, soul-corruption. These effects will always have their maximum effect), however you studied combat and watched local tournaments whilst you were sick. You have a permanent bonus of +5 to all Offensive Statistics.

Raised by Vampires - As a child, you strayed off into the wilderness, eventually finding shelter in a remote cave. You awoke the next morning to find yourself captured by Vampires. Seeing that you were young and could be trained for their uses, they spared your life in exchange for your life-long dedication to them. Once the Great War occured, however, they were enslaved into Dungeons with the rest of the beasts. You still remain a friend to the Vampiric Race, and any/all Vampires encountered in-game will never be aggressive towards you. Some Vampires will even have unique dialogue for you. 

Family of Creators - You grew up in a family where everyone was very skilled in the Creation Skill. You gain 40 levels in the Creation Skill, but due to their odd ways and controversial of creating, you may never join the Creationist Guild. You gain one unique Creation Recipe which no others know.

Warrior Guild Upbringing - As an oprhan, you were adopted by The Warrior Guild. You begin the game with +1 to all Offensive and Defensive Statistics. However, your hardended nature brings about a -5 Disposition to all N.P.C. you encounter.

Heroic Bloodline - Your parents were both heroes of reknown. You begin the game with 2 Quests of your choosing automatically completed. This does not include Master-Quests or Quest-Lines. Many N.P.C. also have unique and varied dialogue in regards as to this Background.

Knight of the Round Table - After you came of age, you become an honorary member of the Round Table. You focused all of your energy on combat, but your use of magic suffered. You have a decreased resistance to magic as a result (-5% resistance permanent). You begin the game with level 40 in all combat stats except for magic.

Abusive Childhood - You grew up in a shack on the outskirts of Ragnarork, which is the poorest and most crime-ridden city in Cynosure. To make matters worse, both of your parents beat you daily. Once you came of age, you ran away without notice and never looked back. As a result of the beatings, you have a +25% increase to your Health statistic. This makes negative status effects much less effective when used against you. You also learned to defend yourself, and begin the game with 25 levels in Guard. However, due to running away without any training or knowledge in proffessions, you found yourself without a job, and had to take loans from the banks. You begin the game with a debt of 100,000 Gold Pieces to all of the banks in Cynosure. You are unable to purchase property or invest until all of these debts are paid in full.

Forge Worker - Before The Great War took place, you held a job as a forge worker. You know your way around the smelting furnaces and anvils. You begin the game with 30 levels in your Forging and Prospecting skills.

Chef - You were once a reknown chef, famous for creative and inventive cooking. You begin the game with 40 levels in your Culinary skill, have a 10% decreased chance to burn any food, and learn one high-tier (level 100) Culinary recipe which no others may learn. The recipe produces the most expensive pie in Cynosure, and may not be traded with other players.&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;Skill Perks/Rewards: Once a player achieves a certain Milestone in a Skill, they recieve a Perk. Listed below is the Perk Scale:

Level 50 - Apprentice Perk
Level 75 - Experienced Perk
Level 100 - Master Perk

Perk Trees: When a player reaches the Milestone in the Skill, they may choose one Perk from the &#39;Tree&#39; of the skill which it pertains to. There are many options and choices, so it is advised  to take your time and choose very carefully based upon your play-style, as you may only choose one per Milestone.

Herblaw Perk Tree:

Level 50:
- Druid Friend - All prices in the Druid Shop (basic Herblaw supplies) are discounted at 75% off.
- Green Thumbs - Experienced gained from cleaning Herbs is permanently increased by 20%.
- Lucky Herbs - Chance of getting a &#39;rare&#39; Herb from cleaning grimy herbs is increased by 10%.
- Vial Supply - The Druid Shop now sells Vials of Water.


Level 75:
- Nature&#39;s Friend - Chance of a Birds Nest falling from a tree is increased by 25%.
- Green-Stained Thumbs - Experience gained from cleaning Herbs is permanently increased to 40%.
- Way of the Druid - A Mortor &amp; Pestle as a tool is no longer required in any aspect of Herblaw.
- Tree Whisperer - 5% chance per log of a random cleaned Herb falling to the ground whilst Woodcutting.

Level 100:
- Earth Friend - Herbs no longer weigh anything, and are now always noted when dropped from any source.
- Greenest Thumbs - Experience gained from cleaning Herbs is permanently increased to 250%.
- Material Master - Only 1 secondary-material is now needed to create 5 potions.
- Herblaw Master - 1 Herb now creates 2 potions.
-----------------------------------------------------------------------

-----------------------------------------------------------------------
Forging Perk Tree:

Level 50:

- Black Knight - The player can now craft Black armor and weapons. However, doing so incuurs Evil Karma. This may be forged using Coal.
- Savory Smithy - You now recieve two of every Platebody below BUT, including Rune each time one is forged.
- The Golden Touch - The player may buy a Golden Hammer from the Forge Attendant, which is wieldable at any level and does not take up an inventory slot.
- Rune-Forge - One less Runite ore is required to smelt Runite Bars.

Level 75:

- Trimming - The player may trim armor of any type any color they choose. Doing so awards Creation, Prospecting, and Forging experience. To create a Gold Trimmed armor, the player must have 1,000,000 Gold Pieces in their Inventory.
- Clueless - The player can forge all of the items and materials needed to complete and progress Clue Scrolls.
- Blazing Forge - You may now forge different colored Firelighters. These are used in the Survival Skill in the Firemaking branch, and award double experience when used to light logs.
- Dwarven Forge - The player may now access the Dwarven Forge. This forge grants double experience when used, however the bank is farther away than most.

Level 100:

- Dragon Smithy - The player can now Forge Dragon armor and weapons. This can be done by mixing Adamantite and Runite ore. You may not craft Dragon Full Helmets, or a Dragonfire Shield.
- Rune Master - Rune Boots are able to be forged.
- Dragon Weaponsmith - Dragon Scimitars and Dragon Daggers can now be forged by the player.
- Master of the Forge - Forging any ore in a Smelter now grants you Prospecting experience as well as forging experience.
-----------------------------------------------------------------------

-----------------------------------------------------------------------
Bow-Crafting Perk Tree:

Level 50:

- Bow-Man - Bow-Crafting any log of any type grants you double experience.
- Robin Hood - Crafting arrows which are Steel and above allows you to craft double the amount of arrows with the same amount of materials.
- Savvy Craftsman - Creating 2 Rune Crossbows allows to you collect one Runite Bar in your Inventory.
- Enchanting Crossbow Bolts also grants you Bow-Crafting experience as well as Magic experience.

Level 75:

- Dark Dragon - The player may now create Dragon Arrows. Doing so will give the player Evil Karma.
- Ice Craft - The player may now create Ice Arrows. These arrows are not quite as good as Dragon Arrows, but are less expensive to craft.
- Father of Robin Hood - Crafting Rune Arrows gives you quadruple the amount with the same amount of materials.
- Dragon Bolt Instructer - Allows you to craft double Dragon Bolts, which come pre-enchanted.

Level 100:

- Blasphemy Bow - A Dark Bow can now be crafted by the player. This can only be done once every 24 hours. Once this is done, the player&#39;s Karmic level is automatically set to the most Evil.
- Void Outpost Ranger - The Void Knight gear from the Pest Control mini-game can now be bought with Gold Pieces. The cost is 75,000,000 Gold Pieces per set. The gear, however, remains non-tradable, and still functions as non-tradable items.
- Method Archery - When the player uses Archery in combat, they not only gain Archery experience, but Bow-Crafting experience as well.
- Crystal Archery - Allows the player to create Crystal Bows. The player must have a Crystal Seed, and 2,500,000 Gold Pieces to create this fine bow.
-----------------------------------------------------------------------

-----------------------------------------------------------------------
Creation Perk Tree:

Level 50:

- Creative Creationist - Chisels are no longer required to cut Gems.
- Gem Trader - Uncut gems cost 25% less to buy, sell for 25% more, and the Gem Shop now has an unlimited stock of all Gems.
- Self-Sufficiency - All Hides of any type no longer need to be tanned before they can be used in Creation.
- Thrifty Spinner - Spinning Flax to Bow String grants twice as much experience, and spins twice as quickly as before.

Level 75:

- Bow-Creationist - Spinning Flax to Bow String now gives you Bow-Crafting experience as well as Creation experience. 
- Expert Creations - Creating high-level Gear now grants you 250% more experience in Creation.
- Skilled Spinner - When you spin Flax to Bow String, you gain one piece of Flax for every two you spin.
- The player can now craft Robin Hood hats and Ranger Boots.

Level 100:

- Masterful Creations - Creating end-game Gear now grants you 1000% more experience in Creation.
- Flax Baron - At the end of each day, 500 Flax is deposited into your Bank.
- Creationist of the Gods - Saradomin, Zamorak, and Guthix DragonHide can now be created by the player; using the perspective colored Hides.
- Gem Baron - At the end of each day, 100 of each Gem is deposited into your Bank.
-----------------------------------------------------------------------

-----------------------------------------------------------------------
Prospecting Perk Tree:

Level 50:

- Sharp Eye - The player is instantly able to identify the type of ore contained in a rock.
- Coal Miner - The player recieves double experience for mining Coal.
- Gem Prospecter - Chance of getting random gems from Prospecting increased by 40%.
- Golden Pick - Allows the player to Buy a Golden Pickaxe from the Mining Grandmaster. This Pickaxe increases experience gained from Prospecting by 10%, and increases the chance of recieving random gems whilst Prospecting by 10%.

Level 75:

- Smelting Master - Allows the player to smelt Cannonballs. This can be done by mixing Adamantite, Iron, and Tin ore.
- Agile Prospecter - The player&#39;s run energy regenerates 50% quicker when their Inventory is filled with Ore of any type.
- Dragonstone in the Rough - Allows the player to have a chance of finding an Uncut Dragonstone Gem whilst prospecting. The chance is 4% for every ore mined.
- Gem Hoarder - Greatly increases the chance of finding Gems whilst prospecting. Rates are: Sapphire 50%, Emerald 45%, Opal 40%, Jade 40%, Ruby 35%, Pearl 30%, Diamond 20%, Ice Diamond 15%, and Dragonstone 6%.

Level 100:

- Legendary Prospecter - Allows the player to prospect Bronze Ore, and turn the Bronze Ore into Bronze Dust. This is the main ingredient in Fire Bombs.
- Gem Runners - Any and all Gems the player gets from prospecting are directly deposited into the player&#39;s bank.
- Ultimate Crafting - Allows the player to prospect Crafting Ore. There is only 1 Crafting Ore Rock in-game, and it is located beside Mage Bank. Once mined, the player is tele-blocked, and must run through 55 levels of Wilderness. This Ore is the most valuable Ore in-game. It can be used as a substitute for any secondary material in any recipe.
- Gem Hunter - The player has a chance of finding an Uncut Onyx Gem whilst prospecting. The chance is 1%.
-----------------------------------------------------------------------

-----------------------------------------------------------------------
Culinary Perk Tree:

Level 50:

- Gnome Preparation - The player can now brew stat-boosting drinks.
- Dwarven Shananagins - Allows the player to cook food in a Smelter. This increases the chance of burning food by 25%.
- Cook Hands - Decreases the chance of burning all food by 20%.
- Cook&#39;s Assignment - Allows the player to speak to the Castle Cook in Camelot to recieve a &#39;Culinary Task&#39;. This functions similar to Executioner, except It&#39;s with food. The player is rewarded with Purple Sweets for each Culinary Task completed; depending upon difficulty and the amount of food prepared.

Level 75:

- Agile Chef - Weight Carried is reduced to 0 if the player has an Inventory filled with raw food.
- Elvish Culinary - Chance to burn all food is decreased by 50%.
- Herbs and Spices - Allows the player to mix Herblaw Herbs with different food to create special recipes. 25% chance of success.
- Survivalist Chef - The chance of burning food on an open fire is now equal to that of burning it on a range stove.

Level 100:

- Iron Chef - Chance to burn food is decreased by 90%.
- Steel Chef - When 5 food are cooked within 30 seconds, the player&#39;s Run Energy is instantly restored by 50%.
- Rune Chef - 5% chance of finding special items from raw shark whilst cooking them.
- Chef of the Gods - The player earns 250% more Culinary experience, and may prepare and cook Enchanted Meat (functions as 2 doses of a Saradomin Brew).
---------------------------------------------------------------------

-----------------------------------------------------------------------
Grace Perk Tree:

Level 50:

- Light Footed - Enemies are slightly less aggressive to you. (Which is equal to 1 tile).
- Grace of a Cat - You can use Grace obstacles and shortcuts which are 10 levels above your Grace level.
- Sprinter - You gain a permanent increase to your Energy of 5%.
- Marathon Runner - You gain a permanent increase of + 5% to your Energy Regeneration rate.

Level 75:

- Agile Thief - You gain a 10% success rate to Pilfering when you pick-pocket any N.P.C.
- Fire-Feet - Everytime you light logs via Tinderbox, you regenerate 4% of your total Run Energy.
- Nature&#39;s Swiftness - When you recieve a log from Survival, you regenerate 3% of your total Run Energy.
- Light Warrior - Weight Carried is reduced by 20% when all gear slots are filled.

Level 100:

- Graceful Master - Run Energy permanently increased by 25%.
- Graceful Marathon - Run Energy regeneration increased by 50%.
- Agile Master - Grace level boosted by 10 levels when the Grace Cape is worn (requires 100 Grace to wear).
- Agile Gatherer - Weight Carried reduced to 0 when Inventory is filled.
-----------------------------------------------------------------------&lt;/blockquote&gt;</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2013 00:51:41 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/team-rocket-the-first-thread-since-the-return-creative/516328.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>[Team_Rocket] The first thread since the return [CREATIVE]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@RiiPiiNFtW RiiPiiNFtW]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/riipiinftw">@RiiPiiNFtW</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>So in simpler words, its just a renamed version of RuneScape?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/team-rocket-the-first-thread-since-the-return-creative/516328/14">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/team-rocket-the-first-thread-since-the-return-creative/516328/14</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2013 00:51:41 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-516328-14</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/team-rocket-the-first-thread-since-the-return-creative/516328.rss">[Team_Rocket] The first thread since the return [CREATIVE]</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Team_Rocket] The first thread since the return [CREATIVE]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Host_Gushers Host Gushers]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/host_gushers">@Host_Gushers</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I think this is a really brilliant idea you have gotten, go with it and update us <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/smiley.png?v=5" title=":smiley:" class="emoji" alt=":smiley:"> Tell me when u are doing beta testing btw <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=5" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/team-rocket-the-first-thread-since-the-return-creative/516328/13">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/team-rocket-the-first-thread-since-the-return-creative/516328/13</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2013 21:54:50 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-516328-13</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/team-rocket-the-first-thread-since-the-return-creative/516328.rss">[Team_Rocket] The first thread since the return [CREATIVE]</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Team_Rocket] The first thread since the return [CREATIVE]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Flame3 John]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/flame3">@Flame3</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Great concepts! I’m glad you’ve returned.<br>
People can stop mistaking me for you now.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/team-rocket-the-first-thread-since-the-return-creative/516328/12">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/team-rocket-the-first-thread-since-the-return-creative/516328/12</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2013 01:54:04 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-516328-12</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/team-rocket-the-first-thread-since-the-return-creative/516328.rss">[Team_Rocket] The first thread since the return [CREATIVE]</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Team_Rocket] The first thread since the return [CREATIVE]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@ox_random_xi ox random xi]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/ox_random_xi">@ox_random_xi</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I had fun creating these with you, I’m glad to have my mentor back. Much love T_R, you know I missed you.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/team-rocket-the-first-thread-since-the-return-creative/516328/11">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/team-rocket-the-first-thread-since-the-return-creative/516328/11</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2013 00:35:59 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-516328-11</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/team-rocket-the-first-thread-since-the-return-creative/516328.rss">[Team_Rocket] The first thread since the return [CREATIVE]</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Team_Rocket] The first thread since the return [CREATIVE]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@strucker Strucker]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/strucker">@strucker</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I’m glad you came, i really missed you.</p>
<p>This is a great concept.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/team-rocket-the-first-thread-since-the-return-creative/516328/10">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/team-rocket-the-first-thread-since-the-return-creative/516328/10</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2013 00:32:33 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-516328-10</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/team-rocket-the-first-thread-since-the-return-creative/516328.rss">[Team_Rocket] The first thread since the return [CREATIVE]</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Team_Rocket] The first thread since the return [CREATIVE]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@ExtremeX-Scape Ryley]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/extremex-scape">@ExtremeX-Scape</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote quote-modified" data-post="3" data-topic="516328">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/user_avatar/forum.moparisthebest.com/davidi2/40/2579_1.png" class="avatar"> Davidi2:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>It’s a good idea, a shame that it has to be done through the runescape engine.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>This exactly.</p>
<p>You have potential, you need to make use of it. Doing it through R.S.P.S is the wrong way to go.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/team-rocket-the-first-thread-since-the-return-creative/516328/9">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/team-rocket-the-first-thread-since-the-return-creative/516328/9</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2013 00:24:33 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-516328-9</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/team-rocket-the-first-thread-since-the-return-creative/516328.rss">[Team_Rocket] The first thread since the return [CREATIVE]</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Team_Rocket] The first thread since the return [CREATIVE]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Teem_Rocket Teem_Rocket]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/teem_rocket">@Teem_Rocket</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote" data-post="7" data-topic="516328">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 arham 4:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Any why make a new account?</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>The account Team_Rocket got a randomized password. I couldn’t get into the e-mail account because the host erased it as well. I’ve still got my Skype if you are thinking I might be someone posing as T_R or something,  :P.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/team-rocket-the-first-thread-since-the-return-creative/516328/8">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/team-rocket-the-first-thread-since-the-return-creative/516328/8</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2013 22:41:45 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-516328-8</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/team-rocket-the-first-thread-since-the-return-creative/516328.rss">[Team_Rocket] The first thread since the return [CREATIVE]</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Team_Rocket] The first thread since the return [CREATIVE]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@arham_4 arham 4]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/arham_4">@arham_4</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Any why make a new account?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/team-rocket-the-first-thread-since-the-return-creative/516328/7">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/team-rocket-the-first-thread-since-the-return-creative/516328/7</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2013 22:40:13 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-516328-7</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/team-rocket-the-first-thread-since-the-return-creative/516328.rss">[Team_Rocket] The first thread since the return [CREATIVE]</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Team_Rocket] The first thread since the return [CREATIVE]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@RandQm RandQm]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/randqm">@RandQm</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Great concept</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/team-rocket-the-first-thread-since-the-return-creative/516328/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/team-rocket-the-first-thread-since-the-return-creative/516328/6</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2013 22:35:22 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-516328-6</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/team-rocket-the-first-thread-since-the-return-creative/516328.rss">[Team_Rocket] The first thread since the return [CREATIVE]</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Team_Rocket] The first thread since the return [CREATIVE]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Teem_Rocket Teem_Rocket]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/teem_rocket">@Teem_Rocket</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I’ve made many attempts to create my own video game. The amount of work needed to put into it is absolutely overwhelming. You have to be extremely versatile and patient (patience isn’t an issue) to be a solo programmer/designer when creating your own video game. Well, if you want it to be able to compete with others anyway.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/team-rocket-the-first-thread-since-the-return-creative/516328/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/team-rocket-the-first-thread-since-the-return-creative/516328/5</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2013 22:25:53 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-516328-5</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/team-rocket-the-first-thread-since-the-return-creative/516328.rss">[Team_Rocket] The first thread since the return [CREATIVE]</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Team_Rocket] The first thread since the return [CREATIVE]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@3lv3n_snip3r 3lv3n snip3r]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/3lv3n_snip3r">@3lv3n_snip3r</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote quote-modified" data-post="3" data-topic="516328">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/user_avatar/forum.moparisthebest.com/davidi2/40/2579_1.png" class="avatar"> Davidi2:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>It’s a good idea, a shame that it has to be done through the runescape engine.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>This. I’d look for another game engine to use. If you’re used to C# and JavaScript programming, you could try out Unity.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/team-rocket-the-first-thread-since-the-return-creative/516328/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/team-rocket-the-first-thread-since-the-return-creative/516328/4</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2013 22:18:35 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-516328-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/team-rocket-the-first-thread-since-the-return-creative/516328.rss">[Team_Rocket] The first thread since the return [CREATIVE]</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Team_Rocket] The first thread since the return [CREATIVE]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@davidi2 Davidi2]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/davidi2">@davidi2</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>It’s a good idea, a shame that it has to be done through the runescape engine.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/team-rocket-the-first-thread-since-the-return-creative/516328/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/team-rocket-the-first-thread-since-the-return-creative/516328/3</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2013 22:06:21 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-516328-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/team-rocket-the-first-thread-since-the-return-creative/516328.rss">[Team_Rocket] The first thread since the return [CREATIVE]</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Team_Rocket] The first thread since the return [CREATIVE]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@amy_webb1 amy_webb]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/amy_webb1">@amy_webb1</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Interesting concept, it almost seems like a whole new game idea running off a rsps base.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/team-rocket-the-first-thread-since-the-return-creative/516328/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/team-rocket-the-first-thread-since-the-return-creative/516328/2</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2013 22:02:40 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-516328-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/team-rocket-the-first-thread-since-the-return-creative/516328.rss">[Team_Rocket] The first thread since the return [CREATIVE]</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Team_Rocket] The first thread since the return [CREATIVE]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Teem_Rocket Teem_Rocket]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/teem_rocket">@Teem_Rocket</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Well, as some of you may know, I left for a while. Shortly after my departure, I went away for a while. Now that I’m back, I’m designing and developing again. The more I thought about it, the more I realized that this is straying too far away to call it a R.S.P.S. even though it still has many core elements and aspects that are the same as a R.S.P.S.</p>
<p>I wasn’t going to release these, but I don’t see a valid reason for me not to. So here’s some things for you guys to peruse. I was also unable to post the entirety of this, due to the character limit of 20,000.</p>
<p>[b]It’s sort of like RuneScape meets Arcanum: of Steamworks and Magic Obscura meets D&amp;D.</p>
<p>Here’s some background information so you won’t be confused or wondering when you read certain parts of this:</p>
<blockquote>attack = Assault
strength = Power
defence = Guard
ranged = Archery
prayer = Faith
magic = Thaumaturgy
runecrafting = Ritualism
hitpoints = Health
agility = Grace
herblore = Herblaw
thieving = Pilfering
crafting = Creation
fletching = Bow-Crafting
slayer = Executionist
mining = Prospecting
smithing = Forging
fishing = Trawling
cooking = Culinary
firemaking/Woodcutting = Survival
farming = Agriculture</blockquote>
<blockquote>[u]Negative Attributes:[/u]
- Poison: Inflicts 1-9 Hitpoint damage every 20 seconds. (Green Hitsplat)
<ul>
<li>
<p>Burn: Inflicts 5-15 Hitpoint damage every 10 seconds. (Orange Hitsplat)</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Drench: Inflicts 1-5 Hitpoint damage every 5 seconds. Reduces Energy renegeneration by 50%. Energy also drains 25% faster. (Purple Hitsplat)</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Fatigue: Lowers Agility level to 0. Weight Carried is increased by 50-500lbs. (Yellow Hitsplat)</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Soul-Corruption: Drains 1-3 Prayer Points and 1 Hitpoint every 2-10 seconds.</p>
</li>
</ul>
</blockquote>


<blockquote>Offensive Statistics:
<p>Assault = Attack Bonuses/Chance to hit<br>
Powerful = Strength Bonuses/Max hit<br>
Thaumaturgy = Magic accuracy/Max hit<br>
Archery = Ranged accuracy/max hit</p>
<p>Defensive Statistics:</p>
<p>Assault = Defence against how often you are hit by melee<br>
Archery = Defence against how often you are hit by ranged/Max hit<br>
Guard = Defence aganst enemy max hits and also game-breaker boss attacks<br>
Thaumaturgy = Defence against enemy magic and how often they splash</p>
<p>Balanced Statistics:</p>
<p>Faith = The rate at which your Faith drains<br>
Health = The rate and variation of which negative attributes effect you.</p>
</blockquote>
<p>Now that we’ve gotten that out of the way, here’s what I’ve been designing in the short time that I’ve been back.</p>
<blockquote>Character Background: Upon creation of a new Character, the Player-Character can choose their Background from a pre-generated list of options. There are quite a lot of choices, many of them are very useful, some of them are more for utility, a few of them are permanent, and a couple may only increase your material wealth. Whatever your choice may be, this is what your Character spent their time doing, or how they lived their life... before the Great War, Collapse, and Awakening of Cynosure.
<p>Backgrounds:</p>
<p>Raised by Monks - You were raised by Monks in a monestary from birth, and spent your childhood learning your purpose. You recieve a permanent bonus to your Faith statistic of 10.</p>
<p>Bookworm - You spent all of the free time you had reading any book which you could get your hands on. You are very well educated, and begin the game with 10 levels in all Skills.</p>
<p>Military Enlistment - When the Great War of Cynosure came about, you signed up to fight for your homeland. You were injured before being assigned to the field (-5 Guard Statistic [DEFENSIVE]), but your training remained intact. All Combat stats are raised to 25.</p>
<p>Son of a Hero - Your Father passed away when you were younger, but before leaving this world, he left you with his tactic of enslaving beasts. You are completely immune to any and all Game-Breaker Special Attacks inflicted by Raid Bosses.</p>
<p>Spoiled Child - Being sheltered as a child and spoiled at every opportunity, you are not as battle-hardened as others (-5 to Thaumaturgy and Archery [DEFENSIVE]), however, your parents left you the family fortune in their will. You begin the game with 50,000 pieces of Gold.</p>
<p>Merlin’s Relative - Not only are you related to Merlin, the great wizard, by blood, but you are also his favorite Nephew/Niece (WILL BE DIALOGUE-DEPENDANT BASED UPON GENDER CHOSEN). You have a permanent + 5 bonus to Thaumaturgy.</p>
<p>Sickly Childhood - You become sick easily and had a weak immune system as a child. You are stricken with a permanent weakness to negative attributes (poison, burn, drench, fatigue, soul-corruption. These effects will always have their maximum effect), however you studied combat and watched local tournaments whilst you were sick. You have a permanent bonus of +5 to all Offensive Statistics.</p>
<p>Raised by Vampires - As a child, you strayed off into the wilderness, eventually finding shelter in a remote cave. You awoke the next morning to find yourself captured by Vampires. Seeing that you were young and could be trained for their uses, they spared your life in exchange for your life-long dedication to them. Once the Great War occured, however, they were enslaved into Dungeons with the rest of the beasts. You still remain a friend to the Vampiric Race, and any/all Vampires encountered in-game will never be aggressive towards you. Some Vampires will even have unique dialogue for you.</p>
<p>Family of Creators - You grew up in a family where everyone was very skilled in the Creation Skill. You gain 40 levels in the Creation Skill, but due to their odd ways and controversial of creating, you may never join the Creationist Guild. You gain one unique Creation Recipe which no others know.</p>
<p>Warrior Guild Upbringing - As an oprhan, you were adopted by The Warrior Guild. You begin the game with +1 to all Offensive and Defensive Statistics. However, your hardended nature brings about a -5 Disposition to all N.P.C. you encounter.</p>
<p>Heroic Bloodline - Your parents were both heroes of reknown. You begin the game with 2 Quests of your choosing automatically completed. This does not include Master-Quests or Quest-Lines. Many N.P.C. also have unique and varied dialogue in regards as to this Background.</p>
<p>Knight of the Round Table - After you came of age, you become an honorary member of the Round Table. You focused all of your energy on combat, but your use of magic suffered. You have a decreased resistance to magic as a result (-5% resistance permanent). You begin the game with level 40 in all combat stats except for magic.</p>
<p>Abusive Childhood - You grew up in a shack on the outskirts of Ragnarork, which is the poorest and most crime-ridden city in Cynosure. To make matters worse, both of your parents beat you daily. Once you came of age, you ran away without notice and never looked back. As a result of the beatings, you have a +25% increase to your Health statistic. This makes negative status effects much less effective when used against you. You also learned to defend yourself, and begin the game with 25 levels in Guard. However, due to running away without any training or knowledge in proffessions, you found yourself without a job, and had to take loans from the banks. You begin the game with a debt of 100,000 Gold Pieces to all of the banks in Cynosure. You are unable to purchase property or invest until all of these debts are paid in full.</p>
<p>Forge Worker - Before The Great War took place, you held a job as a forge worker. You know your way around the smelting furnaces and anvils. You begin the game with 30 levels in your Forging and Prospecting skills.</p>
<p>Chef - You were once a reknown chef, famous for creative and inventive cooking. You begin the game with 40 levels in your Culinary skill, have a 10% decreased chance to burn any food, and learn one high-tier (level 100) Culinary recipe which no others may learn. The recipe produces the most expensive pie in Cynosure, and may not be traded with other players.</p>
</blockquote>
<blockquote>Skill Perks/Rewards: Once a player achieves a certain Milestone in a Skill, they recieve a Perk. Listed below is the Perk Scale:
<p>Level 50 - Apprentice Perk<br>
Level 75 - Experienced Perk<br>
Level 100 - Master Perk</p>
<p>Perk Trees: When a player reaches the Milestone in the Skill, they may choose one Perk from the ‘Tree’ of the skill which it pertains to. There are many options and choices, so it is advised  to take your time and choose very carefully based upon your play-style, as you may only choose one per Milestone.</p>
<p>Herblaw Perk Tree:</p>
<p>Level 50:</p>
<ul>
<li>Druid Friend - All prices in the Druid Shop (basic Herblaw supplies) are discounted at 75% off.</li>
<li>Green Thumbs - Experienced gained from cleaning Herbs is permanently increased by 20%.</li>
<li>Lucky Herbs - Chance of getting a ‘rare’ Herb from cleaning grimy herbs is increased by 10%.</li>
<li>Vial Supply - The Druid Shop now sells Vials of Water.</li>
</ul>
<p>Level 75:</p>
<ul>
<li>Nature’s Friend - Chance of a Birds Nest falling from a tree is increased by 25%.</li>
<li>Green-Stained Thumbs - Experience gained from cleaning Herbs is permanently increased to 40%.</li>
<li>Way of the Druid - A Mortor &amp; Pestle as a tool is no longer required in any aspect of Herblaw.</li>
<li>Tree Whisperer - 5% chance per log of a random cleaned Herb falling to the ground whilst Woodcutting.</li>
</ul>
<p>Level 100:</p>
<ul>
<li>Earth Friend - Herbs no longer weigh anything, and are now always noted when dropped from any source.</li>
<li>Greenest Thumbs - Experience gained from cleaning Herbs is permanently increased to 250%.</li>
<li>Material Master - Only 1 secondary-material is now needed to create 5 potions.</li>
<li>Herblaw Master - 1 Herb now creates 2 potions.</li>
</ul>
<hr>
<hr>
<p>Forging Perk Tree:</p>
<p>Level 50:</p>
<ul>
<li>Black Knight - The player can now craft Black armor and weapons. However, doing so incuurs Evil Karma. This may be forged using Coal.</li>
<li>Savory Smithy - You now recieve two of every Platebody below BUT, including Rune each time one is forged.</li>
<li>The Golden Touch - The player may buy a Golden Hammer from the Forge Attendant, which is wieldable at any level and does not take up an inventory slot.</li>
<li>Rune-Forge - One less Runite ore is required to smelt Runite Bars.</li>
</ul>
<p>Level 75:</p>
<ul>
<li>Trimming - The player may trim armor of any type any color they choose. Doing so awards Creation, Prospecting, and Forging experience. To create a Gold Trimmed armor, the player must have 1,000,000 Gold Pieces in their Inventory.</li>
<li>Clueless - The player can forge all of the items and materials needed to complete and progress Clue Scrolls.</li>
<li>Blazing Forge - You may now forge different colored Firelighters. These are used in the Survival Skill in the Firemaking branch, and award double experience when used to light logs.</li>
<li>Dwarven Forge - The player may now access the Dwarven Forge. This forge grants double experience when used, however the bank is farther away than most.</li>
</ul>
<p>Level 100:</p>
<ul>
<li>Dragon Smithy - The player can now Forge Dragon armor and weapons. This can be done by mixing Adamantite and Runite ore. You may not craft Dragon Full Helmets, or a Dragonfire Shield.</li>
<li>Rune Master - Rune Boots are able to be forged.</li>
<li>Dragon Weaponsmith - Dragon Scimitars and Dragon Daggers can now be forged by the player.</li>
<li>Master of the Forge - Forging any ore in a Smelter now grants you Prospecting experience as well as forging experience.</li>
</ul>
<hr>
<hr>
<p>Bow-Crafting Perk Tree:</p>
<p>Level 50:</p>
<ul>
<li>Bow-Man - Bow-Crafting any log of any type grants you double experience.</li>
<li>Robin Hood - Crafting arrows which are Steel and above allows you to craft double the amount of arrows with the same amount of materials.</li>
<li>Savvy Craftsman - Creating 2 Rune Crossbows allows to you collect one Runite Bar in your Inventory.</li>
<li>Enchanting Crossbow Bolts also grants you Bow-Crafting experience as well as Magic experience.</li>
</ul>
<p>Level 75:</p>
<ul>
<li>Dark Dragon - The player may now create Dragon Arrows. Doing so will give the player Evil Karma.</li>
<li>Ice Craft - The player may now create Ice Arrows. These arrows are not quite as good as Dragon Arrows, but are less expensive to craft.</li>
<li>Father of Robin Hood - Crafting Rune Arrows gives you quadruple the amount with the same amount of materials.</li>
<li>Dragon Bolt Instructer - Allows you to craft double Dragon Bolts, which come pre-enchanted.</li>
</ul>
<p>Level 100:</p>
<ul>
<li>Blasphemy Bow - A Dark Bow can now be crafted by the player. This can only be done once every 24 hours. Once this is done, the player’s Karmic level is automatically set to the most Evil.</li>
<li>Void Outpost Ranger - The Void Knight gear from the Pest Control mini-game can now be bought with Gold Pieces. The cost is 75,000,000 Gold Pieces per set. The gear, however, remains non-tradable, and still functions as non-tradable items.</li>
<li>Method Archery - When the player uses Archery in combat, they not only gain Archery experience, but Bow-Crafting experience as well.</li>
<li>Crystal Archery - Allows the player to create Crystal Bows. The player must have a Crystal Seed, and 2,500,000 Gold Pieces to create this fine bow.</li>
</ul>
<hr>
<hr>
<p>Creation Perk Tree:</p>
<p>Level 50:</p>
<ul>
<li>Creative Creationist - Chisels are no longer required to cut Gems.</li>
<li>Gem Trader - Uncut gems cost 25% less to buy, sell for 25% more, and the Gem Shop now has an unlimited stock of all Gems.</li>
<li>Self-Sufficiency - All Hides of any type no longer need to be tanned before they can be used in Creation.</li>
<li>Thrifty Spinner - Spinning Flax to Bow String grants twice as much experience, and spins twice as quickly as before.</li>
</ul>
<p>Level 75:</p>
<ul>
<li>Bow-Creationist - Spinning Flax to Bow String now gives you Bow-Crafting experience as well as Creation experience.</li>
<li>Expert Creations - Creating high-level Gear now grants you 250% more experience in Creation.</li>
<li>Skilled Spinner - When you spin Flax to Bow String, you gain one piece of Flax for every two you spin.</li>
<li>The player can now craft Robin Hood hats and Ranger Boots.</li>
</ul>
<p>Level 100:</p>
<ul>
<li>Masterful Creations - Creating end-game Gear now grants you 1000% more experience in Creation.</li>
<li>Flax Baron - At the end of each day, 500 Flax is deposited into your Bank.</li>
<li>Creationist of the Gods - Saradomin, Zamorak, and Guthix DragonHide can now be created by the player; using the perspective colored Hides.</li>
<li>Gem Baron - At the end of each day, 100 of each Gem is deposited into your Bank.</li>
</ul>
<hr>
<hr>
<p>Prospecting Perk Tree:</p>
<p>Level 50:</p>
<ul>
<li>Sharp Eye - The player is instantly able to identify the type of ore contained in a rock.</li>
<li>Coal Miner - The player recieves double experience for mining Coal.</li>
<li>Gem Prospecter - Chance of getting random gems from Prospecting increased by 40%.</li>
<li>Golden Pick - Allows the player to Buy a Golden Pickaxe from the Mining Grandmaster. This Pickaxe increases experience gained from Prospecting by 10%, and increases the chance of recieving random gems whilst Prospecting by 10%.</li>
</ul>
<p>Level 75:</p>
<ul>
<li>Smelting Master - Allows the player to smelt Cannonballs. This can be done by mixing Adamantite, Iron, and Tin ore.</li>
<li>Agile Prospecter - The player’s run energy regenerates 50% quicker when their Inventory is filled with Ore of any type.</li>
<li>Dragonstone in the Rough - Allows the player to have a chance of finding an Uncut Dragonstone Gem whilst prospecting. The chance is 4% for every ore mined.</li>
<li>Gem Hoarder - Greatly increases the chance of finding Gems whilst prospecting. Rates are: Sapphire 50%, Emerald 45%, Opal 40%, Jade 40%, Ruby 35%, Pearl 30%, Diamond 20%, Ice Diamond 15%, and Dragonstone 6%.</li>
</ul>
<p>Level 100:</p>
<ul>
<li>Legendary Prospecter - Allows the player to prospect Bronze Ore, and turn the Bronze Ore into Bronze Dust. This is the main ingredient in Fire Bombs.</li>
<li>Gem Runners - Any and all Gems the player gets from prospecting are directly deposited into the player’s bank.</li>
<li>Ultimate Crafting - Allows the player to prospect Crafting Ore. There is only 1 Crafting Ore Rock in-game, and it is located beside Mage Bank. Once mined, the player is tele-blocked, and must run through 55 levels of Wilderness. This Ore is the most valuable Ore in-game. It can be used as a substitute for any secondary material in any recipe.</li>
<li>Gem Hunter - The player has a chance of finding an Uncut Onyx Gem whilst prospecting. The chance is 1%.</li>
</ul>
<hr>
<hr>
<p>Culinary Perk Tree:</p>
<p>Level 50:</p>
<ul>
<li>Gnome Preparation - The player can now brew stat-boosting drinks.</li>
<li>Dwarven Shananagins - Allows the player to cook food in a Smelter. This increases the chance of burning food by 25%.</li>
<li>Cook Hands - Decreases the chance of burning all food by 20%.</li>
<li>Cook’s Assignment - Allows the player to speak to the Castle Cook in Camelot to recieve a ‘Culinary Task’. This functions similar to Executioner, except It’s with food. The player is rewarded with Purple Sweets for each Culinary Task completed; depending upon difficulty and the amount of food prepared.</li>
</ul>
<p>Level 75:</p>
<ul>
<li>Agile Chef - Weight Carried is reduced to 0 if the player has an Inventory filled with raw food.</li>
<li>Elvish Culinary - Chance to burn all food is decreased by 50%.</li>
<li>Herbs and Spices - Allows the player to mix Herblaw Herbs with different food to create special recipes. 25% chance of success.</li>
<li>Survivalist Chef - The chance of burning food on an open fire is now equal to that of burning it on a range stove.</li>
</ul>
<p>Level 100:</p>
<ul>
<li>Iron Chef - Chance to burn food is decreased by 90%.</li>
<li>Steel Chef - When 5 food are cooked within 30 seconds, the player’s Run Energy is instantly restored by 50%.</li>
<li>Rune Chef - 5% chance of finding special items from raw shark whilst cooking them.</li>
<li>Chef of the Gods - The player earns 250% more Culinary experience, and may prepare and cook Enchanted Meat (functions as 2 doses of a Saradomin Brew).</li>
</ul>
<hr>
<hr>
<p>Grace Perk Tree:</p>
<p>Level 50:</p>
<ul>
<li>Light Footed - Enemies are slightly less aggressive to you. (Which is equal to 1 tile).</li>
<li>Grace of a Cat - You can use Grace obstacles and shortcuts which are 10 levels above your Grace level.</li>
<li>Sprinter - You gain a permanent increase to your Energy of 5%.</li>
<li>Marathon Runner - You gain a permanent increase of + 5% to your Energy Regeneration rate.</li>
</ul>
<p>Level 75:</p>
<ul>
<li>Agile Thief - You gain a 10% success rate to Pilfering when you pick-pocket any N.P.C.</li>
<li>Fire-Feet - Everytime you light logs via Tinderbox, you regenerate 4% of your total Run Energy.</li>
<li>Nature’s Swiftness - When you recieve a log from Survival, you regenerate 3% of your total Run Energy.</li>
<li>Light Warrior - Weight Carried is reduced by 20% when all gear slots are filled.</li>
</ul>
<p>Level 100:</p>
<ul>
<li>Graceful Master - Run Energy permanently increased by 25%.</li>
<li>Graceful Marathon - Run Energy regeneration increased by 50%.</li>
<li>Agile Master - Grace level boosted by 10 levels when the Grace Cape is worn (requires 100 Grace to wear).</li>
<li>Agile Gatherer - Weight Carried reduced to 0 when Inventory is filled.<br>
-----------------------------------------------------------------------</li>
</ul>
</blockquote>

          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/team-rocket-the-first-thread-since-the-return-creative/516328/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/team-rocket-the-first-thread-since-the-return-creative/516328/1</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2013 21:48:32 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-516328-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/team-rocket-the-first-thread-since-the-return-creative/516328.rss">[Team_Rocket] The first thread since the return [CREATIVE]</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
