<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Abandoning the Virtual Czar</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/abandoning-the-virtual-czar/2327</link>
    <description>-----------------------------------------------------------

In the Customer Relations team we have over two thirds of our Moderators dedicated to processing your abuse reports as quickly as possible, as well as dealing with macro users and real world traders. Jagex Moderators are also assigned to tracking where the profits of cheating have gone, resulting in the banning not only of scam accounts but also of the main accounts of those who persist in scamming. In addition to this, we are constantly recruiting honest player moderators to help us to identify and remove disruptive elements from the game. 

Beyond the Customer Relations team our Content team is constantly looking into ways to alter the game itself to reduce the ability for people to cheat, for example the recent creation of the Bank PINs and the essence mine changes. 

The main source of information on rule breakers comes from you - our players. Every abuse report we receive is actioned accordingly and will be recorded on the offending player&#39;s permanent record. Processing the abuse reports cannot be done instantly, and action taken happens behind the scenes, so we cannot guarantee that you will always see the offending player being removed from the game - however the good news is that we are now more successful than ever at processing abuse reports quickly and seeking to educate players. [b]Those who are not willing to be educated are removed.[/b] 

So if you are a honest player, you can do your bit to help all this by sending in Abuse Reports whenever you see someone breaking the rules. You can also help yourself by keeping both your account and your PC safe - advice on how to do this being found in the Knowledge Base. 

And if you&#39;re a dishonest player you can do your bit by stopping breaking the rules now. 

[b]We will find you[/b] and we will ban you if you don&#39;t play by our rules. 

--------------------------------------------------------------- 

The below text is all opinionated and shouldn&#39;t be taken offensive to anyone. If you have a problem with my rhetoric simply don&#39;t read it, or reply sensibly stating why I am full of myself. Forgive typos or inconsistencies--this was typed in a state of realization without editing.

[u]Yesterday shall be the last time I ever log into Runescape. [/u] 

I am gladly throwing away a lvl 98 account with over 30M in items and an investment of 2 years. 

It has become increasingly obvious that the sole purpose of this game is to make real-world money for a select amount of individuals. This is accomplished by creating serious addictions to the amount of enjoyment and entertainment that is afforded by the game. Yet, in making such a game so attractive, it has alienated its users from external reality; the one filled with learning, friends, adventure, and happiness. 

It is amazing how the complexities of humanity is expressed in this simple javascript game. Dominance hierarchies, territorial tendencies, and wealth status that we see in so many Western countries is perfectly portrayed by fancy items, gold coins, quest points, stats, etc. And unlike in real life where final accomplishments can eventually be obtained, there is techinically no end to the amount of &quot;experience&quot; (XP) or money that you can earn in Runescape. 

The sad thing is we only get one shot at life; everyone is going to die and the only reflection of the quality of your existence is the effort that you put into making positive changes in your own life and those of others. &quot;Experience&quot; does not include clicking a single pixel for a fabricated reason.

Yet, the people at Jagex are getting rich off of convincing (mostly young) people that there is something to be gained from Runescape other than bragging rights or a cheap elimination of boredom. Hell, parents gladly dish out $5 a month to pacify their children into a passive vegetative state that causes them little problems. 

Millions upon millions of real individuals live and die everyday in a horrendous state of dispair. Poor nutrition, poor education, war, disease, etc. riddle a huge chunk of our population. We can&#39;t all save the world by depositing pennies at McDonald&#39;s and Wal-Mart, but we can certainly be conscious about how our decisions and behaviors affect the rest of the world. Not only could the millions of dollars that Jagex officials pocket be spent on something a little more resourceful, we could all dedicate our time to something more productive than a bright computer screen and a world that only exists on a technological server. 

I am quitting because Runescape, the economy and the officials, is a mirror image of a fascist regime that is obsessed with coercively manipulating its citizens into being loyal. It has become way too frightening to log into a dimension where the cartoons I see are real people who are blind against the REAL game.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 16 May 2006 06:48:41 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>General Discussion</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/abandoning-the-virtual-czar/2327.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Abandoning the Virtual Czar</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@zsakul2 zsakul2]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/zsakul2">@zsakul2</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>dude you spoke out to me as soon as i read this i automattically sent a message to jagex a very offensive message so offensive if i posted on here i would be auto banned from the first 10 words! i hope you don’t mind i posted a link to this forumn thing right here that you made and i posted what you said on exactly 17 diffrent forumns and i wanted you too know that you have the best ever post i have ever saw you are so awesome</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/abandoning-the-virtual-czar/2327/20">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/abandoning-the-virtual-czar/2327/20</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 16 May 2006 06:48:41 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-2327-20</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/abandoning-the-virtual-czar/2327.rss">Abandoning the Virtual Czar</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Abandoning the Virtual Czar</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@PaulT PaulT]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/pault">@PaulT</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote no-group quote-modified" data-post="18" data-topic="2327">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/blackthursday/40/5_8504b32b4165840149d2c3dd52eb0686.png" class="avatar"> BlackThursday:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>If you submit bomb threat to Jagex they’ll unban you.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>And call the cops. I can see it now, SWAT kicks down the door just as you get your whip back. “FREEZE SUCKKA! DROP THE ABBY!”</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/abandoning-the-virtual-czar/2327/19">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/abandoning-the-virtual-czar/2327/19</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 16 May 2006 00:45:10 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-2327-19</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/abandoning-the-virtual-czar/2327.rss">Abandoning the Virtual Czar</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Abandoning the Virtual Czar</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@BlackThursday BlackThursday]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/blackthursday">@BlackThursday</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>If you submit bomb threat to Jagex they’ll unban you.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/abandoning-the-virtual-czar/2327/18">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/abandoning-the-virtual-czar/2327/18</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 16 May 2006 00:15:21 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-2327-18</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/abandoning-the-virtual-czar/2327.rss">Abandoning the Virtual Czar</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Abandoning the Virtual Czar</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@PaulT PaulT]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/pault">@PaulT</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Yeah. I’m just waiting untill it appears in the news that an enraged Runescape super-fan attacks Andrew Gower and holds him hostage for in-game money and items.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/abandoning-the-virtual-czar/2327/17">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/abandoning-the-virtual-czar/2327/17</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 15 May 2006 22:33:18 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-2327-17</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/abandoning-the-virtual-czar/2327.rss">Abandoning the Virtual Czar</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Abandoning the Virtual Czar</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@KyleGut3 KyleGut3]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/kylegut3">@KyleGut3</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>whats funny is that I was getting the whole totalitarian feel from the quote at the top before you mentioned it <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=9" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/abandoning-the-virtual-czar/2327/16">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/abandoning-the-virtual-czar/2327/16</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 15 May 2006 22:30:59 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-2327-16</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/abandoning-the-virtual-czar/2327.rss">Abandoning the Virtual Czar</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Abandoning the Virtual Czar</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@PaulT PaulT]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/pault">@PaulT</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I agree with you,  you’re a just little late, this would have been alot more powerful if you had when members or runescape 2 came out, the two of which combined were the ultimate destroyers of the game itself. I really stopped enjoying it very much after members came out, and I stopped playing it after RS2 came out. Well, stopped playing, but kept PKing, because if you really hate the game, the best way to let out you’re anger is to destroy other peoples items and money in the wilderness, which hopefully might inspire them to quit, haha. Well, not really, I just like pking.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/abandoning-the-virtual-czar/2327/15">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/abandoning-the-virtual-czar/2327/15</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 15 May 2006 22:11:03 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-2327-15</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/abandoning-the-virtual-czar/2327.rss">Abandoning the Virtual Czar</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Abandoning the Virtual Czar</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@BlackThursday BlackThursday]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/blackthursday">@BlackThursday</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>The Virtual Czar… it rules us all… except when you just play to hate Fagex… thats why the cheating community is soo great.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/abandoning-the-virtual-czar/2327/14">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/abandoning-the-virtual-czar/2327/14</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 15 May 2006 21:26:07 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-2327-14</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/abandoning-the-virtual-czar/2327.rss">Abandoning the Virtual Czar</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Abandoning the Virtual Czar</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Brad Brad]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/brad">@Brad</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>it took me one day to stop thinking of runescape… because i found mopar <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=9" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/abandoning-the-virtual-czar/2327/13">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/abandoning-the-virtual-czar/2327/13</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 12 May 2006 20:46:25 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-2327-13</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/abandoning-the-virtual-czar/2327.rss">Abandoning the Virtual Czar</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Abandoning the Virtual Czar</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Zach1188 Zach1188]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/zach1188">@Zach1188</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>It took me months to escape from the grasp of Runescape. The issue is that RS is extremely boring, yet oddly, so addictive. I have no idea why, I have plenty of friends, a happy life, yet I could not go a day without it. RS starts as a fun game, then ends up being an out of control addiction.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/abandoning-the-virtual-czar/2327/12">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/abandoning-the-virtual-czar/2327/12</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 12 May 2006 04:05:23 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-2327-12</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/abandoning-the-virtual-czar/2327.rss">Abandoning the Virtual Czar</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Abandoning the Virtual Czar</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Martin Martin]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/martin">@Martin</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I dont see how anyone could be ‘touched’ be that lol RUNESCAPE IS ONLY A GAME, GET A LIFE AND GO OUT ONCE IN A WHILE.</p>
<p>Oh but im proud of you for leaving and not staying on till you are like 45 or someshit</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/abandoning-the-virtual-czar/2327/11">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/abandoning-the-virtual-czar/2327/11</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 11 May 2006 19:31:52 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-2327-11</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/abandoning-the-virtual-czar/2327.rss">Abandoning the Virtual Czar</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Abandoning the Virtual Czar</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@The_Un-Named The Un-Named]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/the_un-named">@The_Un-Named</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Well written. I’ve been thinking about going out with a big bang, but I got some good friends there.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/abandoning-the-virtual-czar/2327/10">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/abandoning-the-virtual-czar/2327/10</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 11 May 2006 07:14:11 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-2327-10</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/abandoning-the-virtual-czar/2327.rss">Abandoning the Virtual Czar</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Abandoning the Virtual Czar</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@system system]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/system">@system</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>meh its game quit if you want yet my problem is all my freinds live on north side and i got no car till next year then im pissin off handin everything over to bro cuzin or friends on rs</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/abandoning-the-virtual-czar/2327/9">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/abandoning-the-virtual-czar/2327/9</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 11 May 2006 05:06:49 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-2327-9</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/abandoning-the-virtual-czar/2327.rss">Abandoning the Virtual Czar</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Abandoning the Virtual Czar</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@John2.0 John2.0]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/john2.0">@John2.0</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>well, this is truely… well… brutally honest. wanna take a gov position? at least i think you’d be honest and not try to cover up for a future election lol</p>
<p>but seriously, you’re right… to a degree. Unfortunately rs is addicting at first, then you make “friends” in the game… you get bored… then you stop playin for a bit… then you realize you’ve alienated your once real friends… then you go back to the game… and start all over again. It’s a sad vicious cycle for most. as of now i just play it in my spare time though lol. not everyone is addicted, but those who arent see the addictions.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/abandoning-the-virtual-czar/2327/8">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/abandoning-the-virtual-czar/2327/8</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 03 May 2006 19:43:02 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-2327-8</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/abandoning-the-virtual-czar/2327.rss">Abandoning the Virtual Czar</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Abandoning the Virtual Czar</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@doomsday doomsday]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/doomsday">@doomsday</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>nooooo</p>
<p>I hate you from now on… lo j/k</p>
<p>but anyways, i just made 42 new accounts(and im gonna walk arounda tuo typeing AYRAN RULES) anyone wanna join?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/abandoning-the-virtual-czar/2327/7">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/abandoning-the-virtual-czar/2327/7</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 03 May 2006 19:25:50 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-2327-7</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/abandoning-the-virtual-czar/2327.rss">Abandoning the Virtual Czar</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Abandoning the Virtual Czar</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Andrew Andrew]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/andrew">@Andrew</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Too late I alredy asked him for the acnt so haha…</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/abandoning-the-virtual-czar/2327/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/abandoning-the-virtual-czar/2327/6</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 03 May 2006 19:22:02 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-2327-6</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/abandoning-the-virtual-czar/2327.rss">Abandoning the Virtual Czar</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Abandoning the Virtual Czar</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@doomsday doomsday]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/doomsday">@doomsday</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>lol, second hitler, accutally the guy has really smart ideas(can i have your level 98 character now :P)</p>
<p>it is true, everyone in the game is addicated(bassically) and they want real money, and other buy stuff for real mone, this is a game, I AM A PRO GAMER(its al i do) and its kinda sickoning to see such a great game go to waste, oh well halo 3 is comming soon,beta 3 xbox live edition is out, beta testers only(im glad i am one)</p>
<p>i really am a random person…</p>
<p>but seriously dude your smart, ive been scammed 5 times and hacked 4 in the past 2 weeks(i guess tha scamms were hacks because when i press okay i dont get the items that was traded)</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/abandoning-the-virtual-czar/2327/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/abandoning-the-virtual-czar/2327/5</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 03 May 2006 19:20:38 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-2327-5</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/abandoning-the-virtual-czar/2327.rss">Abandoning the Virtual Czar</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Abandoning the Virtual Czar</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Andrew Andrew]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/andrew">@Andrew</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>That said somethin to me…Thats a first.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/abandoning-the-virtual-czar/2327/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/abandoning-the-virtual-czar/2327/4</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 03 May 2006 19:19:52 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-2327-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/abandoning-the-virtual-czar/2327.rss">Abandoning the Virtual Czar</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Abandoning the Virtual Czar</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@thiefmn6092 thiefmn6092]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/thiefmn6092">@thiefmn6092</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote]<br>
I am quitting because Runescape, the economy and the officials, is a mirror image of a fascist regime that is obsessed with coercively manipulating its citizens into being loyal. It has become way too frightening to log into a dimension where the cartoons I see are real people who are blind against the REAL game.</p>
<p>[quote/]</p>
<p>Our 2nd hitler</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/abandoning-the-virtual-czar/2327/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/abandoning-the-virtual-czar/2327/3</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 03 May 2006 19:11:32 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-2327-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/abandoning-the-virtual-czar/2327.rss">Abandoning the Virtual Czar</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Abandoning the Virtual Czar</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@BlackThursday BlackThursday]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/blackthursday">@BlackThursday</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>HOLY SHIT… Bravo… jus Bravo… Anyone else get sumthing out of this? I am in frekin shock and awe at that… its… wonderful.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/abandoning-the-virtual-czar/2327/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/abandoning-the-virtual-czar/2327/2</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 03 May 2006 19:07:46 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-2327-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/abandoning-the-virtual-czar/2327.rss">Abandoning the Virtual Czar</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Abandoning the Virtual Czar</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@intheknow intheknow]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/intheknow">@intheknow</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <hr>
<p>In the Customer Relations team we have over two thirds of our Moderators dedicated to processing your abuse reports as quickly as possible, as well as dealing with macro users and real world traders. Jagex Moderators are also assigned to tracking where the profits of cheating have gone, resulting in the banning not only of scam accounts but also of the main accounts of those who persist in scamming. In addition to this, we are constantly recruiting honest player moderators to help us to identify and remove disruptive elements from the game.</p>
<p>Beyond the Customer Relations team our Content team is constantly looking into ways to alter the game itself to reduce the ability for people to cheat, for example the recent creation of the Bank PINs and the essence mine changes.</p>
<p>The main source of information on rule breakers comes from you - our players. Every abuse report we receive is actioned accordingly and will be recorded on the offending player’s permanent record. Processing the abuse reports cannot be done instantly, and action taken happens behind the scenes, so we cannot guarantee that you will always see the offending player being removed from the game - however the good news is that we are now more successful than ever at processing abuse reports quickly and seeking to educate players. <span class="bbcode-b">Those who are not willing to be educated are removed.</span></p>
<p>So if you are a honest player, you can do your bit to help all this by sending in Abuse Reports whenever you see someone breaking the rules. You can also help yourself by keeping both your account and your PC safe - advice on how to do this being found in the Knowledge Base.</p>
<p>And if you’re a dishonest player you can do your bit by stopping breaking the rules now.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">We will find you</span> and we will ban you if you don’t play by our rules.</p>
<hr>
<p>The below text is all opinionated and shouldn’t be taken offensive to anyone. If you have a problem with my rhetoric simply don’t read it, or reply sensibly stating why I am full of myself. Forgive typos or inconsistencies–this was typed in a state of realization without editing.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-u">Yesterday shall be the last time I ever log into Runescape. </span></p>
<p>I am gladly throwing away a lvl 98 account with over 30M in items and an investment of 2 years.</p>
<p>It has become increasingly obvious that the sole purpose of this game is to make real-world money for a select amount of individuals. This is accomplished by creating serious addictions to the amount of enjoyment and entertainment that is afforded by the game. Yet, in making such a game so attractive, it has alienated its users from external reality; the one filled with learning, friends, adventure, and happiness.</p>
<p>It is amazing how the complexities of humanity is expressed in this simple javascript game. Dominance hierarchies, territorial tendencies, and wealth status that we see in so many Western countries is perfectly portrayed by fancy items, gold coins, quest points, stats, etc. And unlike in real life where final accomplishments can eventually be obtained, there is techinically no end to the amount of “experience” (XP) or money that you can earn in Runescape.</p>
<p>The sad thing is we only get one shot at life; everyone is going to die and the only reflection of the quality of your existence is the effort that you put into making positive changes in your own life and those of others. “Experience” does not include clicking a single pixel for a fabricated reason.</p>
<p>Yet, the people at Jagex are getting rich off of convincing (mostly young) people that there is something to be gained from Runescape other than bragging rights or a cheap elimination of boredom. Hell, parents gladly dish out $5 a month to pacify their children into a passive vegetative state that causes them little problems.</p>
<p>Millions upon millions of real individuals live and die everyday in a horrendous state of dispair. Poor nutrition, poor education, war, disease, etc. riddle a huge chunk of our population. We can’t all save the world by depositing pennies at McDonald’s and Wal-Mart, but we can certainly be conscious about how our decisions and behaviors affect the rest of the world. Not only could the millions of dollars that Jagex officials pocket be spent on something a little more resourceful, we could all dedicate our time to something more productive than a bright computer screen and a world that only exists on a technological server.</p>
<p>I am quitting because Runescape, the economy and the officials, is a mirror image of a fascist regime that is obsessed with coercively manipulating its citizens into being loyal. It has become way too frightening to log into a dimension where the cartoons I see are real people who are blind against the REAL game.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/abandoning-the-virtual-czar/2327/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/abandoning-the-virtual-czar/2327/1</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 03 May 2006 19:01:13 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-2327-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/abandoning-the-virtual-czar/2327.rss">Abandoning the Virtual Czar</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
