<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Xbox Live Update Preview</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/xbox-live-update-preview/310194</link>
    <description>Did anyone else get in on the Xbox Live Update Preview? If you have, how do you like it so far? 

I just finished downloading the updates about an hour ago. And I have to say I&#39;m impressed with them. Facebook is my favorite of the updates, last.fm coming in second. I haven&#39;t tried the twitter application yet, but I&#39;ll get around to it. I&#39;ve run into some glitches, and just some unfavorable behavior. But I&#39;m sure after a few days of the preview the bugs will be fixed. 

Facebook is missing an important feature in my eyes, and that&#39;s Chatting, it also lacks video as well. I was hoping for some free 1080p content to try it out, but all they have is 720p for free. last.fm is really only good if you like to have music playing in the background while you&#39;re doing something else not involving your 360. Which if you&#39;re like me and you&#39;re computer is right next to your xbox, it doesn&#39;t serve much purpose.

Overall though, I&#39;m glad they added these features, Xbox Live felt like it was lacking before. But it feels fuller now, and more like a Media Center rather than just a gaming system.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 23 Oct 2009 15:02:23 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>General Discussion</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/xbox-live-update-preview/310194.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Xbox Live Update Preview</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@eczema3 eczema3]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/eczema3">@eczema3</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Now all they need to do is finish off Project Natal.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/xbox-live-update-preview/310194/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/xbox-live-update-preview/310194/3</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 23 Oct 2009 15:02:23 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-310194-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/xbox-live-update-preview/310194.rss">Xbox Live Update Preview</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Xbox Live Update Preview</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Speljohan Speljohan]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/speljohan">@Speljohan</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I can prolly not access this stuff yet as they r always slow with updates to sweden. Doesn’t really seem like anything i’d ever use</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/xbox-live-update-preview/310194/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/xbox-live-update-preview/310194/2</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 23 Oct 2009 12:05:29 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-310194-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/xbox-live-update-preview/310194.rss">Xbox Live Update Preview</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Xbox Live Update Preview</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@ThAt0n36Uy Elijah]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/that0n36uy">@ThAt0n36Uy</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Did anyone else get in on the Xbox Live Update Preview? If you have, how do you like it so far?</p>
<p>I just finished downloading the updates about an hour ago. And I have to say I’m impressed with them. Facebook is my favorite of the updates, last.fm coming in second. I haven’t tried the twitter application yet, but I’ll get around to it. I’ve run into some glitches, and just some unfavorable behavior. But I’m sure after a few days of the preview the bugs will be fixed.</p>
<p>Facebook is missing an important feature in my eyes, and that’s Chatting, it also lacks video as well. I was hoping for some free 1080p content to try it out, but all they have is 720p for free. last.fm is really only good if you like to have music playing in the background while you’re doing something else not involving your 360. Which if you’re like me and you’re computer is right next to your xbox, it doesn’t serve much purpose.</p>
<p>Overall though, I’m glad they added these features, Xbox Live felt like it was lacking before. But it feels fuller now, and more like a Media Center rather than just a gaming system.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/xbox-live-update-preview/310194/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/xbox-live-update-preview/310194/1</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 23 Oct 2009 03:54:29 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-310194-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/xbox-live-update-preview/310194.rss">Xbox Live Update Preview</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
