<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>MGO Premier Beta - My Review</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/mgo-premier-beta-my-review/204209</link>
    <description>Well i downloaded this and the two updates that came with it and for hardcore MGS fans its a good game, but i have never really enjoyed them and decided to see whether the Next-Gen transfer had done the series any good. From my opinion No it hasn&#39;t.
[b]Character Design[/b]
You can design your own character and name it whatever you like so you aren&#39;t stuck with your PSN name, this was one of my favourite parts as you can choose from quite a variety of different gear for your digital soldier and then you can dive right in. 
[b]Gameplay[/b]
Well the gameplay for this is quite appaling but its a beta so hopefully when the proper game comes it will be better. Starting with the worst thing of all movement, its incredibly slow and you actually get bored while watching your character move. Weapons are in no short supply but they all suck and are badly rendered. Hitboxes are way off and damage is totally unrealistic. Now with damage you can say its a grey area by saying &#39;oh you can&#39;t shoot well&#39; but Konami kindly offer us 100% auto aim instead of over the shoulder aim. And still the damage is way out. If you take the P90 which is a rapid firing weapon and you have auto aim on you can empty a whole clip into a player and they might only just die. Its like this with all weapons. Some appealing features however are the fact you can hide yourself in a cardboard box and sneak around, you can place magazines on the ground that blow up and thats where they end. Games in general are too short and point scores are an impossible goal. Konami will probably fix alot of these but at the moment the beta is very low scoring.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 May 2008 23:32:31 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Games</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/mgo-premier-beta-my-review/204209.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>MGO Premier Beta - My Review</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@sanga282 sanga282]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/sanga282">@sanga282</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Well i downloaded this and the two updates that came with it and for hardcore MGS fans its a good game, but i have never really enjoyed them and decided to see whether the Next-Gen transfer had done the series any good. From my opinion No it hasn’t.<br>
<span class="bbcode-b">Character Design</span><br>
You can design your own character and name it whatever you like so you aren’t stuck with your PSN name, this was one of my favourite parts as you can choose from quite a variety of different gear for your digital soldier and then you can dive right in.<br>
<span class="bbcode-b">Gameplay</span><br>
Well the gameplay for this is quite appaling but its a beta so hopefully when the proper game comes it will be better. Starting with the worst thing of all movement, its incredibly slow and you actually get bored while watching your character move. Weapons are in no short supply but they all suck and are badly rendered. Hitboxes are way off and damage is totally unrealistic. Now with damage you can say its a grey area by saying ‘oh you can’t shoot well’ but Konami kindly offer us 100% auto aim instead of over the shoulder aim. And still the damage is way out. If you take the P90 which is a rapid firing weapon and you have auto aim on you can empty a whole clip into a player and they might only just die. Its like this with all weapons. Some appealing features however are the fact you can hide yourself in a cardboard box and sneak around, you can place magazines on the ground that blow up and thats where they end. Games in general are too short and point scores are an impossible goal. Konami will probably fix alot of these but at the moment the beta is very low scoring.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/mgo-premier-beta-my-review/204209/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/mgo-premier-beta-my-review/204209/1</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2008 23:32:31 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-204209-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/mgo-premier-beta-my-review/204209.rss">MGO Premier Beta - My Review</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
