<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>DeviousPK is Back!</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/deviouspk-is-back/541242</link>
    <description>[CENTER][IMG]http://www.upload.ee/image/3945117/DeviousPK.png[/img]
We are informing all of our old users that DeviousPK has decided to come back to the Runescape Private Server Community.
We are working on a lot of updates to make the server as smooth as possible for our pkers and users. We are gonna host a drop party tomorrow 16/03 22:30-01:00 GMT+0 its gonna be a drop party / pkers event!!! We are hosting this drop party cause we&#39;d like to recreate what was once created we want to give back the items that we have tooken away from people and make everyone as happy as they use to be!

We are really exticed about this release and hopefully we can get this server where it once was! WE WILL be on top again and that&#39;s a promise that will not be broken!

Website Link ~ DeviousPK.com
Fourm Link ~ DeviousPK.com/phpBB3/index.php

:d:d:d:d

We are quite low on staff looking for staff members that are dedicated to the server we launched the server today and within a couple of minutes we ended out with 30+ people online that were pking and enjoying themselves. Remember that can always be you if you tryout DeviousPK, It not a disappointment its a Accomplishment. 

[IMG]http://www.upload.ee/image/3945120/screenshot_2.png[/img]
[IMG]http://www.upload.ee/image/3945121/lol.png[/img]

The forums are new everything on the server is new so if i&#39;d be you i&#39;d join today and start your Adventure today. There will be a lot of great updates and i assure you that you will like them we are probably gonna put Ovls in pkp shops so its fair for everyone on the server, the Donators Island will be much greater then it was before, Superdonators are gonna be able to do ::bank and a lot more interesting stuff, Lets say it will be worth donating for!

[IMG]http://www.upload.ee/image/3945123/Forum.png[/img][/CENTER]</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 16 Mar 2014 06:04:33 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Uncategorized</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/deviouspk-is-back/541242.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>DeviousPK is Back!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Dr_house123 Dr house123]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/dr_house123">@Dr_house123</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[CENTER]<img src="http://www.upload.ee/image/3945117/DeviousPK.png" alt width="" height=""><br>
We are informing all of our old users that DeviousPK has decided to come back to the Runescape Private Server Community.<br>
We are working on a lot of updates to make the server as smooth as possible for our pkers and users. We are gonna host a drop party tomorrow 16/03 22:30-01:00 GMT+0 its gonna be a drop party / pkers event!!! We are hosting this drop party cause we’d like to recreate what was once created we want to give back the items that we have tooken away from people and make everyone as happy as they use to be!</p>
<p>We are really exticed about this release and hopefully we can get this server where it once was! WE WILL be on top again and that’s a promise that will not be broken!</p>
<p>Website Link ~ <a href="http://DeviousPK.com" rel="nofollow noopener">DeviousPK.com</a><br>
Fourm Link ~ <a href="http://DeviousPK.com/phpBB3/index.php" rel="nofollow noopener">DeviousPK.com/phpBB3/index.php</a></p>
<p>:d:d:d:d</p>
<p>We are quite low on staff looking for staff members that are dedicated to the server we launched the server today and within a couple of minutes we ended out with 30+ people online that were pking and enjoying themselves. Remember that can always be you if you tryout DeviousPK, It not a disappointment its a Accomplishment.</p>
<p><img src="http://www.upload.ee/image/3945120/screenshot_2.png" alt width="" height=""><br>
<img src="http://www.upload.ee/image/3945121/lol.png" alt width="" height=""></p>
<p>The forums are new everything on the server is new so if i’d be you i’d join today and start your Adventure today. There will be a lot of great updates and i assure you that you will like them we are probably gonna put Ovls in pkp shops so its fair for everyone on the server, the Donators Island will be much greater then it was before, Superdonators are gonna be able to do ::bank and a lot more interesting stuff, Lets say it will be worth donating for!</p>
<p><img src="http://www.upload.ee/image/3945123/Forum.png" alt width="" height="">[/CENTER]</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/deviouspk-is-back/541242/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/deviouspk-is-back/541242/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 16 Mar 2014 06:04:33 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-541242-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/deviouspk-is-back/541242.rss">DeviousPK is Back!</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
