<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Apache</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/apache/125976</link>
    <description>Zomg apache is hard lol.

Anyways I&#39;m got a website hosted, My friend is helping me learn HTML, hence his name h4x0r on the website.
[url=Http://ilymsn.50webs.com]Http://ilymsn.50webs.com[/url].

Well Since i can&#39;t upload the photos to the FTP because they are apparently &quot;too big&quot; 2.5mb to be exact. I had to use a third party hoster, Imageshack.us. I don&#39;t have a problem with that, but i&#39;m putting music on the website, something to relax people with, music always helps me think and relax. Well Since an .Mp3 file is obviously bigger than .bmp file, Uploading it to the FTP is a no no. So, i asked around, and they said use apache. Well i downloaded Xampp, and installed it. But what do i do now?! 

Never knew website making was so hard lol...I guess it&#39;s just me. Well if anyone can help with me this, i would greatly appreciate it. Thanks in advance!


How my folder is set up:

[URL=http://imageshack.us][IMG]http://img216.imageshack.us/img216/1279/50websdg3.png[/img][/URL]</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 23 Jul 2007 03:15:45 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>General Programming</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/apache/125976.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Apache</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Java_Is_My_Bitch Java Is My Bitch™]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/java_is_my_bitch">@Java_Is_My_Bitch</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Well that i know, but i usually go to sleep late around 5 am, and i wake up around 4 or 6 pm. 13 hour sleep for the computer, and theres an portable Air conditioner on the back of the computer, i don’t like my computer getting heated up =. Well since The only person helping me doesn’t know how lol, i think i will do what you did and forget about it. You know of any hosters that allow unlimited upload size, Free? I would pay but i can’t get my debit card till im 15 or 16 so a year or two to go. I would use it on paypal as it doesn’t cost alot, and its about 5 bucks a month</p>
<p>1.5Gb DiskSpace<br>
40Gb Traffic<br>
Website Builder<br>
Perl, Php, MySQL<br>
and they give you one free domain name, and i think you don’t ever have to pay for it if i read correctly?</p>
<p>But unfortunately that isn’t possible at the moment. So any suggestions on hosters?</p>
<p>Oh and Of course THANK YOU VERY MUCH FOR ALL YOUR HELP! lol, i really appreciate it! Thanks man!</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/apache/125976/7">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/apache/125976/7</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 23 Jul 2007 03:15:45 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-125976-7</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/apache/125976.rss">Apache</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Apache</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@N00b1 N00b1]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/n00b1">@N00b1</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>to be honest you making a load of work for your self here one don’t bother using your pc as a host think about it you can never turn it off again if you want your site to be up 100% also the prob on connecting could be you have a dynamic ip i had that prob and just gave up lmao any who long story short why stay with them your not paying so go get another package.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/apache/125976/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/apache/125976/6</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 23 Jul 2007 03:08:37 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-125976-6</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/apache/125976.rss">Apache</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Apache</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Java_Is_My_Bitch Java Is My Bitch™]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/java_is_my_bitch">@Java_Is_My_Bitch</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Well i have a hosting company and they give me free Sub-Domains, just like <a href="http://Ulmb.com" rel="nofollow noopener">Ulmb.com</a>.</p>
<p><a href="http://SubDomainName.50webs.com" class="onebox" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">SubDomainName.50webs.com</a></p>
<p>The picture’s don’t bother me, they are too large anyways and i can crop them to more smaller size. Its the music i want to know about, The max limit i can upload in a single file is 500Kb(.zip and .Rar Only!, While Multiple file (.Zip &amp; .Rar Too) can be up to 8Mb large.</p>
<p>But an mp3. file is too big to upload to the server, hence the max size limit of one file being 500Kb. So they told me i can use Apache to host my files there so the server would read from there.</p>
<p>So they said once its connected and everything you can do the following:</p>
<p><img src="Http://111.111.11.11/Images/DreamWeaver.jpeg" width="" height=""></p>
<p>Which i find quite hard to believe, but they are the experts. Anywho i tried it and it doesn’t work. At one point it asked for Authentication to log onto my router?! So i’m like WTH, then i read upoun allow and deny connections in ’ httpd.conf '.</p>
<p>This Part:</p>
<blockquote>
    Options FollowSymLinks
    AllowOverride All
    Order deny,allow
    Deny from all
    Satisfy all
</blockquote>
<p>IDK quite how to edit this, I’m guessing Common Sense is my best bet here, unless you consider otherwise?</p>
<p>AllowOverride All --&gt;Lets Anyone do whatever i guess<br>
Order deny, allow --&gt;Allows something?<br>
Deny from all --&gt; Denies connections from everyone, can’t i just put None?<br>
Satisfy all --&gt; What it says, satifies all lol??</p>
<p>Well i’m not sure, i googled on how the auth screen won’t appear, So i Changed AllowOverride None To: AllowOverride All</p>
<p>, I guess that took out the problem!</p>
<p>Uh I logged onto my router to see if it was of any help?</p>
<p>PortForwarding - I portforwarded The service name " HTTP " On port 80 To my router ip, to see if it worked?, No luck.</p>
<p>Then my router has an option called “Dynamic Dns”, ‘DynDNS’.</p>
<p>It told me to put in the following credentials:</p>
<p>Host Name:<br>
UserName:<br>
Password:</p>
<p>I filled those in, No luck! Since the host provider isn’t FROM DynDNS, and that was the only website option, i’m guessing that was the reason it Didn’t work. Theres a button called ’ Show Status ’ im guessing show the status of the Domain. target="_blank"&gt; And i get a " nohost " Says it on the top left hand corner. In my mind i’m guessing its because its not from DynDNS, Could i be wrong?</p>
<p>Anyways I’m using the local host to host my files so i have somewhere to get them from, I will be putting the Dowload DreamWeaver Link on the page, and i want the file to be there but since its 300Megs My hoster just won’t allow it lol. 8Mb is max in case you forgot. I managed to find one at 60Megs But still can’t.</p>
<p>Thats when i heard the idea of using Apache to host my files</p>
<p>[Quote]There is no way to do this unless you have a “in-home” server set up.<br>
Software for this is available such as Apache or Abyss Personal Web Server. [/quote]</p>
<p>Ok i downloaded it, Ran it. Installed it as a service and it runs smoothly, when i press admin, the index file in htdocs shows up saying " It Works! ". So i’m guessing it works! So do i put my files there? NOPE, i just tried putting the folder Images With images inside in ’ htdocs ’ and i loaded my server, nope! Still an X.</p>
<p>I’ll even try just putting the image in the Apache2.2 Folder…Still An X!</p>
<p>Could it be that my computer is just refusing to let the server upload in this case, its resource files?(Being the Images, Download Links, Etc…)?</p>
<p>Wait NaV just came up and it asked me if i should permit Internet Acess for Apache, i put permit, loaded my site, Still An X!</p>
<p>From what i’ve understood from Tutorials on installing Apache for Windows, The document root. Thats where requests are taken from? So i would put</p>
<p>“<a href="http://111.111.11.11/C:/Documents" rel="nofollow noopener">http://111.111.11.11/C:/Documents</a> and Settings/COMPUTERNAME/Desktop/50webs/”</p>
<p>to upload the image? That doesn’t work.</p>
<blockquote>#
# DocumentRoot: The directory out of which you will serve your
# documents. By default, all requests are taken from this directory, but
# symbolic links and aliases may be used to point to other locations.
#
DocumentRoot "C:/Documents and Settings/COMPUTERNAME/Desktop/50webs"</blockquote>
<p>Then Theres the other you have to change as well:</p>
<blockquote>#
# This should be changed to whatever you set DocumentRoot to.
#
</blockquote>
<p>I Did em both, and as stated in in tutorials any changes to httpd.conf, you have to restart Apache, Right? So first i put Stop service, Then i go to taskmanager and delete any other processes, apache.exe(two of them) and the .exe monitoring them, then i go to start&gt;run&gt;services.msc and i make sure Apache service is turned off. If it isnt i turn it off, wait about 30 seconds and turn it back on, i run the Apache monitor, i start the service, which should already be started i guess. And i log onto my site, Nope, still the same!</p>
<p>Btw sry about putting ideas like, if i do this this will make it better, than answer the question is the next sentence, its just disproving theories you might have, because i’ve tried them. Its Long I Know &gt;.&gt;</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/apache/125976/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/apache/125976/5</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 23 Jul 2007 02:09:29 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-125976-5</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/apache/125976.rss">Apache</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Apache</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@N00b1 N00b1]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/n00b1">@N00b1</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>hold on for a sec are you using local host or a actual hosting company if you are using local host just find your htdocks and if you are using a company then just get a better ftp because ive never had that prob or are you trying to use a company that  uses your pc as the file holder?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/apache/125976/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/apache/125976/4</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 22 Jul 2007 20:35:58 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-125976-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/apache/125976.rss">Apache</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Apache</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Java_Is_My_Bitch Java Is My Bitch™]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/java_is_my_bitch">@Java_Is_My_Bitch</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Well true, i have to make them smaller, i was using .bmp, they make it to big in viewing size and in Space size. But the music is what i’m wondering about.</p>
<p>Ok, Now i try to get on my site, and it asks me for authentication? Into my router?! Im guessing the computer as a whole. Well i put my router User and pass, and it still won’t show me the first picture.</p>
<blockquote>
<img src="http://MYIP/Images/overall.bmp" width="" height=""><br>
</blockquote>
<p>Any suggestions on how to make it not ask for authentication for viewing files and the file appearing?</p>
<p>[code]#</p>
<h1>This is the main Apache HTTP server configuration file.  It contains the</h1>
<h1>configuration directives that give the server its instructions.</h1>
<h1>See <a>URL:http://httpd.apache.org/docs/2.2/</a> for detailed information.</h1>
<h1>In particular, see</h1>
<h1><a>URL:http://httpd.apache.org/docs/2.2/mod/directives.html</a></h1>
<h1>for a discussion of each configuration directive.</h1>
<h1></h1>
<h1>Do NOT simply read the instructions in here without understanding</h1>
<h1>what they do.  They’re here only as hints or reminders.  If you are unsure</h1>
<h1>consult the online docs. You have been warned.</h1>
<h1></h1>
<h1>Configuration and logfile names: If the filenames you specify for many</h1>
<h1>of the server’s control files begin with “/” (or “drive:/” for Win32), the</h1>
<h1>server will use that explicit path.  If the filenames do <em>not</em> begin</h1>
<h1>with “/”, the value of ServerRoot is prepended – so “logs/foo.log”</h1>
<h1>with ServerRoot set to “C:/Program Files/Apache Software Foundation/Apache2.2” will be interpreted by the</h1>
<h1>server as “C:/Program Files/Apache Software Foundation/Apache2.2/logs/foo.log”.</h1>
<h1></h1>
<h1>NOTE: Where filenames are specified, you must use forward slashes</h1>
<h1>instead of backslashes (e.g., “c:/apache” instead of “c:\apache”).</h1>
<h1>If a drive letter is omitted, the drive on which Apache.exe is located</h1>
<h1>will be used by default.  It is recommended that you always supply</h1>
<h1>an explicit drive letter in absolute paths, however, to avoid</h1>
<h1>confusion.</h1>
<h1></h1>
<h1>ThreadsPerChild: constant number of worker threads in the server process</h1>
<h1>MaxRequestsPerChild: maximum  number of requests a server process serves</h1>
<p>ThreadsPerChild 70<br>
MaxRequestsPerChild  0</p>
<h1></h1>
<h1>ServerRoot: The top of the directory tree under which the server’s</h1>
<h1>configuration, error, and log files are kept.</h1>
<h1></h1>
<h1>Do not add a slash at the end of the directory path.  If you point</h1>
<h1>ServerRoot at a non-local disk, be sure to point the LockFile directive</h1>
<h1>at a local disk.  If you wish to share the same ServerRoot for multiple</h1>
<h1>httpd daemons, you will need to change at least LockFile and PidFile.</h1>
<h1></h1>
<p>ServerRoot “C:/Program Files/Apache Software Foundation/Apache2.2”</p>
<h1></h1>
<h1>Listen: Allows you to bind Apache to specific IP addresses and/or</h1>
<h1>ports, instead of the default. See also the </h1>
<h1>directive.</h1>
<h1></h1>
<h1>Change this to Listen on specific IP addresses as shown below to</h1>
<h1>prevent Apache from glomming onto all bound IP addresses (0.0.0.0)</h1>
<h1></h1>
<p><span class="hashtag">#Listen</span> 12.34.56.78:80<br>
Listen 80</p>
<h1></h1>
<h1>Dynamic Shared Object (DSO) Support</h1>
<h1></h1>
<h1>To be able to use the functionality of a module which was built as a DSO you</h1>
<h1>have to place corresponding `LoadModule’ lines at this location so the</h1>
<h1>directives contained in it are actually available <em>before</em> they are used.</h1>
<h1>Statically compiled modules (those listed by `httpd -l’) do not need</h1>
<h1>to be loaded here.</h1>
<h1></h1>
<h1>Example:</h1>
<h1>LoadModule foo_module modules/mod_foo.so</h1>
<h1></h1>
<p>LoadModule actions_module modules/mod_actions.so<br>
LoadModule alias_module modules/mod_alias.so<br>
LoadModule asis_module modules/mod_asis.so<br>
LoadModule auth_basic_module modules/mod_auth_basic.so<br>
<span class="hashtag">#LoadModule</span> auth_digest_module modules/mod_auth_digest.so<br>
<span class="hashtag">#LoadModule</span> authn_anon_module modules/mod_authn_anon.so<br>
<span class="hashtag">#LoadModule</span> authn_dbm_module modules/mod_authn_dbm.so<br>
LoadModule authn_default_module modules/mod_authn_default.so<br>
LoadModule authn_file_module modules/mod_authn_file.so<br>
<span class="hashtag">#LoadModule</span> authz_dbm_module modules/mod_authz_dbm.so<br>
LoadModule authz_default_module modules/mod_authz_default.so<br>
LoadModule authz_groupfile_module modules/mod_authz_groupfile.so<br>
LoadModule authz_host_module modules/mod_authz_host.so<br>
LoadModule authz_user_module modules/mod_authz_user.so<br>
LoadModule autoindex_module modules/mod_autoindex.so<br>
<span class="hashtag">#LoadModule</span> cern_meta_module modules/mod_cern_meta.so<br>
LoadModule cgi_module modules/mod_cgi.so<br>
<span class="hashtag">#LoadModule</span> dav_module modules/mod_dav.so<br>
<span class="hashtag">#LoadModule</span> dav_fs_module modules/mod_dav_fs.so<br>
<span class="hashtag">#LoadModule</span> deflate_module modules/mod_deflate.so<br>
LoadModule dir_module modules/mod_dir.so<br>
LoadModule env_module modules/mod_env.so<br>
<span class="hashtag">#LoadModule</span> expires_module modules/mod_expires.so<br>
<span class="hashtag">#LoadModule</span> file_cache_module modules/mod_file_cache.so<br>
<span class="hashtag">#LoadModule</span> headers_module modules/mod_headers.so<br>
LoadModule imagemap_module modules/mod_imagemap.so<br>
LoadModule include_module modules/mod_include.so<br>
<span class="hashtag">#LoadModule</span> info_module modules/mod_info.so<br>
LoadModule isapi_module modules/mod_isapi.so<br>
LoadModule log_config_module modules/mod_log_config.so<br>
LoadModule mime_module modules/mod_mime.so<br>
<span class="hashtag">#LoadModule</span> mime_magic_module modules/mod_mime_magic.so<br>
<span class="hashtag">#LoadModule</span> proxy_module modules/mod_proxy.so<br>
<span class="hashtag">#LoadModule</span> proxy_ajp_module modules/mod_proxy_ajp.so<br>
<span class="hashtag">#LoadModule</span> proxy_balancer_module modules/mod_proxy_balancer.so<br>
<span class="hashtag">#LoadModule</span> proxy_connect_module modules/mod_proxy_connect.so<br>
<span class="hashtag">#LoadModule</span> proxy_http_module modules/mod_proxy_http.so<br>
<span class="hashtag">#LoadModule</span> proxy_ftp_module modules/mod_proxy_ftp.so<br>
LoadModule negotiation_module modules/mod_negotiation.so<br>
<span class="hashtag">#LoadModule</span> rewrite_module modules/mod_rewrite.so<br>
LoadModule setenvif_module modules/mod_setenvif.so<br>
<span class="hashtag">#LoadModule</span> speling_module modules/mod_speling.so<br>
<span class="hashtag">#LoadModule</span> status_module modules/mod_status.so<br>
<span class="hashtag">#LoadModule</span> unique_id_module modules/mod_unique_id.so<br>
LoadModule userdir_module modules/mod_userdir.so<br>
<span class="hashtag">#LoadModule</span> usertrack_module modules/mod_usertrack.so<br>
<span class="hashtag">#LoadModule</span> vhost_alias_module modules/mod_vhost_alias.so<br>
<span class="hashtag">#LoadModule</span> ssl_module modules/mod_ssl.so</p>
<h1>‘Main’ server configuration</h1>
<h1></h1>
<h1>The directives in this section set up the values used by the ‘main’</h1>
<h1>server, which responds to any requests that aren’t handled by a</h1>
<h1> definition.  These values also provide defaults for</h1>
<h1>any  containers you may define later in the file.</h1>
<h1></h1>
<h1>All of these directives may appear inside  containers,</h1>
<h1>in which case these default settings will be overridden for the</h1>
<h1>virtual host being defined.</h1>
<h1></h1>
<h1></h1>
<h1>ServerAdmin: Your address, where problems with the server should be</h1>
<h1>e-mailed.  This address appears on some server-generated pages, such</h1>
<h1>as error documents.  e.g. <a href="mailto:admin@your-domain.com">admin@your-domain.com</a>
</h1>
<h1></h1>
<p>ServerAdmin <a href="mailto:ilymsn34@hotmail.com">ilymsn34@hotmail.com</a></p>
<h1></h1>
<h1>ServerName gives the name and port that the server uses to identify itself.</h1>
<h1>This can often be determined automatically, but we recommend you specify</h1>
<h1>it explicitly to prevent problems during startup.</h1>
<h1></h1>
<h1>If your host doesn’t have a registered DNS name, enter its IP address here.</h1>
<h1></h1>
<p>ServerName <a href="http://ilymsn.50webs.com:80" rel="nofollow noopener">http://ilymsn.50webs.com:80</a></p>
<h1></h1>
<h1>DocumentRoot: The directory out of which you will serve your</h1>
<h1>documents. By default, all requests are taken from this directory, but</h1>
<h1>symbolic links and aliases may be used to point to other locations.</h1>
<h1></h1>
<p>DocumentRoot “C:/Documents and Settings/Jorge Urrunaga/Desktop/50webs”</p>
<h1></h1>
<h1>Each directory to which Apache has access can be configured with respect</h1>
<h1>to which services and features are allowed and/or disabled in that</h1>
<h1>directory (and its subdirectories).</h1>
<h1></h1>
<h1>First, we configure the “default” to be a very restrictive set of</h1>
<h1>features.</h1>
<h1></h1>

    Options FollowSymLinks
    AllowOverride All
    Order deny,allow
    Deny from all
    Satisfy all

<h1></h1>
<h1>Note that from this point forward you must specifically allow</h1>
<h1>particular features to be enabled - so if something’s not working as</h1>
<h1>you might expect, make sure that you have specifically enabled it</h1>
<h1>below.</h1>
<h1></h1>
<h1></h1>
<h1>This should be changed to whatever you set DocumentRoot to.</h1>
<h1></h1>
<p>&lt;Directory “C:/Documents and Settings/Jorge Urrunaga/Desktop/50webs”&gt;<br>
#<br>
# Possible values for the Options directive are “None”, “All”,<br>
# or any combination of:<br>
#   Indexes Includes FollowSymLinks SymLinksifOwnerMatch ExecCGI MultiViews<br>
#<br>
# Note that “MultiViews” must be named <em>explicitly</em> — “Options All”<br>
# doesn’t give it to you.<br>
#<br>
# The Options directive is both complicated and important.  Please see<br>
# <a href="http://httpd.apache.org/docs/2.2/mod/core.html#options" rel="nofollow noopener">http://httpd.apache.org/docs/2.2/mod/core.html#options</a><br>
# for more information.<br>
#<br>
Options Indexes FollowSymLinks</p>
<pre><code>#
# AllowOverride controls what directives may be placed in .htaccess files.
# It can be "All", "None", or any combination of the keywords:
#   Options FileInfo AuthConfig Limit
#
AllowOverride All

#
# Controls who can get stuff from this server.
#
Order allow,deny
Allow from all
</code></pre>

<h1></h1>
<h1>DirectoryIndex: sets the file that Apache will serve if a directory</h1>
<h1>is requested.</h1>
<h1></h1>

    DirectoryIndex index.html

<h1></h1>
<h1>The following lines prevent .htaccess and .htpasswd files from being</h1>
<h1>viewed by Web clients.</h1>
<h1></h1>
<p>&lt;FilesMatch “^.ht”&gt;<br>
Order allow,deny<br>
Deny from all<br>
</p>
<h1></h1>
<h1>ErrorLog: The location of the error log file.</h1>
<h1>If you do not specify an ErrorLog directive within a </h1>
<h1>container, error messages relating to that virtual host will be</h1>
<h1>logged here.  If you <em>do</em> define an error logfile for a </h1>
<h1>container, that host’s errors will be logged there and not here.</h1>
<h1></h1>
<p>ErrorLog logs/error.log</p>
<h1></h1>
<h1>LogLevel: Control the number of messages logged to the error_log.</h1>
<h1>Possible values include: debug, info, notice, warn, error, crit,</h1>
<h1>alert, emerg.</h1>
<h1></h1>
<p>LogLevel warn</p>

    #
    # The following directives define some format nicknames for use with
    # a CustomLog directive (see below).
    #
    LogFormat "%h %l %u %t \"%r\" %&gt;s %b \"%{Referer}i\" \"%{User-Agent}i\"" combined
    LogFormat "%h %l %u %t \"%r\" %&gt;s %b" common
<pre><code>&lt;IfModule logio_module&gt;
  # You need to enable mod_logio.c to use %I and %O
  LogFormat "%h %l %u %t \"%r\" %&gt;s %b \"%{Referer}i\" \"%{User-Agent}i\" %I %O" combinedio
&lt;/IfModule&gt;

#
# The location and format of the access logfile (Common Logfile Format).
# If you do not define any access logfiles within a &lt;VirtualHost&gt;
# container, they will be logged here.  Contrariwise, if you *do*
# define per-&lt;VirtualHost&gt; access logfiles, transactions will be
# logged therein and *not* in this file.
#
CustomLog logs/access.log common

#
# If you prefer a logfile with access, agent, and referer information
# (Combined Logfile Format) you can use the following directive.
#
#CustomLog logs/access.log combined
</code></pre>


    #
    # Redirect: Allows you to tell clients about documents that used to 
    # exist in your server's namespace, but do not anymore. The client 
    # will make a new request for the document at its new location.
    # Example:
    # Redirect permanent /foo http://http://ilymsn.50webs.com/bar
<pre><code>#
# Alias: Maps web paths into filesystem paths and is used to
# access content that does not live under the DocumentRoot.
# Example:
# Alias /webpath /full/filesystem/path
#
# If you include a trailing / on /webpath then the server will
# require it to be present in the URL.  You will also likely
# need to provide a &lt;Directory&gt; section to allow access to
# the filesystem path.

#
# ScriptAlias: This controls which directories contain server scripts. 
# ScriptAliases are essentially the same as Aliases, except that
# documents in the target directory are treated as applications and
# run by the server when requested rather than as documents sent to the
# client.  The same rules about trailing "/" apply to ScriptAlias
# directives as to Alias.
#
ScriptAlias /cgi-bin/ "C:/Program Files/Apache Software Foundation/Apache2.2/cgi-bin/"
</code></pre>

<h1></h1>
<h1>“C:/Program Files/Apache Software Foundation/Apache2.2/cgi-bin” should be changed to whatever your ScriptAliased</h1>
<h1>CGI directory exists, if you have that configured.</h1>
<h1></h1>
<p>&lt;Directory “C:/Program Files/Apache Software Foundation/Apache2.2/cgi-bin”&gt;<br>
AllowOverride None<br>
Options None<br>
Order allow,deny<br>
Allow from all<br>
</p>
<h1></h1>
<h1>Apache parses all CGI scripts for the shebang line by default.</h1>
<h1>This comment line, the first line of the script, consists of the symbols</h1>
<h1>pound (#) and exclamation (!) followed by the path of the program that</h1>
<h1>can execute this specific script.  For a perl script, with perl.exe in</h1>
<h1>the C:\Program Files\Perl directory, the shebang line should be:</h1>
<p>#!c:/program files/perl/perl</p>
<h1>Note you <em>must_not</em> indent the actual shebang line, and it must be the</h1>
<h1>first line of the file.  Of course, CGI processing must be enabled by</h1>
<h1>the appropriate ScriptAlias or Options ExecCGI directives for the files</h1>
<h1>or directory in question.</h1>
<h1></h1>
<h1>However, Apache on Windows allows either the Unix behavior above, or can</h1>
<h1>use the Registry to match files by extention.  The command to execute</h1>
<h1>a file of this type is retrieved from the registry by the same method as</h1>
<h1>the Windows Explorer would use to handle double-clicking on a file.</h1>
<h1>These script actions can be configured from the Windows Explorer View menu,</h1>
<h1>‘Folder Options’, and reviewing the ‘File Types’ tab.  Clicking the Edit</h1>
<h1>button allows you to modify the Actions, of which Apache 1.3 attempts to</h1>
<h1>perform the ‘Open’ Action, and failing that it will try the shebang line.</h1>
<h1>This behavior is subject to change in Apache release 2.0.</h1>
<h1></h1>
<h1>Each mechanism has it’s own specific security weaknesses, from the means</h1>
<h1>to run a program you didn’t intend the website owner to invoke, and the</h1>
<h1>best method is a matter of great debate.</h1>
<h1></h1>
<h1>To enable the this Windows specific behavior (and therefore -disable- the</h1>
<h1>equivilant Unix behavior), uncomment the following directive:</h1>
<h1></h1>
<p><span class="hashtag">#ScriptInterpreterSource</span> registry</p>
<h1></h1>
<h1>The directive above can be placed in individual  blocks or the</h1>
<h1>.htaccess file, with either the ‘registry’ (Windows behavior) or ‘script’</h1>
<h1>(Unix behavior) option, and will override this server default option.</h1>
<h1></h1>
<h1></h1>
<h1>DefaultType: the default MIME type the server will use for a document</h1>
<h1>if it cannot otherwise determine one, such as from filename extensions.</h1>
<h1>If your server contains mostly text or HTML documents, “text/plain” is</h1>
<h1>a good value.  If most of your content is binary, such as applications</h1>
<h1>or images, you may want to use “application/octet-stream” instead to</h1>
<h1>keep browsers from trying to display binary files as though they are</h1>
<h1>text.</h1>
<h1></h1>
<p>DefaultType text/plain</p>

    #
    # TypesConfig points to the file containing the list of mappings from
    # filename extension to MIME-type.
    #
    TypesConfig conf/mime.types
<pre><code>#
# AddType allows you to add to or override the MIME configuration
# file specified in TypesConfig for specific file types.
#
#AddType application/x-gzip .tgz
#
# AddEncoding allows you to have certain browsers uncompress
# information on the fly. Note: Not all browsers support this.
#
#AddEncoding x-compress .Z
#AddEncoding x-gzip .gz .tgz
#
# If the AddEncoding directives above are commented-out, then you
# probably should define those extensions to indicate media types:
#
AddType application/x-compress .Z
AddType application/x-gzip .gz .tgz

#
# AddHandler allows you to map certain file extensions to "handlers":
# actions unrelated to filetype. These can be either built into the server
# or added with the Action directive (see below)
#
# To use CGI scripts outside of ScriptAliased directories:
# (You will also need to add "ExecCGI" to the "Options" directive.)
#
#AddHandler cgi-script .cgi

# For type maps (negotiated resources):
#AddHandler type-map var

#
# Filters allow you to process content before it is sent to the client.
#
# To parse .shtml files for server-side includes (SSI):
# (You will also need to add "Includes" to the "Options" directive.)
#
#AddType text/html .shtml
#AddOutputFilter INCLUDES .shtml
</code></pre>

<h1></h1>
<h1>The mod_mime_magic module allows the server to use various hints from the</h1>
<h1>contents of the file itself to determine its type.  The MIMEMagicFile</h1>
<h1>directive tells the module where the hint definitions are located.</h1>
<h1></h1>
<p><span class="hashtag">#MIMEMagicFile</span> conf/magic</p>
<h1></h1>
<h1>Customizable error responses come in three flavors:</h1>
<h1>1) plain text 2) local redirects 3) external redirects</h1>
<h1></h1>
<h1>Some examples:</h1>
<p><span class="hashtag">#ErrorDocument</span> 500 “The server made a boo boo.”<br>
<span class="hashtag">#ErrorDocument</span> 404 /missing.html<br>
<span class="hashtag">#ErrorDocument</span> 404 “/cgi-bin/missing_handler.pl”<br>
<span class="hashtag">#ErrorDocument</span> 402 <a href="http://http" rel="nofollow noopener">http://http</a>://ilymsn.50webs.com/subscription_info.html</p>
<h1></h1>
<h1></h1>
<h1>EnableMMAP and EnableSendfile: On systems that support it,</h1>
<h1>memory-mapping or the sendfile syscall is used to deliver</h1>
<h1>files.  This usually improves server performance, but must</h1>
<h1>be turned off when serving from networked-mounted</h1>
<h1>filesystems or if support for these functions is otherwise</h1>
<h1>broken on your system.</h1>
<h1></h1>
<p><span class="hashtag">#EnableMMAP</span> off<br>
<span class="hashtag">#EnableSendfile</span> off</p>
<h1>Supplemental configuration</h1>
<h1></h1>
<h1>The configuration files in the conf/extra/ directory can be</h1>
<h1>included to add extra features or to modify the default configuration of</h1>
<h1>the server, or you may simply copy their contents here and change as</h1>
<h1>necessary.</h1>
<h1>Server-pool management (MPM specific)</h1>
<p><span class="hashtag">#Include</span> conf/extra/httpd-mpm.conf</p>
<h1>Multi-language error messages</h1>
<p><span class="hashtag">#Include</span> conf/extra/httpd-multilang-errordoc.conf</p>
<h1>Fancy directory listings</h1>
<p><span class="hashtag">#Include</span> conf/extra/httpd-autoindex.conf</p>
<h1>Language settings</h1>
<p><span class="hashtag">#Include</span> conf/extra/httpd-languages.conf</p>
<h1>User home directories</h1>
<p><span class="hashtag">#Include</span> conf/extra/httpd-userdir.conf</p>
<h1>Real-time info on requests and configuration</h1>
<p><span class="hashtag">#Include</span> conf/extra/httpd-info.conf</p>
<h1>Virtual hosts</h1>
<p><span class="hashtag">#Include</span> conf/extra/httpd-vhosts.conf</p>
<h1>Local access to the Apache HTTP Server Manual</h1>
<p><span class="hashtag">#Include</span> conf/extra/httpd-manual.conf</p>
<h1>Distributed authoring and versioning (WebDAV)</h1>
<p><span class="hashtag">#Include</span> conf/extra/httpd-dav.conf</p>
<h1>Various default settings</h1>
<p><span class="hashtag">#Include</span> conf/extra/httpd-default.conf</p>
<h1>Secure (SSL/TLS) connections</h1>
<p><span class="hashtag">#Include</span> conf/extra/httpd-ssl.conf</p>
<h1></h1>
<h1>Note: The following must must be present to support</h1>
<h1>starting without SSL on platforms with no /dev/random equivalent</h1>
<h1>but a statically compiled-in mod_ssl.</h1>
<h1></h1>

SSLRandomSeed startup builtin
SSLRandomSeed connect builtin

[/code]
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/apache/125976/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/apache/125976/3</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 22 Jul 2007 17:42:05 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-125976-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/apache/125976.rss">Apache</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Apache</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@N00b1 N00b1]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/n00b1">@N00b1</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>still don’t get why you cant upload images like that and anyway your images shouldn’t be that big use gif so they are smaller think about some one with shit internet</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/apache/125976/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/apache/125976/2</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 22 Jul 2007 15:24:15 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-125976-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/apache/125976.rss">Apache</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Apache</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Java_Is_My_Bitch Java Is My Bitch™]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/java_is_my_bitch">@Java_Is_My_Bitch</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Zomg apache is hard lol.</p>
<p>Anyways I’m got a website hosted, My friend is helping me learn HTML, hence his name h4x0r on the website.<br>
<a href="Http://ilymsn.50webs.com" rel="nofollow noopener">Http://ilymsn.50webs.com</a>.</p>
<p>Well Since i can’t upload the photos to the FTP because they are apparently “too big” 2.5mb to be exact. I had to use a third party hoster, <a href="http://Imageshack.us" rel="nofollow noopener">Imageshack.us</a>. I don’t have a problem with that, but i’m putting music on the website, something to relax people with, music always helps me think and relax. Well Since an .Mp3 file is obviously bigger than .bmp file, Uploading it to the FTP is a no no. So, i asked around, and they said use apache. Well i downloaded Xampp, and installed it. But what do i do now?!</p>
<p>Never knew website making was so hard lol…I guess it’s just me. Well if anyone can help with me this, i would greatly appreciate it. Thanks in advance!</p>
<p>How my folder is set up:</p>
<p><a href="http://imageshack.us" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener"><img src="http://img216.imageshack.us/img216/1279/50websdg3.png" alt width="" height=""></a></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/apache/125976/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/apache/125976/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 22 Jul 2007 09:37:25 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-125976-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/apache/125976.rss">Apache</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
