<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Donator Points</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/donator-points/447065</link>
    <description>Okay well I am stuck with something! I want my shop to cost donator points but I don&#39;t know how to make them cost donator points.. My points shop cost points which u can get from slayer, etc.. and all my points prices are in shopAssistant. so hard to explain how do I make them cost donator points not points? I dont know what file to put the donator point cost in since they points system and my donating system are completely different and they cant be in the same file. Example: You get points for slayer, donor points for donating. My points store costs run from shopassistant.java, my donor points shop costs run from ---.

Thats where im stuck, it is hard to explain but think of other server, they have voting point store and pk point stores, where do you put the vote point store costs and where do u put the pk point store costs

LOOOL i hope you understand! :)
Thanks.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 27 Jun 2012 08:22:04 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/donator-points/447065.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Donator Points</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@i_Ban_U i Ban U]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/i_ban_u">@i_Ban_U</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Okay well I am stuck with something! I want my shop to cost donator points but I don’t know how to make them cost donator points… My points shop cost points which u can get from slayer, etc… and all my points prices are in shopAssistant. so hard to explain how do I make them cost donator points not points? I dont know what file to put the donator point cost in since they points system and my donating system are completely different and they cant be in the same file. Example: You get points for slayer, donor points for donating. My points store costs run from shopassistant.java, my donor points shop costs run from —.</p>
<p>Thats where im stuck, it is hard to explain but think of other server, they have voting point store and pk point stores, where do you put the vote point store costs and where do u put the pk point store costs</p>
<p>LOOOL i hope you understand! <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=5" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"><br>
Thanks.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/donator-points/447065/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/donator-points/447065/1</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 27 Jun 2012 08:22:04 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-447065-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/donator-points/447065.rss">Donator Points</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
