<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Community</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/community/242558</link>
    <description>Hey, I started my server a little while ago and im having EXTREME trouble gaining a community. now at one point i had lots of people coming in and out trying out thing, and actually had a few active players :P. Yet now there is no1. I have one coder i managed to find who live&#39;s in africa and cant get on server so he just helps on forums. There a bunch of things I want to get accomplished. I want to come out with a v3 of my client, I want it working for all computer types, and a little more custom. So if anyone can help me out with that post.

2: My friend and I are working extremly hard to get money for a VPS. a beilve having that will help a ton with the community.
The problem there is, I havent had anyone stay on the server long enough to really like it, and donate even a little.

3: i would LOVE to have a web client. I found a couple of ASP hosting sites that would do it, but i dont know how to set it up on the site, or how to work any of the controls on the ASP hosting sites.

So i have a question. Should I try something ENTIRLY new with the server? diffrent source new beggining?

I appreciate any responses!</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2008 01:48:52 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/community/242558.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Community</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@jb_blaze jb blaze]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/jb_blaze">@jb_blaze</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Hey, I started my server a little while ago and im having EXTREME trouble gaining a community. now at one point i had lots of people coming in and out trying out thing, and actually had a few active players :P. Yet now there is no1. I have one coder i managed to find who live’s in africa and cant get on server so he just helps on forums. There a bunch of things I want to get accomplished. I want to come out with a v3 of my client, I want it working for all computer types, and a little more custom. So if anyone can help me out with that post.</p>
<p>2: My friend and I are working extremly hard to get money for a VPS. a beilve having that will help a ton with the community.<br>
The problem there is, I havent had anyone stay on the server long enough to really like it, and donate even a little.</p>
<p>3: i would LOVE to have a web client. I found a couple of ASP hosting sites that would do it, but i dont know how to set it up on the site, or how to work any of the controls on the ASP hosting sites.</p>
<p>So i have a question. Should I try something ENTIRLY new with the server? diffrent source new beggining?</p>
<p>I appreciate any responses!</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/community/242558/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/community/242558/1</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2008 01:48:52 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-242558-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/community/242558.rss">Community</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
