<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Servers owners: how do you advertise?</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/servers-owners-how-do-you-advertise/554835</link>
    <description>Or if you&#39;re a player, how do you play? How do you find cool servers and how do you connect and play them?

I&#39;ve been pretty out of touch with the rsps scene for several years now, from both of these perspectives. I&#39;m trying to get a feel for how people like to play servers nowadays, and what the owners like to encourage/allow.

For example, do you let players connect with an IP address or do you force them to use a webclient? Do they have to register on your website first? Do they have to actually download a client jar? What do you think of this as a player?

And how do you link together advertising with gameplay? For example, do you offer rewards for voting on a toplist and do you use any in-game mechanisms to provide these automatically? What other advertising and promotion mechanisms do you use?

Just stick your thoughts here or if you cba to type it&#39;d be cool if u could just fill in my mini survey - [url=https://www.surveymonkey.co.uk/r/QF7HQ7D]https://www.surveymonkey.co.uk/r/QF7HQ7D[/url] (bonus - leave your contact details to get some free advertising for your server)</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 25 Feb 2016 13:04:04 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/servers-owners-how-do-you-advertise/554835.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Servers owners: how do you advertise?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@xx_matty_xx Justin Bieber]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/xx_matty_xx">@xx_matty_xx</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Or if you’re a player, how do you play? How do you find cool servers and how do you connect and play them?</p>
<p>I’ve been pretty out of touch with the rsps scene for several years now, from both of these perspectives. I’m trying to get a feel for how people like to play servers nowadays, and what the owners like to encourage/allow.</p>
<p>For example, do you let players connect with an IP address or do you force them to use a webclient? Do they have to register on your website first? Do they have to actually download a client jar? What do you think of this as a player?</p>
<p>And how do you link together advertising with gameplay? For example, do you offer rewards for voting on a toplist and do you use any in-game mechanisms to provide these automatically? What other advertising and promotion mechanisms do you use?</p>
<p>Just stick your thoughts here or if you cba to type it’d be cool if u could just fill in my mini survey - <a href="https://www.surveymonkey.co.uk/r/QF7HQ7D" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">https://www.surveymonkey.co.uk/r/QF7HQ7D</a> (bonus - leave your contact details to get some free advertising for your server)</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/servers-owners-how-do-you-advertise/554835/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/servers-owners-how-do-you-advertise/554835/1</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 25 Feb 2016 13:04:04 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-554835-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/servers-owners-how-do-you-advertise/554835.rss">Servers owners: how do you advertise?</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
