<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>[REF]Clan chat and music sideicons not loading</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/ref-clan-chat-and-music-sideicons-not-loading/436938</link>
    <description>[s]I&#39;ve checked the method in the client class that grabs the sideicons from the cache and both the clan chat and music sprites are being loaded. I even checked the cache with a cache editor and the sprites were there. Also, I added the actually clan chat interface but I still cannot click on neither the music nor the clan chat tab. To test to see if they were even loading from the particular method I was looking at, I commented out the quest tab sideicon, and then logged in and it disappeared. I&#39;m not quite sure what my next approach on this should be, but apparently this is fixable because I&#39;ve seen other Refactored clients with the sideicons working (at least the clan chat). If anyone can help me I&#39;d be very thankful.[/s]

[b]Edit: [/b]I fixed the problem by adding the interface loading server sided. Took me 2 hours to find out how to successful load new sideicons, but hey, when I have to do it again I&#39;ll be all set.  ;D</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 20 Mar 2012 02:57:45 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Game Development</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/ref-clan-chat-and-music-sideicons-not-loading/436938.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>[REF]Clan chat and music sideicons not loading</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Tutorial Tutorial]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/tutorial">@Tutorial</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p><span class="bbcode-s">I’ve checked the method in the client class that grabs the sideicons from the cache and both the clan chat and music sprites are being loaded. I even checked the cache with a cache editor and the sprites were there. Also, I added the actually clan chat interface but I still cannot click on neither the music nor the clan chat tab. To test to see if they were even loading from the particular method I was looking at, I commented out the quest tab sideicon, and then logged in and it disappeared. I’m not quite sure what my next approach on this should be, but apparently this is fixable because I’ve seen other Refactored clients with the sideicons working (at least the clan chat). If anyone can help me I’d be very thankful.</span></p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Edit: </span>I fixed the problem by adding the interface loading server sided. Took me 2 hours to find out how to successful load new sideicons, but hey, when I have to do it again I’ll be all set.  ;D</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/ref-clan-chat-and-music-sideicons-not-loading/436938/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/ref-clan-chat-and-music-sideicons-not-loading/436938/1</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 20 Mar 2012 02:57:45 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-436938-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/ref-clan-chat-and-music-sideicons-not-loading/436938.rss">[REF]Clan chat and music sideicons not loading</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
