<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Legends of Turmoil</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/legends-of-turmoil/553923</link>
    <description>Legends of Turmoil is an up and coming server created about a week ago.
I do not have readily available screenshots as I am currently on a work computer, I apologize for this.
The site can be accessed at http://www.legendsofturmoil.com
We have many preview videos and user created videos showcasing the server. These can be viewed on our forums under the Videos section.



We have 0 lag, Regular updates based on forums polls, High Scores list, Everything is fully functioning (Except Construction. Admins will give you 99 in this once you achieve 99 in all other skills), Friendly staff, 100% Uptime, Gambling, Great vote rewards, 5x XP rates (30% bonus for two hours with Well of Good Fortune running), Occasional Double XP Weekend (Starts Tomorrow!), And much more.

We have a fully stocked starter area complete with custom stalls for theiving/money making, Vote rewards, Pk/PvM gear, Grand exchange, Gambling area, and altars for prayer as well as curses and the different magic books.


We have a special magic tab for teleports to Home, Skilling, Training, All Dungeons, Bosses, Minigames, and Deep Wilderness.

All areas are fully functioning, including minigames.

All skill training areas can also be accessed by clicking the skill you wish to train. These areas have a bank and vendor for the specified skill for quick and painless leveling.



We also a Prestige store for players who have reached maximum XP in a skill as an incentive for resetting. (Does not REQUIRE maximum XP to prestige, only 99)



Our donor area comes with donor gear vendors, donor only training portal, druid shop with herbs/overloads, special trees, grand exchange, Non-wildy frost dragon teleport, stat boosting altar, kingly imps, rune armor thieving stall for extra moneymaking, and a bank. 



There is much, much more but I am trying to keep this short and sweet. Check it out, you&#39;ve got nothing to lose. Staff and regular&#39;s are some of the nicest around and are always willing to help out in any way. If you have trouble finding anything or need any other help, just join the &quot;Help&quot; FC and ask away.

I will also be regularly checking this post and answering any questions you may have.

[i][b]Please remember we are newly created and therefore have a small player-base. We have just started to advertise and hope to increase this rapidly within the next week.[/b][/i]

Thank you and I hope you enjoy the server.

                                                                                          - Addy Issues.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 23 Nov 2015 17:07:02 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/legends-of-turmoil/553923.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Legends of Turmoil</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@AddyIssues AddyIssues]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/addyissues">@AddyIssues</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Legends of Turmoil is an up and coming server created about a week ago.<br>
I do not have readily available screenshots as I am currently on a work computer, I apologize for this.<br>
The site can be accessed at <a href="http://www.legendsofturmoil.com" rel="nofollow noopener">http://www.legendsofturmoil.com</a><br>
We have many preview videos and user created videos showcasing the server. These can be viewed on our forums under the Videos section.</p>
<p>We have 0 lag, Regular updates based on forums polls, High Scores list, Everything is fully functioning (Except Construction. Admins will give you 99 in this once you achieve 99 in all other skills), Friendly staff, 100% Uptime, Gambling, Great vote rewards, 5x XP rates (30% bonus for two hours with Well of Good Fortune running), Occasional Double XP Weekend (Starts Tomorrow!), And much more.</p>
<p>We have a fully stocked starter area complete with custom stalls for theiving/money making, Vote rewards, Pk/PvM gear, Grand exchange, Gambling area, and altars for prayer as well as curses and the different magic books.</p>
<p>We have a special magic tab for teleports to Home, Skilling, Training, All Dungeons, Bosses, Minigames, and Deep Wilderness.</p>
<p>All areas are fully functioning, including minigames.</p>
<p>All skill training areas can also be accessed by clicking the skill you wish to train. These areas have a bank and vendor for the specified skill for quick and painless leveling.</p>
<p>We also a Prestige store for players who have reached maximum XP in a skill as an incentive for resetting. (Does not REQUIRE maximum XP to prestige, only 99)</p>
<p>Our donor area comes with donor gear vendors, donor only training portal, druid shop with herbs/overloads, special trees, grand exchange, Non-wildy frost dragon teleport, stat boosting altar, kingly imps, rune armor thieving stall for extra moneymaking, and a bank.</p>
<p>There is much, much more but I am trying to keep this short and sweet. Check it out, you’ve got nothing to lose. Staff and regular’s are some of the nicest around and are always willing to help out in any way. If you have trouble finding anything or need any other help, just join the “Help” FC and ask away.</p>
<p>I will also be regularly checking this post and answering any questions you may have.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-i"><span class="bbcode-b">Please remember we are newly created and therefore have a small player-base. We have just started to advertise and hope to increase this rapidly within the next week.</span></span></p>
<p>Thank you and I hope you enjoy the server.</p>
<pre><code>                                                                                      - Addy Issues.</code></pre>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/legends-of-turmoil/553923/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/legends-of-turmoil/553923/1</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 23 Nov 2015 17:07:02 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-553923-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/legends-of-turmoil/553923.rss">Legends of Turmoil</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
