<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Please read this. As its important</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/please-read-this-as-its-important/106097</link>
    <description>Ok, tbh...I don&#39;t think that saying it is the wrong section, then giving them the answer will help stop them from posting in the wrong section. It won&#39;t stop them from posting in the wrong section...so, this needs to be stopped. Just don&#39;t post anything at all if it is the wrong section or say it is the wrong section for the topic. If someone already says it, then you don&#39;t need to say anything further. That&#39;s just my idea on what may help to stop people from posting the wrong section, thanks.

~J~

p.s. I wasn&#39;t sure where to put this, but I thought that putting it in the &quot;development&quot; section would be the best, as these forums need to develop. ;)</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 05 Jun 2007 04:41:18 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/please-read-this-as-its-important/106097.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Please read this. As its important</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Rudolph Rudolph]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/rudolph">@Rudolph</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Ok, tbh…I don’t think that saying it is the wrong section, then giving them the answer will help stop them from posting in the wrong section. It won’t stop them from posting in the wrong section…so, this needs to be stopped. Just don’t post anything at all if it is the wrong section or say it is the wrong section for the topic. If someone already says it, then you don’t need to say anything further. That’s just my idea on what may help to stop people from posting the wrong section, thanks.</p>
<p>~J~</p>
<p>p.s. I wasn’t sure where to put this, but I thought that putting it in the “development” section would be the best, as these forums need to develop. <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/wink.png?v=6" title=":wink:" class="emoji" alt=":wink:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/please-read-this-as-its-important/106097/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/please-read-this-as-its-important/106097/1</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 05 Jun 2007 04:41:18 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-106097-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/please-read-this-as-its-important/106097.rss">Please read this. As its important</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
