<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>[TUT]How to Auto Using Scar/SRL</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/tut-how-to-auto-using-scar-srl/92903</link>
    <description>[b]How to Auto Using Scar/SRL

by WhoCares357[/b]

In this tutorial, I will teach you how to auto (macro) using Scar. I will further this by teaching you how to setup a script that uses SRL.
To describe Scar in a few sentences: Scar is a program used by lazy RuneScape players. Scar is a compiler that looks for a color in RuneScape and acts upon that (Clicks it or Waits etc.). Each color has a number. You have to tell Scar which numbers (colors) to look for.

First of all, you will need to get Scar 2.03 (or later version) at [url=http://www.dylock.net/scar]www.dylock.net/scar[/url]. 
Once you install Scar and open it, the program will prompt you with an option to download includes. Say yes and wait a bit (minute or two on dial-up) for Scar to download the includes.
Now I and you will take a closer look at all those buttons in Scar mean.

You will first see something like this:
[img]http://i125.photobucket.com/albums/p43/andrey0ll/ScarMain.jpg[/img]

First think you should notice are two text boxes. The top one looks like this:
[img]http://i125.photobucket.com/albums/p43/andrey0ll/Script.jpg[/img]
This is the main text box. This is where you will fill in all you options for the script before starting it.

The smaller text area is called the Debug Box:
[img]http://i125.photobucket.com/albums/p43/andrey0ll/Info.jpg[/img]
This is where all the information about the autoing will be. After you stop the script or it stops itself, check down there. You will most likely see a bunch of information about the autoing session. It will be made up of information like the amount of time the script has run, how many randoms it has seen, and other such information.

Next you will see two toolbars.

The first one should look familiar to you:

[img]http://i125.photobucket.com/albums/p43/andrey0ll/TopToolbar.jpg[/img]

This is where you can Exit, Save, Load, and perform other such actions. There are also some options there for scripters. You shouldn’t worry about that.

If you accidentally canceled the Download Includes prompt or if the prompt didn’t show, you can do download the includes manually. 
Go to File-Download Includes. You will see this:
 [img]http://i125.photobucket.com/albums/p43/andrey0ll/DownloadIncludes.jpg[/img]

Just press Overwrite and wait until Scar downloads all the files.

One more thing you should check in the toolbar is Silent Mouse. RuneScape can detect Silent Mouse so you should make sure it’s unchecked. To do this, go to Tools. Make sure that Silent Mouse does not have a check next to it. If it does, click on Silent Mouse and it will get unchecked.

The next toolbar will look like this:

[img]http://i125.photobucket.com/albums/p43/andrey0ll/MainToolbar.jpg[/img]

You will use this toolbar more than the top one. I will describe each button individually:

[img]http://i125.photobucket.com/albums/p43/andrey0ll/EditingButtons.jpg[/img]

Those are the shortcuts to the options from File in the top toolbar. 
The first button will clear the top text box. 
The next button is used to open a .scar or .txt file (a script).
The third button is Open From Web. The creators of Scar created a few extra scripts that they allow you to use. I do not recommend using these, for they are pretty old. Press Open From Web, wait for the list to load, and press on the script you want. It will take a little while to download the script.
The fourth button will save the script.
The fifth button cuts the highlighted text. (you can paste it after you cut it)
The sixth button copies the highlighted text.
The seventh button pastes the already copied or cut text.
The eighth button searches for a word or phrase in the script.

These first buttons are simple. You should know most of them from other app’s you used before.

The next few buttons look like this:

[img]http://i125.photobucket.com/albums/p43/andrey0ll/RunPauseStop.jpg[/img]

These buttons are used to run, pause, or stop the script. You should memorize the shortcut keys for these three. 

Run: ctrl+alt+r  (start script)
Pause: ctrl+alt+a (pause)
Stop: ctrl+alt+s (stop)

Don’t worry about the next two buttons:

[img]http://i125.photobucket.com/albums/p43/andrey0ll/Skip.jpg[/img]

They are useless unless you’re a scripter.

The next button is very important:

[img]http://i125.photobucket.com/albums/p43/andrey0ll/ColorPicker.jpg[/img]

This is called the Color Picker. It’s shortcut is ctrl+alt+p. Remember how I said that Scar uses color numbers to work? This is how you find the color of a rock or tree or whatever the script options ask for:

Click the Color Picker or press ctrl+alt+p.
Click on the color you want to get the number of. (click the rock or tree etc.)
Look in the Debug Box; (lower text box) You will see something like:
[code]Color Picked: 16777215 at (206, 310)[/code]
The first big number (1677…) is the color number. (206, 310) are the coordinates at which you picked the color.

The next button is not very important:

[img]http://i125.photobucket.com/albums/p43/andrey0ll/ClearDebug.jpg[/img]

This button simple clears the Debug Box.

The Toggle Report button is next:

[img]http://i125.photobucket.com/albums/p43/andrey0ll/ToggleReport.jpg[/img]

This button adds a new text area to the Debug Box. (lower text box)
If you click it, you will see this:

[img]http://i125.photobucket.com/albums/p43/andrey0ll/ScarMainWithReport.jpg[/img]

Notice the Debug Box is split in two at the bottom. To undo this, just click the button again.

The next button is the News button:

[img]http://i125.photobucket.com/albums/p43/andrey0ll/News.jpg[/img]

All this button does is fill the Debug Box with the “News” about Scar. This appears automatically when you first open Scar.

This next button is the most important of them all. It will also require a little more explanation:

[img]http://i125.photobucket.com/albums/p43/andrey0ll/IDWindow.jpg[/img]

You cannot simply click this button. You must drag it over to the RuneScape window and let go of the mouse button. You should see a square enclose RuneScape. You MUST do this every time you open up Scar to auto. If you don’t care about the how and why, skip this next part.

The reason you “enclose” Scar with the box is to make Scar see the RuneScape window as the whole screen. You see, Scar uses coordinates to click. It finds the color at a coordinate and clicks the coordinate. This becomes a problem when the RuneScape window appears in different locations on the screen. (if you’re using a client like SwiftSwitch to play RuneScape, Runescape is on the left of the screen while if you use Internet Explorer, it appears in the center) To fix this problem, the creators of Scar made Scar only see the RuneScape window. This guarantees that Scar will not miss-click. 

Now that you have all those buttons down, let’s look at the way we set options.

Try searching [url=http://www.sythe.org]www.sythe.org[/url] or [url=http://www.srl-forums.com]www.srl-forums.com[/url] for some free scripts. I recommend finding one that uses SRL. Check for something like {.include SRL\SRL.scar} in the beginning of the script to see if it uses SRL.

You can download and install the SRL include from [url=http://www.srl-forums.com]www.srl-forums.com[/url]. A guide to do this can be found at [url=http://www.sythe.org/showthread.php?t=148512]http://www.sythe.org/showthread.php?t=148512[/url].

Once you open a script, you should see something like program Name;. This is the name of the script. Don’t touch that part. Next, you will see lots of green stuff. These are comments left by the author of the script (creator). They will provide you with information about the script. (version, author, etc.)

Look down until you find a bolded black word, const. This is the first part of the options. Under/beside the word const will be something like this:

[code]const
Type = &#39;&#39;;//What to type
MonsterColor = ;//Color of monster
Eat = ;//Eat? true = eat, false = not eat[/code]

These are options. Yours will depend on the kind of script you use, and the amount of options the creator of the script set. There are four types of options: 

The first (Type in example) is a string. This kind of options is used to set what you want to use for text (auto-typing). You must set what you want to type between the &#39;&#39;. So in my example, I would put:

[code]const
Type = &#39;I hungry.&#39;;//What to type[/code]

The next type of option is called an integer (MonsterColor). This type of option is used for numbers. In this example, I have to set the color number of the monster I want the script to kill. Use the color picker to pick the color of the monster and paste the color after the = sign.

[code]const
Type = &#39;I hungry.&#39;;//What to type
MonsterColor =6734524342;//Color of monster[/code]

The final type of option is called a boolean. This type of option has two choices: true, false. In my example, I used Eat as a boolean option. The user (you) would have to put in true if you want the script to eat the food or false if you do not want the script to eat.

[code]const
Type = &#39;I hungry.&#39;;//What to type
MonsterColor =6734524342;//Color of monster
Eat = true;//Eat? true = eat, false = not eat[/code]

You must always remember to look at the name of the option (Type) or the comment next to it (//What to type) for clues on what the option is asking you.

Remember this very important piece of information! If you set a color number for something in one world and go to another world, you must pick the color again. RuneScape changes the colors with a new world.

Now I will teach you how to setup a script that uses SRL. Scroll down in the script a little until you find something like this:

[code] procedure DeclarePlayers;
begin
     HowManyPlayers := 2; //Amount of Players you will use

     CurrentPlayer := StartPlayer;
     NumberOfPlayers(HowManyPlayers);

     Players[0].Name    :=&#39;Username&#39;; //Your username
     Players[0].Pass    :=&#39;Password&#39;; //Your Password
     Players[0].Nick    :=&#39;sern&#39;;  // 3-4 letters from your name, NO CAPITALS (that includes the first character)
     Players[0].Loc   :=&#39;Fally&#39;;  //Don’t worry about this one (Don’t touch it)
     Players[0].Active  := True;  //Will you use this player?

     Players[1].Name    :=&#39;Username&#39;;
     Players[1].Pass    :=&#39;Password&#39;;
     Players[1].Nick    :=&#39;sern&#39;;
     Players[1].Loc     :=&#39;Fally&#39;;
     Players[1].Active := True;
end;[/code]

This is pretty simple. These are the things you need to change: 

HowManyPlayers: How many players will you use? Put the number after :=.

You must set options for each player.  Set the Username and Password. The “Nick” is used for randoms. Instead of looking for the whole random, it will see if it finds the random calling out your name. For this option, set 3-4 letters of your Username. Do not put a capital letter.

The next option is Location. Do not touch this one. Most scripts won’t even have this. Finally, there is the option Active. This just tells Scar if the character is going to participate in this autoing session. (True = will work; False = will not work)

After you set all the options and ID the Window (Drag the CrossHair over RuneScape) press Run (ctrl+alt+r). Remember that to stop you must press ctrl+alt+s. (to pause ctrl+alt+a)

Have fun cheating.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 12 May 2007 07:53:13 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/tut-how-to-auto-using-scar-srl/92903.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>[TUT]How to Auto Using Scar/SRL</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@WhoCares357 WhoCares357]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/whocares357">@WhoCares357</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[b]How to Auto Using Scar/SRL</p>
<p>by WhoCares357[/b]</p>
<p>In this tutorial, I will teach you how to auto (macro) using Scar. I will further this by teaching you how to setup a script that uses SRL.<br>
To describe Scar in a few sentences: Scar is a program used by lazy RuneScape players. Scar is a compiler that looks for a color in RuneScape and acts upon that (Clicks it or Waits etc.). Each color has a number. You have to tell Scar which numbers (colors) to look for.</p>
<p>First of all, you will need to get Scar 2.03 (or later version) at <a href="http://www.dylock.net/scar" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">www.dylock.net/scar</a>.<br>
Once you install Scar and open it, the program will prompt you with an option to download includes. Say yes and wait a bit (minute or two on dial-up) for Scar to download the includes.<br>
Now I and you will take a closer look at all those buttons in Scar mean.</p>
<p>You will first see something like this:<br>
<div class="lightbox-wrapper"><a class="lightbox" href="http://i125.photobucket.com/albums/p43/andrey0ll/ScarMain.jpg" title="ScarMain.jpg" rel="nofollow noopener"><img src="http://i125.photobucket.com/albums/p43/andrey0ll/ScarMain.jpg" alt width="575" height="500"><div class="meta">
<svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-far-image svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#far-image"></use></svg><span class="filename">ScarMain.jpg</span><span class="informations">640×556</span><svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-discourse-expand svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#discourse-expand"></use></svg>
</div></a></div></p>
<p>First think you should notice are two text boxes. The top one looks like this:<br>
<img src="http://i125.photobucket.com/albums/p43/andrey0ll/Script.jpg" alt width="640" height="320"><br>
This is the main text box. This is where you will fill in all you options for the script before starting it.</p>
<p>The smaller text area is called the Debug Box:<br>
<img src="http://i125.photobucket.com/albums/p43/andrey0ll/Info.jpg" alt width="481" height="149"><br>
This is where all the information about the autoing will be. After you stop the script or it stops itself, check down there. You will most likely see a bunch of information about the autoing session. It will be made up of information like the amount of time the script has run, how many randoms it has seen, and other such information.</p>
<p>Next you will see two toolbars.</p>
<p>The first one should look familiar to you:</p>
<p><img src="http://i125.photobucket.com/albums/p43/andrey0ll/TopToolbar.jpg" alt width="629" height="22"></p>
<p>This is where you can Exit, Save, Load, and perform other such actions. There are also some options there for scripters. You shouldn’t worry about that.</p>
<p>If you accidentally canceled the Download Includes prompt or if the prompt didn’t show, you can do download the includes manually.<br>
Go to File-Download Includes. You will see this:<br>
<img src="http://i125.photobucket.com/albums/p43/andrey0ll/DownloadIncludes.jpg" alt width="263" height="265"></p>
<p>Just press Overwrite and wait until Scar downloads all the files.</p>
<p>One more thing you should check in the toolbar is Silent Mouse. RuneScape can detect Silent Mouse so you should make sure it’s unchecked. To do this, go to Tools. Make sure that Silent Mouse does not have a check next to it. If it does, click on Silent Mouse and it will get unchecked.</p>
<p>The next toolbar will look like this:</p>
<p><img src="http://i125.photobucket.com/albums/p43/andrey0ll/MainToolbar.jpg" alt width="633" height="25"></p>
<p>You will use this toolbar more than the top one. I will describe each button individually:</p>
<p><img src="http://i125.photobucket.com/albums/p43/andrey0ll/EditingButtons.jpg" alt width="193" height="24"></p>
<p>Those are the shortcuts to the options from File in the top toolbar.<br>
The first button will clear the top text box.<br>
The next button is used to open a .scar or .txt file (a script).<br>
The third button is Open From Web. The creators of Scar created a few extra scripts that they allow you to use. I do not recommend using these, for they are pretty old. Press Open From Web, wait for the list to load, and press on the script you want. It will take a little while to download the script.<br>
The fourth button will save the script.<br>
The fifth button cuts the highlighted text. (you can paste it after you cut it)<br>
The sixth button copies the highlighted text.<br>
The seventh button pastes the already copied or cut text.<br>
The eighth button searches for a word or phrase in the script.</p>
<p>These first buttons are simple. You should know most of them from other app’s you used before.</p>
<p>The next few buttons look like this:</p>
<p><img src="http://i125.photobucket.com/albums/p43/andrey0ll/RunPauseStop.jpg" alt width="73" height="28"></p>
<p>These buttons are used to run, pause, or stop the script. You should memorize the shortcut keys for these three.</p>
<p>Run: ctrl+alt+r  (start script)<br>
Pause: ctrl+alt+a (pause)<br>
Stop: ctrl+alt+s (stop)</p>
<p>Don’t worry about the next two buttons:</p>
<p><img src="http://i125.photobucket.com/albums/p43/andrey0ll/Skip.jpg" alt width="48" height="21"></p>
<p>They are useless unless you’re a scripter.</p>
<p>The next button is very important:</p>
<p><img src="http://i125.photobucket.com/albums/p43/andrey0ll/ColorPicker.jpg" alt width="27" height="26"></p>
<p>This is called the Color Picker. It’s shortcut is ctrl+alt+p. Remember how I said that Scar uses color numbers to work? This is how you find the color of a rock or tree or whatever the script options ask for:</p>
<p>Click the Color Picker or press ctrl+alt+p.<br>
Click on the color you want to get the number of. (click the rock or tree etc.)<br>
Look in the Debug Box; (lower text box) You will see something like:</p>
<pre><code class="lang-auto">Color Picked: 16777215 at (206, 310)</code></pre>
<p>The first big number (1677…) is the color number. (206, 310) are the coordinates at which you picked the color.</p>
<p>The next button is not very important:</p>
<p><img src="http://i125.photobucket.com/albums/p43/andrey0ll/ClearDebug.jpg" alt width="26" height="26"></p>
<p>This button simple clears the Debug Box.</p>
<p>The Toggle Report button is next:</p>
<p><img src="http://i125.photobucket.com/albums/p43/andrey0ll/ToggleReport.jpg" alt width="21" height="22"></p>
<p>This button adds a new text area to the Debug Box. (lower text box)<br>
If you click it, you will see this:</p>
<p><div class="lightbox-wrapper"><a class="lightbox" href="http://i125.photobucket.com/albums/p43/andrey0ll/ScarMainWithReport.jpg" title="ScarMainWithReport.jpg" rel="nofollow noopener"><img src="http://i125.photobucket.com/albums/p43/andrey0ll/ScarMainWithReport.jpg" alt width="575" height="500"><div class="meta">
<svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-far-image svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#far-image"></use></svg><span class="filename">ScarMainWithReport.jpg</span><span class="informations">640×556</span><svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-discourse-expand svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#discourse-expand"></use></svg>
</div></a></div></p>
<p>Notice the Debug Box is split in two at the bottom. To undo this, just click the button again.</p>
<p>The next button is the News button:</p>
<p><img src="http://i125.photobucket.com/albums/p43/andrey0ll/News.jpg" alt width="19" height="21"></p>
<p>All this button does is fill the Debug Box with the “News” about Scar. This appears automatically when you first open Scar.</p>
<p>This next button is the most important of them all. It will also require a little more explanation:</p>
<p><img src="http://i125.photobucket.com/albums/p43/andrey0ll/IDWindow.jpg" alt width="25" height="24"></p>
<p>You cannot simply click this button. You must drag it over to the RuneScape window and let go of the mouse button. You should see a square enclose RuneScape. You MUST do this every time you open up Scar to auto. If you don’t care about the how and why, skip this next part.</p>
<p>The reason you “enclose” Scar with the box is to make Scar see the RuneScape window as the whole screen. You see, Scar uses coordinates to click. It finds the color at a coordinate and clicks the coordinate. This becomes a problem when the RuneScape window appears in different locations on the screen. (if you’re using a client like SwiftSwitch to play RuneScape, Runescape is on the left of the screen while if you use Internet Explorer, it appears in the center) To fix this problem, the creators of Scar made Scar only see the RuneScape window. This guarantees that Scar will not miss-click.</p>
<p>Now that you have all those buttons down, let’s look at the way we set options.</p>
<p>Try searching <a href="http://www.sythe.org" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">www.sythe.org</a> or <a href="http://www.srl-forums.com" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">www.srl-forums.com</a> for some free scripts. I recommend finding one that uses SRL. Check for something like {.include SRL\SRL.scar} in the beginning of the script to see if it uses SRL.</p>
<p>You can download and install the SRL include from <a href="http://www.srl-forums.com" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">www.srl-forums.com</a>. A guide to do this can be found at <a href="http://www.sythe.org/showthread.php?t=148512" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">http://www.sythe.org/showthread.php?t=148512</a>.</p>
<p>Once you open a script, you should see something like program Name;. This is the name of the script. Don’t touch that part. Next, you will see lots of green stuff. These are comments left by the author of the script (creator). They will provide you with information about the script. (version, author, etc.)</p>
<p>Look down until you find a bolded black word, const. This is the first part of the options. Under/beside the word const will be something like this:</p>
<p><code>const
Type = '';//What to type
MonsterColor = ;//Color of monster
Eat = ;//Eat? true = eat, false = not eat</code></p>
<p>These are options. Yours will depend on the kind of script you use, and the amount of options the creator of the script set. There are four types of options:</p>
<p>The first (Type in example) is a string. This kind of options is used to set what you want to use for text (auto-typing). You must set what you want to type between the ‘’. So in my example, I would put:</p>
<p><code>const
Type = 'I hungry.';//What to type</code></p>
<p>The next type of option is called an integer (MonsterColor). This type of option is used for numbers. In this example, I have to set the color number of the monster I want the script to kill. Use the color picker to pick the color of the monster and paste the color after the = sign.</p>
<p><code>const
Type = 'I hungry.';//What to type
MonsterColor =6734524342;//Color of monster</code></p>
<p>The final type of option is called a boolean. This type of option has two choices: true, false. In my example, I used Eat as a boolean option. The user (you) would have to put in true if you want the script to eat the food or false if you do not want the script to eat.</p>
<p><code>const
Type = 'I hungry.';//What to type
MonsterColor =6734524342;//Color of monster
Eat = true;//Eat? true = eat, false = not eat</code></p>
<p>You must always remember to look at the name of the option (Type) or the comment next to it (//What to type) for clues on what the option is asking you.</p>
<p>Remember this very important piece of information! If you set a color number for something in one world and go to another world, you must pick the color again. RuneScape changes the colors with a new world.</p>
<p>Now I will teach you how to setup a script that uses SRL. Scroll down in the script a little until you find something like this:</p>
<p>[code] procedure DeclarePlayers;<br>
begin<br>
HowManyPlayers := 2; //Amount of Players you will use</p>
<pre><code> CurrentPlayer := StartPlayer;
 NumberOfPlayers(HowManyPlayers);

 Players[0].Name    :='Username'; //Your username
 Players[0].Pass    :='Password'; //Your Password
 Players[0].Nick    :='sern';  // 3-4 letters from your name, NO CAPITALS (that includes the first character)
 Players[0].Loc   :='Fally';  //Don’t worry about this one (Don’t touch it)
 Players[0].Active  := True;  //Will you use this player?

 Players[1].Name    :='Username';
 Players[1].Pass    :='Password';
 Players[1].Nick    :='sern';
 Players[1].Loc     :='Fally';
 Players[1].Active := True;
</code></pre>
<p>end;[/code]</p>
<p>This is pretty simple. These are the things you need to change:</p>
<p>HowManyPlayers: How many players will you use? Put the number after :=.</p>
<p>You must set options for each player.  Set the Username and Password. The “Nick” is used for randoms. Instead of looking for the whole random, it will see if it finds the random calling out your name. For this option, set 3-4 letters of your Username. Do not put a capital letter.</p>
<p>The next option is Location. Do not touch this one. Most scripts won’t even have this. Finally, there is the option Active. This just tells Scar if the character is going to participate in this autoing session. (True = will work; False = will not work)</p>
<p>After you set all the options and ID the Window (Drag the CrossHair over RuneScape) press Run (ctrl+alt+r). Remember that to stop you must press ctrl+alt+s. (to pause ctrl+alt+a)</p>
<p>Have fun cheating.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/tut-how-to-auto-using-scar-srl/92903/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/tut-how-to-auto-using-scar-srl/92903/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 12 May 2007 07:53:13 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-92903-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/tut-how-to-auto-using-scar-srl/92903.rss">[TUT]How to Auto Using Scar/SRL</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
