<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Getting Started running your very OWN RUNESCAPE PRIVATE SERVER! ULTIMATE GUIDE!</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/getting-started-running-your-very-own-runescape-private-server-ultimate-guide/407874</link>
    <description>[SIZE=6][B]Welcome guys to the very first tutorial and well basically everything you will need to know/need to run your very own Runescape Private Server. Okay well let&#39;s get started:[/B][/SIZE]

[SIZE=5][B]STEP 1: PROGRAMS[/B][/SIZE]

Programs/Stuff you may need if not installed or being used:

[SIZE=5][B]WinRAR:[/B][/SIZE]

[url=http://www.downloadvance.com/winrar/]http://www.downloadvance.com/winrar/[/url]

WinRAR is free to download and is used to unzip all the programs you download and will need.


[SIZE=5][B]Java SDK:[/B][/SIZE]

[url=http://www.oracle.com/technetwork/java/javase/downloads/index-jsp-138363.html]http://www.oracle.com/technetwork/java/javase/downloads/index-jsp-138363.html[/url]

That is to the direct link to the download, select your platform and install :D, Java is the language that Runescape is written in, language that we understand that the computer takes and converts it to what it understands and executes what we want it to do.


[SIZE=5][B]SOURCE AND CLIENT:[/B][/SIZE]

First off, you&#39;re going to need to have a client, and a source, so lets check out some websites that have these: (KEEP IN MIND YOU MAY NEED TO SIGN UP ON FORUMS)


[url=http://www.google.org/forums.php]http://www.google.org/forums.php[/url]


Once you find the Source and Client of the server you want proceed onto the next step in the tutorial :D, also if you are just beginning to run a server it is recommended that you find a Source and Client that is [PI] or Project Insanity.



[SIZE=5][B]You are going to need to have a bit of money in the case you are running a serious server so lets set up a paypal:[/B][/SIZE]

[url=https://www.paypal.com/]https://www.paypal.com/[/url]

Paypal is a safe place to make safe transactions with buying and selling.

We will use this for the portion of Donations so make sure you have the account set up to receive gifts.


[SIZE=5][B]VPS:[/B][/SIZE]

I would post a url but the forums restrict me for 4 urls only :\

VPS is (Virtual Private Server) that can be accessed from remote control on your computer basically it is used so that you can run your server on that Virtual Private Server 24/7 instead of hosting on your computer which you would have to leave on 24/7 o.o.

[SIZE=6][B]STEP 2: SETTING UP ENVIRONMENTAL VARIABLES[/B][/SIZE]

Alright now that we have downloaded what we need for running a server lets get our/your server ready for playing :D

Setting up Environmental Variables:

1. Now once you have downloaded Jave JDK SE you are going to need to set up environmental variables so that your computer knows where to find and use Java.

2. Let&#39;s do this by clicking START:

3. Once your in START click on COMPUTER:

4. and go into your C:DRIVE or Local Disk:

5. In that folder you may have to scroll down but go into PROGRAM FILES:

6. Once in that folder go into JAVA:

7. In the folder Java you will see Jdk 1.6.0_26 or whatever version you downloaded:

8. go into that and go into &quot;bin&quot; and right click on &quot;appletviewer&quot; the last option &quot;Properties&quot; select:

9. Now a new window will pop up the third information bar will be Location: C:\Program Files\Java\jdk1.6.0_26\bin 

10. COPY C:\Program Files\Java\jdk1.6.0_26\bin


11. Now go back into START:

12. RIGHT CLICK COMPUTER and select the option Properties:

13. On the LEFT select the option &quot;ADVANCED SYSTEM SETTINGS&quot;

14. A new window will pop up and on the bottom right select the option &quot;ENVIRONMENTAL VARIABLES&quot;

15. There will be two things User Variables for &quot;Your name&quot; and System Variables we will NOT BE TOUCHING SYSTEM VARIABLES:

16. In the User Variables Select New and name it PATH

17. the Variable Value will be this -  %JAVA_HOME%\bin

18. Click Okay and select New in User Variables again:

19. Name this one JAVA_HOME it is also essential for the name to be exactly like that: 

20. The Variable Value will be this  C:\Program Files\Java\jdk1.6.0_26\bin\

NOTE: THE 26 IS THE CURRENT JAVA RELEASE IF YOUR VERSION IS DIFFERENT PLEASE CHANGE THE 26 TO YOUR VERSION!

21. Select Okay and Okay to the next 2-3 windows and it will be saved :D

[SIZE=6][B]STEP 3: GETING ON YOUR VPS[/B][/SIZE]

1. Now that we have Java configured we can start our server :)

2. So go ahead and access your VPS by going into START and search &quot;Remote Desktop Connection&quot;

3. RUN the program and type in your username and password for your VPS:

4. Now that we are in our VPS we are ready to get going!
[SIZE=6][B]
STEP 4: GETTING THE SOURCE ON VPS[/B][/SIZE]

Here is where we get our server running on our VPS: 

1. Wherever you have saved your Source for your server go to that now and RIGHT CLICK it:

2. Select the option &quot;Add to archive&quot; and make it a ZIP select okay and it will take your Source and make a copy in WinRAR Format:

NOTE: THIS IS NEEDED FOR UPLOADING!

3. Once you have that complete go to:

[url=http://uppit.com/]http://uppit.com/[/url]

4. Browse: select the file Source in WinRAR Format and Upload!

5. Once you have uploaded it completely it will give you a link copy that link!

6. Now go back into your VPS open up Internet Explorer and paste that link into the Address Bar:

7. Download the file!

8. You now have the Source on your VPS and it is ready to run!
[SIZE=6][B]
STEP 5: GETTING YOUR SERVER UP AND RUNNING[/B][/SIZE]

1. In the Source on your VPS RIGHT CLICK Compiler and change the JDK version to your version 26 in the case you followed this guide.

2. Now that we have changed that LEFT CLICK Compiler and run it, once it has finished Compiling you will click any button to continue.

NOTE: YOU MUST COMPILE AFTER ANY CHANGES YOU MADE TO THE SERVER!

[SIZE=6][B]STEP 6: Hooking your Client up with your VPS![/B][/SIZE]

1. Run the Server on your VPS and go to your Client on your own desktop.

2. Open the client and go into GUI.JAVA and change the IP ADDRESS to your VPS.

3. Once you have changed it save and go into CLIENT.JAVA and search for &quot;127.0.0.1&quot; and change that to your VPS as well.

4. Change the Compiler in the Client to your version and Compile!

5. Run the Client and if you can log in your server is now up and running!


Now that you guys have your server up and running you can have some fun editing and adding to your server and Now I will teach you guys how to do that now!


[SIZE=5][B]MAKING YOURSELF AN OWNER![/B][/SIZE]

1. Log into your account on your server:

2. Log OUT

3. Go into your Source on your VPS from there go into DATA

4. CHARACTERS

5. And select your username and open it.

6. Make your Rights 3 instead of 0.

7. Save changes and log into your account

NOTE: YOU MUST BE LOGGED OUT TO MAKE CHANGES IN THE CHAR FILES!


[SIZE=5][B]CREATING AND EDITING OBJECTS![/B][/SIZE]

1. In DATA in your Source on your VPS go into &quot;OBJECTSIZE.JAVA&quot;  This is in DATA do not click in anything else once your in it.

2. Find the object your wishing to edit for example I will choose an altar the id of the object is &quot;409&quot;

NOTE: IF YOU ARE AN OWNER YOU MAY CLICK ON AN OBJECT AND IT WILL TELL YOU THE ID AND COORDS IN SOME CASES!

3. Now that you have found the object your willing to Edit or add go back from DATA and go into SRC

NOTE: SRC IS NOT IN DATA!

4. Now go into SERVER / WORLD

NOTE: WHEN I PUT A / THAT MEANS THAT WHATEVER COMES AFTER THE / IS INSIDE WHAT IS BEFORE THE /

5. Once in WORLD select &quot;objectmanager.java&quot; scroll down and you will find something that looks like this multiple times:

[code]c.getPA().checkObjectSpawn(7315, 2328, 3170, 1, 10);//Donor Portal Room[/code]

NOTES: Now I am going to explain what this is.

c.getPA() is getting the information .checkObjectSpawn is where it is getting the information from &quot;7315&quot; is the object ID, &quot;2328&quot; is the X COORD and &quot;3170&quot; the Y COORD, &quot;1&quot; is the direction in which the object will face and &quot;10&quot; will be the same in all. &quot;Donor Portal Room&quot; is just how I name things to keep it organized and if naming things to keep organized you must put a // before!

NEW CODE:

[code]c.getPA().checkObjectSpawn(409, 2328, 3170, 0, 10);//Altar[/code]

6. Now that you know how to add objects find an area you want the altar or object and do ::mypos take the coords and modify the coordinates in objectmanager.java 

EXAMPLE: I would change the 2238, 3170

NOTE: YOU CAN SEE WHAT THE OBJECT LOOKS LIKE IN GAME BY GOING OVER THE SPOT AND DOING ::object AND THEN THE ID THIS WILL PUT THE OBJECT IN-GAME IN THE DIRECTION &quot;0&quot;.

7. Compile your server and if players in-game do ::update 0 

NOTE: ::update WILL KICK ALL PLAYERS OFF SAFELY AND SAVE THEIR ACCOUNTS THE 0 IS THE TIMER, AND AFTER DO ::update YOU WILL NEED TO GO ON YOUR VPS AND EXIT THE SERVER AND RE-RUN THE SERVER IF YOU HAVE DONE THE OBJECT CORRECTLY YOU WILL SEE IT WHERE YOU PUT IT :D!

[SIZE=5][B]EXTENDING ON OBJECTS MAKING THEM HAVE ACTIONS![/B][/SIZE]

1. Remember the object ID and go into SRC / SERVER / MODEL / PLAYERS / Actionhandler.java

NOTE: THE / IS WHATEVER IS AFTER THE / IS WHAT IS IN WHATEVER IS BEFORE THE /

2. Search for movePlayer and you should see something like this

[code]case 70:
				c.getPA().movePlayer(2872, 5269, 2);
				c.sendMessage(&quot;You have entered Armadyl, To leave click the Pillar.&quot;);
				c.sendMessage(&quot;Note: Ruby bolts (e) and Diamond bolts (e) are recommended!&quot;);
			break;[/code]

the &quot;case 70&quot; is the object and the c.getPA().movePlayer is the command on moving the player to whatever is in the ()&#39;s the &quot;2872&quot; being the X COORD the &quot;5269&quot; being the Y COORD and the &quot;2&quot; being the height. Ignore the c.sendMessage this is an example and I used the God Wars dungeon.

NOTE: IF YOU WANT TO MAKE THE OBJECT TELEPORT THE PERSON INSTEAD OF JUST MOVING CHANGE IT TO SOMETHING LIKE THIS:

[code]case 5959:
			c.getPA().startTeleport2(2539, 4712, 0);
		break;[/code]

and it is the same thing as editing or adding the movePlayer except it is startTeleport and will have the animation of teleporting.

NOTE: IN SOME CASES THAT WILL CAUSE AN ERROR! IF IT DOES CHANGE IT TO .startTeleport(X, Y, H &quot;modern&quot;); AND IT SHOULD WORK FINE!

[SIZE=5][B]ADDING NPCS![/B][/SIZE]

1. Go into DATA like you did for the object ID&#39;s and go into npc.cfg and find the npc you wish to use for what you want!

NOTE: IF YOU ARE USING A MONSTER YOU MAY HAVE TO SET THE HP AND COMBAT LEVEL IF IT IS 0 TO MAKE IT ATTACKABLE!

2. In DATA select spawn-config.cfg and you will see something like this:

                       spawnX    spawnY   height      walk      maxhit      attack     defence      description    NOTE THIS IS FOR SHOWING YOU GUYS WHAT IT IS!

[code]spawn = 1294	3508	3240	0	0	0	0	0	Dungeon Shop[/code]

&quot;1294&quot; is the npc ID and note after the npc ID EVERYTHING YOU ARE GOING TO ADD WILL NEED A TAB BETWEEN IT! 3508 is the X COORD 3240 is the Y COORD then it will be like shown above height, walk, maxhit, attack, defence, and description.

3. Do ::mypos where you want the npc and make a new spawn for example i will use the npc 494 a banker:

[code]spawn = 494	3508	3240	0	0	0	0	0	Banker[/code]

4. Compile and do ::update 0 and close and re-run your server!

5. If you have done it correctly your npc should be right where you put it!

[SIZE=5][B]MAKING A NPC A SHOP![/B][/SIZE]

1. Now that you have an npc spawned go into DATA and go into shops.cfg You will see something like this:

[code]shop = 80	Donor Shop	2	2	10458	10	10460	10	10462	10	10464	10	10468	10	10466	10	10470	10[/code]

NOTE THIS IS NOT MY FULL SHOP BUT FOR AN EXAMPLE I CUT IT DOWN A BIT!

2. Make a new shop and make the shop = any # but one that has not been taken already, for this case I will use 100.

[code]shop = 100	New Shop	2	2	10458	10	10460	10	10462	10	10464	10	10468	10	10466	10	10470	10[/code]

3. &quot;New Shop&quot; is the name of your shop and make sure to give it a name!

4. the 2 and 2 is what the shop is so this 2 is buying only a 1 would be selling and buying.

5. next are the items 10458 is the item ID for example and 10 is the amount in which is in.

NOTE: YOU MUST HAVE A TAB AFTER THE shop = 100 or whatever number your shop is!

6. To find the item ID&#39;s you can go into item.cfg!

7. Once you have found all the ID&#39;s you want in the shop go into SRC / SERVER / MODEL / PLAYERS / Actionhandler.java

8. Once in actionhandler.java search for (10) and you should see something like this

[code]case 919:
				if (c.isDonator &gt;= 2) {
				c.getShops().openShop(10);
			} else {
				c.sendMessage(&quot;You must be at least a Super Donator to view this stop!&quot;);
				return;				
			};
			break;[/code]

this is a donator shop the case is the npc ID and if your making a shop that has no need for rights you will see something like this :

[code]case 919:
			c.getShops().openShop(10);
	break;[/code]

The &quot;case 919&quot; being the npc ID you were wanting to use and the c.getShops() being the getter or Accessor .openShop() being the command to open the shop and the number inside those () is the shop number.

So to open our shop 100 you would do something like this:

[code]case 919:
			c.getShops().openShop(100);
	break;[/code]

NOTE: YOU MUST PUT BREAK AFTER OR IT WILL CAUSE MANY ERRORS , THIS IS BECAUSE BREAK; IS MEANING THAT THIS CASE IS DONE EXECUTING.

9. Compiler do ::update 0 and close and re-run server :D

10. If do correctly when talking to npc it will open the shop and have the items you put in!

[SIZE=5][B]EXTENDING ON SHOPS[/B][/SIZE]

NOTE: IF YOU WANT TO ADD RIGHTS OR RESTRICTIONS ON SHOPS YOU WILL NEED TO ADD AN IF STATEMENT LIKE SO:

[code]case 919:
				if (c.isDonator &gt;= 2) {
				c.getShops().openShop(10);
			} else {
				c.sendMessage(&quot;You must be at least a Super Donator to view this stop!&quot;);
				return;				
			};
			break;[/code]

This is a donator shop like shown above it is stating that if isDonator is greater or equal to 2 then open shop, else if it is not send the message blah blah, this is useful for making a donor shop at home or an object such as a portal that you want to have restrictions on, it will cause curiosity in the players which makes them want to have donor :D

 

[SIZE=5][B]GIVING CUSTOM YELLS![/B][/SIZE]

1. Go into SRC / SERVER / MODEL / PLAYERS / PACKETS / COMMANDS.JAVA

2. Search for yell and you will see something like this:

[code]if (c.playerRights == 0){
								c2.sendMessage(&quot;&lt;col=255&gt;[Player]&lt;/col&gt;&quot;+ Misc.optimizeText(c.playerName) +&quot;: &quot;
												+ Misc.optimizeText(playerCommand.substring(5)) +&quot;&quot;);				

							}else if (c.playerRights == 1){
								c2.sendMessage(&quot;&lt;col=255&gt;[Mod]&lt;/col&gt;&lt;img=1&gt;&quot;+ Misc.optimizeText(c.playerName) +&quot;: &quot;
												+ Misc.optimizeText(playerCommand.substring(5)) +&quot;&quot;);

							}[/code]

Now this example shows both player and mod yells showing the player being the first if statement will be &quot;if&quot; the rest that follow will be &quot;else if&quot; you don&#39;t need to know anything about this except that &quot;col&quot; is the color of the yell [Player] is the title that comes before the player&#39;s name and in the mod yell it has &lt;img=1&gt; is the silver crown img=2 being gold.

3. Now for making your own custom yell if there is a command for Owners or Player Rights 3 delete it completely making sure you get everything!

4. Making your own Custom Yell will look something like this so you can add it right under one of these or the Admin yell:

[code]}else if (c.playerName.equalsIgnoreCase(&quot;ryan&quot;)){
								c2.sendMessage(&quot;&lt;shad=9440238&gt;[Owner]&lt;/col&gt;&lt;img=2&gt;&quot;+ Misc.optimizeText(c.playerName) +&quot;: &quot;
												+ Misc.optimizeText(playerCommand.substring(5)) +&quot;&quot;);

							}[/code]

Now this is the ignore case saying that if the playerName is ryan system send message in this color [Owner] and have a gold crown. This shad is purple btw and I prefer having shads because it has so much more life then col. :D

5. Once you have done this Compile do ::update 0 and close and re-run server and it should work!


[SIZE=6][B]THIS CONCLUDES YOUR BASICS ON RUNNING AND EDITING A SERVER ANY QUESTIONS FEEL FREE TO POST A COMMENT OR PM ME! I WILL BE MAKING AN ADVANCED GUIDE ON EDITING AND ADDING THINGS IN SO PLEASE MAKE SURE TO CHECK THAT OUT TOO![/B][/SIZE]</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 02 Aug 2011 19:41:53 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/getting-started-running-your-very-own-runescape-private-server-ultimate-guide/407874.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Getting Started running your very OWN RUNESCAPE PRIVATE SERVER! ULTIMATE GUIDE!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@davidi2 Davidi2]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/davidi2">@davidi2</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Your entire tutorial consists of links and large text. Nothing is really learned and what you do say is already on this site somewhere.</p>
<p>This does not constitute a real tutorial anyway.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/getting-started-running-your-very-own-runescape-private-server-ultimate-guide/407874/9">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/getting-started-running-your-very-own-runescape-private-server-ultimate-guide/407874/9</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 02 Aug 2011 19:41:53 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-407874-9</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/getting-started-running-your-very-own-runescape-private-server-ultimate-guide/407874.rss">Getting Started running your very OWN RUNESCAPE PRIVATE SERVER! ULTIMATE GUIDE!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Getting Started running your very OWN RUNESCAPE PRIVATE SERVER! ULTIMATE GUIDE!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@imsuperman05 imsuperman05]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/imsuperman05">@imsuperman05</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote quote-modified" data-post="7" data-topic="407874">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 Ryan ZigiScape:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>That is not for you to tell someone that is for the moderator to tell someone “Server Help” I am 100% sure that is where all “Server Help” goes but excuse me for my incorrect terms and “posts”.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p><a href="https://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php/board,51.0.html" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">https://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php/board,51.0.html</a></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/getting-started-running-your-very-own-runescape-private-server-ultimate-guide/407874/8">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/getting-started-running-your-very-own-runescape-private-server-ultimate-guide/407874/8</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 02 Aug 2011 18:35:57 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-407874-8</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/getting-started-running-your-very-own-runescape-private-server-ultimate-guide/407874.rss">Getting Started running your very OWN RUNESCAPE PRIVATE SERVER! ULTIMATE GUIDE!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Getting Started running your very OWN RUNESCAPE PRIVATE SERVER! ULTIMATE GUIDE!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Ryan_ZigiScape Ryan ZigiScape]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/ryan_zigiscape">@Ryan_ZigiScape</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>That is not for you to tell someone that is for the moderator to tell someone “Server Help” I am 100% sure that is where all “Server Help” goes but excuse me for my incorrect terms and “posts”.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/getting-started-running-your-very-own-runescape-private-server-ultimate-guide/407874/7">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/getting-started-running-your-very-own-runescape-private-server-ultimate-guide/407874/7</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 02 Aug 2011 18:34:10 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-407874-7</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/getting-started-running-your-very-own-runescape-private-server-ultimate-guide/407874.rss">Getting Started running your very OWN RUNESCAPE PRIVATE SERVER! ULTIMATE GUIDE!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Getting Started running your very OWN RUNESCAPE PRIVATE SERVER! ULTIMATE GUIDE!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@imsuperman05 imsuperman05]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/imsuperman05">@imsuperman05</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote quote-modified" data-post="5" data-topic="407874">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 Ryan ZigiScape:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Well let’s take a look, seing as I posted in “Server Help” I would prefer to think that I did post in the Server Help section and seeing as the sticky has no matter for showing what kind of post it is, because the person may look at the title and know exactly what this is. Also seeing as though this forums has a nice warm welcome from it’s players and community I will mark this forums as bad, you don’t know who you were communicating with.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Idc who are you.  Your not listening this is the wrong section.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/getting-started-running-your-very-own-runescape-private-server-ultimate-guide/407874/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/getting-started-running-your-very-own-runescape-private-server-ultimate-guide/407874/6</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 02 Aug 2011 18:31:20 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-407874-6</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/getting-started-running-your-very-own-runescape-private-server-ultimate-guide/407874.rss">Getting Started running your very OWN RUNESCAPE PRIVATE SERVER! ULTIMATE GUIDE!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Getting Started running your very OWN RUNESCAPE PRIVATE SERVER! ULTIMATE GUIDE!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Ryan_ZigiScape Ryan ZigiScape]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/ryan_zigiscape">@Ryan_ZigiScape</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Well let’s take a look, seing as I posted in “Server Help” I would prefer to think that I did post in the Server Help section and seeing as the sticky has no matter for showing what kind of post it is, because the person may look at the title and know exactly what this is. Also seeing as though this forums has a nice warm welcome from it’s players and community I will mark this forums as bad, you don’t know who you were communicating with.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/getting-started-running-your-very-own-runescape-private-server-ultimate-guide/407874/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/getting-started-running-your-very-own-runescape-private-server-ultimate-guide/407874/5</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 02 Aug 2011 18:29:52 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-407874-5</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/getting-started-running-your-very-own-runescape-private-server-ultimate-guide/407874.rss">Getting Started running your very OWN RUNESCAPE PRIVATE SERVER! ULTIMATE GUIDE!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Getting Started running your very OWN RUNESCAPE PRIVATE SERVER! ULTIMATE GUIDE!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@imsuperman05 imsuperman05]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/imsuperman05">@imsuperman05</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“Ryan ZigiScape, post:3, topic:407874”]If you’re not in the mood to post comments in restraint to control your problems or issues please re-direct yourself elsewhere.</p>
<p>Thanks for the help “senior member”[/quote][quote=“imsuperman05, post:2, topic:407874”]Looks horrible been done before.  Wrong section homey.[/quote]<br>
Is this the Server Help section?  Is there a sticky in the correct section explaining this?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/getting-started-running-your-very-own-runescape-private-server-ultimate-guide/407874/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/getting-started-running-your-very-own-runescape-private-server-ultimate-guide/407874/4</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 02 Aug 2011 18:25:18 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-407874-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/getting-started-running-your-very-own-runescape-private-server-ultimate-guide/407874.rss">Getting Started running your very OWN RUNESCAPE PRIVATE SERVER! ULTIMATE GUIDE!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Getting Started running your very OWN RUNESCAPE PRIVATE SERVER! ULTIMATE GUIDE!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Ryan_ZigiScape Ryan ZigiScape]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/ryan_zigiscape">@Ryan_ZigiScape</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>If you’re not in the mood to post comments in restraint to control your problems or issues please re-direct yourself elsewhere.</p>
<p>Thanks for the help “senior member”</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/getting-started-running-your-very-own-runescape-private-server-ultimate-guide/407874/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/getting-started-running-your-very-own-runescape-private-server-ultimate-guide/407874/3</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 02 Aug 2011 18:22:19 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-407874-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/getting-started-running-your-very-own-runescape-private-server-ultimate-guide/407874.rss">Getting Started running your very OWN RUNESCAPE PRIVATE SERVER! ULTIMATE GUIDE!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Getting Started running your very OWN RUNESCAPE PRIVATE SERVER! ULTIMATE GUIDE!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@imsuperman05 imsuperman05]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/imsuperman05">@imsuperman05</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Looks horrible been done before.  Wrong section homey.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/getting-started-running-your-very-own-runescape-private-server-ultimate-guide/407874/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/getting-started-running-your-very-own-runescape-private-server-ultimate-guide/407874/2</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 02 Aug 2011 18:20:18 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-407874-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/getting-started-running-your-very-own-runescape-private-server-ultimate-guide/407874.rss">Getting Started running your very OWN RUNESCAPE PRIVATE SERVER! ULTIMATE GUIDE!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Getting Started running your very OWN RUNESCAPE PRIVATE SERVER! ULTIMATE GUIDE!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Ryan_ZigiScape Ryan ZigiScape]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/ryan_zigiscape">@Ryan_ZigiScape</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[SIZE=6]<span class="bbcode-b">Welcome guys to the very first tutorial and well basically everything you will need to know/need to run your very own Runescape Private Server. Okay well let’s get started:</span>[/SIZE]</p>
<p>[SIZE=5]<span class="bbcode-b">STEP 1: PROGRAMS</span>[/SIZE]</p>
<p>Programs/Stuff you may need if not installed or being used:</p>
<p>[SIZE=5]<span class="bbcode-b">WinRAR:</span>[/SIZE]</p>
<p><a href="http://www.downloadvance.com/winrar/" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">http://www.downloadvance.com/winrar/</a></p>
<p>WinRAR is free to download and is used to unzip all the programs you download and will need.</p>
<p>[SIZE=5]<span class="bbcode-b">Java SDK:</span>[/SIZE]</p>
<p><a href="http://www.oracle.com/technetwork/java/javase/downloads/index-jsp-138363.html" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">http://www.oracle.com/technetwork/java/javase/downloads/index-jsp-138363.html</a></p>
<p>That is to the direct link to the download, select your platform and install :D, Java is the language that Runescape is written in, language that we understand that the computer takes and converts it to what it understands and executes what we want it to do.</p>
<p>[SIZE=5]<span class="bbcode-b">SOURCE AND CLIENT:</span>[/SIZE]</p>
<p>First off, you’re going to need to have a client, and a source, so lets check out some websites that have these: (KEEP IN MIND YOU MAY NEED TO SIGN UP ON FORUMS)</p>
<p><a href="http://www.google.org/forums.php" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">http://www.google.org/forums.php</a></p>
<p>Once you find the Source and Client of the server you want proceed onto the next step in the tutorial :D, also if you are just beginning to run a server it is recommended that you find a Source and Client that is [PI] or Project Insanity.</p>
<p>[SIZE=5]<span class="bbcode-b">You are going to need to have a bit of money in the case you are running a serious server so lets set up a paypal:</span>[/SIZE]</p>
<p><a href="https://www.paypal.com/" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">https://www.paypal.com/</a></p>
<p>Paypal is a safe place to make safe transactions with buying and selling.</p>
<p>We will use this for the portion of Donations so make sure you have the account set up to receive gifts.</p>
<p>[SIZE=5]<span class="bbcode-b">VPS:</span>[/SIZE]</p>
<p>I would post a url but the forums restrict me for 4 urls only :\</p>
<p>VPS is (Virtual Private Server) that can be accessed from remote control on your computer basically it is used so that you can run your server on that Virtual Private Server 24/7 instead of hosting on your computer which you would have to leave on 24/7 o.o.</p>
<p>[SIZE=6]<span class="bbcode-b">STEP 2: SETTING UP ENVIRONMENTAL VARIABLES</span>[/SIZE]</p>
<p>Alright now that we have downloaded what we need for running a server lets get our/your server ready for playing <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/smiley.png?v=5" title=":smiley:" class="emoji" alt=":smiley:"></p>
<p>Setting up Environmental Variables:</p>
<ol>
<li>
<p>Now once you have downloaded Jave JDK SE you are going to need to set up environmental variables so that your computer knows where to find and use Java.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Let’s do this by clicking START:</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Once your in START click on COMPUTER:</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>and go into your C:DRIVE or Local Disk:</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>In that folder you may have to scroll down but go into PROGRAM FILES:</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Once in that folder go into JAVA:</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>In the folder Java you will see Jdk 1.6.0_26 or whatever version you downloaded:</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>go into that and go into “bin” and right click on “appletviewer” the last option “Properties” select:</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Now a new window will pop up the third information bar will be Location: C:\Program Files\Java\jdk1.6.0_26\bin</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>COPY C:\Program Files\Java\jdk1.6.0_26\bin</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Now go back into START:</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>RIGHT CLICK COMPUTER and select the option Properties:</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>On the LEFT select the option “ADVANCED SYSTEM SETTINGS”</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>A new window will pop up and on the bottom right select the option “ENVIRONMENTAL VARIABLES”</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>There will be two things User Variables for “Your name” and System Variables we will NOT BE TOUCHING SYSTEM VARIABLES:</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>In the User Variables Select New and name it PATH</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>the Variable Value will be this -  %JAVA_HOME%\bin</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Click Okay and select New in User Variables again:</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Name this one JAVA_HOME it is also essential for the name to be exactly like that:</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>The Variable Value will be this  C:\Program Files\Java\jdk1.6.0_26\bin\</p>
</li>
</ol>
<p>NOTE: THE 26 IS THE CURRENT JAVA RELEASE IF YOUR VERSION IS DIFFERENT PLEASE CHANGE THE 26 TO YOUR VERSION!</p>
<ol start="21">
<li>Select Okay and Okay to the next 2-3 windows and it will be saved <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/smiley.png?v=5" title=":smiley:" class="emoji" alt=":smiley:">
</li>
</ol>
<p>[SIZE=6]<span class="bbcode-b">STEP 3: GETING ON YOUR VPS</span>[/SIZE]</p>
<ol>
<li>
<p>Now that we have Java configured we can start our server <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=5" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
</li>
<li>
<p>So go ahead and access your VPS by going into START and search “Remote Desktop Connection”</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>RUN the program and type in your username and password for your VPS:</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Now that we are in our VPS we are ready to get going!<br>
[SIZE=6]<span class="bbcode-b"><br>
STEP 4: GETTING THE SOURCE ON VPS</span>[/SIZE]</p>
</li>
</ol>
<p>Here is where we get our server running on our VPS:</p>
<ol>
<li>
<p>Wherever you have saved your Source for your server go to that now and RIGHT CLICK it:</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Select the option “Add to archive” and make it a ZIP select okay and it will take your Source and make a copy in WinRAR Format:</p>
</li>
</ol>
<p>NOTE: THIS IS NEEDED FOR UPLOADING!</p>
<ol start="3">
<li>Once you have that complete go to:</li>
</ol>
<p><a href="http://uppit.com/" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">http://uppit.com/</a></p>
<ol start="4">
<li>
<p>Browse: select the file Source in WinRAR Format and Upload!</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Once you have uploaded it completely it will give you a link copy that link!</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Now go back into your VPS open up Internet Explorer and paste that link into the Address Bar:</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Download the file!</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>You now have the Source on your VPS and it is ready to run!<br>
[SIZE=6]<span class="bbcode-b"><br>
STEP 5: GETTING YOUR SERVER UP AND RUNNING</span>[/SIZE]</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>In the Source on your VPS RIGHT CLICK Compiler and change the JDK version to your version 26 in the case you followed this guide.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Now that we have changed that LEFT CLICK Compiler and run it, once it has finished Compiling you will click any button to continue.</p>
</li>
</ol>
<p>NOTE: YOU MUST COMPILE AFTER ANY CHANGES YOU MADE TO THE SERVER!</p>
<p>[SIZE=6]<span class="bbcode-b">STEP 6: Hooking your Client up with your VPS!</span>[/SIZE]</p>
<ol>
<li>
<p>Run the Server on your VPS and go to your Client on your own desktop.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Open the client and go into GUI.JAVA and change the IP ADDRESS to your VPS.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Once you have changed it save and go into CLIENT.JAVA and search for “127.0.0.1” and change that to your VPS as well.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Change the Compiler in the Client to your version and Compile!</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Run the Client and if you can log in your server is now up and running!</p>
</li>
</ol>
<p>Now that you guys have your server up and running you can have some fun editing and adding to your server and Now I will teach you guys how to do that now!</p>
<p>[SIZE=5]<span class="bbcode-b">MAKING YOURSELF AN OWNER!</span>[/SIZE]</p>
<ol>
<li>
<p>Log into your account on your server:</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Log OUT</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Go into your Source on your VPS from there go into DATA</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>CHARACTERS</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>And select your username and open it.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Make your Rights 3 instead of 0.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Save changes and log into your account</p>
</li>
</ol>
<p>NOTE: YOU MUST BE LOGGED OUT TO MAKE CHANGES IN THE CHAR FILES!</p>
<p>[SIZE=5]<span class="bbcode-b">CREATING AND EDITING OBJECTS!</span>[/SIZE]</p>
<ol>
<li>
<p>In DATA in your Source on your VPS go into “OBJECTSIZE.JAVA”  This is in DATA do not click in anything else once your in it.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Find the object your wishing to edit for example I will choose an altar the id of the object is “409”</p>
</li>
</ol>
<p>NOTE: IF YOU ARE AN OWNER YOU MAY CLICK ON AN OBJECT AND IT WILL TELL YOU THE ID AND COORDS IN SOME CASES!</p>
<ol start="3">
<li>Now that you have found the object your willing to Edit or add go back from DATA and go into SRC</li>
</ol>
<p>NOTE: SRC IS NOT IN DATA!</p>
<ol start="4">
<li>Now go into SERVER / WORLD</li>
</ol>
<p>NOTE: WHEN I PUT A / THAT MEANS THAT WHATEVER COMES AFTER THE / IS INSIDE WHAT IS BEFORE THE /</p>
<ol start="5">
<li>Once in WORLD select “objectmanager.java” scroll down and you will find something that looks like this multiple times:</li>
</ol>
<pre><code class="lang-auto"></code></pre>
<p>NOTES: Now I am going to explain what this is.</p>
<p>c.getPA() is getting the information .checkObjectSpawn is where it is getting the information from “7315” is the object ID, “2328” is the X COORD and “3170” the Y COORD, “1” is the direction in which the object will face and “10” will be the same in all. “Donor Portal Room” is just how I name things to keep it organized and if naming things to keep organized you must put a // before!</p>
<p>NEW CODE:</p>
<pre><code class="lang-auto"></code></pre>
<ol start="6">
<li>Now that you know how to add objects find an area you want the altar or object and do ::mypos take the coords and modify the coordinates in objectmanager.java</li>
</ol>
<p>EXAMPLE: I would change the 2238, 3170</p>
<p>NOTE: YOU CAN SEE WHAT THE OBJECT LOOKS LIKE IN GAME BY GOING OVER THE SPOT AND DOING ::object AND THEN THE ID THIS WILL PUT THE OBJECT IN-GAME IN THE DIRECTION “0”.</p>
<ol start="7">
<li>Compile your server and if players in-game do ::update 0</li>
</ol>
<p>NOTE: ::update WILL KICK ALL PLAYERS OFF SAFELY AND SAVE THEIR ACCOUNTS THE 0 IS THE TIMER, AND AFTER DO ::update YOU WILL NEED TO GO ON YOUR VPS AND EXIT THE SERVER AND RE-RUN THE SERVER IF YOU HAVE DONE THE OBJECT CORRECTLY YOU WILL SEE IT WHERE YOU PUT IT :D!</p>
<p>[SIZE=5]<span class="bbcode-b">EXTENDING ON OBJECTS MAKING THEM HAVE ACTIONS!</span>[/SIZE]</p>
<ol>
<li>Remember the object ID and go into SRC / SERVER / MODEL / PLAYERS / Actionhandler.java</li>
</ol>
<p>NOTE: THE / IS WHATEVER IS AFTER THE / IS WHAT IS IN WHATEVER IS BEFORE THE /</p>
<ol start="2">
<li>Search for movePlayer and you should see something like this</li>
</ol>
<p><code>case 70:
				c.getPA().movePlayer(2872, 5269, 2);
				c.sendMessage("You have entered Armadyl, To leave click the Pillar.");
				c.sendMessage("Note: Ruby bolts (e) and Diamond bolts (e) are recommended!");
			break;</code></p>
<p>the “case 70” is the object and the c.getPA().movePlayer is the command on moving the player to whatever is in the ()'s the “2872” being the X COORD the “5269” being the Y COORD and the “2” being the height. Ignore the c.sendMessage this is an example and I used the God Wars dungeon.</p>
<p>NOTE: IF YOU WANT TO MAKE THE OBJECT TELEPORT THE PERSON INSTEAD OF JUST MOVING CHANGE IT TO SOMETHING LIKE THIS:</p>
<p><code>case 5959:
			c.getPA().startTeleport2(2539, 4712, 0);
		break;</code></p>
<p>and it is the same thing as editing or adding the movePlayer except it is startTeleport and will have the animation of teleporting.</p>
<p>NOTE: IN SOME CASES THAT WILL CAUSE AN ERROR! IF IT DOES CHANGE IT TO .startTeleport(X, Y, H “modern”); AND IT SHOULD WORK FINE!</p>
<p>[SIZE=5]<span class="bbcode-b">ADDING NPCS!</span>[/SIZE]</p>
<ol>
<li>Go into DATA like you did for the object ID’s and go into npc.cfg and find the npc you wish to use for what you want!</li>
</ol>
<p>NOTE: IF YOU ARE USING A MONSTER YOU MAY HAVE TO SET THE HP AND COMBAT LEVEL IF IT IS 0 TO MAKE IT ATTACKABLE!</p>
<ol start="2">
<li>
<p>In DATA select spawn-config.cfg and you will see something like this:</p>
<pre><code>                spawnX    spawnY   height      walk      maxhit      attack     defence      description    NOTE THIS IS FOR SHOWING YOU GUYS WHAT IT IS!
</code></pre>
</li>
</ol>
<pre><code class="lang-auto"></code></pre>
<p>“1294” is the npc ID and note after the npc ID EVERYTHING YOU ARE GOING TO ADD WILL NEED A TAB BETWEEN IT! 3508 is the X COORD 3240 is the Y COORD then it will be like shown above height, walk, maxhit, attack, defence, and description.</p>
<ol start="3">
<li>Do ::mypos where you want the npc and make a new spawn for example i will use the npc 494 a banker:</li>
</ol>
<pre><code class="lang-auto"></code></pre>
<ol start="4">
<li>
<p>Compile and do ::update 0 and close and re-run your server!</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>If you have done it correctly your npc should be right where you put it!</p>
</li>
</ol>
<p>[SIZE=5]<span class="bbcode-b">MAKING A NPC A SHOP!</span>[/SIZE]</p>
<ol>
<li>Now that you have an npc spawned go into DATA and go into shops.cfg You will see something like this:</li>
</ol>
<pre><code class="lang-auto"></code></pre>
<p>NOTE THIS IS NOT MY FULL SHOP BUT FOR AN EXAMPLE I CUT IT DOWN A BIT!</p>
<ol start="2">
<li>Make a new shop and make the shop = any # but one that has not been taken already, for this case I will use 100.</li>
</ol>
<pre><code class="lang-auto"></code></pre>
<ol start="3">
<li>
<p>“New Shop” is the name of your shop and make sure to give it a name!</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>the 2 and 2 is what the shop is so this 2 is buying only a 1 would be selling and buying.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>next are the items 10458 is the item ID for example and 10 is the amount in which is in.</p>
</li>
</ol>
<p>NOTE: YOU MUST HAVE A TAB AFTER THE shop = 100 or whatever number your shop is!</p>
<ol start="6">
<li>
<p>To find the item ID’s you can go into item.cfg!</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Once you have found all the ID’s you want in the shop go into SRC / SERVER / MODEL / PLAYERS / Actionhandler.java</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Once in actionhandler.java search for (10) and you should see something like this</p>
</li>
</ol>
<p><code>case 919:
				if (c.isDonator &gt;= 2) {
				c.getShops().openShop(10);
			} else {
				c.sendMessage("You must be at least a Super Donator to view this stop!");
				return;				
			};
			break;</code></p>
<p>this is a donator shop the case is the npc ID and if your making a shop that has no need for rights you will see something like this :</p>
<p><code>case 919:
			c.getShops().openShop(10);
	break;</code></p>
<p>The “case 919” being the npc ID you were wanting to use and the c.getShops() being the getter or Accessor .openShop() being the command to open the shop and the number inside those () is the shop number.</p>
<p>So to open our shop 100 you would do something like this:</p>
<p><code>case 919:
			c.getShops().openShop(100);
	break;</code></p>
<p>NOTE: YOU MUST PUT BREAK AFTER OR IT WILL CAUSE MANY ERRORS , THIS IS BECAUSE BREAK; IS MEANING THAT THIS CASE IS DONE EXECUTING.</p>
<ol start="9">
<li>
<p>Compiler do ::update 0 and close and re-run server <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/smiley.png?v=5" title=":smiley:" class="emoji" alt=":smiley:"></p>
</li>
<li>
<p>If do correctly when talking to npc it will open the shop and have the items you put in!</p>
</li>
</ol>
<p>[SIZE=5]<span class="bbcode-b">EXTENDING ON SHOPS</span>[/SIZE]</p>
<p>NOTE: IF YOU WANT TO ADD RIGHTS OR RESTRICTIONS ON SHOPS YOU WILL NEED TO ADD AN IF STATEMENT LIKE SO:</p>
<p><code>case 919:
				if (c.isDonator &gt;= 2) {
				c.getShops().openShop(10);
			} else {
				c.sendMessage("You must be at least a Super Donator to view this stop!");
				return;				
			};
			break;</code></p>
<p>This is a donator shop like shown above it is stating that if isDonator is greater or equal to 2 then open shop, else if it is not send the message blah blah, this is useful for making a donor shop at home or an object such as a portal that you want to have restrictions on, it will cause curiosity in the players which makes them want to have donor <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/smiley.png?v=5" title=":smiley:" class="emoji" alt=":smiley:"></p>
<p>[SIZE=5]<span class="bbcode-b">GIVING CUSTOM YELLS!</span>[/SIZE]</p>
<ol>
<li>
<p>Go into SRC / SERVER / MODEL / PLAYERS / PACKETS / COMMANDS.JAVA</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Search for yell and you will see something like this:</p>
</li>
</ol>
<p>[code]if (c.playerRights == 0){<br>
c2.sendMessage("&lt;col=255&gt;[Player]"+ Misc.optimizeText(c.playerName) +": "<br>
+ Misc.optimizeText(playerCommand.substring(5)) +"");</p>
<pre><code>						}else if (c.playerRights == 1){
							c2.sendMessage("&lt;col=255&gt;[Mod]&lt;/col&gt;&lt;img=1&gt;"+ Misc.optimizeText(c.playerName) +": "
											+ Misc.optimizeText(playerCommand.substring(5)) +"");

						}[/code]
</code></pre>
<p>Now this example shows both player and mod yells showing the player being the first if statement will be “if” the rest that follow will be “else if” you don’t need to know anything about this except that “col” is the color of the yell [Player] is the title that comes before the player’s name and in the mod yell it has &lt;img=1&gt; is the silver crown img=2 being gold.</p>
<ol start="3">
<li>
<p>Now for making your own custom yell if there is a command for Owners or Player Rights 3 delete it completely making sure you get everything!</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Making your own Custom Yell will look something like this so you can add it right under one of these or the Admin yell:</p>
</li>
</ol>
<p>[code]}else if (c.playerName.equalsIgnoreCase(“ryan”)){<br>
c2.sendMessage("&lt;shad=9440238&gt;[Owner]&lt;img=2&gt;"+ Misc.optimizeText(c.playerName) +": "<br>
+ Misc.optimizeText(playerCommand.substring(5)) +"");</p>
<pre><code>						}[/code]
</code></pre>
<p>Now this is the ignore case saying that if the playerName is ryan system send message in this color [Owner] and have a gold crown. This shad is purple btw and I prefer having shads because it has so much more life then col. <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/smiley.png?v=5" title=":smiley:" class="emoji" alt=":smiley:"></p>
<ol start="5">
<li>Once you have done this Compile do ::update 0 and close and re-run server and it should work!</li>
</ol>
<p>[SIZE=6]<span class="bbcode-b">THIS CONCLUDES YOUR BASICS ON RUNNING AND EDITING A SERVER ANY QUESTIONS FEEL FREE TO POST A COMMENT OR PM ME! I WILL BE MAKING AN ADVANCED GUIDE ON EDITING AND ADDING THINGS IN SO PLEASE MAKE SURE TO CHECK THAT OUT TOO!</span>[/SIZE]</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/getting-started-running-your-very-own-runescape-private-server-ultimate-guide/407874/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/getting-started-running-your-very-own-runescape-private-server-ultimate-guide/407874/1</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 02 Aug 2011 18:19:10 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-407874-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/getting-started-running-your-very-own-runescape-private-server-ultimate-guide/407874.rss">Getting Started running your very OWN RUNESCAPE PRIVATE SERVER! ULTIMATE GUIDE!</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
